All right. I'll say how are you all
receiving of your time as you create
time to exist.
Before we begin this idea of the
interaction this evening of your time,
allow us in this
way to share with you some
ideas of some of the release and
channeling and
transformation of electromagnetic energy
that is shifting in your planet at this
time. and simply remind
you that without necessitating the idea
in any way, shape, or form of what you
call fear, fear,
without
generating in any way, shape, or form
the idea of needing what you call
panic. In this way, allow us to remind
you that we did, as you say, quote
unquote, promised to keep you
posted. Therefore, in this
way, though nothing in your
terms is, as you
say, chiseled in
steel, all things are still malleable as
always. At the same time, our sensing
of the
energies. The idea you call
electromagnetic and physiological custal
shifting in this way therefore will be
felt will be perceived to
be at this time high degree of
probability of activation once again in
the area that has been already to some
degree activated what you call
borderline zone.
moon. The area you call between your
area California, your area
Nevada, highest degree of
probability as the energy is sensed to
be what you
call tomorrow of your
time, probable release of energy in
magnitude. What you call
High six and or in seven
range following or to
call Thursday and or Friday of your
time. high degree
probability energy magnitude in areas
you call ranges of
fives for the area you consider to be
around your own
local. These are electromagnetic
fluctuations, low vibrational energy
fluctuations as they are being perceived
in many individuals in this way at this
time. and
and
represent not a certainty but a high
degree of
probability that these gateways, these
releases, these channelings of energy in
your physiological
Earth can find themselves
can find themselves
manifesting once again on what you call
the 23rd, 24th, and or
25th of this your presence
You all follow along
in this area. Once again, it is an
opportunity for you to understand that
many of the ideas of the shiftings in
electromagnetic energy that are taking
place and are being released at this
time is your opportunity to know that
you are allowing the whole idea of all
the shifts that need to take place to
take place in minute quantities.
Allowing yourself to release and
transform and rechan this energy in more
positive ways. allowing yourself a bit
at a time to shake yourselves up in this
way to gain the level of energy, the
level of excitement. So you can rechan
this energy through you in more positive
ways so that you now can understand. You
do not have to manufacture the idea of a
release of this type of energy in a
negative way, a catastrophic way, a
destructive way. For you now are
beginning to understand that you know
you deserve ecstasy. You deserve
happiness. It is your birthright. And
you do not have to do anything special,
nor do you have to go through a trial by
far in order to know you deserve this
idea. Your transformation can be one of
ease, can be one of excitement, can be
one of ecstasy, can be one of
creativity. And in this way, you are
giving yourself an opportunity to avail
yourselves of some of this energy,
releasing it in minute amounts,
acceptable amounts, comfortable amounts,
amounts that you can assimilate,
allowing yourself to come to terms with
the idea of all the different symbolic
manifestations subconsciously,
unconsciously, archetypically of the
area in which you live to know it is a
high energy area. It is a moving area.
And that is why you have attracted
yourself to this position on your
planet. In this way, you are at one of
the primary energy nodal points of your
planet. It is situated along the
so-called fault lines which represent
the fracture zones of the crystallin
plates of your world. So you are finding
yourself at an area very close to an
area where there is an apex of all of
these lines that represent the
culmination or
interse. As you find the crystallin
becomes more aligned into its fourth
density matrix, then some of these
sudden shiftings will occur at different
places around your world. Once again, it
does not have to be represented by the
idea of a catastrophic shift in this
way. But you yourselves are allowing
yourselves to feel this energy in minute
amounts, comfortable amounts, acceptable
amounts, so that you know that you can
utilize it. It can invigorate you. It
can excite you. It can move you ahead.
You can rechan and transform the energy
of anything in your physical reality
into something that will allow you to
know and sense your own momentum, your
own forward motion, your own
transformation, and your own
crystallization. All of the shiftings of magnitude that
All of the shiftings of magnitude that
take place within your physiological
energy field, all of the emotional
patterns that are falling into place,
all of the disorientation that you are
feeling in this way, all of the magnetic
disorientation, you are simply finding
that you are putting yourself into a
limbo state that allows you to know you
are unlocking previously from one
reality and allowing yourself to float
in between the choices of the realities
you will experience in fourth density.
For there is only in your terms a very
short period of time left in which you
can allow yourself to float in such a
free state limbo when all ideas are
equally available to you in this way. So
you can choose what ideas you wish to
represent the fourth density reality,
the physiological reality that you wish
to experience. When you allow yourself
to begin to solidify into what you have
called the new age, the fourth density
state, you are now in a free floating
zone, a limbo state, a free zone. All
possibilities are open to you. This is
why you are finding all these shiftings
to take place until it settles in to an
understanding of what it is you prefer
to be. Then you will simply as always
find yourself exactly where you need to
be when you need to be there interacting
with exactly whom you need to interact
with. And you will understand that even
if there are individuals upon your
planet that have chosen to experience
some of these shiftings in a negative
way, you will simply not be present
having already unconsciously,
subconsciously or collectively,
consciously led yourself into another
area where you will simply be able to
know that such an idea, such an
interaction is taking place. But you
will not have to have the negative
experience in that way because you
simply know what reality you are. Are
you all following along? Yes.
Therefore, in this way, there is no need
for fear. There is no need for panic in
the idea of this so-called prediction.
As we have said, there is no such thing
as a prediction of the future. Only a
sensing of the energy that has the
highest degree of probability at the
time the prediction is made. That can
change. And many times the prediction in
of itself has to do with changing the
outcome in that way. It is up to you.
But simply recognize this is as the
energy is sensed by us by many
individuals upon your planet at this
time. And it simply represents one more
opportunity to feel the release in an
acceptable way at acceptable levels, at
comfortable levels of the energy of the
shifting going on in your planet. So
that it can allow you to bring yourself
to terms with all portions of yourself.
So that all the different plates and
facets that make up the being that you
are can all shift and settle comfortably
together to form one multi-dimensional
crystal that will allow you to live your
life as you desire it to be lived.
Sherry Bash for sure. Hey, um I'd like
to thank you for some information you
shared with me back in the fall and I
went on to do some music that I felt in
my heart and the financial end is coming
together. Thank you. And I did dedicate
one of the pieces to you. Thank you. In
this way, once again, thank you for
being a reflective example that if you
simply act upon what excites you the
most, then all necessary ingredients
that are necessary to support the idea
you are willing to be will automatically
synchronistically be there. Because in
this way, every idea comes complete with
all the ingredients necessary for the
continuation of the manifestation of
that idea. Because the universe does not
do extraneous and/or pointless things.
Thank you for being such a willing
reflection. You're welcome. Is there any
way I could share that music with you
that you would be able to hear that? Or
have you heard it already?
We can feel to some degree the idea in
this way as it blends in your field as
it blends in the general field that we
perceive all of you to be together. It
adds a richness and in a sense a
sweetness to the overall interaction of
the energy that we perceive if I may put
it that way. Thank you. The name of the
piece for you is Ancient Sky. Thank you.
We have been in many. Shane,
Shane,
um I have a couple things. Um about
earthquakes and creating your own
reality. We've had two um fairly recent
earthquakes and I live in Santa Monica
right near the ocean and both times the
building was affected and both times in
the middle of the night my roommate
Carrie woke up and saw her furniture
going moving around the room and um
after the first one which I didn't wake
up for and didn't experience um I told
her I thought it would be it would have
been interesting had I woken up and so
the second time when she woke up she
came into my room and saw that nothing
was moving. It was as if nothing was
going on in my room and she was having
an earthquake in her room. And um I
think that's interesting because we were
obviously creating our own reality. Our
rooms are only 5 ft apart. So I thought
that was really neat. Thank you for
recognizing once again the literalness
of the idea that you are your own
universe.
Okay. And I just want to share um parts
of two dreams and kind of explore them a
little bit with you. Oh, what? Um about
a week ago, uh part of the dream was um
I was standing outside in a square of
some sort with um some people and I
believe I had brought them out there. It
was at night because I had seen the
stars fall from the sky in front of me.
And so I brought them out to see these
stars fall. And lo and behold, we watch
stars fall right from the sky in front
of
us. And um that's it. And I was
wondering because usually I don't have
dreams of that nature and I know and
it's it doesn't seem very complicated
but um I was thinking perhaps that is
that a sign of validity? It's
complication. No. Uh-uh. But usually they're so
No. Uh-uh. But usually they're so
straightforward and and this is in some
ways that I wouldn't bring them up with
you because I don't think I've shared
any of my trainers with you before. And
this one I wanted to explore a little
bit. Right. Um because I thought in a
sense it meant that I will experience
certain things and then I'll want to
share them with other people and and
assist them in in um a making it part of
their and you can be in a sense a magnet
and an attractant for the understanding
of the creation of bringing the heavens
to earth in this way and completely
reorienting the foundations or what you
call the firmaments upon which you have
always relied. in your reality,
recognizing that it does not have to
represent something so stable any longer
and that all the patterns of what you
call astrology are now beginning to
blend together.
Thank you. Oh, thank you. And um last
night part of my dream was that I was
sketching a model wearing some clothes
and there was an older woman who was
looking over my shoulder and as I was
drawing the lines of shading around the
neck I realized I think afterwards upon
waking up that I was seeing the
lines like on the astral plane over the
image and then just kind of tracing them
on. Thanks. The older woman is you, your
future self in this life, assisting you,
speaking back through time to you to
guide your hand to your own future.
Oh, cuz I thought it was because in the
dream I was aware that the spirit plane
was assisting me. Nice.
Yeah. Thank you for being so self-reflective.
Well, thank you.
What will happen if I leave my job?
Are you leaving your job to do something
that excites you most? I don't know.
What does excite you? I don't know. Oh,
come now. Understand that when I ask you
what excites you, I am not asking you to
define the idea that you think would
excite you most in your entire lifetime.
What of all the things that are
immediately accessible and available to
you to do now with whatever skills and
abilities you have to do anything with?
What out of all the things that are
immediately obviously available to you
excites you most? Anything at all?
I you know it's very hard. I don't know.
I've been thinking about it for quite
some time. And perhaps you are simply
once again assuming that what you have
to come up with has to be something
monumental, something that would stand
out. Right now, I will assume that what
excites you the most is being where you
are. Yes or no? Yes. All
right. When this interaction ends, so to
speak, what then do you think will
excite you the
most? Will you go home? Will you go
somewhere else? What will you do? Do you
know? No. All right. Will you act upon
whatever you feel would be the most
enticing and exciting thing to do once
this interaction is at an end? Yes. Then
why worry? Mhm. If you are always
following your instinct and simply doing
at any given moment what it is that
excites you the most, you can take it
for granted that you will always be
leading yourself exactly where you need
to be and you do not have to look for
anything that comes with trumpets to
understand that you are simply being the
path you chose to be and you can simply
enjoy who and what you are. And if you
have the inclination to change or
transform the idea of what you do for a
living, then simply trust that if your
decision comes from the cognition of
what is true for you, then no matter
what it is that will happen will and can
only be representative of the
continuence of the path you chose to be.
So you will be just fine.
Okay. All right. Thank you. Thank you.
I was getting this feeling listening to
her talk that
um maybe she's just really merged with
everything nothing really needs to some
individuals on your planet do worry when
they don't find anything to worry
about. I I heard on the radio coming
over here as a talk show and uh the guy
was calling us. He was 30 and he still
was looking for the meaning of life and
the lady the the doctor said uh well you
probably haven't grown up yet. When you
get to be 30 usually you know there is
no meaning. It's just, you know, there
to live it is the meaning of life. And
that maybe for some people who are more
merged than others, nothing is going to
stand out as being any better than
anything else because all things are
equal. Exactly. Yeah. That's the
feeling. Has that assisted you? No. I as
a matter of fact, I would disagree 100%.
Oh well.
Why? Because I feel that there are
responsibilities to who?
To yourself is to loved ones.
Responsibilities to Yes.
Responsibilities for no.
Okay. Do you understand the difference?
No. Responsibility to someone is being
completely who you are. Being completely
true to yourself. You cannot be
responsible for someone. What they
choose to experience in their lives is
their choice, not your responsibility.
Okay, I'll buy that. Then responsibility
to All right. But understand
responsibility to someone is while
functioning within your integrity, while
interacting with those individuals in
the ways that you have attracted into
your life to represent the obvious
interactions that you know you do wish
to have with them. At the same time
being responsible to them is acting upon
the things you know to be true for you.
Now understand that what that individual
said in no way, shape or form actually
contradicts anything you believe in. It
is simply a matter of differing
terminologies. That I'll agree with you.
Then in this way allow yourself to
recognize that all the individuals, all
the objects and all the situations
around you can always afford you the
reflections and the answers that you
need to find if you are willing to adapt
to the understanding that even though
someone else's terminology may not be
yours, they may still be saying the same
thing. And that is the equality that was
being spoken of.
You follow me?
No. All right. When you allow yourself
to feel in your life that it does not
matter per
se what you do that there is not
anything that in and of itself stands
out. It can be as was being suggested an
indication that you have arrived at a
point in your life where you understand
that the way to attract into your life
the thing you desire most to do. The way
to attract that is by allowing it to be
no more important than anything else
that could be chosen by you. When all
choices you could make could make are
equal, then every choice is on the same
level. You don't have to reach for it,
nor do you have to climb to
it. Nor in this way do you have to bring
yourself up from something less than
where you think you are going. So what
you're saying is that every single
choice has its own merit, its own val.
Thus in a sense though they are all
different, they are all equal. They are
all fundamentally neutral and do not
come with built-in meaning. You supply
meaning to any event. All events are
fundamentally neutral. Okay. But when
you ask me what you would want to do, of
course the natural human response is I
want to do. Speak for yourself.
My own it is in your terms not natural
human response. It is learned human
response. Okay. My response would be I
want to do the thing that I like which
is which I have to decide what I want to
do. And you're right that I feel that as
each moment comes along you're right I
will pick which one I like to do. And I
think that's very right. However, a lot
of times that I find for myself that
when I pick something, it just might
also turn out that I don't like it. Then
it has served you by granting you an
opportunity to see and experience
something you do not prefer. Thus giving
you an opportunity to know what it is
you do prefer. That does not mean that
just because it has allowed you to
recognize what you prefer that you have
to judge that experience as being
something less than what you prefer
because it has served you equally by
giving you an opportunity to know what
you do in fact prefer.
Okay. It is only when you judge or
invalidate what you do not prefer that
you automatically fixate yourself on the
thing you don't prefer
because you are saying that it has more
power to hold your fascination than what
you do prefer.
So in a way you almost prefer that.
Yes, I'll find that. So the idea is in
fact to do what you are doing. Relax.
Letting all things be equal is what will
allow the ideas you prefer to
paradoxically stand out.
All right. Mhm. Okay. Does that assist
you? Yeah, I like it. It is up to you.
Your choice. Only a suggestion. Your
life. Thank you.
Hey. Well, what about goal setting? What
about what about it? Um, I mean, what if
you what you're saying is that if you
set everything up so that it all appears
equal in your interpretation of things,
then um All right. All right. All right. You
um All right. All right. All right. You
know, the idea of goal setting is that
you can use it as a tool as long as you
do not rigidize it with expectations.
You can become very excited by setting
yourself a goal, having a visualization
of something that would excite you, that
you desire very much. That is all well
and equal. The understanding is that you
are using that as a model. Now, that is
not to say that the goal cannot manifest
totally, specifically literally because
many times it does.
As long as you are willing to understand
that it does not have to and yet the
same effect can still be created in your
life. Then in whatever way, shape or
form the situation or the so-called goal
needs to manifest, it will. You will
still have the same feeling, the same
feeling you expected you would have even
when you thought it had to manifest in
the specific way you envisioned it or
set yourself up to have a
goal. Because simply setting the goal is
what allows you to move in that
direction. But it does not necessarily
give you all the different doorways. It
does not necessarily give you analytical
conscious awareness. nor does it have to
give you analytical conscious awareness
of all the different doorways through
which that goal could be realized. Thus
to put a very rigid expectation well if
that goal does not manifest exactly this
way. If I do not exactly do this A B C 1
2 3 then there is no way that goal can
manifest. If you structure it that
narrowly, that rigidly, then you may
actually be responsible in that way for
closing all of the doors through which
the so-called goal may have manifested
quickly in this way, easily in this way,
and quote unquote unexpectedly in that
way. When you put the expectation that
your goal has to manifest exactly as you
have envisioned it, you are only
allowing one doorway to be valid. And it
may not be the quickest
doorway. Simply know that having a goal,
having the visualization is your way of
activating your engine of
excitation. Emotion, desire,
Emotion, desire,
emotion, energy, motion.
That is what
realizes manifests your
belief. So simply take it for granted
that if you know something excites you,
if you know you have a
desire for a certain idea, certain goal,
certain feeling, certain
situation, simply know you are quote
unquote kicking yourself in that
direction. You are that
vibration. You could not be anything
else because you were able to conceive
of the idea to begin with. You have to
be what you
conceive. You are what you perceive. You
are the vibration. You are the thing.
Only that your society believes that
there must be a necessary intermediate
process in order to become what you have
imagined you desire to be. So you do not
simply let yourself in the imagining of
it be the thing already and begin to act
like you are already that thing. Acting
like you are already the thing you have
imagined is what will allow your
physical reality to begin to transform
into a reflection of that certainty of
that knowledge. But your civilization
says no no my imagination is not real.
Thinking the thing imagining the thing
is not the same thing as being the
thing. It is not the real reality.
Therefore, I must find, I must search, I
must discover the necessary process that
will allow me to attain at some point in
the future this manifestation I wish to
achieve. Way out
there. When you know that you are the
thing, when you know that you must be on
the same frequency in order to even be
able to conceive of an idea and you
simply begin to trust that that is so
and act like it, then the physical
reality which is the shadow of your soul
must conform to the new shape the body
of the soul has taken.
Does that assist you very much? But I
have one thing I wanted to ask you. Oh,
right. Um, that sounds really great, but if you
Um, that sounds really great, but if you
die,
if you decide that you're going to be
this thing that you envision for
yourself, um, how can you just
automatically start acting as if you're
that thing? A thank you. It is very
simple. Well, I mean, you can't be a
brain surgeon overnight. I mean, you go
to school for years. No. Or if you want
to do something that requires Are you
paying attention? No.
You can in what you call the twinkling
of an eye be anything you believe you
can be. It is only a
preconceived taught conception that you
can't be. Now understand, we understand
that quote unquote, it is rare in your
society, but there have been individuals
who have done it and if one can do it,
all can do it because one is all and all
are one.
It simply depends upon the degree of
need, the degree of desire, the degree
of excitation, and the degree of
knowingness and the degree of
trust. That is all it takes. If you
totally beyond a shadow of a doubt
knew that you were in fact the idea of a
brain surgeon, you would be able to
operate in the very next second. You
would instinctively know what to do. You
would instinctively know what tools to
reach for, what nerves to cut and
repair. you would instinctively know
exactly what you were doing
because the present is not a result of
the past. All
past. All
learning is simply in a sense
remembering more of who and what you
are. Recognizing that you create memory
in the present will allow you to know
that no matter what you have learned or
what you think you need to learn and
retain, you in any given moment can
simply know whatever it is you need to
know to be who you think or believe you
are at that given moment. All it takes
is that degree of
trust. You do not think twice about
something you know for a fact you own.
It is only when you think you don't own
it that you worry about it. If you have
the same degree of conviction about
being a brain surgeon as you do about
the ability to walk 10 ft, you would be
a brain surgeon. You don't think twice
about being able to walk 10 ft. You
follow me? Yes. Because you simply allow
yourself to know beyond the shadow of a
doubt that that is something you can do.
The same degree of trust when applied to
the idea of whatever it is that excites
you the most will allow you to be that
idea and you will simply have right at
your fingertips all the information you
need instinctively to function as that
idea. That is how the universe works.
Then Charles why is it that our society
felt the need to create this sense of
learning? Because you wanted to explore
separation and limitation. So the first
primary prerequisite for being able to
explore that idea is to forget that you
are in control of it. Otherwise you
cannot experience limitation. Now you
are at the end of the game of
limitation. That is why you are
beginning to explore this integration.
Learning about more of yourself, finding
your spirituality and understanding that
you are connected to the universe. That
is the beginning of what is going on
right now in your society. The
remembrance of the fact that you are the
creator of your reality. But you did
wish to experience limitation. And for
many tens of thousands of years, you
have until now you have arrived at the
point where you are masters of
limitation. This is a tool you no longer
need. You are at the end of that cycle.
That is why we are now allowed to
interact with you because you have
finally invited the possibility that
there is more than just what you can
immediately see around you.
the beginning. You follow me? Yeah.
I have something I'd share with them.
The experience that you just talked
about happened to me in 1969. I came
from Australia to England and uh there
was an acting job going that was wanted
by every actor in the world. It was to
be uh the new James Bond after Shan
Connory. I'd never met an actor. I
walked in the door and got the job
because I wanted to be
him. And I had no reason to believe I
couldn't be because I'd never met an
actor who told me I couldn't do it. You
see, I had Australian accent. I I
supposed to have a different accent. I
was supposed to be this hell with it.
Let me have a go at it. And uh there I
was three months later with the job with
all the guys scratching their head. So I
think that what he's saying is is
frightening because I didn't want the
job. You see that's the mad thing about it.
You see that's the mad thing about it.
You get these things sometimes without
thinking about them. Perhaps your
consciousness is not aware of the fact
that you want the job, but the obvious
physical reality speaks for itself. Yes.
But then when you get in there, it's a
different situation than what you
thought it was. And it's a has
responsibility to a lot of people that
you don't want to be involved with. All
right. And responsibility to yourself.
Yes. Thank you for your sharing and for
Thank you for your sharing and for
synchronistically being present in this
interaction to function as an
illustration. My pleasure.
My pleasure.
Bashar you then you I have not been here
for a few months and the last time I was
here I remember you having your hands a
certain way and keeping them together.
There has been more blending, more
acceleration and more opportunity in
this way to have the transformation of
the energy to come through in different
ways that are more let us say
immediate. There are different
communications being shared with you on
different levels through what you are
perceiving to be the motions of the
physical channel's hand. There is more
of our consciousness present than just
what is being translated locally. And we
are in many ways speaking to you on
other levels through the physiological
actions you are perceiving and on other
levels that you are not physiologically
perceiving at all.
Do they have anything to do with mood
drugs? In a sense, yes, they are
representations to some degree of the
nodal points, the balance points within
the overall mass consciousness energy
matrix that we sense you all
collectively to be. They are
representative of fluctuations and
vibrations within your soul patterns to
some degree. Energy flows.
Does that answer your question? Yes, it
does. Thank you guys. Um why did it take
why has it taken us so long? Oh, it is
very simple. Limitation. Very simple.
Understand that you create time space.
You follow me? Separation and
limitation. Separating yourself implies
that you need more time space in which
to experience the all that is that you
are. Now you will find that as you begin
to integrate, you will experience less
time. It is simply the result andor what
you call the product of the mode in
which you have been functioning.
Experiencing separation requires more
time because then you create more pieces
to explore. When you pull yourself
together into an understanding of
oneness, you don't have to go as far or
take as
long. Therefore, that is why you will,
now that you have begun the cycle of
integration, only be physiological upon
your planet for approximately 2 to 3,000
years more. And that is
it. Tens of thousands of years of
exploration of limitation. 2 to 3,000
years of exploration of integration in
physical reality is all that is
necessary for you. Then you will not be
physiological any longer. You will go on
to fifth density. 2 to 3,000 more.
Understand that because it will be the
exploration of integration and because
you will be experiencing your ecstasy
and because therefore you will be
enjoying every moment it will pass in
the twinkling.
You know what to say when you are having
fun. It is not really so much that time
flies. It is that more literally you
actually do not create as much of it. So
things literally take less time.
Living in the moment. Living in the
now. Enjoying every moment for what it
is. Not needing to think that what you
are going to experience in the next
moment is going to be better. simply
different. will allow you to
This is a continuation.
uh dividing of people that's happening
now plus prejudice that we have that I
have and everyone I imagine has in this
room uh with color and creed and and
some eating habits uh just general
language uh we there's a lot of barriers
there that I can see that are going to
take a long time maybe maybe not to
break through. Now understand it does
not have to take a long time and one of
the reasons it would take a long time is
simply because you are now stating that
you have a
preconceived judgment that it has to.
Yes, that is the only thing that makes
it take a long time. The belief that it
will. Yeah, but there's certain things
that just upset you straight away like
smells. These things once again you are
assuming to be natural reactions. They
are learned and they can be unlearned.
Yeah, I see that. I mean, I've seen my
children eat their, you know, watch it
in their napkins and they think it's
great fun until you tell them it's not.
All right, then. And and uh so I must
have been saying
myself, someone along somewhere along
the line, someone said, "That doesn't
smell right. You shouldn't eat that."
And you believe them. Yes. Now, how do I
undo that just like that and say, "Hey,
that no longer smells bad. You can eat
that. That's fine." Now understand if
you simply recognize in this way that it
is not something you prefer then so be
it. But you do not have to judge it to
understand you do not prefer it. And
therefore just because you prefer
something else as long as you are not
judging what you do not prefer. It will
not create any reaction within you at
all. You simply will recognize perhaps
it is not for you but it will not create
a negative reaction. Mhm. Well, that's
it will be neutral.
Like I I ride a motorcycle and I'm going
along. I see people in cars doing their
hair, doing their makeup, eating their
drinking their coffee and all that. And
I feel like saying, "Hey, watch out for
the other guy down the road. You might
care about yourself, but you're going to
smash into somebody if you don't watch
who you're driving." Now, we are not
saying that you may not be recognizing
that they may not be functioning within
integrity and they may in fact be
creating a negative situation. We are
not saying that that does not happen.
All we are simply saying is that for
yourself in this way you can begin to
recognize as any individual can that
when you begin to grant equality to the
infinite diversity within your society
that is when you will afford yourself
the best opportunity to actually begin
to experience unity and therefore rapid
acceleration in change.
Yes, I see your point. I but the thing
is How can I see it work? I mean, oh,
thank you. Perhaps this
way recognize if you already
recognize if you already
don't nothing nothing nothing nothing
nothing happens by accident. You follow
me so far?
Yes. Do you believe that? Well, I don't
know. Some people have invented things
by accident. No.
seems to be an accident but never
is. It is the idea that in your society
you call
synchronicity. It is simply that
everything all of it. Everything comes together to
all of it. Everything comes together to
reflect whatever an individual who is
experiencing the idea believes their
reality to be. Everything is the right
place, the right time, exactly when and
where it needs to be to reflect the
beliefs that are ingrained in the
individuals having the
experience. Therefore, recognizing that nothing
Therefore, recognizing that nothing
happens by accident can allow you rather
than judging a situation that you may
see to begin to become fascinated by the
degree of choreography present.
There is absolutely beyond a shadow of a
doubt no accident when you are as you
might have said traveling in your
traffic in your automobile. It is no
accident who is in front of you, who is
behind you, what color their car is,
what they are wearing, what color the
clothes are that they are wearing, what
time of day it is, whether they go to
the left, whether they go to the right.
It is no accident. Now there may be
relative degrees of let us say
importance to you about what it is
that's going on but it is still no
accident that you are there
participating because you in entering
this physical reality made an agreement
with everyone else to be of service to
everyone else. Therefore, you will also
whether a particular situation has a
degree of relevance to you or not, you
will still agree to participate in that
situation so that it might have a degree
of relevance to someone else in that
situation. So, it is still no accident
whether you can perceive what meaning it
has for you or not is not necessarily
relevant. The idea is that it does have
meaning for someone and it has meaning
for you in that you agreed to
participate to allow that someone else
to see what they needed to see. So none
of it is by accident. It is all
choreographed. And if you allow yourself
to begin to become fascinated by the
degree to which it has been
choreographed, then you will begin
perhaps to unlearn what you have learned
and cease to judge it and begin to
become fascinated and enveloped by the
fact that you will begin to feel
yourself being connected to all of these
apparently singularized events until you
allow yourself to begin to feel as if
you actually are all the events you are
seeing. then you will cease to judge it because
then you will cease to judge it because
then you will recognize that all you are
doing is judging yourself.
Very good. Very very well said for you.
Perhaps that will assist you. I did. And
uh but it does sound a lot like
hallucination. Very good. May I remind you there is a
Very good. May I remind you there is a
very fine line between what you think is
solid and what is not.
This physical reality is a
hallucination. Yeah, that's hard for me
to grasp right now. It is all right
because the idea is that the
purpose that you have created in your
life is being served by you imparting
the illusion of solidity to this
particular hallucination. Your purpose is being
hallucination. Your purpose is being
served by maintaining that illusion. So
do not deny that you have a reason for
doing so. It is all right if you do not
feel you can grasp it. There is a reason
why you don't grasp it. Simply trust
that what is happening is what needs to
happen and you will understand what you
need to understand when you need to
understand it. Thank you. Yay. Um
Lazarus has said that tomorrow I believe
is the highest day of energy or the day
of highest energy in this year. It is a
gateway and that is why it may be
exemplified by the release of the
shifting in your electromagnetic fields
and crystal plates that we have
indicated. Oh okay. Well, some of us
decided to get together and have an
impromptu tapping into this energy so
that we can do some meditations to help
create more of the reality that we
prefer. Um, are there other thing? I
believe we could do this all of us any
day. It's kind of exciting that
tomorrow. Oh, I guess I just answer it.
Excitement. May I remind you also at
this time and take this opportunity to
reflect from you another day, another
energy gate that we have already shared
with some members of your civilization.
What you call 7787,
right, will be the end of the 40th orbit
since 7747, which was the date whereupon your
7747, which was the date whereupon your
civilization understood beyond a shadow
of a doubt that there were in fact other
civilizations other than your own. Can
you say both those dates again? 7747.
Mhm. The date that your civilization
discovered that there were other
civilizations in the universe beyond a
shadow of a doubt.
7787, the end of the 40th orbit since
the discovery. Understand that there is
a repetition in your history of the idea
that transformations between gates are
represented by the cycle you call 40 40
days. 40 years for a complete
transformation from one idea to another.
40 days for an individual, 40 years for
an entire
civilization, 40 orbits.
7787 will be another
gate and there will be much acceleration
from that point
forward with regard specifically in many
ways to the understanding of whatever
level of equality you are now willing to
become with your governments with your
media with your military with regard to
the idea of the expression of
information that your governments your
media and your military do in fact know
beyond the shadow of a doubt that we
exist.
That is another gate
question. I know that you say that um we're all
I know that you say that um we're all
one and we're all connected, but I'm
curious about the idea of um soulmates,
individuals on the planet with whom we
have more. You have made many
agreements. In this way, do recognize
that such agreements exist as you are
referring to. But also do recognize that
every individual you interact with, you
have made an agreement with. And so for
whatever particular interaction you are
having, that individual is your soulmate
for that moment. Understand also again
many ideas about what you think a
soulmate does for you. For many
individuals will not allow themselves to
be happy until they find a soulmate. But
recognize they are only thinking that
they need the soulmate to be complete.
wherein therefore they are not willing
to recognize they are complete already
and therefore only attract another
individual to reflect their belief in
their own
incompleteness. When you know you are
complete as an individual to not need
the relationship then you are willing in
this way to reflect your completeness.
That reflection of your own completeness
is what attracts the individual you made
the agreement with to come into your
life to reflect your completeness to you
thereby seeming to be complete in
themselves. Then you have an accurate
mirror reflection of the idea that you
are your own creator and thus attract
the soulmate that made the agreement
with you to reflect that to you when you
arrived at that point. But it takes you
understanding that you do not need that
relationship in order to be complete.
That it is a reflection of when you are
willing to know you are complete. That
is what a soulmate is for.
You follow me? Yes. Thank
you. the shark.
Uh within the last 10 days, I channeled
a female
entity that uh had a very discreet
message for me.
And uh what I'm asking
is can you predict that I will go on to
channel anyone else? As we have said, is
that it? There is no way to predict the
future. Or can you observe? It is
possible. I understand it's possible.
Well, then you are the one to make that
decision. Why are you asking me to
perceive something as if it were
completely and utterly fixed when it
isn't? If you decide right now to stop
channeling, so be it. That is your
decision and therefore that is your
reality. If you decide to open yourself
up to more, there is always more that is
willing to be of assistance to your
planet at this transformational time. So
you will make your agreements as you go.
There are always more. Always.
Okay. There is an infinite supply of
consciousnesses willing to be of
assistance to those that open themselves
up to be of assistance in that way.
There must be an infinite number. I
agree. Therefore, follow your instincts.
Do what excites you and what you enjoy.
Recognize that nothing is going to push
you faster than you are capable of
handling because then there would be no
point. You would not be able to function
in service. So
relax. The more you relax, the more you
will be cognizant of the agreements you
are making and the more you will
recognize when something or one else is
tapping in. Okay. Is there any way to
find that I've had an agreement with an
NC that I'm willing to perform? Now,
close your eyes. Take three deep
breaths. Repeat after
me. In love in love and light and light.
I I am self-empowered. am self-empowered
to acknowledge to acknowledge any and
all any and all portions of my
consciousness portions of my
consciousness in whatever way in
whatever way serves all concerned serves
all concern to allow me to allow me to
allow myself to allow myself to be of
service to be of service and express and
express my particular my particular and
unique and unique manifestation
manifestation of all that is of all that
is that is it have pleasant dreams you
will make your connections okay thank
you I'm curious as to what you would uh what
I'm curious as to what you would uh what
you have to say about the disease aid
and when you think all right one more
time recognize very briefly first of all
we will keep is succinct because there
are ideas we have shared many times
already and they are available to you in
this way. It stems primarily from a
reluctance because of the exploration of
separation that your society has been
doing. It has created within itself in a
sense a seeming illusion of inability to
reintegrate certain portions of itself
specifically what you call the
polarities of the male and female energy
within each and every one of you. It is
a reluctance to integrate those
polarities of male and female energy
that has caused a need in your society
to have certain individuals choose to be
born to exemplify what appears to be in
your society the dichotomy or the
polarization of an expression of a
certain type of energy through a
seemingly opposite type of physical
being. Now because that in itself also
was not enough for the mainstream let us
say of your society to accept that it
has both energies within itself and to
acknowledge an equality of those
energies. You quote unquote you in
general the mainstream of your society
once again sought to judge those
individuals willing to reflect that each
and every individual has maleness and
femaleness within them. And those
individuals who were willing to reflect
that maleist and femaleist took upon
themselves to believe in those judgments
and so recognized unconsciously that
there was no other way to reflect back
to the mainstream of society their lack
of willingness to accept and adopt the
blending of the maleness and femaleness
within each and every individual except
to create within themselves a judgment
upon themselves that would create a
disease that would force the mainstream
of your society to come to terms with
that section of society it had
ostracized that was willing to reflect
the idea of maleness and femaleness to
them. By creating a disease that by
symbolic implication is the removal and
the dropping of all
barriers so that you are forced to blend
and interact and share compassion and
come to terms with the idea of what it
is to blend maleness and femaleness
within each and every individual. Now,
the idea of what you call homosexuality
in your society is not right, is not
wrong. It simply is a reflection of your
society's lack of willingness to accept
that each and every individual has the
polarities of maleness and femaleness
within them and to allow that to be
equal. When you allow yourselves to do
that, you will find that there will no
longer be the need for the tool of
homosexuality in your society. It will
not vanish because it is wrong. It will
simply disappear from your society
because it is no longer needed. Because
you are willing to accept within
yourselves that you contain both sides
and do not need to create a disease to
force yourself to know that all of your
immunity to new ideas has been erased.
You follow me? Yes. Will that have
assisted you? Yes. Thank you. Thank you.
Um, Bashar, the message that you just
gave our friend over there, was that
something that you'd be able to repeat?
I'd like to write it down. It already
exists in many different ways. Allow
yourself to avail yourself of the
information that it already exists upon
what you call your transcripts and
tapes. Oh, all right. Thank you. Hey,
sir. Michelle, you can you communicate
with me?
I don't know what to ask you
specifically, but I want you to
communicate with me. Why? I don't know.
All right.
Do you feel you are being of service in
your life? Mhm.
How the life
What is being of service? How do you be
of service? Serving people. How
Physically, how what do you share with them that
how what do you share with them that
allows you to know you are being of
service? I work in development area.
I work in development area.
Development of what? Development area of
problems. All right. Prepare
myself. Conscious process. Conscious
process. In this way
recognize the idea of your assistance is
already in a sense a conscious process.
Is it not?
What other conscious process do you
think you need other than being of
service? I don't think I need that.
I don't think I need that.
Well then I wanted to experience the
communication with you. What are you
experiencing now? communication. Well,
then understand in this way that
communication with us is not so much
exactly the idea of communication with
us. It is your willingness to allow us
to act as a mirror to reflect back to
you what you already know to be true.
We are not here to give anyone any
answers. We are only here to remind each
and every one of you that you have all
the answers you need and that you chose
to be where you are, that you create
your reality as you see fit, and that if
you know that what you are doing is true
for you, then all you need to do is to
continue to experience that
idea. Communication with us will only be
more and more willingness to be
communicative with yourself. In this
way, therefore, that is why we have said
many times that it is not so much that
you cannot ask questions. They are of
service as well. They are a type of
sharing. The idea is that being willing
to share equally of who you are will
allow more and more interaction with
your society, with our society, with
many other societies on a more equal
footing. And the idea of equal sharing
is not so much talking. It is going out
and doing what it is you know to be true
for you. That is communicating equally
with us. Simply doing what you know you
are all about. So we will thank you for
your communication and simply being
willing to do what you know is of
service to all that is. Actually what
they wanted what they found out is they
wanted some of your communication with
me to go to go beyond my belief system.
Beyond your belief system? Yes. How can
we do that? By communication with you. I
want to see if I can go beyond my belief
system. I was very scared to come into
this room to listen to you. Why do you
think so?
What did you think you would find that
scared you? I don't know. Something's
beyond my beyond my known everything
that is known. Ah well let that be a
lesson to you. There is nothing that is
beyond you. Nothing. All things. While
there will be many differences that you
will explore and discover in the
universe. None of it is beyond your
understanding. For you are all that is.
I know this is my head but I wanted to
experience it. All right. We are sharing
with you right now and there are
vibrations and you are assimilating more
of yourself. We appreciate your
willingness to allow yourself to open in
that way and recognize that
vulnerability is not weakness. It is
infinite strength. Mhm. I know. I know.
You know,
we are simply
vibrating. And in this way, in the
sharing of the vibration, allowing you
to assimilate at whatever rate is
comfortable for you, the understanding
that there is no need to fear anything.
For all fear is a message and a
messenger to yourself about another
portion of yourself that you wish to be
aware of. For sure. Thank you. Thank you very
of. For sure. Thank you. Thank you very
much. Chakra of
Chakra of
intention. Solar
plexus. Heart
blending. Crystal eye.
Thank you.
Uh continuing your conversation you had
previously about AIDS, is there anything
that you can
contribute to uh to try and bring a
remedy for some ideas are already being
undergone with the idea of what you call
visualization therapy and the
understanding that to get in touch with
the belief system can allow an
individual to create whatever reality
they so desire. Another idea we have
shared to some degree that we do feel
has a degree of validity within the mass
consciousness is exploration and
experimentation with the substances and
juices and extracts that you call
different of the berry family and
cherry. Oh, I see. Does someone have this
Oh, I see. Does someone have this
information already? We have simply
shared this many times. Okay. We do not
know how far it has gotten in your
society. I was just watching a program today uh
I was just watching a program today uh
on Donahoo where they had all the
medical advisers there saying they've
not really uh gotten onto anything that
can help them at the moment. That is
simply because they are looking into the
ideas of all of the complex ways that
they are used to looking in and not
allowing themselves to look within their
hearts. So you're saying thought and berries?
So you're saying thought and berries?
I is there any particular berries and
cherries that you could recommend? Again
the idea extract cherry, blueberry,
raspberry
and uh and what do they do in their
thought process?
They allow there to be a type of
distillation that takes place within the
majority of the individuals in your
society that represents a cellular
invigoration, a stabilization of certain
enzyatic actions within the body,
chemical reactions within the body and
thereby electrical neuronic interactions
within the brain that can cause to some
degree some stability and allow there to
be the idea you would call an arresting
of the process of disintegration.
Is it possible now to take one
individual oneon-one who has AIDS and
use him as an example? Yes. Uh but could
one person do it or would you say the
whole community has to be involved? It
can begin with one individual for any
one individual is their own universe.
And if you simply find that there may be
an individual who will automatically
synchronistically attract themselves
into such an opportunity, then they will
present themselves in the right place at
the right time. As have already many
individuals presented themselves in the
right place at the right time,
undergoing the idea and attracting
themselves to the individuals who are
assisting modulating the visualization
therapy. And there are many individuals
who have quote unquote been killed.
trying to say something guys. Um there's
a woman in Santa Monica named Lou Pre
who's written a book you can heal
yourself so you can heal your life and
um she cured herself of vaginal cancer
in and of herself and then turned around
and is helping many AIDS victims both
privately and weekly and sessions in
public. She nothing like this came up on
this show today. It's she's
good neat. I have very little faith in
the medical society apart from surgery
when it's absolutely necessary.
That is simply your definition and
description of your belief system which
is just as valid as any other. We will
once again thank you and all of you for
allowing each other to be once again a
synchronistic reflection of the
information that you need and giving
yourself the opportunity to see is right
at hand within the individuals that you
are surrounded with. That's interesting.
on the other hand I mean that's very
interesting what you said about the
berries over overcoming uh AIDS but I
mean do you have any ideas suggestions
how you could make this sort of a public
thing let us say if we were to give you the
let us say if we were to give you the
idea of a so-called opinion or
estimation the visualization for now
would be more
apppropo for in this way you will find
that because the idea of the berries may
involve the undertaking of what you call
the medical chemists. They may be
reluctant in this way to approach that
until they have exhausted every other
route. So in other words, it's going to reach
So in other words, it's going to reach
the I know you don't like predictions,
but it looks like the prediction in my
mind is that it's going to reach
epidemic proportions before they start
seeking other ways if that is what they
listening to. Yes. Although there can be
what you would call once again quote
unquote an underground movement which
has already begun.
Very good. Thank you. Thank you. Sure.
Thanks. Um I spoke to you about my fish
tank last week and the fish and um how
they reflected my idea of the flow and
contentedness in my life. Nice. But a
lot of them have died and they can and
it says they're reflecting um death as
change. Rapidity of change within my
having served as the symbols you
required they move on. Right. Um is
there any way more I don't know you are
not restricted by a bowl.
It's not a bowl. It's a 30 gallon
rectangular tank. Same thing. [Music]
[Music]
Move beyond the
boundaries of what you think is the
reality in which you exist. For they
have done so. They are
swimming beyond the boundaries of
physical reality through the glass and beyond.
reality through the glass and beyond.
Sure.
Do you know of the works of Jane Roberts
and of the uh spirit that came through
her set? To some degree. There was he
described in great length a concept
called the entity and the cells that
derived from the
entity. Do you know what I'm speaking
of? There are variations in your definition.
There are variations in your definition.
I'm sure. Can you be more specific?
Well, that's why what I was hoping that
you would because I was trying to
understand the concept within the book.
Oh. All right. Thank you.
What remains of your 3 minutes after
your break?
You may all take a short break.
Oh, repeat and define the idea you are
familiar with in the way you have stated
it. It is the concept
It is the concept
of there's an
entity and from the entity comes
cells and the selves because there is no
past or future. A
there is simultaneous manifestation of
what might be termed in a sense an
oversoul projecting itself in a myriad
number of simultaneous existences that
take on different aspects, different
perspectives and reflect different
points of view of the same single
oversoul entity. in this way and
manifest in whatever type of framework
reality is necessary for the experience
that the overall entity wishes to have
of itself. Whether it be the creation of
a past, present, or future or alternate
structural dimensional experience, all
is perceived by the singular entity that
any one of its fragments is a part of to
be one
simultaneous knowing experience.
Are there many entities or in a sense
yes there are divisions of divisions of
divisions of divisions of divisions? And
in this way you can recognize that there
is one all that is and at the same time
the one all that is recognizes itself to
be one and at the same time recognizes
itself to be the combination of all the
divisions. It is all the entities it is
all the fragments of all the entities it
is. Okay. So all the entities are belong to
Okay. So all the entities are belong to
the whole and the one. All is the one.
All is the one in its
multi-dimensional, multiaceted, simultaneously manifested
multiaceted, simultaneously manifested
ways of
existence. Everything is the same one
thing manifesting in all the different
ways it
can at the same time in a sense.
You follow me? Yes. I'm also wondering
there's no beginning and end, right? Not
really. Although those illusions can be
created in a time frame structure,
spatial frame structure such as the one
in which you have projected yourself to
exist. You can create the illusion of a
beginning and an end in that way. And
within the structure, they are in a
sense real beginnings and real endings
because you define that there can be
such an idea in your reality. But in an
overall sense, no. Existence simply is
and always is existence.
Then getting on to something like in an
astrological term of our
universe that the big bang theory would
not apply because there's Oh, it can
because that can simply be
representative of one particularly
physically manifesting universe as a
particular way in which it chose to
express itself into a particular type of
existence. It is just as valid and just
as real and just as true as all the
different ways that all the different
universes have created their own
manifestation from the consciousness
that supports them.
Thank you. Thank you for what do you
mean by the consciousness that supports
a universe? You are creating the
universe. All that is created you. You
create the universe of your experience.
You're not speaking then of the universe
to be a a sun with its uh planets that
is a solar system and is part of the
universe and in a sense you create that
in a sense I create that but who created
the sun with the planets
the mass combined consciousness of all
of the fragments that you are as a
system. In other words, there is a
collective entity that is represented by
all the individuals on your planet that
have ever existed on your planet or will
ever exist on your planet and all the
other dimensions of existence on any of
the other planets that make up your
system. This combined entity creates the
creation of the idea of an expression of
its consciousness that you recognize as
stars and planets. It is in a sense let
us say just to be colloquial a miniature
God so to speak within the all that is
God so to speak.
Where does
this energy that becomes this overall
source to create a universe come from?
How does it evolve to what it is? It
simply is. It is the primal fundamental
foundational energy that permeates all
that is the impingement of consciousness
upon that energy can allow to take what
you would call the illusion of solid
matter mass forms solidified energy if
you will but the energy is everywhere.
If a entity or an energy force was to
say today I want to create a universe
with a sun and a solar system can that
happen? Yes. It does all the time. It
does. Nice. All right. Where does the
idea or the the energy is the idea? The
entity is the idea the idea and becomes
the entire experience of that system.
Could I do that? On many levels. You do
understand the you you think you are now
by definition is a fragment of the
overall entity that created the system
in which you as a fragment are having an
experience. Okay. I'm a fragment of this
overall system. Is that overall system
my oversoul or is that a it is one level
of an oversold. One type of an oversold.
There are many different divisions. They
are all relatively arbitrary, but you do
create them to be real as you decide to
need them to be real.
Divisions, there are levels upon levels
upon levels. Add infinitum. Now, does a
oversoul a divide and then the divisions
of it create a universe in a sense? Yes.
Very good.
Let me ask you another question. Oh,
right. How many times have I been
incarnated? Several thousand at least. We cannot pin
Several thousand at least. We cannot pin
down what you would call a finite
number. And that is only in what you
call the earth plane. That has nothing
to do with parallel earths. It has
nothing to do with alternate dimensions.
It has nothing to do with other
civilizations. Now did you answer this
question from the point of my oversoul
or from my ego or the uh fragment that I
am of the oversoul? I answered it from
the general combination general pool
over soul of your entire society that
recognizes that all of its fragments or
most of its fragments I shall say have
incarnated many many hundreds if not
thousands of times. As a
fragment, can you tell me how many times
I have incarnated?
You as a fragment have only incarnated
once. Once.
You are not the same fragment in all the
other incarnations. The you you are here is
incarnations. The you you are here is
the only time you were ever this
you. So in a sense when you say you only
live one life, that is true for any
specific fragment. The idea of
reincarnation in that way involves a
totally different personality structure
and therefore literally is not
technically the same
view but it is a part of the same
oversoul energy. What the term ascension
yes how do you define that can be
defined in a few ways. One way that we
perceive it within the mass
consciousness that you are is an
acceleration of your energy, a
cognition, an expansion of your
awareness of more of yourself and
thereby the resultant reflection or
action in your life as if you are in
fact being more of yourself. It is an
alignment to more of yourself. It is the
channeling of more of yourself, more
energy present, more manifestation in
your life.
Thank you. Thank you. Nice. than you as
a fragment in this lifetime as myself
when I pass on as a fragment what
happens oh many different things there
are also the creation in your reality of
many different levels so to speak even
in non-physical reality and they can
range all the way from not even knowing
you are dead all the way up to leaving
this entire system alto together
you follow me
anything in
There are many different opportunities,
many different exciting experiences that
you have created for yourself many times
in what you would call in between your
physical lives. But as the fragment when
I pass on, do I become part of the
entity? In a sense, yes. But this does
not mean, although I know this may be
quote unquote difficult for many of you
to understand, it does not mean that you
lose the individuality.
You still can at any time claim
cognition and perception through that
particular window for it always exists.
Thank you.
Thank you guys. Uh there's a woman in
New Mexico who gives you experiences
with past lives. So I've written a book
with acupuncture. Nice. Now what I can't
understand is if you have fragments and
you never come back to this life as the
same personality but it is a part of the
same oversoul energy. All right. So one
fragment is connected to the other
fragments in the same way that each and
every one of your fingers can be traced
back to the same hand. So you can find
in a sense another finger by going from
one finger up through the hand and down
into another finger. They are connected
on some level. Yes. But what she does is
give you pictures in your that is what
you create for yourself from the
stimulation of the energy that you are
allowing that individual to assist you
within. Okay. Well, if you put faces to
them, yes, how come the faces would be
recognizable if they're not the same?
Because you have a sense of energy
recognition. Many times as you do in what you call
Many times as you do in what you call
your dreams, you do recognize that you
are dealing with someone you are
familiar with even though they do not
quote unquote look as they do in
physical life. You simply recognize that
they may have many many many different
aspects and the aspect is different and
you recognize it to be different but the
vibrational signature of the soul is the
same. And in many cases that is how we
quote unquote recognize some of you even
though you may go through many changes.
The signature soul vibration does not
change that much. Well, all right. The
other question I had is how come the sun
doesn't burn out if it's on It's a fire,
isn't it? It is what you would call
physically speaking a nuclear reaction.
Thus, in a sense, it will quote unquote
burn out. But its lifespan is measured
in what you would call tens of millions
of years. So, the temperature really
doesn't vary that much, does it? Oh, it
does fluctuate, but in an overall sense, you
fluctuate, but in an overall sense, you
can say there is an average, but it gets
hotter and colder and hotter and colder,
so to speak. It doesn't go colder on
down. Like, for example, if it's burning
out, the amount of heat it's putting off
should be less. It will be
in time. Uh-huh. Not in my lifetime, of
course. Not in this fragmentaryary
lifetime. Okay. You are in your own estimation
Okay. You are in your own estimation
approximately quote unquote
halfway through the life of your
particular central star. As long as it
has burned quote unquote burned, it will
burn for that much longer. I think I put
this question to you before. What is
this game all about?
Again, recognize it is about learning
that this kind of game exists, that you
can experience it and add to from the
overall entity oversoul point of view
that much more cognition of all the
different ways you can experience all
that is. I know that from the point of view
is. I know that from the point of view
you are as a fragment, you have created
a society that seeks to find the
purposes behind everything. But in this
way, the idea you call purpose is your
invention. And therefore, it came after
the creation. And that which created
creation. And that which created
creation existed quote unquote before,
so to speak, the creation of your
invention of purpose. Therefore, that
which has existed before purpose does
not need a purpose to do anything. It
does it because it is what it is.
The idea that when you chose to explore
this, you chose to explore limitation
from the viewpoint of being, let us say,
just to be colloquial in your language,
perhaps a little more definitive, you
chose this idea as a mass collective
entity. So while it may not seem to make
too much sense to the fragments that the
entity became, to the entity, it makes
sense because to the entity, it is an
overall experience that adds to its
enrichment and understanding of itself.
Very good. Now what about if this soul
is projected soul is down here to have a
certain experience
and it it doesn't occur. Does that mean
he reincarnates again and tries again or
what? Oh it does occur or it has to
occur in a sense. Yes. Whatever occurs
is what needs to
occur and that adds to the overall
knowledge of the entity. And is that the
purpose that he decided on before he
came down or generally generally
general experiences are determined in
that way by the oversoul or higher self.
The actual specifics of how you go
through that general experience are up
to the free will that is bequeath to you
from the oversoul as a physical
construct. How you experience the idea
is up to you. The oversoul experiences
all that you choose to do, positive and
negative, as learning. It does not
judge. At what point do we realize where
we came from during this procedure? Any
point you wish to. It's like you can
realize it now or when you die. Correct.
And uh what will bring this about? You I
uh what will bring this about? You I
know. But how? The fact that you are
even aware that it is possible has
already brought it about. All you have
to do is believe that it has and your
physical reality will begin to reflect
that you believe
that. You simply are not acting like you
believe that it has. So you are not
giving yourself an opportunity to create
a type of physical reality that
reinforces it with feedback. Mhm. But
you are doing that actually and bit by
bit you are doing it more and
more because you are agreed upon to be
in this life in this civilization at
this transformational time. Therefore,
by definition, simply because you are
exploring what you are exploring, it
means you are exactly perfectly in the
right place at the right time that you
need to be and learning exactly what you
need to know at exactly the rate you
need to know it. So relax.
Easy for you to say. Yes, it was. And it
is just as easy to do when you allow
yourself to stop treating the phrase
easy to you to say as something like a
fundamental law of the universe.
It is just as easy to do as it is to say
when you begin to say
that it will become so.
Thank you. Thank you.
You then you then if we if we look at
our past lives for example we don't
really need our physical brain to look
at those past lives.
You in a sense as a fragment may require
the utilization of your physical brain
in order to create an interpretation
that your physical consciousness can
understand. But as a consciousness, no,
you could perceive directly the idea of
yourself as any one of those past
fragments. In order to have a physical
understanding, you will need to utilize
the brain to create symbols that you can
understand as a physical being. Okay.
But so the soul carries or accumulates
all these experiences or is all these
experiences all at once. Yes. And that's
like a nonvolatile memory bank and it's
also non-physical which is so it's like
the universe is really basically a a
memory bank. Well in a sense but
understand it is not that the soul is a memory bank
it is not that the soul is a memory bank
because your idea memory implies that it
has to stretch into a past to the soul
it is all simultaneous. It is not
remembering so much in that way. It
simply is knowing what it is in a
different aspect.
Yeah, that's pretty clear. Thank you.
No. Um, I'm intrigued by the idea of
energy transference as it applies to
uh passing on and maybe becoming a new
um, you know, person or
entity. and our awareness of that fact.
Um, it seems
that it's even possible that our our
our consciousness in one lifetime may
not be, you know, the same as the other.
Although I know it's all one. We
understand. Okay. There are many
possible ways and many more ways are
becoming more probable to your
civilization. Okay. You are ending your self-imposed
Okay. You are ending your self-imposed
linear karmic cycle limitations. So
there are many more methodologies of
interacting with your earth sphere than
there used to be.
Good. Is is your is our awareness as we move
Is is your is our awareness as we move
through thousands of years in different
forms is it a uh like you say we're
we're not the same person. We're we only
go through life once as we are and then
we go through it again as something
else. Yes. But the soul contains again
the experience. Okay. The higher self or
whatever contains all all of it. Well,
yeah. We we contain all of everything.
Okay. Thank you. Thank you.
Sure. Yay. Uh I had another tip in my
tongue when you were talking then about
uh when
you I have to drop it for
you. Please forgive me. Oh
nothing. I haven't picked it up yet.
No, guys. You were saying that the
guys. You were saying that the
oversoul, the oversoul knows all that is
or comprehends it or is aware of it in a
sense. Then why does it need the fragments to
Then why does it need the fragments to
experience it?
Because it is one way it can.
Again, you are looking for a purpose.
The only purpose it needs is that it can
do it. Period. That is justification
enough. It is one way to experience all that is
It is one way to experience all that is
so you thought it would be um No. And
it's really a
when you made the original decision
[Music] you are having a good time.
Yeah. But what
are you also very hard then? You are
only choosing to reinforce that it is
not as simple as you can believe. I know
it and that's what's the [\h__\h] As soon
as you allow yourself to know that
everything you experience in your life
is there for a reason and there as a
part of the positive idea you desire to
be. Then you will begin to experience it
as such. Again, every situation is
fundamentally neutral. There is no such
thing as a situation that has builtin
meaning. You give it the meaning and the
meaning you give it determines the
effect you get out of it. So when you
are willing to cease making the
assumption that there can even possibly
be such a thing as a situation that
could occur in your life that would be
an interruption in your flow. When you
cease that point of view, then you will
only allow yourself to know that every
situation, yes I mean every situation is
there as a part of your positive flow.
And then that is the only way you will
allow yourself to experience
it.
Period. [\h__\h] you. It works. Fine you.
That is the thing we can guarantee
100% it does. in fact work if you let
it. Always. Always.
Always.
Always. Oh, did I mention always?
Oh, thank you for reminding me. It
always works.
Yes. Oh, you're still looking.
Oh, all right.
I would like to ask you about uh a
health thing that has been bothering me
in at different times. Sometimes my
scalp is really dry and it bothers me
and other times I don't think about it
and it seems like there's no problem and
I think there's an emotional tie there.
Ah and could could it also be a dietary
thing? Oh, there could be some association with
Oh, there could be some association with
that. But our original perception in
this way, let us say the way we perceive
your energy is that it is more the idea
of allowing your mentality to become a
little bit too fevered.
Thinking hard. Thinking too hard.
Ace will burn you out, dry you up. Good boy.
Good boy.
more than uh just e eating too much
sugar or bad things that are do
understand that we are saying that there
may be a connection but the idea of
ingesting some of those substances is
more of a reaction to what is already
going on within your mentality being
attracted to certain foods that I eat
because of yes what are you so fevered
about what are you in such a flurry
about you are eternal what's the rush
I don't
Uh at times I don't feel rushed at all.
All right. And I feel very peaceful.
Then that is probably when you are
lubricated.
Thank you. Can I ask something else? You
just have. Okay. Um I was recently
traveling and at places where I was up
very high in the mountains hiking and
did not find very much fear in being up
in mountains and nature. that many times
I've been on top of buildings where I've
looked out from a 10-story building that
seems very high and I seem to have a
fear looking down right from man-made
structures but not from mountains or
that is because you believe that quote
unquote man and woman made structures
are not natural.
Was there ever a time that I ever
experienced a death from falling? Yes.
Is there something I need to deal with
that and being comfortable being from a
high place or is it okay just to be
there and look down and be fearful and
continue that for whatever reason that
has you may simply find that as you
continue to hike through your life. You
will encounter all the different
portions of yourself that need to be
integrated and you may simply find one
day that as you look down from one of
your structures the fear is gone. You
have integrated it. You have climbed the
mountain within yourself. I have a real
feeling that I could jump off and fly.
And either that I've been a flying
creature, have done things in piloting
different crafts and vehicles and have
some of that and also the idea that you
have a strong attachment to your astral
out-of body projection
experiences. It is not impossible.
However, I would not suggest pushing it
for it is not necessarily that you have
a very strong attachment within the idea
of that belief reality at this
time. However, we understand the feeling
that you mean, and bit by bit, it will
accelerate and acclimate into your
reality as you allow each and every one
of yourselves to become more and more
beings of
light, which is what you are, but you do
not think so. As you allow yourselves to
think of yourselves more and more of
beings of light, then you will not have
any weight to be pulled down.
and you will fly. In a
sense, you are simply
precognizing and
recognizing the blending of your past
and future and accelerating in the
present. In that
way, you may in your life have
spontaneous what you would call
teleportations from time to time or
spontaneous levitations. These can
become more and more common in your
society as you enter fourth density.
Simply go with them according to the
idea of the timing as to when they
naturally occur. No need to fling
yourself. All right. Okay. Thank you. Sure. Ah,
All right. Okay. Thank you. Sure. Ah,
did you lost it all? Yeah. Thank you. Do
share. What it was was, have I ever
incarnated as an extraterrestrial?
Yes. Now, as to whether you wish to consider
Now, as to whether you wish to consider
that a past tense or a future tense is
up to you. In a sense, it is both. Do
recognize that in an overall sense, none
of you are quote unquote original to
your planet.
Uh-huh. How many planes can we incarnate
on? As many as you wish. Oh, really?
Really? So, you are unlimited.
You are in Why do I choose here? Well,
this is one of the places you have
chosen. Do not forget that they are all
going on at the same time. Even the ones
in the past and the future are going on
at the same time, so to speak. This is
simply one viewpoint. And simply by the
definition of this viewpoint, you may
not have as much realization as you will
have that you do in fact exist on all
the other planes you have chosen at the
same time simply because that is the
definition of this particular fragment.
To not know that until now. Uhhuh. Okay.
Okay. Is it possible for me to be in two
or three different bodies at the same
time on this plane? Yes. On this plane?
Yes. Interesting. So there are already
Interesting. So there are already
variations and versions of this idea
that are called counterparts.
The idea is that a counterpart is
another fragment, another physical form
that you would recognize as a separate
individual from yourself that is in fact
a part of the same soul and responsible
for your fragment and the fragment of
that other individual or other
individuals. It is the same thing as
having a past life and a future life
except it exists in the same time frame.
And this is quite common. The average
idea is that many of you may have well
at least three or four if not more. Mhm.
Many times you have interacted with them
without ever gaining a sense that they
are your counterparts. You do not have
to feel attracted to a counterpart. You
may even have created scenarios where
you were in opposition to your
counterparts, but that was the purpose
of creating that reflection.
Crazy people we are very creative. Yeah.
Yes. But that idea is not uncommon at all.
But that idea is not uncommon at all.
You will find that idea in many
civilizations. It is quite a natural
thing. And how many souls are there? Oh,
Oh,
two three four five six seven. It
depends on what level you're looking.
Well, I I'm interested to get some idea
of
the idea of this. All right. All right.
All right. All right. All right. One
more. [Music] [Music]
One less.
One more.
Our immediate perception, now this
fluctuates very rapidly, our immediate
perception for now is that out
of roughly
roughly the approximately five billion
physical incarnated fragments upon your
planet. Those 5 billion physical beings
represent roughly within the immediate
influence of the energy of your
planet approximately 3 million souls.
Wow. So there are that many
counterparts. Wow.
I had a funny feeling there was
something strange going on here.
Now that is within one particular
immediate level but it is the level to
which we were attracted. So we will
assume that that is the answer that
makes the most sense and has the most
validity for this interaction at this
time. Okay. But that gives me an idea of
how many counterparts there are on the
earth.
it. It is everywhere and nowhere. It is
all right here and now. Space and time
are illusions in that sense.
It is all within you. You are
holographic in that sense. The universe
is holographic. That is any point within
the hologram contains the information
for the whole hologram
following. Yes, that is the way the
universe is. It is all one and the same
thing in every fragment. Getting back to
the plane we're living on. If I wanted
to find a counter counterpart and come
up and say, "Hey, I know you." How would
I go about that? Use your instinct, your
intuition and your imagination and your
meditation to divine for yourself what
purpose that would serve and then you
will simply find yourself attracted and
you will simply give yourself the
indications that are necessary. You will
know when it is necessary to know.
Sometimes you will go through the
experience and then know because to know
during the experience may not serve the
experience but you will know when you
need to know. You see, and again, it is
all relatively arbitrary. So many times
you will find that you simply do not
need to know.
No, I gather that. But I'm just
interested. There are times when you can
know. Well, you can know.
Very good. So, one moment.
Now this may not be exactly as literal
as the counterpart idea we have already
defined. There may be some fluctuation
of associations of fragments in
different ways according to different
contracts, different agreements and
different purposes for which this is
being served. But our immediate
perception is that within the
individuals gathered this evening of
your time with specific reference to the
time with specific reference to the
fragment that you are, you have between
three and five connections in this room.
Is that right? But it is within a degree
of
fluctuating interaction.
There are let us say some that represent
more solid counterparts as we have
defined them and a few that are
fluctuating in and out of the agreement
because they only need to interact as
let us say a moderate associative way.
So in a sense they may be from the same
basic soul source but there can also be
the splitting off of soul energy into a
totally different soul ramification that
has its own projections which then you
may relate to as quote unquote distant
cousins and can be viewed as
counterparts of a different type. We're
going to have a good laugh when this is
all over, aren't we? Oh, you're having a
good laugh now? I mean, when we go out
there, at least I am.
I mean, you know, in other words, some
of our um Yes. our wives might be our
counterparts. Oh, yes. Oh, yes. Oh, yes.
Yes. Yes.
and your children and your parents and
your enemies and your so-called enemies
very often many times.
Thank you. Thank you
um can you give a definition of evil and
how you see it to be working in our
lives? The description you call evil is
only a judgmental labeling of what you
perceive to be negative energy.
Nothing is
evil. There are expressions of negative
energy, negative effect, and negative
affectation that are reflections or
representations of a desire to separate
the self from the rest of all that is.
If you wish a definition, then that is
quote unquote evil. But that is all it
is.
Does that assist you? Yeah. Thanks.
You sure? Yes. dead.
Well, what about uh murder and rape and
all right all that kind of stuff. Thank
you. Do recognize that in what we are
about to say there may be many
preconceived ideas and notions within
you. So allow yourself to perceive that
what we are saying in this way is not an
excusing of what you would perceive to
be the perpetrator.
However, the idea of what you would call
a so-called victim is someone who has
created within themselves a belief andor
fear, which is the same thing as a
belief that that can be a reality for
them. Thus, in a sense, they create it
by attracting it. Now, this does not
mean that that excuses the so-called
perpetrator that is attracted to create
the victim to be a victim through the
victim's fear of beabling to be a
victim. But in this way, it is an
opportunity for the so-called
perpetrator to also stand fast within
their own self-empowerment, their own
strength, and refuse to heed the call
sent out by the victim. Refuse to give
away their power in that way. Refuse to
take the victim's power in that way. Not
being willing to play that game.
Understand that the idea of like any
polarity, victim and perpetrator, is two
sides of the same event. the same
action. Therefore, because a so-called
victim radiates the idea into their
reality that they can be a victim, that
they can be victimized, and that they
believe that that is the strongest
possible reality they can experience.
That radiation attracts the individuals who
radiation attracts the individuals who
are not strong enough within themselves
to recognize that they are as powerful
as they need to be to get anything they
want without having to hurt anyone else
to get it. Therefore, in a sense, the
perpetrator is the victim's victim.
And therefore the victim is in a sense a
perpetrator just as much as any
perpetrator is. When individuals on both
sides of that
polarity recognize that they do a create
their own
reality and b are self-empowered enough
to have any kind of a reality they so
desire without having to hurt anyone
else to get it. There will be no more
perpetrators and no more victims. Those
two things is all it
takes. Does that answer your question?
Yes. Thank you.
You Oh, well. Okay. I was thinking, but what
Oh, well. Okay. I was thinking, but what
about the family surrounding? That is
all a choice to be attracted to that
individual who
then gives that family an opportunity to
come to terms with fears and beliefs
within themselves for having
participated in that idea.
Now a family in that way simply may for
many reasons have attracted themselves
to that individual. For in this sense
you may find that many of these ideas
may be the quote unquote carryovers or
momentum or results of other lives that
they wish to balance out in another life
in a particular life. And it may simply
be that if they know they've attracted
or are creating such an experience for
themselves in that way, they have drawn
around them the family that they need to
experience that with them to learn from
that experience and or have supported
them and help them up to the point of
that experience to allow them to enable
themselves once they have had the
experience. And perhaps if it leads to
what you call death, once they are on
the other side, the non-physical side to
learn and gain from that experience and
also perhaps interact as spirit guides
for those that are left behind in
physical reality. There are many agreements, as
reality. There are many agreements, as
many agreements as there are
individuals. It depends upon the
contract that has been written as to why
those individuals are together and
experiencing what they are experiencing.
You follow me? Yes, I do. Thank you.
Thank you. You sure? Yes. you than you.
Uh, two questions. First, are my wife
and I counterparts?
Why? Uh, I was reading in Seth book the
other night about counterparts and
suddenly that idea just popped into my
head. Well, then for now it will do.
Again, it is an arbitrary distinction,
but recognize that if you find yourself
attracted to it, then that is the way
you need to relate to it to allow you to
proceed and progress through your own
process. Okay. Simply trust that whatever sparks
Okay. Simply trust that whatever sparks
within your imagination is the tool you
need. Follow it for it will lead you to
more of yourself in the way you chose to
be led.
Okay. Second question is why am I fat?
In this way, many times we will simply
give you the overall understanding and
the mass consciousness understanding
that we have as there is a wonderfully
creative parallel symbolic
interpretation in your particular
language that goes along with this that
we have utilized many times and it will
explain by analogy some of the idea.
individuals who are not willing to do
what it is that excites them the most
are waiting to do. Thus, they attract
all that energy and rather than let it
out, they allow it to transform into
mass because they don't use it. When you
begin to do what it is that excites you,
your activity level will increase in
that way and you will begin to channel
all that energy through you and it will
not collect around you and turn into
mass when you stop waiting.
Then you will not carry excess
weight. You sure? Has that served you?
Yes, very much. Thank you. Thank you.
Yeah, I was just going to say diet must
have something to do with that, is it?
Oh, yes. But in this way, do recognize
that the idea once again of what you
call diet is only a reflection after the
fact of how you think of yourself. For
many individuals will find that many
times they may eat and eat and eat and
eat and never gain a pound or they may
starve themselves and never lose weight.
It depends upon the idea they are
carrying of themselves and why they
think they need to make an attachment
and an association with the idea of the
sustenance that which sustains them. To
some degree there will be some
fluctuation but that is not the core of
the beginning of the creation of that
idea. It is primarily that most of the
individuals with a few exceptions are
simply not doing what it is that would
excite them the most.
You will find that when you are doing
what excites you the most, your diet
will regulate itself quite naturally.
You will simply eat what you know you
need to
eat and your weight level will maintain
an even balance.
Why doesn't that manifest in other
people that are waiting or not doing
what excites them? But it doesn't they
might still different individuals
manifest different things in different
ways. For sure. One moment. What are you
following? Well, if I then let's put it this way.
Well, if I then let's put it this way.
Let me put it this way. Would you prefer
the idea of excess weight or migraines
or ulcers or cancer?
I think you have to pick. Yes.
Obviously, you have made your
choice. Therefore, relax.
All right. So, then really any of those
are manifestations can be representative
of that idea. Yes, they all represent
the so-called blockages of your
energy which only occur and appear to be
blockages because you are simply not
willing to trust that what excites you
the most is valid in your life and that
you will be supported in the doing of it
automatically. That is all there is to
it. It is that simple.
Oh, thank you. Yes. along those lines.
Um, it doesn't I don't believe it has to
be as dramatic as migraine or overweight
or whatever. No, it just when you were
talking about that it was so great. I
had this recognition I guess it was
recognition that um at this time in my
life I'm just I am so inspired to write.
Yes. And I'm at such peace with that.
That is what excites me the most and I'm
doing it. Thank you. And uh I found just
in this conversation that when I'm not
doing that, right, the way that
manifests in my life is negative
thoughts, negativity, um you know, and
in harmony with life in my thinking. But
when I'm doing what I know I'm supposed
to be doing and exciting me, it's like a
freedom from that. Excitement is your
barometer that lets you know that you
are doing what it is that represents the
path you chose to be. Nothing's getting
stored up in me which causes all the
negativity. Correct. Right. Okay. I
wanted to share that. Thank you.
Manifest in so many different ways and
Okay. The other thing I wanted to um get
back on victimization
um retrospectively if you were a victim
and now you know an adult trying to deal
with that. Yes, I can see how you could
just like kiss it off but uh as just
being all part of life's experience that
you needed to experience but and another
part of me says you need to work it out
and and your choice, right?
But the the
one is not better than another way.
Okay. The
typical mana uh manner in dealing with
that is going to therapy and or group
therapy or whatever. It just seems like
all that stuff is so trivial and petty.
Not for the individuals going through
it. Yeah, I'm speaking for myself. If it's
Yeah, I'm speaking for myself. If it's
uh then you are simply stating that you
know what you prefer for you. That does
not mean you have to judge what is valid
for others. Oh no, I'm not even judging
what then it is not trivial or petty.
No, just for myself. Not even for
yourself. It simply isn't the idea that
you are. That doesn't make it trivial or
petty. It simply makes it not you. I'm
not even sure if those are the right
words. We
understand. Thank you,
guys. I'm preoccupied with this pending
earthquake. Oh, pending. Pending. And
I'm concerned about my sister because I
know she's real afraid of it. And I'm
afraid that her fear Well, I have some
fear, too. Does when you're afraid of
something like that, the more fear you
have, can you attract things you're
reinforcing it? That's the idea. because
you're believing. Yes. By being to fear
that something is real is to say that
you believe that that is the most likely
reality to occur. And what if you really
do believe that's the most likely
reality? I mean then that is what you
will experience. So you just have to
change your belief unless you want to
experience. Understand that if you are
cognizant that that may be within you
the most likely reality then ask
yourself how would it serve you if that
was your experience.
If you can glean the understanding of
why you would think that you would teach
yourself something in that way, then
perhaps you can allow yourself to
recognize there may be other ways to get
the same message. And then you won't
have to let that be the only way you
will receive the message. Then you can
utilize your imagination and simply
understand that if you know you will
accept all the messages you are giving
yourself, then you will simply allow
yourself to be attracted to wherever you
need to be so as not to participate in
that experience should it occur. Okay?
And Is there some way that um now am I
making it worse for my sister by being
concerned about her being afraid? Well,
in a sense, although you cannot really
affect someone else's reality, but you
can in a sense give off the impression
of the reinforcement that they do have
something to be afraid of.
Thank you. Thank you, Mich. Yay.
Fragments and guides are guides.
Fragments of the oversold can be. Do not
have to be can be. Or what are they if
they're not other souls? Total oversold.
Can be.
Can you amplify that a little bit? Like
uh maybe observing my guides and tell me
are they fragments or are they souls?
Let's say if you had seven of
them, three of
them could be counterpart type
fragments.
Two could be associative souls.
Ones that you have had many life
experiences with before that are not
part of the same over soul as you. All
right. One could be an
alternate version of yourself.
an idea so to speak of a future and/or
past. You coming from that point of view
and or an alternate dimension expression
of another form of your oversoul. Not
exactly what you would call a
counterpart, but perhaps from another
level altogether, something beyond the
immediate oversoul. And the last one
would be something possibly that you
would call completely detached that
comes from somewhere else
entirely outside of what you would call
the earth experience realm.
How or when does a that is how it
generally can average out. This will
fluctuate. How how or when does a
fragment or a soul decide to be a guide
to a fragment or another soul? It can be
done in the
moment. It can be set up prior to the
physical life. The
timing does not matter. It will be
activated when necessary.
What what causes them the necessity? My
thoughts or theirs?
Perhaps the idea that you wish such an
interaction and on their part a desire
to partake in such an interaction both
are necessary to have the interaction.
angels. Yeah. What are they relative to
a oversoul or generally they are
representative of either aspects of your
higher consciousness and or other
consciousnesses not immediately a part
of your own soul that can let's say
generally be said to be the aspects of
consciousness that have never
experienced physical reality at all.
The Lazarus could be an angel.
Do angels participate with the fragments
that are incarnated? Oh yes. In what
way? Whatever way is necessary to assist
those fragments in whatever purposes
they have created their lives to be. Are
they? But relatively, usually
unobtrusively because the idea of any
kind of a guide is to lead the one you
are leading to more of that self so that
they function as their own guide and do
not need another guide to assist them.
So the paradox of a spirit guide is
usually one that allows you to be led to
more of yourself so that you can
function as your own recognizable guide
and become equal to the guide that has
given you an assistance. When I become
equal to that guide, you are equal now.
All right. When I recognize that I'm
equal. Yes. At
what function do I then serve? Whatever
you wish. Be of service in whatever way
excites you. Do I then have guides that
are at a higher level can? Yes, if that
is what excites you. Yes. Again, there
is always consciousness available to
interact with you in whatever type of
interaction excites you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Push hard. Nice. Um I recently injured
my knee. Nice. and I've been told by
doctors that I'm going to have about a
year of physical therapy. I'm wondering
what I can do. Um, what occurred to you
in your imagination first? What would
you like to do? I um it seems like there
could be things that I could wrap it
with. I know such as such as trust trust
trust trust such as I don't know the
name. Trust trust trust trust.
You do not have to know the names to
know you can attract them into your life
and they will be obvious to you when
they arrive. Okay? If you simply know
that that is something you can do, you
will always attract yourself as you may
have done this night of your time as
there may be individuals willing to
share information with you that can be
of service to you in this way. You will
always attract yourself exactly to the
right place, the right time and interact
with exactly the right individuals to
assist in reflecting to you what you
need to support the idea you are
trusting that you are being. So simply
know that without needing analytical
cognition, you will simply always
receive the opportunity to recognize the
things that will assist you. You follow
me? If that is what moves you most
strongly, that particular methodology,
then simply take it for granted that you
will in no uncertain terms and very
rapidly find yourself being given the
ingredients that you need simply by
having been putting out the energy that
that is what you need. Now that you have
been willing to share that idea, there
are individuals who recognize your
particular situation, your particular
vibration, and are more than willing to
assist you with their knowledge. Again,
it is not that that knowledge has to be
absolute in your eyes, but it can always
allow you to be comfortable with your
imagination and alter the information
they share with you in whatever way,
shape, or form you feel most comfortable
with. Can be the attraction of
information from individuals. Can be
that you will walk up to what you call
one of your books. It'll be exactly the
book you need. You will turn exactly to
the page you need and there will be the
information that you need. It can
manifest in many different ways. All you
need to do is trust that you will have
what you need and you will. And trust
that my knee will really recover. Yes.
Again, the universe does not do
pointless things. And the idea is that
if you know the manifestation of that
desire is relevant to the idea of the
balancing of your knee, then you can
simply understand that in many cases, as
it may be in your case, the idea of
having done that to your knee may simply
be for the purpose of allowing you to
take advantage of your own trust. And
you may find that many times it may not
even have to play all the way out. And
as soon as you are willing to take
advantage of your own trust, by the time
you get the ingredients, the knee is
already healed because that is what the
purpose of the injury was all about.
Just trust me. Thank you. Try comfort.
trust me. Thank you. Try comfort.
Oh my, what a coincidence.
Back to the guide question. All right.
Are there negative guides, so-called
negative guides that help like criminals
perpetuate their lifestyle? In other
words, are there guides? There are
consciousnesses that can desire to
express the idea of
negativity. In this way, like anything,
first of all, recognize this. No one, no
guide, positive and or so-called
negative, can possibly influence anyone
that does not agree to create the
illusion of being influenced. But they
are creating the illusion
themselves. Therefore, the idea of a
guide is more of the idea of an
association. And if an individual is
willing to explore the idea of
negativity in that way, then any other
consciousness that is choosing to
explore that idea can form a type of
association with any other individual
forming that type of a reality for
themselves. So in that sense, you can
say yes, there may be negative guides.
But in that way, it is simply because
that what you decide to be is the quote
unquote crowd you hang out with.
You follow me? Yes, I do. Um supposing
that um like a criminal deviant did uh
hook up with a so-called negative guide,
how could he break that connection?
Would he have the choice to break that?
Of course, always. Again, recognize
this. However, by definition, most of
the idea of what you would call
non-physicality by definition implies
that it is quote unquote balanced and
therefore usually does not express
itself negatively. Therefore, what would
usually be perceived by you in your
civilization as a so-called non-physical
negative guide is usually an extension
of the consciousness of the individual
and not a separate entity. The
individual on the physical plane. Yes.
Because beyond fourth
beyond fourth
density by definition it is almost not
possible to express negativity because
you are completely integrating it. Okay.
So that person would be tapping into
that information and putting his own
negative meaning to it. Okay. All right.
Thank you. Thank you. It is another
manifestation of the degree to which you
can create separation. Okay. And give it
life. Sure. Because you are agreeing.
Yes. Would Hitler be a good example of
that? In a sense. Yes. the
willingness to act as a reflection for a
large percentage of mass consciousness
fear and negativity and channel that
through himself.
Was he a channel? Everyone is. Okay. But
was he a channel in the sense that he
used to sit down and no? more of a
channel in the sense that he was willing
to not recognize his own
self-empowerment. Willing in that way to
express the idea of everyone else's lack
of belief in their own self-empowerment
and express that back to them,
channeling the fears of your
civilization. And where is he now? Is he back on the
And where is he now? Is he back on the
earth?
No. There is no reason for you to hope
not. For understand in this way again
the idea is fundamentally neutral and
that individual allowed your society to
come to terms with many of its fears.
Now the energy as we perceive it of that
individual after having taken on that
particular type of manifestation is that
what you would colloquially call the
soul that was incarnated as that being
is still in what you would call a rest
state. For in this way, according to the belief
For in this way, according to the belief
systems at the time it entered the
non-physical plane, there could not be a quick
plane, there could not be a quick
transformation out of all of the
negativity that was experienced by that
individual. And it will take some time
for what you would call
repair. Then it will have an opportunity
to become completely polarized and
balanced in the opposite way and express
as much light and love as it expressed
negativity, limitation, and separation.
quickly. No, this to be quick. I was
just thinking a lot about fear. It seems
to be coming up a lot tonight and I've
been thinking about it a lot myself. Oh,
right. Once again, simply let me remind
you. Fear, the negative portion that you
experience in this way is only judgment
of messages that are coming to yourself
from yourself about portions of yourself
you simply have not been willing to
face. Recognize that fear is a
messenger. It always and can only ever
bring you a portion of yourself that is
yet simply one more portion you can add
to the total being that you are and
integrate within you thus allowing you
to expand. So do not judge your fear and
it will not bring with it a negative
manifestation in your life. It will not
bring with it a negative effect. You
follow me? Thank you. Make a friend of
every portion of you. In this way you
will allow yourself to become a unified
individual. And that as a knowing
complete individual is what will allow
the total mass consciousness to unify
itself. Once again, the granting of
validity and equality to all the
differences within your society is what
will create the unity that you seek. We
extend our appreciation and our
unconditional love to you in allowing us
to experience the unique and lovely
manifestations of all that is that each
and every one of you are individually
and collectively. We bid you exciting
dream lives and life dreams. We bid you
a fond and loving good night.