Let me asal signature
asal signature
vibration each and every one of you is a
work a matri of enery at the heart of
which in is a spark of the primal enery por
doorway other dimensionalities which
allows each and every one of you to
function as a single holographic
consciousness and at the same time to
function as an individual identity.  Each
and every one of you collectively th
forms in this way a single facet of a
multidimensional cstall lat work crystall
matrix that in of itself when
combined may a portion of another level
and another level beyond that beyond that
and on and on into what you call
infinity each and every one of you
however contains with structure of the
cstal the cstal matri that each and you
are individually the entire as you say
blueprint the entire pattern the entire
template for all of the universes the
multiverse in that way each and every
one  of you is a microcosmic
representation of what you call the
macrocosmic cstal structure of physical
reality as
as
from the primary fundamental temporal consciousness consciousness
itself is the template upon which
physical reality is structured in this
way th recogn that each and every one of
you are a complete let us say genetic
code for the entire universe a complete
template for the entire universe and that
Why when you simply allow yourself to
recogn that you can be in touch with
primaline frequency with each and every
one of you you therefore are able to recognize that
you  have at your immediate
accessibility  all of the information all
of the answers that you need to
understand your in this life you have
created yourself to live and that it is
all in the immediate present for you
immediate here now and th that is why
you do not have reaching into what you to
be theant future to extract information
with great stri and great strum nor do
you have to go delving into the dim dark
in this way to dredge up from these
bottomless pits some scanned information
that you are struggling to receive to
understand yourself in the present
recogniz that the only reason  you can in
touch at all with the ideas of your soable
futures and the ideas of any p is
because both the future and the past
exist with you now in the primal energy
cstal matri of your existence th you
are not traveling anywh everything you
need is right at hand so to speak right
with you in the here and now all the
future all the
al right with you
All your to one more timely
timely
to prim signature
vibration thates
your matri is what we have described and
discussed with you to be the vibratory
experi you  call excitement excitement is
yours  physiological
you to that is you can always and
always will to any given what is in that excites
you will always be automatically
for inollowing excit you will
consciously on sym
chow through sych
allicality from being to be a reflection
of the support that you require in
exactly the right place and the right
time in order to allow you to continue to
function as the idea you know you are being by
the simple act of acting
Yes.  We are only responsible feeling that so responsible
in this sense you are responsible
to everyone else in your reality not for
them and you are responsible to yourself
in this sense to simply know you are in control
and are creating whatever reality
you desire.  So in that sense the idea
of ​​the blending of your transformational age is yes
in a sense
to recognize that your true cognition is
to allow the ecstasy that is your
birthri to be reflected in your life no
matter how you bring that about with
integrity in other words it is also the
cognition as we have said that you are
as powerful as you need to be to have
anything desire without having to
any force upon anyur anyone
else in order to get what you know to be
true for you because you are as powerful
as you need to be  to have it
automatically be attracted into your
life um if something gives you discomfort
let's say there's a belief
structure.  I'm scared of water and I'm
sitting by the pool and got this nervous
and I decide to change this right and I
start to put there that I'm not scared
of water anymore.  And then my son comes
up and ask me to fix his toy and I
forget what I'm doing for and I start fixing
that and I come back and then I
the old belief structure seems to play
back in.  What does the existing belief
structure have going for the new belief
structure?  Ask yourself how
having and
maintaining.  The one belief structure
you do not prefer.  Ask yourself how
maintaining it does in fact serve you.
What does it let you discover about
yourself that you may need to discover
to integrate within your being in
whatever time frame you are comfortable
with to allow you to come to terms with
something that you are not facing.  Ask
yourself how having the belief does in
fact serve you.  Ask yourself what could
that believe what message could that
believe be attempting to deliver to me
that I could allow to be delivered in a
way that does not have to come in a negative
package I found that difficult that is
because you believe it is difficult and
also because you may be putting to many
demands upon yourself for how you think
it should change or the rapidity with
which you think it should change again
in this if you know that your physicality isle to be
and you find that seems to have
a certain insistence in your life
then simply recognize you are choosing  to
have that experience to learn something
positive and as soon as you are willing
to look at the experience as a positive sustaining
idea then it will lose quote its
negative qualities and you will
become fascinated with the positive side
of the situation you are experiencing
and it will in a sense leak
out.  So I could just sit there and I
could about that I have.  Yes.  Invite
your fear to be your friend.  Recognize
that many times the fear is simply the
way that you will pay attention to the
message.  Ask yourself if you are willing
to listen to the message.  If you are
willing to listen to the message in
another way then you will automatically
by exploring this avenue become
fascinated with the idea of ​​receiving the message
in another way and you will
not feel any longer.  Totality is
fascination and curiosity.
exploring knowing that
everything everything that you could
ever experi in your life serves you and
is a part of the you chose to be and not
interruption in
you let see here how to
when
you speak about youqu
so
clearly use a syem
ofering to concepts repeating the
various words
that describ that concept i clarify this
several years ag i study bysation of spe
and communication and recogn that one of
the reasons that some communications are
not
because are not clear
to something and usefic
nonpal pronouns
to that confuse
another  way you do that will
use some
unclear very good concept
spe it is aunction of our perception of
you in that we see each and every one of
you as a series of relationships and so
in this way attempt to approach the idea
you are being from many different points
of view hence theinge but is always from
a slightly different angle attempting toou you
I understand what you said that's not
exactly whatering
to let that you such concept as large boy
with bl
each time you are to large boy with bl
you will the entire as rather than say
it using  the enas  make that very enerytimes will
have over and
overlear enough toevate ener spe but I
do and because
you connects with communicate I I
connection I with you
through
mental waybing Whatering to is
of friends who kind think of me asion
of you because I I am able to articulate
your ideas to them.  They may not listen
to the tapes or come to see you but are able
to communicate basically what I have
learned from you what you have reflected
to me about myself I reflect to them what
they need reflected in very similar
ways very very useful to them and
theyose very loving friends thank you
for allowing in this way the opportunity
of experiencing the enery of your
communication yes And I realize that
that's connection that you and I
have.  What I am wondering I don't need to know this
but I find it interesting
is whether this was something that we
agreed upon or there is an agreement at
some level.  On some level there is
simply like vibration and hence an
attraction and hence on some level
communication. agol
understand as long as you
are into some form of reality you will have ego by ego ego
because is a focus to you
focused you have chosen to your that also
also
nego negative ego is primarily judg of
ego in that sense or any
other through the you
thought about there some drills
you could do it just to get any there
are many ideas drills
to giving you
whatever methodology
you
basically way under there and don't know what it is
sort of underlying uneasing
do you mean anxiety bom anxiety
and bom at the
time necess thank you very
much  All right.  And it robs
you of
my ease before
and it geten
but I don't understand why it now
all right thank you cre by doing what
excit you are you doing what excit you the
you are you doing what excit you the
Why not?
We are not asking you
tobit are you
will understand only your choice to not do
what excites you the most gives you
the scenario of appearing to be stuck.
So do what
you will translate
anxiety into excitement because anxiety
and excit are the same enery but anxiety
is exciting.
exciting.
Bor is not allowing yourself to in the
moment by doing what excit
because implies that you are
waiting for something better.
rather enjoying whatever is you are
experiencing in that th
when you are better to come you
create a need for pa creates impatience
what if you feel you need
somebody else to help you with the
excitement and they're not cooperat
they're not cooperat well I don't I do
n't know what the word would Why should
Why should
you upon someone else choices for you to know what is
true for
you?  It is your choice to do so, but you certainly do not have to do so
.
So any experience that you are having
where it seems that you mustely upon someone
else before you will be willing to be
excited about what you know to be
true for you to your power ability from
you and put on someone else I understand
the absurdity of but I
not absurd it obviously can teach you
many things about
yourself but in this way that is the The
idea is that if you find that to be
happening, you are simply not willing to
believe you are as powerful as you need to be to generate
all the excitement and
ecstasy that you can regardless of what
someone  else in that way is
experiencing.  You may also recognize
that if you are willing to generate that
excitement then perhaps you will inspire
them to inspire you back to inspire them to
inspire you back and so on and so on
and so on all
you speak up did you he what I said yes iconed jud
came in talking all these different Thank
you very much for your own
self-reflective cognition.  I [music]
I think about it and then I think
something that would excite
me.  Then I get all excited
and then I don't do it because then I think
of something else
exciting.  Then I get excited again and
then I still don't do it because it kind
of goes down something else can.  So I I don't think to do I
just like in my
dimension all go exciting but it's not exciting
enough to make it happen.  You
are simply reviewing all the probable
realties in that way that are open to
you to act upon.  When you decide to act
upon any one of them, you will then generate
a flow of excitement that has a degree
of it.
excited by the idea that you make
contribution about being channeling voices that they are
about being channeling voices that they are
the
elementals fire
good you are in touch with the
archetypal substam of the
entiation and chann them in symbolic symbolic
so conscious
all that is remnit judg
you willate in time if you are
interest and excited about ceeding along
with a you call the Oh yes.
You are with basic elements of your
personality consciousness interrelationship
structure in this way you
are dealing with the very interconnective
shall I say
tissues of the energy that your
civilization utilizes to create its reality
and translating it in symbolic syicun
a little more as you are
doing
any one su we can have of course to as
you see but in ice
understand form in that way and the idea
of ​​what you call the lowering of
temperature that will allow you with
regard to any energies you areing to
become superc that is our our
suive your
attally And it will enable you
understand and ququ handle with more eas
all other manipulations of the ener you are you are you
with weigion to
weigion to
somere how you compare your philosopher that
teaching
in many ways not many differ you
recogn again that some those come
from time in
yourationersilation more willing to
their own intuitive link to all that is
now in this way we will find that the
main differ may still be that there is
involved perhaps in that shall i call it practice
the idea still of
may be underst
be necessary in the
understanding of the areess for
whoever I  understand that do you feel
that we can reach people
as well through
because you know
many individuals will find that
they are attracted to that idea because
of that reason and it may because of all
the different rituals that have been
created in your society be
something that at first they may more
easily relate to coming from the point
of view that they are coming Thank
you.  Thank you.  Every symbol is
valid in this way and all the different
ways you have manifesting your own self
-cognition are on your planet because
of all the different ways that you exist
with your society so that there is
always for one to be able to understand
the fundamental
can be interpreted back to
theion so people have in
so people have in
a sense in this way we would in
the sense
also suggest that the idea in a
sense of utilizing your term religion as
we perceive the way it is usually
understood upon your planet is actually
contrctory to what you are
saying I do uh very
muchigion  all right we are simply saying
many ofigion upon is not being and doing a butollowing
someone else he a
yes we understand the terminology in
that way in which you mean it we simply point
out that you may find that
certains in your terms may as the idea
of ​​the world since they are
in conne and sigion
they are extensions of you
there is no reason why they should asig you know peopleig
know peopleig
not going to accept it if you use it as uing forces and
and
all people accept
better I found that if it's ritualed and
used as a type of   worship
if that is the way that excites
you the most that is what is for I
you more expation
any doing and primarily for getting
others to do it you that
is when paradoxically by simply doing
it for yourself because that is
what you enjoy that you actually
create the biggest opportunity for other
individuals to perhaps want to choose Thank you very much much
about
things like I know she decided she
wanted to meet lots of handsome men.
deed that one way of doing that was to
see all mansome.
But I thought to myself, well, what's
going to happen when some guy walks up who
just isn't really her handsome is?
I came here I thought
that the closest I got to understand it
was that maybe we were dating with archetypes
in a sense you are but now
you kind of opened up new exploration
you give me some more insight into how
specifically for exle I a lot of my
friends who want to come here with me
have planets 2 Libra which in our zodiac
would be where the spur are in this way
simply recogn asy equivalence equivalence
ener all
agre
made you Oh
yeah.  Who helps make up those
agreements?  Do we all do it together?
Yes.  Are there no master planners?  Yes.
All of you together is the master
planner of your
system.  Do we do this in our dream
states?  Many times many times in what
you call in between lives.  And at any
given moment you are actually doing it
because you all exist on all different
levels simultaneously.
How would we all plan
would we all plan
2bra to have experience not so much that
you are that agre
andysical sy
that idea isle to you in
externalized youoll
can you more about how it has to do [music ]
]
It will be to some degree some idea of
the balance of polar and this way with
specific regard to what you call tourist
will also be the cognition for emotional
balance. willoufied serv more I hope I hope
so.
Tons of questions whenever you're ready
to whenever you are ready to answer them
perhaps that is when the discussion will take place do
not hope un you choose to and
remember that if you choose to hope implies despair hope
is not knowing
you are you
sure have to think about if
something will happy you are not you areing that might not so you think
you have to hope
simply know what reality you are know what is
true for you and you will not need hope
because you will simply
know you will have the knowledge that
you seek recogn a question is the answered concept you can
can
you every question each and you is
indication you are the answer but are
judging your not to be so you create
ainder that you are the answer and you
call thatinder a
question well that's true sometimes I
feel that we I know everything but it
seems that that feels very arrogant you
know no no you know everything you need
to know to function as the being you
chose to I feel another
another
to many different levels.  But
understand no being in
the knows more than you about what you
need to know to be you because you are the only you
.  You follow me.  Yeah.
percep thatan you are not aware of all
things you need tounction
as you if you did not even one
fragment even one small variable if you
were unable to know even one small
variable of the it takes to
you would need to equal my you
was I don't know and I don't have access
to all the knowledge thee that I only have access
to that enables me to be me
and to do those things which I chose to do
by the definition of the reality you
have projected yourself into.  It is not
that you do not have let us say connection to
all that is but perhaps
you have limited your access so that you
can in fact function as the being you
are choosing to function as in this
reality. On the other hand since
On the other hand since
the
asse is
holographic we do have information yes I did not
say you did not have it I simply suest
that many of you create an
inaccessibility to much of it simply
because it does not serve you to be who you are
but you have total accessibility
to all the information that lets you be who
you are in the reality you have
chosen
Yeah.  Thank you.
I feel wonderful to and the worksh speak up I
work I don't know what was it emal oh
very emal then it can be eaten for now to be
emal then it can be eaten for now to be
attached to the idea of ​​the vibration
up there might be like this energy might
speak through me as you speak through
and I was not aware of any words
either to speak I was more Thank
you.  This week uh they dive down to the
Titanic again.  The record of Titanic was
sank in
191 uh the ships Titanic sank in 1912
and they were sent down the uh camera and
they couldn't find a gash in the side
where supposed the iceberg
s.  Uh have you any ideas of how
and why the Titanic S?
Still in this way perception is as
reported they simply do not understand
in this way that there is not as
occurrence as was necessary as they
think was necessary they will find that
a portion of it in this way is stilling
in what you call the um
there's something that intrigues
me about the Titanic um there's a phrase
that God went down with the Titanic what
it meant was that
period up to the time titanic sank was the
longest peri of peace in Europe
since Roman times and at that time the man
was very optimistic that he could  solve
all his problems with his new technology
but after the Titanic sank just all hell
brought loose he got the founding of
federal reserve the following year then
world war two two years later then the
Russian revolution then the Wall Street Crash
what else is there anything
or what?  Excuse
me.  Is there any anything sort of
symbolic about thinking of the Titanic
that fascinates so many people that you
can talk about?  There are always many
events in this sense that your mass
consciousness in recognizing a change
about to occur can use to symbolize the
change in that consciousness that was
simply one of
them.  You don't do not think that could be a expertise
for this individual
here.  Yes, I do.
4 what happen on ju 7
1985 I mean
1947 there was for the first time in what you call modernation
conclusive toivation otherivations
this was underst you call
the crash of a spaceship upon your
planet and the recovery of that ship by
your own government and what happen to
it is still in the hands of your
government but they suppressed thatent oh
yes the people being alive
in there of in
the end of the gateway of 40 orbits
40 years and will be then in  a sense in
our perception explosion of awareness
of the existence of other civilizations in
your civilization and
explosion of awareness in your
consciousness that will allow to begin
the acceleration of your that creations creations
with
you7 how the crash was intal not so much in
this way recognized there was to some
deree some ideas of interference to some
degree with the idea of ​​what you call
your radar with the navigational systems of
the ship but also in connection with
that idea because of let say distracted attention
the idea is that ship
also existed within a high active
electrical storm and in this sense what
you would  call a
of
the because field had in a sense  been
impaired by the radar frequencies.
sucep the field
could the field made a very
attractive for the expos attractive
element of the
metallicle where was where
did crash which is i just told
you why i said
Rosswell New Mexico.
is represented as a typical cycle in
your consciousness as it changes from
one total point of view to another.  40
years for en culture 40 days for an
individual that is why you find many
biblical ideas of transformation 40 days
40s and 40
years you said the first oneering to the
first crash
what about the second what
information you have on a second I did
n't know that there was second have
been a
few in this way theyle integrity
willing toake of thoseing acc to connect
to the and of toare comp
with yourar superers that themselves to be beyond
compit this are ind three very
three very
exciting many  direcadi [music] New ze [music]
more innection
and another level to any
any
timing there are factors that must be
set in place but you are the
are the
other weekend days ag and spoke about creating United
states and I can feel the
progression from New
from New
Zealand of people and coming back and very
and very
good than you much for the individual that
are parpa and journey to what in this way
parpa and journey to what in this way
can be as heart chakra of your planet
Hawaii will return with a type of energy
and a type of reflection that will be
felt and will make a difference as it  in
that sense then leaks into the  the remainder
of the
society about the trip to I at first a
very strong feeling about having a
channel on a boat in the water with all
so that we Thank
you for being so excited about
being who you are.
I want to show something happened about
a week ago.  I had a cramping in my lower
bag and I remember that you had told a
woman who had a similar pain something
to do and it was using deep breathing
which I used for years.  So I began to
bend over and exhale and straighten up
and inhale and I was using also right
and after a while those became someone
else I heard other voices and there were to be
a lot of men whiling and I was I
was getting
scared concern you just touching into
different levels of
I responsible for those well in a sense
you were since they are all
yours.  But I I listen to them and they
were beautiful and then you appeared and
you said dance
and I began to dance.  It was a
Greek slow dance and I started laughing
and then I sat down
and then it just came to me I I
know I was a Russian officer and all
of a sudden I realed that those men were my
men and they were whiling because they
were hurt and some of them were dying.  I
assure them that they were going on that
it was all right.
And I'm just wonderful.  I smiled and I
just lay down.
you for following your intuition creating
your own connections and
allowing yourself to cstal so that you
can see in your own perly aligned
all the reflections that will
let you know the ideas you are all about so
that you can in center in the
now thank [ music] L more
more
chun I know how I can that are you
trusting that what exc you can
you by
or do you think you need something to
fall back on just in case
well as long if that is what you are
doing as long as you choose to continue that
attachment then you will  not be
allowing yourself to experience
100% that I
need to have
more trust is
all of the outer activity will change when you
of the outer activity will change when you
change yourself it is automatic your
outer reality is the shadow of your soul
when you change the shape of your soul
which is the idea that you are your
outer reality has no choice but to reflect
So if I just work on the trust the will
change yes but you do not have to work
on the trust you can trust you can trust
as
well up to you so
one and knows that it will come about that's
all needed yes if  also one
recognizes that it may not have to So it
can manifest precisely as one has envision
because one never knows one
may have changed and may not want that
precise vision by the time it shows up
but may need something more
representative but the effect will be the
same. know what shouldion that may not exactly what you
know what shouldion that may not exactly what you
really it doesn't matter that is
how one uses the idea of ​​the visualization
one uses the idea of ​​the visualization
as a
key to kick off the
momentum but does not put the demand
that if that visualization does not
material exactly does not put that demand on it
exactly does not put that demand on it
because then you more than
more than
you in other goce the
ence of the idea perceive the perceive
the idea of ​​what you prefer to
feel like and all of the manifestations
that need to be there to allow you to have that
feeling will be there.  may be
exactly as you have envisioned them but they
may not but
you can use what you have
envisioned as a guide as a
representative temp are you to enjoy the you think you don't
temp are you to enjoy the you think you don't
necessarily want corre correct
because if you are truly trusting then
you know that everything that is
happening to you is a part of the path
you are trusting you that is your and
inent yes not so much cont
but for contex can vary and you will
simply by being the content allow
yourself to create
what needs to translate that into [music]
content  becing very excited about how being
all right and someone recommended
that I took
and I did over and over own again was
veryed and excited
about prnanc wasinated
by what I want those
want those
back will come back
will simply trust your
timing and if you agreement
in that way will be fulfilled
but also recognize that there are
many different ways of fulfilling
different agreements in that and also
the fulfillment of all those other
agreements allows you to
become the person that has made the
agreement with the specific other that
you can bear as a
child is like preparation
through  you will be able to
toate that  prevly
toent well preparation gek i
to
session and there was psychic who was
told me that iychers
everyone was everyone
saying you have
trusting and not afraid power of your
own mind that i had a dream that i
mind that i had a dream that i
on astron ship and the ship and got diagram
and three compartments and in
the middle compartment there were women astronauts
there and one man and the man
asked me if I was astronaut and I said
no I'm astronaut
and then looked at this table
and there was
audioess being  completely unraveled by
the people there and I think to I w
up and a few days
later I wasting
my husband about and I all these
vibrations and I closed my eyes and I
began to med and
all again and I [music
] like to
my
husband through something on the very
over him backit
and go for
littleation and I gave it to him and was talking
was talking
about thank you foring your con as more and
More and more we are perceiving your
willingness to act upon that which excites
you and to allow yourselves to
represent an equality between  yourself
and all other consciousness with which
you are in contact.  We thank you for
this gift of your willingness more and
more synchronic are we experiing from
each and you and we than you for your
willingness to accelerate.  We thank you
for your willingness in this way to be cognit
of the creator in each and every
one of you.  We thank you for being
willing to give yourselves the same
unconditional love and respect that all
that is bestows upon you for you deserve
nothingess. you you
about
the up they [music] [music]
CR
you thank
you all
you all thank
in first of
all that you have ch to be a specific
individual in this
life yes
all recognizing that you have chosen
recognizing that you have chosen
this then you understand that being that
individual must play a part in being of
service to the totality [music
]
If you are willing totally first of all totally
be the individual that you have
chosen to be and follow what excites you
in that way then you will be allowing
yourself to be acting as if complete and
th you will be willing to be of service
to
individuals in
your service that
being trusting that by being by sharing
your abilities that excite you the most
with all other individuals you will
automatically be provided for because in being of
service to all that is you
being a part of all that is will
automatically be served simultaneously
Yeah.  Does that answer your question?
Yes.  Thank you.  Thank you.  It is also
recognizing in this way once again that
you are willing to allow other
individuals to recognize their own
selfempowerment and their own ability to create whatever reality they
so desire.
Not that you have to force that belief
upon them, but simply act as an example
in that way and show them the trust that
you have in all that is that by simply
being what it is that excites you, you
are automatically supported in
that and share with them whatever you
are moved through love to share.
Thank you. [music]
Yes.  Thank you.  I believe last week you
told somebody that there were thousands on
somebody that there were thousands on
your planet listening into the
conversation between you and the person
you speaking with.  Did I get that right?
I'm wondering what it's like for those
thousands.  Is it like listening to a
talk show on the radius?  Is it a real time
experience for them something into? y assim
without something that they are doing
while they are doing something else like
we might be working while the radius or
something it can happen but more often
than not they are simply willing
although what they will do is add their
energy to the exchange in that way so
that any idea that is being shared with
the interaction can and perhaps will take advantage
of that energy they are
doing but what they are doing is focus
focus
like answering question they in
yes
guiding of your cons to make yourself youle
they would do that would do
different things can both
it will depend upon the affinity
they have  for
andationship that they have Yes.
Yes.  I was under that that was a virtual
personality and I'm wondering is it virtual
or it is virtual
why why would it be considered
future then is it simply because your planet
exists in our future in a sense?
Yes, I can still think it as Oh yes.  Oh
yes.  Oh yes.  Oh yes.  Thank you.  Thank
you. are
are
allesser magnitude in this way to be a
dispersal of the enery
you will find they are litur thank you
one there is
with the 48 hours
processing alternatively you are in your
spaces nearby space and tims things
and several weeks I
describ any analy I used to understand
that all things are happening
simultaneously as if one is up in the
rafters of a large house with many
different rooms and you can see into all
the different rooms each room is a
different time
well it seems to me that your
perspective is  ours where you can see
into many rooms which we would call the
future in a
coming in spaceship and viewing compare
to what you do in your channeling using your imagination
in terms of your
ability to orb to gather information
about us it will depend on what I do
when I get to where you are if I am
simply are you you
someeing enery
levels emingevel consciously taking place
so and
so when you're here yes can happenely in
this sense but many times there will be
simply the need for the timing
How you are creating
this interaction in other words  if I try to
interaction in other words  if I try to
translate what you told me  into my frame
of reference I my body down and I imagine interaction
but then creating
the interaction of course you are not gather
I understand there and some reason I ca
n't get that all
right thanks to what
isu that when you put your body spaces
and get your
spaceship space to our planet
Yes, that basically imagination also.
Yes.  So your physicality so is
everything.  Yes, I understand that
concept
but I still bump up against the
sensation reality that is in differ.  All
right.  I use a
colloqual that may ass you.  Okay.  All it
takes is
[music] practice.  Okay.  When you simply do it
practice.  Okay.  When you simply do it
often enough and begin to believe that
your imagination is the reality you
experience and vice versa then you will be
able to create for yourself the
ability to slip in and out of different.
So you and
people learn how to do this but normal of
in
time from physical manation from your physical man
and from
your in other physical manifestation is
one of many ways in manifesting
that except that we have learned to use
the idea of ​​the fact that we exist on
many levels whereas simply that is not a
concept you are familiar with consciously
but you will become so as a
society right and it is a
different idea of ​​what you call your technology
as compared to
in being here have differing environ of [music] [music]
you
myination myagination for few I that of
myagination for few I that of
exemely physically red and I don't want
to get out of bed you know get into
that I guess away from actually doing physical labor what
brings that what
brings that on it is simply a habit of
looking at physicality as something more
difficult to accomplish than what you
can accplish in your initiation
As you have said on a labor of love is labor
at
all your equate that your experiences in your imagination do not have to be separated
separated
from your experiences in physical reality that
both experiences come from
your imagination that you  can simply
blend the two together so that what  you
believe to be very easily accomplished
in your imagination physical dimension can be just
as easily accomplished in your physical
dimension because your physical
dimension is an extension of your
imagination well it seems to me that my
ego [music
]
no in that I understand but that is
simply the idea of ​​your translation of
the fact that you think you exist on
many levels
imagination is the
dimension of your existence in a sense it
is the dimensional vibration of your
soul itself it is your access doorway uses imagination
uses imagination
perhs not in the same way that
is different but is the same
imagination that they are using  how to
describe imagination space how in a
sense it is a dimension it is the
dimension Ily Ily
unit
all right
and now do
understand that is created by the being
itself that is seeing as a unit of
consciousness that definition is not being created
by theer of the being that
knows itself to be more than justle
knows to be all
but then the all is simply I
a tool that all that is uses or is
imagination simply the all that is from
a
different in a sense it is the l it
is the
idea of ​​your
cognition of yourself as all that is but from as
you have said  a particular point
of view my are [music]
[music]
with All rights.  All
right.  Yes.  Thank
you.  What we can use to give you the
closest analysis is what in a sense we have
already shared with you.  If you simply
use your imagination the way you are
used to using it and add the one inient
of
trust that what you are envisioning is a
reality and that it is something you can explore
really then you will have the closest
analysis to the way we experience that
idea.  Thank you.  Thank you very
much creativity and [music]
creuse my body.   that idea ofut
you can about dream if you dream about
someone over well doesn't have to be
over long of time you are in connection
withevel of their consciousness whether
they are physiologically aware
arep yes and agre obviously or you
woulding to someone else now
else now
one at the time you are still creating
your own version of them to communicate
with but That does not mean that they are
not aware of that idea and therefore
on that level participating in the interaction
by supplying you with the
template in a sense out of which you can create
your version of them to act  with.
How can we use our dreams when we
are communicating with our dreams?
Perhaps one very one very
pragmatic
prical upon the recollection of the
dream you a
dream was you and allow yourself to
understand therefore that if you are all
the emotions all the objects all the
individuals you are interacting with all the
scenarios you are acting
in your dream then you can
more let sayose understanding
because you will be able to
understand more closely the idea
behind the symbol if you know that that
symbol is you as opposed to someone else
you do not think you have access to information
but it is also that other
person yes but the idea is that it is
for you to  understand yourself
regardless
that may one idea let you might prefer not prefer you
are in the dream state many
times examined scenario
Absolutely because once again in the
dream state you are a thought form in a
world of thought forms you are let say
slightly more representative of the idea
of ​​yourself as a soul and you recognize
that physical reality in a sense by analysis is
therefore the shadow of the
soul and if you change the original
image the shadow and the reflection must
follow how do we tell ourselves how to do that
you just did
By exploring the idea at all, you are
capable of being aware that you contain
the  idea.  If that is something that excit are
going to at this pointed to do
everything you need to do to allow
yourself to avail yourself of that scenario
.  All right.  Thank you.  Have
fun.
Allow to tr thates come is
instantly a part of the idea you
now you are being it seems to be or not that is
what will allow it to
consciously to be aart more quickly
what causes the what causes
the yeah simply the collectivity of your
consciousness that hasmined what is a
comfortable rate
will have take
more of not most scenarios that
involve a high degree of involvement
with you personally in that way that
have a high degree of involvement with
respect to your individual life in that
sense will usually not take any longer
than the idea of ​​months to manifest the
average can be three of your weeks and
in this way it does not really have to
take any longer than your
days that is a different type of ide
although it does have
ownid miss that simply in this way
simply understand you have decided to
live in a time space frame network
somee as long as
youace frameetwor you will things to
take some
time they invve other
but it does not necessar have to take
any longer than of days if you are
willing to understand that from the very
instant you know yourself to be changed
then simply accept and allow and take  it
for granted that no
Even though  it may not be apparently
different is different it is not the
same it is not reflective of the way it
used to be it is reflective of the way
it now is and that will allow you to see
in the quickest way possible those
things to transmute into their new symbolic
representation forms you
also that there is
a fact of
automatically you are
you can only be that one idea there
is no room to be another idea.  You can
only be one idea at a time.  Good.  Thank
you very much.  Thank
you.  This what you spoke of kind of help
me for tonight is the idea of ​​what I am has dramatic shift
in the last year and
a half
that I'm now at a point where a belief
system that has been a foundation for 30
years is now being threatened for the
first time to a point where I'm actually distrusting
my distrust for the first
time.  And I'm just wondering if you have to say that
might help me through it.
period of tremendous anxiet about 48
hours but I can really feel with the
idea of ​​what I am and a shift in what my
belief system has always been.  Are you
having a good
time? Having had the journey all recogniz one
Having had the journey all recogniz one
more time that your fear is your
opportunity now to gather together in
this new time all of the different
portions you have for so long not been
looking at.  If it is a time of confusion
that is what it is for cousion fusion with
more of yourself if
you are in this way disoriented that is what it
is for reorienting from one
reality to another it is all right to
enjoy the limbo stat you are simply
changing gears you are in a sense for
a while but that is a
natural you thank
21 is not in your dimensional
frequency.  In this way the closest
approximation is 500 of your light
distance directly in the direction of
the constellation you call or not
precisely relatively in the same
direction what we are saying is that you
can use that as an analogy All
All
In you for
a third star what you call from your point
of view the hand star in the
min you have it Are you attct?