allow to commence this intera with the
time with the
idea of the nures and the labeling of
what you refer to in your society as
good and evil recognize in this way that
from out of perspective these ideas are
now being examined in your Society
because of the transformational time the
transformational and transitional age
that have created into me but you will
recognize that at this time the idea of
the examination of what you call
colloquially good and evil is receiving
partial understanding on your
planet many individuals will de within
themselves and intendedly understand
what is meant when they hear the phrase
whether there really is no such thing as
good or even really is no such thing as
right and wrong but they will not
necessarily understand the specifics of
the mechanism of how that is so and
therefore when they perhaps will be rep
this idea to an individual who does not
understand at all the direction that
they are approaching the ideas that they
are intending transfer to them will
perhaps allow some confusion in your
terms to be created with this idea for
it will seem as if to say well there is
no right and wrong there is no good and
evil is to say well all right do
anything you want anything goes but
recognize that is not what is being said
now we know that individuals can
intrinsically feel and and understand
that that is not what is being said but
allow us now at this time to
specifically illuminate the mechanism
that is being discussed so
that you in coming across more and more
opportunities in your transformational
age to explain this idea to individuals
who may have only heard a part of the
idea and not the whole idea Perhaps it
is your opportunity to allow the idea to
be fully understood in this way the ey
idea of course first and foremost is
that the idea right and wrong the labels
good and evil are value judgments
whereas the actual specific mechanism
that is being discussed is positive and
negative energy positive and negative
Action Now positive and negative action
can simply be defined mechanically in
the following way positive action is
that which
integrates gathers together into a
unifying format the circumstances of any
given situation negative energy is that which
situation negative energy is that which
segregates and
separates the circumstances in any given
situation positive energy is that which
allow there through the creation of the
unity to be a power eyes a
self-empowered a
powerful format negative energy through
format negative energy through
separation limitation segregation allows
there to be a format expressing
powerlessness in this way recognize that
these are perhaps more precise
connotations positive negative energy
because the idea is that in your Society
the idea is the value judgments of Good
and Evil can become in your terms
confusing as to what they are referring
to in terms of an action for there can
be many positive interactions that some
individuals may feel are evil and many
negative interactions that some
individual may feel our good thus you
can more precisely and more succinctly
and clearly understand the circumstances
of any action that you simply recognize
whether it is self-empowering and
integrating ative thus positive or it is
in this way segregative limiting
removing of power and therefore
expressing the idea of collection
through domination or
domination or
forcefulness rather than the simple idea
of sharing and the expression of
unconditional love you all follow along the body
love you all follow along the body
in this way therefore recognize that the
ideas as you experience them in your
Society in terms of the negative energy
as we have said are expressions of
powerlessness for if you know that the
idea you are being represents you as a
fully empowered being a being that knows
Beyond The Shadow of Doubt that you are
a part of creation that you are attached
to the universe in that way and always
derive your substenance and power from
the totality of all that is that you
know you are connected to then the first
primary idea that you recognize for
yourself to be true is that you are as
we have said many times as
self-empowered as fully self-empowered
as you need to be to have anything at
all you desire to have in life without
having to hurt anyone else or yourself
in order to have it the idea of an
individual expressing negativity in the sense of
expressing negativity in the sense of
forcing themselves forcing their point
of view forcing their negativity upon
another individual what that is an
example of is that the individual or the
group doing the forcing obviously does
not believe in the inherent power of
what they say they believe
in you follow me thus it is an
expression of
powerlessness it is an expression that
they do not feel connected to all that
is that they do not know they are
self-empowered enough to get what they
want without having to hurt anyone else
or themselves to get it they are
expressing complete and utter
isolation from all that is from their
own creativity from their own Creator
Hood Therefore your
Therefore your
willingness as unconditionally loving
connected beings is to express
your conviction in them that they are
worth loving that you do believe in them
that they do have what it takes to
create what they need and what they want
without having to rely on a parasitic
relationship of other individuals energy
in order for them to attain what they
wish to attain they have enough of their
own energy and you can by loving and
sharing that certainty with them
cocreate a reality in your civilization
wherein there does not need to be any
more perpetrators or
victims so all follow
along thank you very
much sure
sure
you about two months ago I a tape of one
of these sessions
on the tape uh I don't quite know how to
put this but you channeled an entity uh
by the name of
neon from Orion and as I was listening
to the T I found myself getting very
emotional to the point where I was you
were not alone yeah I found that out and
I felt very connected to the person who
was being
channeled and I was wondering I thought
thought about it later and thought
perhaps it was a past life Connection in
a sense yes a totally different time
track all together not one relating to
what you call your planetary Earth along
with many other individuals who have
also chosen to be in the earth sphere at
this time you are all reconnecting
regrouping and accelerating forward in
new positive
momentum me yeah in that other time
track there was
much separation much limitation much
negativity that individual that you are
referring to at that time sought to help
many other
individuals but in this way did not
directly nor could not directly
partake but formed an anchor and in this
way now formed an anchor for those
now formed an anchor for those
individuals seeking to blend the
polarities of the negativity and
positivity they have now explored
through incarnations in your Earth
feere so that they can now know that
that individual as was represented then
in the channel you are referring to was
in a sense a message from the past and
that that individual now reincarnation
speaking though they are still in the
same system now exist within a system in
which there is much positive
life because of the willingness of the
individuals to reincarnate on the earth
system from the original system to learn
what they needed to learn about
negativity to learn what they needed to
learn about the blending of positive and
negative energy so that there can be a
positive effect that learning has let us
say sent back to the home stations all
the understanding all the necessary
energy to allow the home stations to
also partake in the blending of positive
and negative energy so that there can
only be positive manifestation within
the original
system oh that's beautiful you are
speaking and referring to the idea of a
large group of
Associates all that desired and sought
positive manifestations within systems
heavily Laden with negativity after time
this is no longer
ration
those hey current um astronomical
understandings that's propagated on this
planet it is said that our Milky Way
galaxy contains upwards of 100 million
stars and that uh 100 billion 100
billion stars hey
okay approximately
Orting and that there are many many such
galaxies in oh yeah does this parallel
with your understanding of the physical
structure of this dimensionality yeah
okay what
percentage in the Milky Way galaxy of
these Stars contain planetary systems
with intelligent life that are
approximately in your third density
structure in what you refer to as the
Milky Way galaxy approximately once
again Gort 67 million inhabited worlds
oh okay very good now that represents
approximately between what you would
call 17 this is a fluctuating figure
because of the nature of dimensionality
between 17 and
25% of all the different levels and
dimensionalities of planets that are
quote unquote inhabited say that again
I'm sorry between 17 and
25% it is by far the largest faction of
inhabited worlds in the third density
reality good and just scanning a
percentage wise in terms of
uh oh this is a little more let me see
if I can praise this
correctly giving a culture that we would
call prehistoric and a culture that we
would call uh Advanced technological
what are the percentages of
distribution we do not know do not we
have not explored them all we are aware
of the general configuration and outlay
of life but we have not explored nor
contacted them all understood good thank
you man ask you personal question good
okay um I have been encountering something
um I have been encountering something
that I have not yet identified even well
enough to formulate what I'm trying to ask so
to formulate what I'm trying to ask so
then why not
wait because it's here all right and it
has has to do
with um a negativity that occurs in terms
um a negativity that occurs in terms
of
[Music] succeeding succeeding
[Music]
um in this Dimension I find I find for
instance that when I expand my scope
onto projects that I enjoy and excite me
and are large in scope then I function
extremely well as you might imagine oh
right however I find that my attention
goes back to the necessity to apparent
necessity to earn
finances to cover the apparent next
steps that are needed and then when I do
that I find myself solidified get
into negative energy fear these sorts of
things all right so are saying you need
a booster shot of
trust yes that is correct trust in that
uh yes that's good trust that at any
given moment the idea at that moment
that excites you the most is what you
can pursue now again simply recognize
that the idea of what it may be that
will excite you the most with regard to
your entire lifespan is not necessarily
what you may be focused on in a
particular given moment the idea of the
excitement can shift to the things that
allow you to partake of what will
sustain you physiologically if you will
but recognize that a momentary shift in
perspective away from what appears to be
the overall idea that excites you the
most and a shifting of that energy into
something that is a momentary High
excitement is indicative of the little
things that will lead you to the things
that will sustain you in other words if
you are very excited about the overall
process project as you have def find it
and then find that all of a sudden for
some reason all of that excitement has
momentarily shifted to the idea that
well all of a sudden I simply would like
to take a walk down that street do so
because walking down that street having
the excitement shift from the grand
project into the specific idea of the
moment is what will lead you to the
situation that will sustain you so that
you can continue with the grand proit
that I do not have difficulty with that
path I seem to follow naturally M all
right the difficulty seems to be when I
pull back and consider
that for instance I I I am seeking a
location now to build a series of models
and as I reach out for that I realize I
don't have the wherewithal to pay the
rent and that causes me to pull back
into the concept of a
the concept of a
necessity to do
something to generate that income before
I reach forward this kind of a are you
saying that there is no other thing that
excites you that would be something a
situation you could attract to yourself
that would allow you to be sustained no
I'm not saying that um are you finding
that you are attracting situations but
not acting on them
yes yes I judge them why uh as
apparently well I can see they don't
necessarily excite me but I can see that
they could be economically they could
pay the rent quote unquote all right in
this way you may find that the idea may
come to you in that form because what
you may be excited about more excited
about than almost anything else is
paying the
rent in other words all you are
attracting are situations that will
quote unquote fill the bill do the job
but they in and of themselves may not
bring excitement with them because the
actual exciting idea has been fulfilled
the more exciting idea of Simply being
able to pay the rent you follow me no I
didn't in other words you are
assuming that the situations that you
attract to yourself in and of themselves
must feel exciting and they can
but because your focus is on the
excitement of paying the rent then the
situations that come in and of
themselves when you are focused on the
idea of the need of paying the rent the
situations that will allow you to do
that themselves may not appear exciting
because your excitement is focused just
on the idea of paying the rent and you
do attract situations in which you can
do that now if you are willing
to allow yourself to
trust that that
exciting
situations are what come to you and that
by definition they will also allow you
to pay the rent which is not really what
is exciting you then the situations
themselves will be exciting and along
with that will be the and the support
you require but because your focus is so
strong upon the idea of the rent itself
rather than the
excitement then the situations are being
deprived of their excitement by you
because you are focusing the excitement
only on the scenario of paying the rent
rather than simply doing what excites
you okay I think I let me see if I let
me clarify this I'm not excited about
paying the rent at all but in a sense
you are that is where your focus is that
is where your high degree of desire and
energy as a necessity as an apparent
necess parent necessity within the
structure apparent that is your key word
apparent necessity you are allowing an apparency
necessity you are allowing an apparency
to become the nucleus around which you
evolve thus it becomes more than
apparent it becomes a necessity for you
uh not not apparently you know I go and
do the project and get very very excited
and then the time to pay the rent comes
forth this comes I hav put any attention
on it at all it comes in because of the
mechanics of the time system the rent is
due but you are reinforcing a belief in
those mechanics all the time you are
doing the project if you are open and
honest with yourself and look into your
subconscious you can be aware of the
fact that you are counting off the
minutes you are counting down how much
time do I have before it is due again I
will be excited about this project but
how much time do I have before I have to
start thinking about this again that is
true that is what creates it over and
over again and doesn't allow you to
recognize that many situations may have
come your way that in and of themselves
may have come with more excitement had
your focus been on the trust that those
situations could sustain you and could
be exciting rather than the idea of
keeping your focus on the idea of having
to do this having to do this having to
do this so it's more Trust on the
concept that what exitement could will
also sustain and
also do you remember the idea of what
you call the technique that we refer
heard you all too the causal flame
Technique No in this way the idea of that which
No in this way the idea of that which
has been presented by the Consciousness
you call
Lazarus will allow you a very conscious
reference in terms of the degree of your
control over the creation of your
reality Avail yourself of this
information it can assist you greatly
there are individuals present this side
of your time who can give you that
information and the information is what
is turn it is what you would call an
exercise or a technique for allowing
yourself to get in touch with the level
what you call the causal plane
non-physical level the level in which
you actually create the physical reality
you experience you have that yeah good
thank you for sure thank you for sure
you Hi V uh a couple of things when you
mentioned the third density inhabited
planets in our
galaxy uh those two density planets if
we had the technology to in fact travel
to them yes would we perceive them or
are they a
different basically you could but every
single planet whether it is in third
density or not is on a slightly
different phase frequency you would
still have to make a slight adjustment
in order to perceive the inhabitants and
sometimes in order to even perceive the
planet itself but that would come
naturally to you because the idea of
travel through space is the idea of
travel through time right okay I have
another question talking about
excitement I've been wondering thinking
about that quite a lot um there been
periods in my life when I felt I had
done everything I needed to do and there
was absolutely really nothing that
excited me guys for the moment right and
I'm sort of going through a period like
a right now I'm going this is a very
very very large and strong limbo period
for many members of your society in
which things are now in a sense
disconnecting yeah and in this way you
will find they will begin to reconnect
and when they do watch
out you will be more highly accelerated
but at this time you are all passing
through a Civ you are all passing
through a membrane and the vibrational
frequencies now of the levels of your
trust and willingness and conviction and
excitement and ecstasy and knowingness
will determine how you reconnect to the
forth density shift and at what rate you
reconnect but reconnect there will be
reconnection within what you call the
next one to three of your months and it
will accelerate once again towards what
you call the spring time of your for New
Year at that point there will be an
explosion of expansiveness and it will
seem that you yearn for these quiet
time thank you very much this is a
symptom now of many individuals upon
your planet you are simply now examining
all the options
everything everything and I do mean
everything is up for
grabs uh could you
elaborate a little bit on quote
everything that forr all that you have
previously held in your belief systems
about what you think your reality should
be is all coming
unstuck it is all coming aart at the
seams they are all being broken down
into their various components so that
you can now replug in and rearrange them
in any way you wish to so that's why in
fact the lazar's information is very
yes right now because we can do that yes
you can consciously rearrange them in
this limbo state in this shifting of
Gears if you wish to put it that way you
can now determine which cogs meet when
you re-engage wow that's exciting I me that
re-engage wow that's exciting I me that
is
good thank you thank you one moment you
want yes thank you sure I've uh once
again become really appreciative with
the the
in the day and the night the Sun and the
Moon once again and I just want to uh
last week after our anniversary paning
we had a beautiful full moon and a
perfect rainbow around it after and I
just wanted to thank you for coating
with us that that the that was we thank
you for the synchronicity of all the
symbology within the event that together
we all are and I had and I had another
question I went to a Mayan uh exhibition
of
Museum and they had many stones there
with uh with glyphs and there was uh
they were saying that glyphs were not
they did not really know what they
signified and I have I touched them and
I felt that they were are they symbolic
of the mind's contact with either their
gods or extraterrestrial some of them
are not many but some some of it is
implied what is what is the reason for
the almost they're very similar
but yet I'm sure they're not what what
what are they what are they they are in
your terms pictographic each one
represents an entire chain of Concepts
they are not like what you would call
your English letters they are more each
and every one of them like your English
sentences they depict action whole
events encapsulated
down and arranged according in diagrams
with each other to get across an entire
meaning an entire
idea uh and one thing I have a very de
friend of mine keeps through meditation
and through dreams keeps continuing to
receive uh hits that she was from a
place called Angora is there a planet or
Star somewhere called Angora did you
know we do not recognize the vibration
in that way
there may be other references at this
point it is not within our scanning
range in terms of our mentality we do
sense that obviously there is connection
to other civilizations upon your planet
in what you would call your historic
path and some of this may actually be
some of the association they are picking
up on and simply
labeling other associations off your
world with the same connotation was was
at one time anchor of turkey referred to
as angor not
angor not
precisely CU I thought maybe that would
be is there a high propensity of this
individual for what you would
call the Far East or Indonesian
areas I don't know ask the individuals
see if they feel that they may be
connected in that way either to the
Tibetan areas or what you would call the
ancient race you would refer to as
ker in that area you will find
that the labeling the terminology terminology
angor
angor and this may have some closer
connotations because there was Heavy
quote unquote as you say
involvement extraterrestrial in that
area fantastic thank you than you
hey I guess few days ago there was
aanti Sting of
five oh one year I guess the police it
was pretty obvious was on the news that
um any additional to that at this time
our sense is that it is an Excursion who
would call the
pry delate I guess it's pretty
deliberate that was some identification
and interaction on some level going on
with certain individuals in the
area
yeah on signing like in the last four6
weeks in thebrass Valley or for the
first time they say there's been uh five
sting and one
exploded uh and we had got some of the
information that it was a experimental
CRA to some degree that the actual
exploded the one that exploded but
within the it's the first time it's ever
been noted in that area which course I'm
quite delighted over there is an energy
point in that area a magnetic resonance
field up in the grass area okay would
that have anything to do with
what we talked about before on the
vortex Vortex that's what I any more
information on why there's so much just
recently the experimentation so to speak
is primarily for the purpose of a
particular type of what we refer to as
vibration identification it is like a
leaving out a balancing out a
synchronization with a certain idea
format that the place represents
it is an attempt in a sense to pass
through different energy Gates different
dimensional
gates in your terms there was simply
what would be called a miscalculation
with the harmonic resonance field the
gate in a sense let us say vibrated out
of syn with the
ship or vice
versa thus the material form the
representative material form could not
sustain its integrity and it
disintegrated rapidly
you follow me yeah that is that also
that was creating am I
correct we feel that there are other
connections as well some of which in
your terminology we are not at Liberty
to
discuss um all right thank you one one
other question I did commment earlier
and SP to about it the
last I I'm not quite sure two three
nights or days or whatever I've had a
very experience
and it's not it's not negative by any
means it's almost like there's
a I'm going to say helmet for lack of a
better word that seems to be surrounding
my head
um and it it's some kind of electronical
I the words are very difficult because
I'm not quite sure how to explain it but
all I know is my body kind of go into
all right thank you for now let us say
you are
are sort of creating an inertial
guidance system symbolically for
yourself you are orienting toward a
particular fixation or
Focus am I co-creating
or co-creating or more my own you are
always co-creating there is assistive
energy but you are doing the scanning
and you are feeling
out where the corridor is down which you
wish to walk you are
scanning you are looking for those
doorways yourself and thus in a sense
you can understand the mirror
reflectivity of the idea of what the
craft was attempting to do as well look
for doorways now in this way the
doorways now in this way the
idea of what you make May perceive to be
their lack of
alignment can be one
way as your participation in that area
can be one way for you to understand
they have already taken upon themselves
with the utilization of that symbolic
craft the idea of any misalignments that
need to be found and therefore anything
you will find you will be aligned with
for they have identified and leavened
the area out
is this making
sense to some
degree it's difficult to absor my mind
doesn't seem to function quite the way
it us all right now let us put it simply
this way not that this was the only
purpose of the crowd but let us say it
is like there is recognition that
individuals in that area are going to be
searching for certain gateways or
certain doorways if there is any
probability that the discovery of those
doorways would cause misalignment within
those individuals then a device has been
sent on ahead to take the brunt of any
misalignment there is and take the
charge upon themselves and draw that
charge out of the area so that the area
is balanced so that any doorways you
discover you will not misalign
with do you understand me more clearly
now no thank
you yay uh I lost my mother behind the
Iron Curtain
and I was very close to her yeah she
died I couldn't get her out that does
not mean she is lost uh yeah I would
like to know what's happening
to time frame of what you call
physiological death about 56 and
gu her name was
Helen I think she died from hunger and
uh probably
as far as we can perceive and this at
this time is only our
perception basically you are referring now to an
basically you are referring now to an
individual still female approximately 13
years of
age as you would say
reincarnated you follow me right our
first sensing or scanning of the
timeline would be that the individual
reincarnated in the area you call
P if the individual is still there it is
probable that she is not but if she is
still there she is on the verge within
the next two or three of your years of
working out all of the past connections
to the other
life in that area then she will move
from that area if she has not done so
already the primary focus may be either
in what you would
call one of three locations either
somewhere in what you would call
Europe somewhere in what you would call
your United States or somewhere in what
you would call Canada
this is what we feel we can share at
this
time will this do yeah can you see my
kic pattern to I feel like there is some
kind of great involvement there is
always a great involvement do not forget
that karma is completely self-imposed it
is not something that is imposed upon
you from outside
but you have always interacted very
closely in Many Lives Many Lives and in
this way you will find it
possible that you may physiologically
meet again and recognize her when you
see her but we perceive that that at this
her but we perceive that that at this
point is not
necessarily in the high end of the
percentage however communicate with her
you do quite often in your dream
realities when you are out of your
body one moment
if you will
focus in your meditations in your
imagination on a very
slender 13-year-old
Brown ha or
female long brown
ha tied back in what you would call a
single
ponytail this may assist in bringing the
vibration closer and allowing more
conscious memory of the communications
you are having in your dream St
St
now if you are willing
to allow us we can also sense that there
may be an
opportunity for you to function as a
nonphysical guide for this individual
later in her
life and then after that an opportunity
for you to Incarnate together at the
same time in another life all
together once again
at the same
time for now this is what we can share
you get good name by the
chance this may only be an
approximation at this point we will
suggest that you do not take it
literally for it may only be
representative of her energy and it may
not be the colloquial Ming vibration
upon your planet but our perception is
that something similar to what you would
call freia thank
you then you what um what do you think
about desire it is very
desire it is very
exciting desire
is what creates is what activates the
beliefs that create your physiological
reality um tell me
more are you examining the idea from
positive or negative point of view well
I'm looking at it
like having you know when sometimes you
had one big desire and you go for it
very ex yes andtime you have many little
and it's not as exting but there little
all right again those can be
representative of those momentary
excitements that allow you to enact the
overall desire as
well they can be in a sense quote
unquote pieces of the same
desire farmed out if you will into
different situations Each of which can
possibly connect link up and lead you to
the more expanded desire so you can
actually sit down and think
about always if you are
willing you can know that all situations
can come to you that are necessary to
come to you to allow you to create what
you desire again the technique to which
we have referred can assist you very
very very strongly it is now a ful point
in this transitional state in this limbo
State use that technique get in touch
with what you do believe with what you
actually do want with what you truly do
desire the technique will help
you okay than
you guys
um I I've been playing this game you a
little bit um past few times I I come
right after the initial opening that you
give okay and then afterwards I listen
to it and uh I just want to and it's
always incredibly synchronous always
what incredibly you know that's a figure of
incredibly you know that's a figure of
speech Yes I am now playing with you I
know um uh and last week the theme for
me last week um was I happened to meet a
person that person I told you you about
that we went up in the plane and all of
that and that person was very very
pragmatic yeah um and during the break I
asked Daryl about you know what do you
do with the pragmatic not knowing that
Daryl had just finished discussing all
of this then I listen to the p and of
course you know you spent a great deal
of time on that subject and I was
absolutely Blown Away by it was
wonderful um and that the other thing is
I experienced this week a sense of um
you know you experience time going by
very quickly if there's less time this
time I was semia awake in the morning
and I was waking up and I looked at the
clock and at 7 say 7 o' 7 o' okay that's
what small segment of time as we know
time to exist
um and it felt like hours ago and I did
it again I did that three or four times
and I was with the sense
of what is that now what is that you are
creating time and you can change the
rate at which you experience it relative
to the time frame you are used to
experiencing okay you are creating it
completely utterly that is really true um also
utterly that is really true um also
another
thing no don't don't forgive him
um uh the other thing is uh it
it's it's really true that uh things are
really in flu and um I have the sense
that um I have a sense that I don't want
to lock myself into anything that is
that I can't get out of so to speak so
speak for an for example though here's a
good example for you oh right um I'm in
the
I'm in the process of possibly getting
this $20,000 bank loan now this loan and
I got in mind to make money too but the
means I have of making money is not
something I I love too much I really
would like to do something else but I'm
not sure what and I've also been
availing myself of myself of other
things and people um who are doing other
things and things that fight me and you
know we get a jet plane ride here we get
to go play music over here we get to do
this over here none of it makes
money so none of it costs it either
that's right a really good point yeah for that
right a really good point yeah for that
is what abundance is all about the
ability to do what you want to do when
you want to do it regardless of the
symbol you use to do it with which is
not always money that's really I really
do see
that I'm try to I want to get great
because when
that when that explosion comes I want to
be whatever that is
[Laughter] um um and I'm also seeing that everyone
um um and I'm also seeing that everyone
around me when I really see them uh in
light of the fact that they have created
their own reality and boy they really
created those realities those realities
are very
fascinating and um and very beautifully
defined it's atic to me to see what
people have
done and there is I lose
lose
really I do have a
question let's talk about the 12 pointed
star why well I just thought I'd bring
it up in case you wanted to say anything
but you would if you wanted to okay and
it was
something I just thought
I I just thought it would be funing it
up no thank you it was a great deal of
[Music] fun do you have anything you would like
fun do you have anything you would like
to say about
that will you allow me a moment
there is a great deal of
attention focused on the polarities by
that particular Consciousness the
polarity upon your planet that you call
your United States and your Soviet
Union there is a very
large percentage of
influx of new births connected to that
energy in those two areas of your planet
so that more and more from
within there can be joining blending
Harmony you will begin to see examples
of this more and
more participate in them when and where
you wish
to for you will assist in the Accel
ation
thereof January as you call
it portions of February as we call
it and up to a certain point in
March there may be high degree of
information coming
from and through perhaps ourselves and
new sources regarding the origin of that
Consciousness you would call arus and
the association of the 12 CED stars that
symbolically goes along with it
thank you thank you one more thing
please we are waiting oh all right um
I'm going to be going across the desert
tomorrow by
car that's 5 hours out
there hour track at night well why don't
you do just the opposite of what you did
before and allow 5 hours to become 10
minutes okay but during that time
anything anything you want you know for
anything I want F during that time
humbly request humbly request that's B
just keep yourself open all right all
right do not look so hard well you know
I try that and I'm just I don't know
keep yourself
relaxed okay now you can
also it is only our suggestion you do
not have have to do
this follow what if I may refer to it as
B's rule of thumb
thumb
if you cannot
tell that what you are looking
at is obviously a spacecraft then it
isn't one even if it is
for wi
string when it needs to be obvious to
you it will be so if you cannot tell
then it isn't one even if it
is that paradoxical
relaxing is what will allow you to
remain open so that whatever happens will be in
open so that whatever happens will be in
your estimation what needs to
happen simply enjoy the desert for what
it is for many of you do not even
recognize upon your own world that the
ideas you surround yourself with all the
time have many more levels and many more
meanings than you allow yourself to be
aware of simply because you think of it
as so
mundane thank you at this
time allow me to suggest that this
evening's tape is labeled
cluing true time thank you you may all
take a short PR oh
all right say
sharing hey what is anything difference
going on in your space at this
time within the ship no within the
channeling okay yes could you talk about
it there is more interaction from many
different levels of the consciousness of
the physiological Channel there is
interaction from other connections
within other levels in areas of what you
would call the life track of the
physiological Channel there are
switchings in a sense going on from
certain Pathways that have been taken
onto new Pathways new focuses new
approaches in this way since we are now
at the Crux of the idea of what you call
the end of the first threeyear cycle in
the channeling and the beginning of the
second threeyear cycle you will now find
that there will be exemplified IND this
changes within the idea of delivery
changes within the idea of the content
and changes within the idea of the
periodicity of the channeling for in
this way you will find that what it will
now come down to will be let's talk more
do me yes uh what do you mean by perity
let's talk more do uh L
channelings it's are you planning to to
have fewer evenings like this is that it the
fewer evenings like this is that it the
idea is that there will be less need for
the interaction on the level you are
experiencing it now when you develop
more willingness to do the things that
excite you you will then come to
understand that doing those things is
what we have always referred to as
speaking on equal terms with us so the
dialogue will become one of action
thus all the interactions that we are
going to begin to have will be more
interactive in the sense of what it is
you are doing coherently and
concurrently with what it is we are
doing in relationship to
you okay thank you thank you
sir hey have any new
girlfriends there are always new
interactions and relationships occur
within our society this is for fun you
know you having any more you know
sharing a little fun some fun I am
always you some how about sharing some
of your good times
on good all
right once again rendered into your
colloquial terminology I will keep it
the same the
idea to
being walking alone
[Laughter] [Music]
that's if any of you have a spe on you
sh it out
out
and they see a third being in need of
some assistance so one of the original to
assistance so one of the original to
goes over to the third being and assists
them in every way shape or form that
they can and then after they have done
so
rejoin the first
being and in this way the one being that
the assisted being has rejoined
says you are
always assisting others you are always
being of service you are always being of
help don't you ever want anything for
yourself that you
the now that is a representative for
density and the idea is of course that
as you assist others you are
always for us to pun was the
first what was that again how [Laughter] many
hey hardly any at all
to recognize that the function of what
you call sleep is to be in touch with
other levels of yourself this is what we
do consciously all the
time so the idea the mode of connection
that you would consider to be an
inactive mode would we call flee is
something that occurs within us very
spontaneously and very instantaneously
the connection is established and we
continue as we move toward
toward
yes um attemp at this point there are no
sh and you don't have to force yourself
to do anything the idea will come to you
naturally when you begin to follow your
own natural
cyle you me yeah do not forget that many
times the idea of the So-Cal sleep that
you need is the result of forcing
yourself out of your natural biological
Rhythm and of deiving yourself of the
connections when they would naturally
occur and forcing yourself to have those
connections when you have the energy to
be up and about and doing your
business but I I feel that maybe we were
training to sleep8 hours yes you have
been and so but now that you are
connecting many of you find that you are
fighting this early training and because
you may still believe that that is
natural for you and find yourself not
being able to do it many of you then
create the belief that oh I can't
believe something is wrong with me I
have a disease called insomnia you take
the baby like they they born and they Le
so much you know at first because they
are still more highly connected to the
Physical Realm okay up to the idea of
what you call 3 years of age
approximately in your terms of counting
they have the option to
disconnect so after 3 years if you don't
force them to go to
bed if you don't train them like hours
at first because they are also in need
of the idea of physiological sustenance
in this way then they may still sleep a
great deal of the time but also like
recognize that the rate at which they
sleep is also directly representative of
the reality they have been born into and
they are simply copying what they
see
okay I've read
that to be able to remember your
dreams how do you feel about that the I
again is simply a cognition that certain
individuals can follow more than natural
cycle it is not so much that it is is
better in one way or another but it is
representative of an idea that might be
more akin to your true natural cycle
thus allowing you more full cognition of
the state you do change into and out
ofk really really I
apprciate I love and I knew that
I knew it
was I wanted to ask you I was thinking
the day about
generations and you had mentioned a
couple weeks
ago you elaborate on that simply that it
represents in terms of the consciousness
of second density awareness one that has
a strong vibrational Affinity to what
you call the human form being
in this way it's let us say
representative wisdom or
age in your terms is reflected of having
felt or identified with many of the
changing patterns of your Humanity upon
your planet and thus they can read you
and tense you very
easily oh yes commun with [Music]
them this is something now of course you
can communicate with any aspect of
nature since it is an extension of your
own Consciousness the idea of eucalyptus
will have specific reference to the idea
of the electromagnetic field in certain
minical ways and magnetic ways it is
also something that allows us to be
strong bonding of the water molecules
within the cellular structures of your
body I think back time I
did I took a
branch Ro and
I
I do weing Willows someone told me
weeping willows have a tendency to grow
on certain energy negative
en to some degree although it is also
WRA in some of what you would refer to
as mythology but it is an indication of
an awareness that certain of
the what you would call Vegetable life
form do have an affinity for certain
types or weave or warps of
energy that is one that is particularly
sensitive to certain types of of energy
that may represent let us say a
stos a calm a noal point yeah what
does between trees and is
it what it like a
transmission some sort of feeling from
One Tree to another what was going on a
level between vegetables there are
electromagnetic fluctuations in the
field of your planet but do not forget
they are also connected directly through
the crystal in Earth
so think there are pulsations of lower
vibrational frequencies that they can
feel and sense as the communication
coming from each other through their
roots oh see it is like no pun intended
listening to the gra Vine
how do you how do
you we simply recognize the
association yeah but I'm saying like you
come up with things I know you're not of
this language but you seem know language
just the associations the intentions we
simp we push the button that represents
the intentions and the proper words we
assume come out okay what do you what do
you get back as a signal do you are you
part of you hearing the vibration in
this level if hearing can be said to be
the case in one sense but it is more
actually sensing all right so if you
were here in physical form hearing
English without the simac and all that
would you personally understanding
English to some degree now more than I
did when we began but still not as much
for there is no need at this time okay
so the signac is your living dictionary
to
the
transl and just think of a place and be
there yes um when will we be able to do
this and how can we speed it up oh thank
you first of all of course recognize
that in our civilization we still do use
the idea of the image you call the
spacecraft although we are recognizing
that we are translating into a level
wherein we no longer need that device
however of course it is still the same
thing because all motion is an illusion
anyway and the spacecraft is still like
anything a projection of the individual
piloting it to begin with but the idea
of instantaneous transmission across
what you would call SpaceTime is still
created with the idea of the craft and
you find first of all that your Society
does have this technology and you will
find that a highly
accelerated let us say
sharing of the fact that your Society
does contain this
technology is as we can perceive it
geared at this time for releasing what
you would call your spring time of your
New Year I'm talking about without a just by
Year I'm talking about without a just by
thought you can do it anytime you wish
but recognize you will do it according
to what you believe you can do and what
purpose it serves to do
so now do understand in a sense you are
doing that right now when you quote
unquote walk across a
room you are relocating yourself
instantaneously in each and every
different moment but you are doing it at
a rate that seems to perceptually be a
Continuum all you need to do is remove
the intervening moment and you can be
years in
they by living completely in the now
completely utterly totally in the
now without regard to what you call the
creations of the past or the
future you don't have to ask if you
ask the drug that they
call is that a stealing
Dr it can be an orienting one it can be
an Ling one but recognize once again
anything you call a drug is a tool like
anything else as a physiological pmol
and though you have agreed to abide by
what you think the tool is actually
causing within you you are actually
causing the effect the tool is a
reflection a mirror to show you what you
are capable of and from that point
forward once you know what you are
capable of you really don't need the
tool any
longer but yes it can align you
rebalance recenter you and thus by
definition if you bring yourself back to
the let us say idealized templet form of
yourself you can be healed of any
imbalance you were holding on
to is it possible to become just the
flow in a sense yes but recognize that
by definition you have some purpose in
being within to some degree the linear
time frame Matrix of your physiological
reality if you become a flow that has no
purpose in physical reality then you
will disappeared from
it now we assume that since you are here
you are here for some reason and any
flow you become will be congruous with
the idea of what service you can be in
this transformational age on your
physical planet for a time so what might
be represented in your imagination as a
complete flow will still be a derivation
of a flow that will allow you to
accomplish what you need to accomplish
as a physiological being as well you
follow me in other words you will be able to
me in other words you will be able to
incorporate whatever degree of the flow
function as the physical being you chose
to be
I yes you can but that is what we are
saying is you have chosen to be here for
a reason thus it is at this time not
impossible but unlikely you will become
such a flow because then you would in
fact by definition remove yourself
completely from physiological reality
and since you are still here if you are
obviously here for some reason right so
first iological purp oh yes but you can while
iological purp oh yes but you can while
doing that completely and totally flow
within joy and
easy you can allow that flow to be
cognizant within you but simply
represented in physiological terms which
is what you call ecstasy ecstasy
physiological ecstasy is the physical
counterpart of what you are referring to
as the flow
so go ahead be
excited all right what is the
way there is no best way except that
your way is the best way now there are
many techniques that tend to share that
may tap into the general belief system
of the math Consciousness and therefore
they may appear to work very strongly
for you whereas another technique may
not that does not happen to the mass
Consciousness but in this way Trust
first and foremost that the reason you
have an imagination to begin with is
that your imagination is the blank key
it is the tool that is moldable in
providing for you whatever technique you
think you need to do what it is that
excites you that is what your
imagination is for it is keyed to your
vibrational energy thus if you have a
desire to do something all you have to
do is
imagine yourself doing it and Trust up
the images that come in your imagination
are the methodology that you require to
do
it thank you it is very simple may we
simply suggest and remind you keep it
simple all
right yes yes the um U physical Universe
a couple questions related to the
physical Universe the flashing the
groing effect how how PR that occurring
on an agreed upon basis like how many
times a second or is there is it set
like that to some degree it can be now
we can sense many different fluctuations
one of which is approximately 64 million
times a second but that is not
necessarily representative of the exact
level on which you exist okay in other
words as I move my hand across the face
the hand is disappearing at one
fractional location reappearing at
another at that pretty much standard
rate then right who degree yes you are
recreating the entire scenario at quote
unquote pretty much a standard rate okay
this is the interesting thing to me part
of me is cartooning it all very quickly
yeah and U go and U and and then this
other part this like remote monitoring
part is is does does the word
automaticity involved here it seems very
automatic cons to allow all that yeah
are there other realities which would
operate not on that in between the
frequency yes oh oh I see so every individual
yes oh oh I see so every individual
would have his own individ
individualized flash a pattern right to
some degree although it will be
generally homogeneous with the overall
agreed upon flat pattern and then in
between the moments you think are real
our other moments that other being think
are real and not
yours wow that seems like a hell of a
lot of creativity going on absolutely
how you understand a small degree of
what it actually means to be a
multi-dimensional Creator yeah it seems
I mean to be able to paint this room so
many times a second with all the little
details changing oh God that's the
changing oh God that's the
[Laughter]
IDE thank you thank you very much yes um
the first off I'd like to thank thank
you for your your help on a promotional
letter that I was doing last week that
absolutely came out incredibly we thank
you for your co-creation and your
willingness to give vent and conviction
to your own connections and energies it
was so marvelous every time that I read
it I just flew out you know and um I
think other people when they read it
they're going to just I think they're
really going to have an experience just
right there and if it stops right there
that's fine you know then the next thing
is um I have a question on what does
embarrassment that that idea where does
that come from and then I have a
question ask it comes from the idea of
guilt it comes from the idea of
invalidating portions of yourself and
believing them to be Unworthy of sharing
of not thinking of yourself as a
gift well right
okay the reason I asked that because I
have something
embarrassing I see understand that
anything you have to say as with anyone
is something that all others can learn
from therefore it is a gift of sharing
right okay um first part of that
question is that I had an experience
recently which reminded me of a reality
that I used to hold regarding implant which
implant which
Tye mental
yes okay implanting an idea yes or
restriction or
um pattern yeah pattern in an
individual did he just implant that in
you but I knew and that's
help right but without someone
are deviously so that someone is not
consciously aware of that we understand
what you are referring to but you are
always the one doing the planting even
if it occurs on an unconscious level
okay that's and that's cool and I can
accept that but also the mechanics still
do exist the mechanics exist but the
mechanics only Define that you still are
the only Gardener doing the planting
right like by agreement yes right right
okay well that's really fantastic
because um it's it's interesting because
we talked last week about that there was
a situation that I was finding myself in
with a friend that I didn't quite
understand and you said well there would
be a present there and don't unwrap your
present before Christmas or some
something like that right and
interestingly enough just by being being
involved in the situation some peeling
off has occurred in regards to a a real
heavy duty situation that my attention
had been on for ages but in
involving um a situ this is the
embarrassing part I'm trying to not say
a
minut involving
involving
um let's see the words the words the
words
um involving going a little bit Bonkers
on the idea of sexual
relationships Define
fongers out of control out of logical
control just kind of
reactive um to where you
where a a person
is kind of being controlled by the
situation instead of controlling the
situation you know of course that that
doesn't happen right but it see it has
an apparency to happen yes right and
that there's a cause behind that and
that that's kind of the thing that has
been unfolding any apparency of a
situation controlling you is a removal
of the responsibility for the creation
of the situation from yourself right I
understand that all right I do
understand that but finding that
responsibility where that responsibility
is you can say yeah I'm responsible for
this but if the situation is keeping on
continuing then that's great you know
that you're responsible for it but have
you know how do you then correct it is a
different thing allow yourself once
again to remember that no situation has
built in meaning you may be
automatically assigning a meaning to it
that you don't have to keep assigning
the meaning you assign to a neutral
situation a neutral symbol determines
the effect you get out of that situation
and if you keep assigning the same
meaning yes you keep getting the same
effect regardless of whether or not at
first it is the same symbol doesn't mean
anything it is the meaning you keep
giving it that allows it to continue to
create the same effect when you change
the meaning
then the symbol in due time will be able
to transform to fit the new meaning you
are giving it but if you keep giving it
the old meaning it will only remain the
same old symbol right so if you keep
battling with that and keep battling
with that and keep battling with that
you keep creating and creating if you
know you are different then don't give
an old symbol the same old meaning give
it a meaning that represents the new you
you know you are you still do live in a
world of time and therefore to some
degree transformation may still take a
little bit of time so if your first
inclination upon knowing you have quote
unquote changed is to still creat a
symbol the same symbol in the same old
way then you are not acting like you
truly believe you have
ch right so if that situation pops up
then give it a new meaning as fit the
new person you
are then it will be able to
transform right it is the symbol the
situation the exterior is only the
shadow of the content you fill it
with therefore if you continue to fill
it with the same old content it doesn't
have to change it shapes if you give it
a new content it must
conform so if you say this situation
Ares and you go oh Jesus this is
fundamentally neutral neutral blank zero
so then you just relax yes and be there
it is your opportunity to change what
you do not prefer into what you
do the symbol is your reflection it is
your tool it is saying here I am once again
tool it is saying here I am once again
completely and utterly blank now whoever
you happen to be at this point you put
your mark on me and I will respond in
time it is always going to be there as
long as you are physical you are always
going to have to use some physiological
template or symbol right make it what
you wish then it will
wish then it will
be that's really good because that's
actually accidentally kind of been doing
and it has been changing there are no
accident right but I thought well yeah who knows
right but I thought well yeah who knows
will po up
again so it
happens you know on a bradi
scale the more you are willing to
recognize that you have the opportunity
to reassign a meaning to that old symbol
then the quicker you will allow it to
transform and you will get therefore the
type of feedback that will allow you to
trust more and more and accelerate more
and more
accordingly but trust is the first thank
first thank
you you're talking about being in limbo
I think a lot of people relating to that
and oh yeah oh yes and that's where I'm
right now all right very good
congratulations welcome yes it feels a lot better now
welcome yes it feels a lot better now
than it did a couple hours ago um one of
the things that's happening right now
you're also talking about dream and I've
always I've always dreamed a lot um and
always been able to remember dreams
relate to them Etc what I'm finding now
is I'm Dreaming I I have a sense of
dreaming I know there's a lot of a lot
of stuff in those dream and I cannot I
can't is it it's recognize that there
are many reasons for that interaction
but one of them that is a symptom of
moving into more acceleration is
recognize that your dream reality and
your physical reality are the same
reality the idea you normally refer to
as a dream that which you remember upon
Awakening is there as a bridge and a
link to remind you that you did have
another experience and that link has to
be there because you are saying that the
physical experience is disconnected from
the non-physical one so you have a dream
by which to remember that there is a
link as soon as you begin to actually
create an experience
link and know that the dream reality and
the physical reality are actually one
and the same reality and that you are
dreaming right now then you don't ever
wake up from the
dream so you don't go into a different
type of reality that you have to make a
comparison through the dream symbol
with that's exactly what's
happen your dream uh you mentioned
uh you mentioned the uh time moving in
time and what I've noticed just in the
past month is that I'm having what
people would call flashbacks uh things
are just coming out of nowhere and
they're not future but but they are time
they're time yes you are integrating
integrating integrating is it possible
to go forward you are going where you
need to go
okay yes it is
okay as long as you find that you do not
unduly restrip
yourself by
precognition and take all the
surprise no I don't think so but right
now I'm really scared it's the right
words I'm feeling a lot of apprehension
and I don't know why I just am oh
thanky it is because you are very
excited but you are still out of habit
inv validating that excitement because
anxiety is the same energy as the energy
of excitement but it is
Jud invalidated you are very excited you are
invalidated you are very excited you are
only feeling the vibrational core of
your being let it be all right to feel
that it is your indestructibility that
you are feeling
thank
you thank you very much he um two or 3
years ago um I an experience where uh I
hyperventilated and had the uh
impression that uh I I I lost my body
and and ended up in some dark chamber
where there some some white thing
appeared and we seem to have a a
discussion of some hours long about
whether um I should die whether I should
continue in my life as it was or whether
I should continue with a life which is
more um more at risk and doing doing
more um extravagant things all right and
we had this long discussion and um about
which one I should choose and really
there was only one choice to take the
third one of course more risky type of
existence uh I also had the impression
that this uh whatever it was
rolled out these alternative uh what my
life would be like in these two
Alternatives um I don't remember it now
but I did at the time can you explain
what that was it's very simple and your
term R is quite
accurate the idea in this way is that
sometimes individuals will allow
themselves to view the crossroads that
they come to in life from the point of
view out of the body discussing it with
their di their assistance
those energies that are always in touch
with you to allow you to know where you
stand within any given level of reality
physical and or non-physical it is a
mirror a reflection of yourself
presented by another loving individual
who is willing to assist you in your
decisions in that way you simply have
done it in the fashion of rising above
the physical level and seeing what is
laid before you then making your
decision from that point of view rather
than from within the physiological
reality the IDE is the different
scenarios are in a sense literally
rolled out to you they are expanded as
spherical ID is 360° and rolled across
wherein you take them in absorb them
expand them within your 360° shell of
projection screen to see how they will
play out and in that way fold them back
up put them within yourself in that way
and as you make your choice then
reproject yourself back into physical
reality to continue the flow that you
have chosen you simply are in that sense
or at least at that time were very
Loosely connected to physical reality
and chose to Simply have the
decision-making process done on another
level other than the physical
one do this is isue yes that being is
still with you and will be for quite
some time thank you yay what knowledge do you
time thank you yay what knowledge do you
have concerning an entity from the
seventh Dimension Nam Mau oh thank you
and this connection with being in the
inner earth over the next three weeks
know recognize that the idea first of
all of the what we call inner earth
beings is that they do exist on a
slightly different dimensional plane
than what you would call your immediate
third density also it is not that they
quote unquote literally occupy the
interior of your planet in your
dimension but that they are represented
in that interior space in a slightly
different out of phase Dimension other
than your own the connection has to do
with many of the civilizations that have
existed upon your planet already as some
of those civilizations were aware of
some of that sixth and seventh density
level Consciousness have been in
communication with it before there is
some connection from time to time of
past occurrences upon your world with
some of these ideas of connection as
they projected themselves these
Consciousness level projected themselves
and communicated with various
individuals who were open who were
sensitive who were willing in this way
some of the past civilizations upon your
planet have been established through the
opes of intercommunication and
understanding of these levels in that
way and the expression of these
understandings and Communications were
played out in many different various
civilizations upon your world now the
idea also at this time is that the
particular energy as we perceive it in
your vibrational state mahu in this way
will be directly representative of many
different Communications not from but
through the energy level let us say
projected through using the substance of
the energy level that represents in your
physiological Society what you would
call the archetypal substream
Consciousness and therefore is able to
tap into many ideas of self-empowerment
through what you would term very
mythological State we are not saying
they are not real but the idea you have
closest terminology is in mythological
Consciousness that is why you will find
that at this time because each and every
one of you are beginning to recognize
the quote unquote magician the sorcerer
within your C there is a strong
connection with that seventh density
Consciousness level in terms of feeding
across information through this energy
level of your own subconsciousness in
the form you would call Merlin aspect
and Merlin energy are you following
along yes in this way it represents to
some degree a slightly higher
pulse of some sixth density levels of
consciousness that have already
previously been in touch with your
civilization it is a representative
acceleration a stepping up a
transformed level of a similar form of
Consciousness identity but now that you
have accelerated it can also represent
this acceleration by coming from the
next level of
itself does this assist you yes and in
the next two
weeks Earth ch in our
area to some degree there are energy
fluctuations electromagnetic shiftings
as we can perceive them there may be
some small seismic
shiftings around the general
local you venue I've been experiencing
some changes with my right ear and it
seems like an in infection but I've
never experienced it like this before
just um does it feel more like a
pressure uh just yes
yes will you immerse
yourself in warm
water uh like my the right side of my
head my ear both yeah let it be
balanced let another type of pressure
teach you how to balance the pressure
within
you you can if you wish
Place some of what you might turn
turn
allows once again perhaps the eucalyptus
fragrances within the water also to some
degree a little bit of what you might
call Soul this can be of assistance at
the same time within your imagination
you can also imagine blue white
electromagnetic balancing energy around
you in a homogeneous form and also
Golden Light Within the center of your
brain allow the pressures to be released
allow the pressures to be released
through the energy channels and conduits
of the different Cher points upon your
body allow yourself to be pressurize and
balance out you are becoming more
sensitive and more attuned to the
background vibration of creation but you
are simply doing it in a little bit of
an off-balanced state so it is creating
an unequalized version of pressure
within your it will acclimate an
your it will acclimate an
equalize okay some of this may
automatically release as some of the
pressures that we have just been discussing are
that we have just been discussing are
also released recognize that some of the
electromagnetic shiftings and seismic
pressures in your planetary sphere are
experienced not only the heart chakra
but also the sinus chakra in this sense
not a chakra exactly but a conduit and
the idea of the interconnecting valves
within your
cranium because it is highly sensitive
to Magnetic fluctuation your
CES let the energy be released through
you and out into your electromagnetic
blue White oric Field let it be balanced
and then your entire cellular structure
can also balance
accordingly all right okay thank you
thank you very much now another bit of
assistance may be allowing yourself to
be attracted to what you find to be very
and I underlying this as many times as
you can or do very enjoyable
melodious tones
Bon all right okay this can also assist
in a type of
balancing thank you very much F you
hey I've beening a
line I've
beening what you just said because I
felt represented the
mag innoc yes what I've been developing
as personality to kind of represent that
guys and also I've been using the symbol
of the Dragon oh yes very ancient
wisdom oh okay what I wanted to know is
there there are like two types of
dragons that are used artistically one
is a Chinese type of dragon the other is
an aruan type of dragon which has bat
wings okay what is there a difference in
the symbol of those two that's
significant or is it different society's
way of seeing similar it is both it does
generally represent the same overall
base consciousness but in this way there
are significant differences in the
application of the understanding the
idea in Arthurian terms may involve what
you would
call perhaps more ethereal
Realms wherein in the what you would
call Asian sense may represent more the
fundamental Motive Power or Foundation
of nature itself
W like an like the symbol of the Dragon
way um almost like an energy R way it
fluctuates In
Waves yes the foundational
frequency vibration the first Primal
incarnations so then the dragon would
represent that that kind of wisdom
Ancient wisd Ancient wisdom also kind of
that ancient connections to Nature on
many different
and thenal thus different representations of
thenal thus different representations of
the dragon can represent different
connections to different levels of your
planetary sphere and some that are
extraterrestrial as well oh really yes
that is why there have been instances of
what you would call sightings of craft
with diagrams of dragons upon
them I didn't realize that
yes okay and could you reflect more to
me on that one about the ex structure
what what how does it differ Dr
it will be more representative of the
interweaving connective strings that
form the weave of the fabric of creation
itself between the
stars as a representative in nature of that
as a representative in nature of that
which can ply space and time between the
Stars the
corridors the doorways
the tunnels between Dimensions
energy are you referring to the idea of
a
Gateway no I'm referring to um in they
talk about that we have personally like
energy Tel Chels in the body those are
gateways oh
gateways a version of
ask you one more thing B in my paintings
for years now crystals keep showing up
they just sort of decide to be painted
in okay and um I wanted to ask you if
you would reflect to me a little bit
about um what do you all already
understand you have the intuition
already trust it Go With It is it from a
past time in Atlant some yes that it
works with Crystal oh
yes the dragon connotations are also
very strong from that era as
well I have a sense that that there's
more about crystals that I haven't
allowed myself to see yet you will
discover them in
Joy okay well I'm keep exploring I'm
having fun with them yes keep exploring
all right step into your
paintings step into
them then they can communicate more
directly to you that's a great idea use
your imagination okay it is the primary
pet thank you very much thank you
you I just had a wonderful realization
oh
my and it was enhanced by what you were
sharing um Al synchronous thank you I
really finally got the idea of
hown synchronous is part of it too about
how how we all are crystal and the way I
got that is uh about a week go this is
all part of it it's all part of the same
thing um the same one thing that is what
it means to be synchronous yeah um
anyway what what it is is a couple weeks
ago you know I was tching and Ming about
you know integrating everything all the
time if it was something okay one more
thing and then then it'll be good right
no no got another thing why are those
people talking to me that way why is she
saying that that and and all that kind
of stuff instead of just then all of a
sudden I could make no Rhyme or Reason
of it it was totally ridic
and I started being amused by it and
then the next thing that happened is I
thought it was hysterically funny and
then the next thing I did was totally
surrender to all of it oh welcome to
Fourth density to the degree that I did
now I have little
lasses but nevertheless there is that
there is it's all right they are very
cute little laughes
and Sal so now now when she was sharing
that thing about a crystal I never could
get this idea you know and you gave me
the same crystal I what are you calling
that for and then um it's a lovely name
I I think ni name and pretty but all of
a sudden I got this idea you know like
we're all part of the same one thing and
there is no skin I mean all this stuff I
say intellectually but right
now uh it's like there is nothing
between us all and the Ecstasy part when
you surrender to that neutrality you can
go oh that was good what what so what do
you think about that and the person
would go you go wonderful and then you
go to that person so what do you think
and know all give you their advice and
from their Viewpoint and it's all
different and it's all your own creation
or your own considerations and finally
you just laugh and you go that's all
fabulous I think I'm going to do this
yes and it's just and then thank you
it's wor being yay I see why you love us
so yes
what else can I say you have said it all
okay continue to do oh thank you byk you
by you thank you you are welcome
than yeah
yeah
um the last two weeks I found I've just
felt a tremendous pull to come here for
uh no particular reason I have no
questions I haven't seen you in over a
year and the story came out of the blue
and I've been getting you wonderful
little messages from almost everything
that's been said here tonight but I was
wondering if you had a direct statement
for me or simply that you are being
reflected the degree to which
synchronicity can function in your life
and allow all the elements in your life
to Simply come together when and where
they will knowing that when they do it
will be exactly the perfect place in the
perfect timing get
timing get
it and I'd like to statement for you
what um when I first started coming to see
um when I first started coming to see
you a couple years ago it was like I I
was perfectly creating a mess it was
great I really enjoyed it and things
have changed a lot for me over the last
two years in this very moment the last
two weeks I've noticed a a total and
complete turnaround occurring in my life
yes and a lot of it has been because of
allowing just whatever is going to
happen to happen because I know that's
the way it's supposed to
be um now that does not mean you can
canot prefer and create your preference
oh yeah I have like three different
preferences and I can go all
right I just wanted to thank you for the
the mirroring that you've done for me
and for all of us over the last few
years let's have some more fun always
thank you very much there will be a few
of your moments remaining for this
interaction shorter session
tonight for the blending and the channel
for that and
for your enjoyment of the action you are
becoming rather than the
talking but it's so wonderful to just be
here and do even if you don't talk
okay but like sleep you will need less
of it in this form and you will
recognize that when you are out there
doing you will being in touch with us
wonderful yay I've written a book which I call
yay I've written a book which I call
over mind should I bother
going I bother going through motions
bother bother bother will it happen are
you excited about it very excited about
it then why are you considering that it
will be a bother the consideration is
I'm excited for myself
well who else do you need to be excited
for others others will be excited
according to their own
willingness if it is what excites you do
it if you think it would be a bother it
obviously doesn't excite you very much
so don't do
it it is that obvious keep it that
obvious do what excites you if it
doesn't excite you don't do
[Music]
it all right strawberry cool
it do you understand the idea absolutely
for in this way if you are saying that
you can perceive that the idea will be a
bother then you are telling yourself you
are going to make the experience un
exciting it seems it would be exciting
if it happened without any effort on my
part that excites me understand that if
you are excited about it it will happen
without any
effort that is the whole connective idea
the cause and the effect are the same
event both are there at the same
time you follow
me thank you very
much hey is that negative energy when
that something is about it in a sense
because you are limiting it separating
it from yourself now you can recognize
something you do not prefer but then
simply recognize that if you are doing
what you you prefer the thing you don't
prefer will never never be experienced
in your reality so it is also still not
a
bother thank you thank you Rashad hey I
have a question for a friend of mine um
Jerry asked me he said that a couple
years ago you talked about his mother
having uh been a spirit guide for him
but not his father and she died and she
was waiting in the grave for about a
year I just to refresh your memories so
um and he would like to know what she's
doing now now in this way you understand we
now now in this way you understand we
did not say she was waiting in the grave
well she was being she she died to to
allow her husband to go on living fully
evidently okay to lure him into more of
himself so that he would quote unquote
follow her
oh to a higher realm I see while still
physical his question was what is she
doing now our perception is that she is
still functioning as a
guide for for Jerry and others and
others okay thank
you yes what exact one
moment there are some other things as
well we cannot share them at this time
you can gleam this information from
mothers if you wish all right thank you
continue um I was wondering um this idea
of a guy um how do do guys interact with
us in dream state or oh yes oh yes oh
yes dream state in Wake state in Wake
State more
unobtrusively because the idea is to
lure you into more of yourself and
recognize you are in full control a gu's
job is to allow you to know you don't
really need them per se
but that you can interact with them and
co-create a loving reality and a
creative one and an ecstatic one um is
there um I've just been thinking I've
just been aware I've just recently
become aware of a um I guess one of my
guides and I'm wondering if there's some
more direct communication that I could
experience with this time again for now
trust your imagination allow yourself to
program yourself in your dream dream
state before you dream before you sleep
with the understanding that you will
communicate and that what you will
remember will be exactly what you need
to remember to get the job done that
they have assisted you with but again
they will be mostly unobtrusive if you
follow me yes the idea is to let you
live your life not sit around
talking okay thank you can these can
these guides manifest other than
meditational yes they can from time to
time now again this idea however is more that
now again this idea however is more that
you have been
impressed upon on your higher level of
communication to recreate your own
version of them to manifest in your
physiological reality to act as a
reflective symbol that is the mechanism of The
symbol that is the mechanism of The
Apparition for sure he what kinds of
things will we do more
seems to me what you want but I'm doing
things all the time so obviously it's
going to be
different the idea once again will be
mostly an example and an expression of
your complete and total Reliance upon
trust and the recognition once again
that any so-called questions immediately
represent answers in whatever form you
need to know them on whatever level of
Consciousness you need to be aware of
them and that you do not need someone
else to tell you this oh that I
understand all right again it will be
more activity and more directly it will
be more and more activities that are
directly proportionally representational
of activities that would allow you to
always function effortlessly and
ecstatically and more interaction with
other beings upon your planet through
synchronistically similar inex thank thank
you this
time allow us once again and for the
first time to thank you all very much
for the love of your willingness to
share the gift of your Consciousness
with us so that we together can Coke
create an equality a new facet a new
dimension a new expression a new
Direction within the already existent
multi-dimensional Crystal of all that
is unconditional love and energy with
you all we B you a fond and
all we B you a fond and
loving good day good
how did everything go great wonderful
thank you thank you all for thank e e for