all right we will say how are you all
but see you time as you create time to
exist bold flowing bold flowing all
right so may we continue with an idea I
have been discussing this week of your
time the idea of Daring you to be
yourselves in this way allow us
to let us say preceive this idea
if I may become a little bit intimate
with you may I all right
now many times you will find
that many of what you call the
consciousnesses to which you refer to us
as ourselves in that way and many other
what you call
entities coming through many other what
you call channels or
mediums upon your planet at this
time allow me to discuss an idea with
you with regard to the idea of the
channelings that are taking place upon
your planet at this time from many
different levels of
consciousness do not forget including
your own for in this way as well your
own future selves your own higher selves
are involved in this process for they
know already where you are headed and
and they are looking back reaching out
your hands to yourselves and helping
yourselves across the span of time you
follow me yes
now understand that to use your
terminology to be colloquial to be in
your terms practical for a
moment allow us in this way to
illuminate the idea that dealing with
you as we
do part
particularly particularly when there is a gathering
particularly when there is a gathering
of you as opposed to an
individual you will find that though we
are in this way creating the interaction
with you in and of the
moment there will be ideas that flow
into this
interaction that will regulate the
balance of how the
information and how the interaction
takes place with him
recognize it this way if you will the
idea that with so many differentiating
consciousnesses as you have allowed
yourself to create yourselves to be it
is in a sense a balancing act to
find the let us say
commonality by which we can deal in that
way on some level that represent
something you can allow yourselves to
work with in terms of information that
we can share with you to recognize many
times in this way the polarities the
dichotomies and the paradoxes that we
find in this way you have created in
your Society will enable us many times
in a sense to create the type of
interactions with you from all the
different entities channeling to you at
this time that form a subtle
balance a subtle shall we say
engineering of how you receive the
information now understand we are not
engineering you against your will
no what we are doing however is choosing
in this way in the moment from our
knowing selves what type of information
will be of best service to the overall
understanding and impact even though
you're outter aware immediately focused
physical Consciousness may not make
sense of the immediate idea of the
answers and the sharings that we have
with you recognize that this is also part and
you recognize that this is also part and
parcel of what you have many times come
to understand as discrepancies in
information in this way between various
entities recognize that you allow us to
perform a very delicate balance with you
in this way and the idea of fulfilling
assistance to you in the overall way you
do desire us to do so means that from
time to time time you will find that
between all of the Consciousness AES
that are channeling to you we will come
up with methodologies that may seem to
contain discrepancies differentiations
dichotomies but that are specifically
engineered to bring you to a certain
creative pressure point you follow me
yes in this way understand that when I
told you in your terms that my
job was an
engineer it is not just a technical
engineer it is a sociological engineer
it is the reason for why I have allowed
myself to pattern the interaction with
you it is the idea of the engineering in
the now
moment of interactions between
civilizations understand we are not meaning in any way
understand we are not meaning in any way
shape and form
to express this idea as superiority to
you no but in this way simply do
recognize that we have done this many
times and we do not wish to frustrate
you we do not wish to disappoint you we
do not wish in this way at any time to
allow you to feel that we are
chastising that we are in any way shape
or
form not willing to share with you you
that which your heart so strongly
desires for this is far from the case
but simply in our point of view from our
experience the way we are sharing with
you is the way that is what will grant
you your desire with regard to what you
seek with us and many other
Civilizations for in this way you have
created your specific civilization to be
a very strongly focused one in its own
accord and any transformation from that
Focus to another focus is going to
contain a large degree of very delicate
shifts and
balances and in this way when we give
you a little of this share a little of
that when you allow yourself to come to
a point of pondering ideas that have
been discuss when you feel within yourself
discuss when you feel within yourself
that you are at a standstill at a loss
racked with confusion doubting
yourselves judging
yourselves feeling chastised feeling
held back simply allow yourselves to
understand that all of the places that
you find yourself to be are in a sense a
part of the
emotionality that needs to be
experienced so that you can engineer
yourselves into the approach appropriate
creative pressure
points that are the doorways through
which you will step and find yourselves
where you have for so long desired to be
when your timing is appropriate you
follow me
yes always we love you very much and
always we love you very much and
appreciate your willingness to allow us
to interact with you in this way for
always the interaction with us for us
with any
civilization has enriched us beyond
measure enriched us Beyond
counting enriched us Beyond
naming for it allows us the opportunity
as we have shared with you many times to
understand that much more of creation
and all the different ways that all that
is has of manifesting itself within the
creation of itself and the knowingness
of itself through all that it has
created within now the
now the
idea is to allow you to be aware
consciously of this type of
engineering because now you are since
this is the activity time the doing time
able to begin to know that you are in
control of everything that occurs in
your life and that you are the engineers
and you can now consciously recognize
that fact we have not so much been doing
any engineering for you but have only
been reflecting to you the engineering
that your higher cells have been
ordaining so that you would reach the
point you have
desired we thank you for allowing us to
reflect this to you in this way and we
will now continue to co- engineer on an
equal basis sure you venue venue can you give
basis sure you venue venue can you give
us some specific um examples of what
you've been talking about
not without treading on too many
toes and in a sense not without
revealing something at this time which
is personal to many individuals okay I
presume that something came up that has
inspired in this way it is simply the
idea as it has now clicked over as you
say into many different personal events
within the mass Consciousness that
allows us to recognize that this is the
timing for this
information if each and every one of you
or some of you find it has personal
meaning accept it as such and apply it
as such as your own engineer okay uh
since this is activity month would you
say that will always now be the case and
also that will be the underlying energy
that will allow you the opportunity to
express that energy in terms of physical
action outwardly okay thank you thank
outwardly okay thank you thank
you I have uh a little bit
U I'm in some cusing all right okay
co-use with
us a friend of mine called me uh last
Wednesday night I was not here and I
real excited and I want to go out and I
want to do something because this was
activity month what in your words right
and uh as soon as I got up and I started
doing things and I ran to the door and I
realized there was nothing for me to do
so
nothing nothing at all nothing
physically nothing at all that's what
I'm that's what I'm asking actually I've
were you present when we suggested the
writing of your
letters no all right suggest in this way
recognize one of the suggestions we have
made is that in the practice so to speak
quote unquote of recognizing that you
are your government your political
institutions your social economic and
religious institutions that you are
equal to them communicate with them
write to them every day every day let
them know not
chastising not
denuncia not judging not admonishing but
with love and compassion and equality
let them simply know that you prefer
peace every single day I prefer peace
thank you very
much your
friend that is one thing you can do
allow your imagination free reign for
you would simply find that if you are
willing to allow your imagination free
reign you could have thought of a
million and one things to do in that
moment just by simply sitting down and
doing them okay there were things that I
did yes sort of such well I meditated a
lot all right and we are talking about
outward action as well now well that's
what I wanted to understand um does it
mean physically out yes yes this is the
physical Universe you are in this is the
idea it is the application of
knowledge in your world that makes the
difference it is your willingness to act
as a Creator not to sit and think of
yourself as a Creator who does not
create on all levels
it is the idea of being willing to in
your terms walk your
terms walk your
[Laughter]
talk we will utilize whatever phology
and Tool fits the
Bill thank you thank you the idea is
that now now that you have taken it in
put it back out okay thank you very much
yes yes I want to talk about the idea okay
yes I want to talk about the idea okay
the idea a few weeks ago and we've been
talking about the idea that the um the
present is not the result of the past
okay no um one more time now with
feeling now all right um a lot of quote
gurus say from the east from India and
from that masters from different okay
we'll talk about the idea of Karma and
and I guess you know if you read books
that were written in the 1950s and stuff
there'll be a lot of talk about Karma
now is that uh that's a is that
considered a third density idea in a
sense okay now yet these these people
who I've been in the presence of during
the U over the years seem very much
enlightened now are they teaching that
out of the idea that we were very much
invol with their density and they they
were also aware that there's no such
thing as karma or did they really some
of them may have different degrees of
realization and in this way though they
may know intrinsically of the idea of
Enlightenment they may still be
utilizing the symbologies that
individuals are used to so that the
individuals can understand what is being
said that's what I was saying now
however they were taught by their
masters those or their teachers those
same kind of ideas cause and effect and
and so I wondered how much these ideas
are beginning to
change understand that even at the base
of all they are teaching quote unquote
is the idea of the transcending of the
karmic cycle right now understand that
the fundamental methodology of
transcending the karmic cycle is to know
you created it and do not have to choose
it right that is the whole idea in a
nutshell as you say okay now they also a
lot of the writings will say you need to
have a this is simply a reflection of
the pattern that you all have laid down
in your society and are still very
willing to give yourselves in that way
it is the need that is only the need of
the expression of what you have set up
to be your needs and so you will fulfill
that interaction understand as has also been
interaction understand as has also been
pointed out many times you are your own
teachers you are all Masters yeah no I
agree with that in fact uh well I guess
about a month ago I was talking to you
about an experience I had and you
kiddingly or I felt very lovingly said
always the rebel nice okay and um can be
the same thing as a master a thank you
because there are times when I um I have
anyway um in the past as we know the
past exist um judged myself because that
it's like I felt like well um cuz I'm
not someone that would just go along
with the group and may I remind you of
something yes had not all individuals
that you perceive to be Masters at some
time also judged themselves they would
not be Masters for they would not have
experienced all they needed to
experience okay all right um I also have
another thank you I have a question now
when you said when we experience the
idea of uh that the present is not a
result of the past then we will be
experiencing fourth density now okay go
ahead now okay
now when we um make the move into fifth
density yes does that still apply or is
that no longer a truth in fifth deny I
mean does that does that sound strange
but ultimate truth is composed of all
truths okay so is there such a okay so
does that still apply when you're in
fifth stand totally different it is more
the well it is different yes but it is
also the idea that you will now to use
your term
lose tools you will drop them by the
wayside okay I I and so it will not be
so much that you will gain that idea
back it will remain gone for in this way
you will also understand that in fifth
density the very
concepts of past present and future will
become more one idea literally
experientially because you will not be
physical as you have known it at all
okay now the idea of meditation which I
now the idea of meditation which I
enjoy I would too okay now um do you
meditate on your plan or or not so much
as you understand the setting aside of a
time in that way we are in a sense
always active and always meditating at
the same time like I feel a lot that I'm
meditating as I'm doing what I'm doing
there are all types of meditation okay
now um when you go into F like you said
when we when real
what what is it you know that is there
feel and all of a sudden you're in the
the fifity it will be the recognition
first of all that you simply no longer
need the entire tool of physicality
anymore at
all this is why you will find at the end
of fourth density
experience what we perceive to be in a
couple of thousand of your years as you
count on M you will simply begin to well
leave your bodies okay not through
disease or aging just leave okay now I
found that for me right now is it's of
course because I have a lot of my life
not wanted to be physical and resisted
what my choice so um actually even
though what from what you just said even
though I'm anxious for fifth density I
realized that let me tell you you would
not want to miss
forth I'm starting to feel that now yeah
oh thank you yeah St it's starting to be
okay now understand that in between each
and every life you have had you have
always had the choice to go where you
wanted to right obviously you made the
choice to be here yeah I'm and I'm you
know starting to discover my purpose you
know thank you
telling P that she wouldn't want to miss
forth but in fact she hasn't I mean
since everything is happening now yes
yes yes yes yes do not allow for the
negative confusion of the idea of the
Paradox of having to speak in your
language to describe certain things do
not think we are contradicting what was
said before but simply that as long as
you are asking a question in a time
frame we will answer it in a time frame
yeah but a lot of times I feel that I am
existing in different existences of
course you are and and so that uh I
don't want Miss forth either you won't
but I'd like to share something uh go
ahead last week uh I was doing a lot of
third density work again but at the same
like before that I share with you but
the whole time I felt like I was May I
point something out for a moment just as
a point of Interest
yeah the idea of continuing to make the
separation ation between what is third
density work and fourth density work is
a third density
idea uh okay I I don't think I wasn't
aware of it at the time all right uh
that's what was so interesting uh I was
in meetings all week from morning to I
was never bored and I just experienc I
was really in and now it was a very
interesting thing uh there was a funny
incident um towards the end of the week
at one point right and a person across
the table said um well R is is trying to
say i' said it and everybody everybody
laughed and I laughed too but I'm sure
we laughed for different reasons because
talking about if I had said something to
the effect well you don't try since you
do everything in an now you do you don't
try they would have thought I was crazy
oh who says maybe do oh maybe not yeah
maybe do but I thought it was kind of
funny I enjoyed the the
incident oh very good thank you for
being bold enough not to object but to
subject any objection is a subjective
point of view uhhuh okay you are simply
delineating what your particular
subjective point of view is on a certain
idea willing to be subjective in that
way okay all right I'll think about that
okay all right I'll think about that
eyes aren't quite as good as they should
be what what what what what should
should should oh yeah we have discussed
many times the
idea well I can't always read things
real well without my eyes getting blurry
then perhaps you don't need to perhaps
you have the information you need to
have already well what I was going to ask you
already well what I was going to ask you
about is that during that week too I was
looking at a type sheet of paper and I
can read it but it's it makes my eyes
tired all right and at
uh at one point everything was for about
a second or two Crystal Clear yes and I
was wondering if that at that point I
jumped into four density brief and came
back or what does that you gave yourself
an opportunity to experience the idea
that you yourself as a being are clear
on what you need to understand at any
given moment and that the idea of the
limitation of your eyesight is something
that you are choosing to do for a
specific reason and it simply showed you
it is under your control ah
interesting and therefore it is an
indication to you that you are doing it
for a reason uhhuh so it is not that
they should be anything they are what
they are to serve your purpose I realize
that I have a theory that you go back
and forth a one goes back and forth a
little bit up and then down into towards
forth density and then back and and up
oh there are some pendulum swings in
sense it is the average idea that
represents your acceleration and your
momentum but can we go a little up and
then back and then you are leveling out
right as soon as you begin to in your
terms let us say work through the idea
of the polarity then as you begin to
blend the polarity it will even out okay
and that will increase the acceleration
uhhuh okay thank
you first I want to thank you and tell
you how much I appreciate this joyous
occasion we always appreciate the joy of
the experience of you all thank you I
have two questions my husband and I are
raising our 8-year-old
grandson and he is a very special and
exceptional being all right have a
strong anger that comes and seems to to
possess him or take take him which is
why we have him and I have never had
much of this so it's I'm wondering what
does it give you an opportunity to look
at within yourself about the idea of
what you are describing to be Ang what I
have experienced is that I was raised
that you didn't Express anger or have
right anger right and U I'm what is
anger um frustration nope no no well
I've heard frustration is Judgment yes
what is
anger natural anger the natural emotion
anger it feels like objection in a sense
in a sense yes I feel he wants to be
what he is he wants to be himself and
feels the idea of anger that is
naturally expressed in your civilization
usually only lasts 10 to 15 of your
seconds beyond that it is Judgment the
idea of anger is that when you see
something that does not represent the
idea you know yourself to be your anger
centers you where you know you are what
idea you are relative to what you are
seeing not that you have to continue to
judge what you are seeing as something
less than what you know yourself to be
but the anger gives you the opportunity
to Simply see where you are relative to
what you are seeing yes he goes
immediately into judgment and um action
and um all right then simply you are
being of assistance by allowing him a
reflection of a being that can know he
does not have to go that can show him he
does not have to go into judgment that
the anger in and of itself is Perfectly
Natural and healthy and teach him that
it is simply his way of aligning himself
to the idea
and that once he is aligned the
frustration is not necessary because
once you are aligned that allows the
reality to take care of itself you do
not need to continue with frustration on
the assumption that now that you have
the anger you have to force the reality
to go the way you think it needs to that
is why there is frustration again it is
an offshoot of the idea that in your
Society do not believe that imagination
and cognizance is just as real as
physical reality and that the having of
a conception and the realization that
your anger gives you is not the
beginning of a process that you need to
start creating to take steps to achieve
something it is the end of a process you
have gotten to the point of
realization and that means that at that
moment you are that being and that it is
only necessary from that point to trust
that if you are the being you have now
realized yourself to be relative to what
you see around you then that is the type
of reality you will begin to experience
if you let yourself be the being you
have realized you are yeah teach him
that right all right how do you reflect
that to a
youngster sometimes they create the idea
of not understanding those ideas
sometimes they do why not simply see if
that is the case before pondering a what
if what if one's already discovered that
that is in case when they oh right that
are are many forms of communication and
the idea first and foremost is that if
you have agreed to have an interaction
with that other entity that other being
you call the youngster in that way
recognize that if you are willing to
Simply Be the being you chose to be and
are being that being then you are being
the being they made the agreement to be
with that is all that is necessary
wonderful what they are doing is their
choice let them do what they have chosen
to do
very good all right yes on the other
hand um in being oneself is frequently a
um in being oneself is frequently a
response to their their frustration
their judgment all right what kind of a
response it might be along the similar
lines to theirs why not in terms of
judgment so much as uh anger all right
all right but after the first 15 seconds
then
what well that's a good question
question because some so your anger has
not particularly created a change in
their their frustration well your anger
cannot change them right right well
let's put it on a co-creational basis
right all right
so the apparency is that that there's
been no growth or transformation on the other
no growth or transformation on the other
person's part not possible it is a new
moment in time is it not yes well then
it is not the same moment it was before
and therefore not the same moment of
frustration but the the the the goal
here is not so goal yeah goal why
goal well if you are making it a goal
for that change then perhaps that is
where some of the frustration comes when
the goal is not achieved quickly enough
according to your expectation of how you
think the change should occur to give
you an indication that the goal is being
achieved you are setting up the terms of
the experiment in this way and setting
them up for failure in a sense I
understand what you're saying all right
simply the idea is that if you are in
the state of
knowingness that you are doing
everything that you know you need to be
doing to maintain your
integrity then every single moment that
they choose to need to continue to feel
frustration are all the moments they
need to make their own realizations
they need to be frustrated then
according to their own understanding of
themselves for an hour for a day for a
week rather than for the split second
that you might think would benefit them
okay let me get very specific well all
right let's say that their judgment and
their resulting frustration create I'll
call it a disharmony which you don't
prefer but understand if you are
centered within yourself you don't
experience it as disharmony you
experience it as their learning process
which to you is a lovely
thing that's the whole point
experiencing the idea as disharmony is
your judgment of it not allowing
yourself to know that you love them for
the experience they have chosen to
create for themselves well that seems to
invalidate the concept of preference why
well because if you prefer one
thing because it is harmonious uh yes
but understand judging anything as
disharmonious then the idea of
preference doesn't seem to if you prefer
Harmony then you don't experience
situations in your life no matter what
type of situation as a disharmony if you
are experiencing it as disharmony you
are preferring
disharmony it is that
simple I see what you're saying that is
all there is to it and it is literal I'm
looking at the idea of consciously
choosing because we're still in the
process can be conscious you do not have
to say we are still in the process you
can know if you really stop and think
about it consciously for a moment that
you do make a conscious decision to be
annoyed by something oh yeah all right
I'm not I'm not contesting that all
right then keep it conscious you know it
is a conscious preference to be annoyed
okay my my point here is that is the
idea of
unconditional love is that you don't
care when it happens for to you it is
never disharmony okay it is always a pleasing
disharmony okay it is always a pleasing
sound so you never notice perhaps even
when it does change because it has
always been Pleasant for you
you
well my Su is that you experience it
sometimes find out what it's like in my
past I have okay understand again you
are making an excuse and saying well if
you were only to experience it you would
know it has more power than you do HW
that's what I'm saying yes it is what
you are saying what I'm saying it is
what you are saying I'm saying that
there is another way to look at this of
course there are many ways to look at it
but that is a choice that would that
would enable us
to create consciously our our harmonious
preference I think you are missing the
point
your choice of attitude about any
situation will determine how you
experience it and to an individual who
is in harmony with themselves and with
the understanding that what occurs in
their life is a part of the overall
Harmony of Creation in that other
individuals are choosing to learn in
their own way even if it includes the
choice of experiencing
frustration that to a harmonious
individual is just as sweet a sound as
any note that is the whole and complete and
note that is the whole and complete and
total
Point how you choose to look at the
situation and how much power you choose
to give over to the choice of believing
that the situation has to be experienced
as disharmony
okay you follow me yes it is all a
choice plain and simple and it is quite
conscious okay I was trying to relate
that to the idea of activity what one
can do rather than just viewing it as a
certain way what can one do well if you
were a harmonious being in that way
create harmonious ideas that may allow
the other individual the opportunity to
then choose to interact with you on that
level if they don't you don't care
because you are already a harmonious
being and understand that the choice
they make to interact harmoniously with
you or not is their choice and that to
you the fact that they can make a choice
is the very stuff of Harmony of course
well if if they don't as you say what do
you do you keep doing what you need to
do as the being you are all
right and live your choices plain and
simple again if you are a harmonious being you
again if you are a harmonious being you
do not care that it takes time you are
enjoying every moment so what do you
care whether they choose to be
harmonious today or 3 years from now you
are always having a good
DME I always am all right then do not be
concerned about someone else in that way
because that is taking responsibility
for them rather than being responsible
to them
thank you thank you I have one more
question one moment guys I I have been
experiencing U recently problems in that
seemed like problems in their head and
yet they didn't seem like problems in
their head and I was told by another
Channel twice that he saw a swelling in
the head and that I should have it
checked did you I had it checked they
checked two different ways and and they
found nothing yes and I um have not felt
Disturbed all right about this but I
thought I would just ask if you had any
suggestions simply in the way of the
idea the swelling can come and go as a
physiological representational idea to
symbolically represent the idea of
expansion of your
Consciousness thank you thank you
bashash you V you okay well Bashar I
have a few questions for you all right
thanks and for yourself um the first
thing is is with um the the issue of
anger uh I have a particular situation
to ask you about I teach fifth grade
which is in our yes yes okay I got 31
Boys in this
CLP one
moment listen to your
reaction listen to your
beliefs I have 31 voice
oh and you sit there and wonder why you
experience the reality that you do my my
my
[Music] uh these boys have a very long school
uh these boys have a very long school
day A N I believe a 9h hour day first 6
hours of thought you had 24 hours in a
day okay um they sit for the first I am
making a
point continue we will talk about it
later yes okay I'm F all right okay so
they sit for about the first 5 hours
studying Jewish religious studies they
have a short break and then they have
all of their quote English studies in a
3our time period yes and um so much
judgment attached to your educational
facility and they they they don't seem
to enjoy staying inside the room and
sitting down they choose let me say they
choose to get out of their seats and
move around during classes now I come to
class prepared to put across a few few
different lessons that are on the
curriculum which I have accepted in uh
I'm infusing the curriculum with more uh
right brain
activi which they enjoy all right
however I'm not able to keep up with the
curriculum because there's so much
activity in this classroom spend a lot
of time talking with them I will use
your term that you are all very familiar
with and I will tell you I appreciate
your dilemma
[Music] and at the same time I am very excited
and at the same time I am very excited
that you are a part of the
transformation of your educational
system for it is not going to stay that
way much longer if you want it
to understand you are simply in the
Middle where you chose to be of the
transformation the process of the change
of your understanding of what education
is all about and simply do what you are
doing do the best you
can thank you very thank
you the more you do the more difference
you will
make and the cleverer you are about it the
and the cleverer you are about it the
more your children will appreciate
[Music] it okay one moment I'd like to move on
it okay one moment I'd like to move on
then we are going over there I'd like to
move on to next thing you've talked
about us becoming our government and
being our government thank um and uh the
first thing is the sharing the second
thing is information the sh rally right
last weekend uh to protest our
government's giving Aid to the cont
suggest not protest protest thank you
suggest suest okay but okay but many of
the people that were at this rally are
following the form that that are
suggests which used to be protests in
the 60s okay with the same format with a lot
60s okay with the same format with a lot
of I understand okay continue so now my
question to you is is it possible and
how to transform that angry energy
frustration that set the frustration
that sets that in a in a sense is a part
of setting up an opposition to what
already exists into a more supportive
peaceloving Force well you are a teacher gather them
Force well you are a teacher gather them
together and teach the idea see how many
are willing to share it with you and
then form a group of individuals that
are willing to do it that way
thanks that's a great idea for
addresses of where to write I have them
tonight oh great and that's all thank
you very much thank you very much guys
my all right
[Music] I have a couple questions all right um
I have a couple questions all right um
the first is I'm working right now on a
story about a situation that's been
propagated supposedly between the hopes
and the Navajo that there's a a segment
of land that the US government wants to
confiscate yes I've been working with
the Hope elders and they they've been
saying that in their prophecies this
piece of land is like a heart portion of
our continent all right and that if it
gets out of balance you know and I I do
know the transformation is part of all
this but if it gets out of balance it
will cause havoc on the continent can
you give me any information on one if
that piece of land is inde the heart in
a sense yes and especially obviously to
them in their
reality and in this way you can
recognize that in a sense it is already
out of balance and that is why as
a nation you experience so many of what
you call heart attacks
but you may also
remind the dear
Hy that they can take heart in the
understanding that what they know about
that idea is indestructible in its Essence
idea is indestructible in its Essence
remind them and in this way allow them
to know that things are proceeding
though they may be bumpy they are
proceeding and there is is the choice
and the opportunity of the Gathering
Together of the ideas and the sharing of
the different cultures it is proceeding
whether it seems to be or not in that
way remind them that they do not have to
adopt the pessimism that is rampant in
the civilization that they see to be the
so-called cause of their
dilemma you follow me right well when I
asked the naho elders they said this
woman said no I don't think they were no
I Su said you don't mean that because
it's horrible somebody needs to say and
I don't that's whatever it is all right
allow me again to Simply suggest that
you look at her squarely in the eyes and
say I thought you were
Navajo yeah talked about too and i'
never thought about this concept but is
forcing them to go to regular school
they losing their language all right but
again at the same time
see what is happening to the regular
schools yes and in this way you are
blending to form one idea it is taking
time but you can if you are willing to
rise above it see the
patterns and not feel like you are
caught within it if you can Rise Above
It transcend all the Judgment it is easy
to see the patterns and where it is
heading well when the help told me that
that they felt that they had preserved
the the old ideals of living because
when the trans as the sort of the
physical destruction occurs on the
planet if that is the way it plays out
that they they know how to live without
as much material as the rest of the
people and they feel that they can share
this so yes I feel it's really an
integral part of the transformation all
right and again allow them to know as
well that there are different types of
Nature and we are not saying that the
idea of what has been created has not
thrown the relationship of your
civilization with nature out of balance
in that way but that simply since you
are a natural being anything you create
in a sense is natural and that it is
their opportunity as well to recognize
that through this
transformation the blending that is
going to occur within all the
civilizations upon your planet is not
going to wind up
exactly being the way they used to be
but the way you will all be together in
a slightly variation of the way they
used to be otherwise it would not be a
change forward okay I have a coule all right I
forward okay I have a coule all right I
have a question recently I did some work
on a concert that you were involved in
and I worked for five or six months with
a group of people and during that
concert some things happen a real
separation occurred between me and in
particular one of the the the women
spoken to each other since and I do
realize part of that separation has been
for my own inner process I needed to
come in for the last few weeks but I'm
wondering what I know I can't really do
anything to change another person's
attitude except for offer unconditional
love but it feels so strange to have
been so close to someone but you are
still close but simply a different
definition of the relationship you are
obviously still very strongly tied
together even if it is through
alienation is there a way to change that
is there a way to change that
alienation I've
tried do your best that is all you are
required to do if you are satisfied that
you have done your best do not take
responsibility for their choice okay and
speaking of that there you know some
other members and I were talking about
the Orion and everything and how worked
and do some quote unquote promotion work
to get you out there and I didn't need
to I mean I did out of love things
there's a group of people here and a
group people there and certain people
over there are making videos and Tes and
people over here and it seems like
there's I mean it seems in a way that
there's a split and there's not a
blending because all these people in
fact it has become competitive in a
sense understand the idea does not have
to be what you call competitive simply
because there are many expressions of it
the idea is that there is Unity through
infinite diversity no I I don't feel the
competition but that's you can also
trust something else yes again if you
are willing to rise above it you can as
we do see the overall patterns and the
reasons for why they are all interacting
in that way and it all fits in don't
worry about it I'm not worried all right
yes it is um can you tell
me where Tera is I spoke to at this time
I cannot perhaps another individual can
for there may be connections that you
need to form through another
individual in this
room we'll leave that up to you to find
out okay thank you very much thank you
and you than you me oh um I would like
to know I mean I've learned a lot you
have answered so much already but me no
you yes me the realizations to set in
and the wisdom um I would like to know
if you have any suggestions to me as far
as
where and if I will find like my home
and I don't know if you have if you can
read me without me speaking it I don't
know that but
um why do you making this so complex I
know it's like do you know what's going
on with me I have no idea do you um um
yeah sometimes and all right but it's
like am I going to get the things I want
I understand I don't know you don't know
are you I hope so why why why do you
hope so uh instead of knowing instead of
knowing that whatever you get will be
exactly the thing you need and not one
extra thing this is true I always take
it from there and say and limit it and
say structure it this is the way it
should be in my mind all right I
understand that I should be are you
having a good time doing that I guess I
am or I would not be doing it oh thank
you very much I understand that thank
you you cannot tell me then or if you
have any suggestions
like nope direction of going inward well
nope direction of going inward well
um but as far as
like inward yes that is where your home is
inward yes that is where your home is
sure okay thank you thank
you you venue B I've had a a pattern
which i' like oh patterns again the idea
that you put stock into the belief of
habit into the belief of pattern that
creates pattern yep that's what I did already
pattern yep that's what I did already
all right however you are not doing it
now right okay then let's look at an
idea all right
um I'm looking at this on a Time stream
I used to have the concept that um are
you going to be clever about this
yes let's see if I can sneak the idea of
patterns in from another
Direction you also said you were not
believing in them now I lied oh
no you did not the you that said you did
not believe in them didn't the you you
are now does it is not the same you so
there was no
lie right when you
realize that there was no lie you will
have your
answer when you realize there was no lie
you will have your answer I got that I
got that thank you now I want to address the
that thank you now I want to address the
idea oh
address proy I have had uh the sixth camera
proy I have had uh the sixth camera
stolen out of my car tonight
yes the the third time I had I I had it
so I prided myself on never having my
car broken into why why is that
something to pride yourself on because
it was a an idea of creating a a safe
space who says it is not still safe
me all right your choice continue
right on the third time I did it I wrote
a book called I want to kill the guy who
broke into my
car oh what probably judge as a [Music]
[Music]
bestseller critical acclaim
in the book I played uh an idea of
of wanting to love the love despite all
reasons one should not against the the
impulse to kill this son of a
[\h__\h] and I found when that when that
was stolen tonight I wanted to know who
it was I wanted to get a hold of him my
my my you certainly are giving yourself
opportunity after opportunity to learn
that you do not have to judge
that's true and it is the Judgment in
and of itself that you are willing to
maintain that allows you to keep
experiencing the same situation but
what doing a great
reflection understand that because you
have prided yourself on the idea that
you have created a safe bubble into
which no one can intrude you yourself
have made it wide open because you are
segregating it and calling
[Music] attention look everybody look at this
attention look everybody look at this
nice safe space it's a secret don't tell
anyone come over here and look at this
safe face look what's
inside boy oh boy is it
safe don't forget to put that on the
news tonight
are you catching my point yeah I caught
it from the beginning oh all right then
in this way when you understand you
cannot be a victim except by your choice
to look at it that way then you will
continue to create spaces which can be
violated when all space is your space no
violation of of it can occur from
outside when you fill all of your space
when there are not bubbles within
it when you don't not have the need for
the security you will not create a
violable space You Follow
space You Follow
Me would agree all right when you
take let us say a vast ocean of
water and you decide that within that
ocean of water you will build a bubble
that keeps the water
out then understand the amount of
pressure pushing in on that thin and
fragile shell and that if there is even
one tiny break the entire thing will
collapse good I understand that concept
thoroughly all right that was not the
concept that was created I created love
and caring and the idea obviously the
idea simply is is that you are exploring
in love of the idea of
victimhood and in this way simply the
idea is if you are willing to look at it
not as a violation but something that is
providing you with a reflection of what
you want to discover about yourself and
the habits that you create yourself to
have then you will let it serve you and
it will not be a
violation many of you miss the point
when you say well I am creating this
situ situation out of love I am
surrounding this idea with love so no
one will violate it but you are
contradicting yourself when you believe
something needs a defense you are
building and designing the
assault you cannot separate the two it
is the polarity one side of the coin
always brings the other side and in the
belief in need of protection you bring
automatically with it the
attack you cannot have an isolated
bubble in that
way that was the concept I was teaching
well many times individuals teach so
they can hear themselves so they can
learn what they are
saying of course all right then live
what you
teach and understand that if you are
teaching that idea and along comes a
situation that has the power to make you
think that something different is going
on other than what you were teaching
then you're not listening to what you're
saying and it is a lesson for you to
understand that if you truly wish to
teach something you had better believe
it therefore it is an opportunity to
integrate and give you the opportunity
to believe what you are
teaching so it has Serv
you okay I still have an Impulse to
punch you in the mouth all right but
that is the picture you are making I
know and this is not my nature it has
not been you do not have a nature how
Bel you have a nature this is a you know
the state what is your
nature loving caring your nature is
existence itself everything else is your
Your Design upon your basic fundamental
nature which is only that you exist that
is your nature good now I understand you
communic okay
duplicate see your
willingness to take what I said to you
as an attack shows how willing you are
to believe in that type of a
reality that I would say something to
you that would accost you knowing the
love that we have shared is an
indication to you that you are more
willing to accept the reality of an
attack than of Simply understanding you
don't need a
defense thank you very much sure for
allowing a loving
reflection pleasure thank you m you are
very welcome indeed Always Forever
Forever
you go ahead you
well um um about talk about anger
again um I was think you I've got myself into
um I was think you I've got myself into
situations to where I've not expressed
it then yes
now now after that has happened guys do
I really need need to is it a judgment
if I think that
that I should have expressed it or in a
sense yes and at the same time you can
simply know that having expressed it in
a loving way simply standing up for the
idea you happen to be would not have
created the need for the opportunity to
allow frustration and judgment to set in
to get to the point where you start
judging yourself for what you should or
should not have
done now if you find that you have
simply had anger had centering found
that you needed to express it and didn't
all right so you get to a later Point
don't judge yourself for having not done
it otherwise you are only compounding
the situation in that way um in that way
situation in that way um in that way
it's not like I need
to Simply understand that if you are
willing to from that point forward
express it understand that that does
mean that I need to that doesn't mean I
have a buildup of anger inside no yeah
right okay because because unless of
course you believe in that idea unless I
believe yeah from a lot of different
schools of thought we're kind of taught
that we have this buildup of anger if
you didn't express it then say if I
chose not to express it last week I was
in a situation and I didn't think it was
appropriate to express my anger um that
I would have this buildup of energy that
I have to all right now look if you are
dealing with that belief system then use
your imagination and if you feel you
have a buildup then say all right right
I will set aside uh 30 seconds tomorrow
and I will set aside all that time 30
seconds to allow all that built up anger
to oh well go through me all right and
then you will stand in your home you
will face a wall face a picture face a
flower face an animal face a crystal
face whatever and you will simply
Express that anger for 30 seconds and
then know all right it's all gone now
that is just a symbol but if that is
what works for you in allowing you to
know that all the so-called builtup
anger is gone then do
it all right yeah um basically a lot lot
of situations I can see to where I
contributed to uh making that happen
where I would be angry have
confrontation with someone else and so
if I just take the Judgment away and I
will be more certainer and express the
way I feel in the future understand that
if you are willing to actually do that
in and of the moment it will not be a
confrontation it will be simply a
statement of your perspective given in a
loving way and there will be no need for
arguing and shouting and all of that you
will simply make a
statement does not have to be a
confrontation you follow
me stating who and what you are is
simply a statement of who and what you
are there is nothing to
confront because you are not trying to
say that whoever you are having the
discussion with is worse or better than
you it is not a
contest you are simply stating who you
are they are stating who they are
whatever you find within those two
statements that you can form as an
interaction that works do it what
doesn't work don't use it where's the
confrontation all right thank
thank you yes within that 10 or 10 15
seconds that natural anger occurs yes
are you speaking of an internal
experience or are you talking about
usually perhaps a verbal explosion no
not an explosion an internal experience
that Rush of wait a minute what is this
where do I stand relative to this idea
okay now I know that's what I've always
interpreted what you're saying
being but there is the verbal explosion
comes from
judgment what if you're able to get what
if you're able to get that verbal
explosion out in the first 10 seconds I
mean it is not so much that we are
saying that whatever occurs whatever
occurs in the first 10 to 15 seconds is
only anger that was my joke uh for my
colleagues here thank
here thank
you not one moment are you through well
not actually I'm trying to um I am
actually creating process
of understanding where the explosion the
verbal explosion comes in but judgment
why do you feel that in this way now I
am not accusing you just I am using the
vernacular you the idea simply that if
you know you are a certain idea and you
know that it it does not matter what
someone else believes then there is no
cause for attempting to force your point
of view forcefully on someone else by
some verbal explosion it just
doesn't compute well it's not a thought
process where you go I think I'm going
to explode verbally but it is a belief
it is a belief it is an indication it is
a barometer of a belief at the moment in
time that it occurs it's a feeling yes
of course but then the IDE is that once
it has happened you can use it as a
barometer to show you that you have
within you a certain belief that you
need to do that to communicate okay then
you work with that idea so let's talk
about that belief what about it I have
just been talking about it the idea that
you think you need to bowl someone over
in order to convince them of the
rightness of your
position rather than simply knowing that
your position is your position their
position is their position and you are
never going to be able to force them to
change their mind anyway and you do not
have to shout at them because you need
to defend your
position so it is the idea of containing
within you the belief of
helplessness again another variation of
victimhood and trying to stand up to
struggle to fight for your right when
you don't have to because who you are is
right enough in that sense just being
who you are you do not have to convince
anyone else and you do not have to
convince yourself that who you are is exactly who
yourself that who you are is exactly who
you need to be that is the only reason
shouting occurs because you feel you
have to convince somebody of something
and it is actually usually
yourself okay well it sounds like what
you within what you've been saying here
is a dep of that belief which creates
out of which we create that OT emotional
response to
explode yes and therefore once you have
exploded it allows you the opportunity
to say well why do I explode I I have a
belief Within Myself I need to explode
why and then you can begin to explore
that the reason perhaps May simply be
that you explode to create such a loud
Ruckus to cover and gloss over the
knowledge that perhaps you don't believe
what you're saying
either I I personally have uh in the
past experienced a lot of that and in
the last old half dozen years or so have
gotten to the point where I do not
explode in that way yes a great great
majority of the time I still do it once
in a while because I still contain it
yes um but in transforming to a position
where I expressed myself in a more
harmonious calm way yes I had not looked
specifically at those beliefs and so
what I'm doing here is understanding why
other people do that and why I do it
myself in those small occasions that I
do so I can understand there well all
right well there may be many specific
reasons within the overall reason right
of course but they all fall within the
umbrella of basically yeah yeah okay
thanks thank you sure
I okay okay first of all I have a title
for tonight all right
equality equality equality all right
okay now I have two things one thing is
um
now the idea of we can be in one reality
at any time and then switch to another
reality and now for instance um if
someone says to to say someone says to
me I'm going to do something and I say
fine I'm going to call you say are you
going to talk about
integrity I guess so you know now if
that per if the phone call isn't made
like the person said does that mean that
well Ely it's my creation okay and
however does that mean that I moved into
a reality where that person never made
that agreement for instance not
necessarily the idea can simply be the
exploration of the maintenance of
Integrity to be true to oneself in that
way and perhaps the individual is simply
not being true to themselves in the
fundamental sense of your interaction
perhaps they are reacting instead of
acting okay my creation of that would be
for my own to look at that in whatever
way I I needed to look at that well
perhaps and again again understand that
many times individuals will allow
another individual to go through their
scenario not that it specifically says
that there is something within you that
is doing the same thing but that you
because you are who you are are willing
to allow them the opportunity to look at
that within
themselves okay um you don't not have to
sit and wonder and say well they didn't
call what's wrong with me why did I
create that I must be a miserable
Creator to have created that when all
along you are to Simply being of service
to allow them to look at a few things
within themselves okay right know which
you will know okay now when you are
within your own Integrity you will know
and when you are being responsible to
people and not for them you will know
okay now what if what if the per what if
someone says I don't remember saying
that I don't remember saying that I
would do that all right now again in the
overall sense it does not matter if that
is what is being played out is their
opportunity to create for themselves
another type of reality in which that
does not exist for themselves
consciously then simply if it is in your
reality that they did say it simply
accept it as such and use it in whatever
way you wish to I guess yeah I'm just
wondering if we can switch to different
realities in way yes it can be done it's
like you know you go say however you
will find that while that is possible to
occur the more Blended you all become
it's not that it will happen without the
Integrity as well okay all
right wait wait no one more thing the
family that the that um I think they
were called BR Braun family or something
last week that disappeared for a few
days and hour oh okay thank thank
you uh John's uh scenario brought up an
idea that do we have power even if
someone's sick and you sort of you're
you're among friends and you do
something like we call a healing Circle
that sort of thing are we giving power
to this person's sickness that we are
putting into the healing
Circle well now this balances a fine
line of
definition in a sense yes in a sense no
the idea first and foremost is that you
know you are giving power to the idea
that they do not have to be sick and at
the same time you are acknowledging that
they have created a sickness which in a
sense reinforces the reality for them
but that is all right do not short
circuit yourself over that dichotomy the
idea simply is is that you are willing
to know you are sharing a reality with
them in which they have created a
disease and at the same time you are
willing to reflect to them that they do
not have to create the disease and that
for now because this is the
transformational time in which you can
experience many different ju depositions
in that way it is all right to
experience this and that and it does not
have to be this or
that all right
one moment you may all take a short
break all right I'll say
Shing you I've had tremendous amount of
tension in my body this last and it's
because I've got so much energy all
right no need to translate excitement
into anxiety allow it to flow it is the
same energy excitement anxiety same
energy allow it to flow
again the idea if I may use the term
remedy for all of those types of
so-called blocks and manifestations of
your accelerated energy is to do
something with it you follow me and if
you find that it is building up in a
certain area then do something that
allows you to utilize that area if you
can find the function specifically in
that way like talking
yes okay chering in that sense
the willingness to express the idea that
you are is the first step into putting
it into action you follow
me yeah then follow through and the
energy will flow through and you will
acclimate to the rate of the vibration
of the energy and it will not be
overwhelming okay all right well how can
I get to sleep at night right sleep when
you are tired when you are not tired do
not sleep no matter what hour it is okay
up and write letters if you wish it is
up to you or do whatever your
imagination tells you is something you
can do all right y have
fun you looking at the idea of
engineering a more unified it is up to
you it does not have to happen all the
time do you perceive that as something
that be effective it will be effective
for those that will make it
effective it is a tool like anything
else you do not have to ask me if it
will be effective if it is effective for
you then this is a perfect example of
what we are talking about at the
beginning of your session if you simply
feel like doing that do it those that
feel like doing it with you will do it
with you those that don't
won't stat um yeah
um I have begun to create a book or a
pamphlet all right
and I think right now I just wanted to
oh thank you very creative and very fun
no oh very good yeah thank you thank
you Bashar Bashar you Bashar could you
explore the concept of original thinking
is there any original yes every moment e
truth is is composed of all
truths the collective way you are doing
it the average of all the ways you are
doing it in your Society is the way you
need to do it what I was getting at are
we upsetting any balance by by so so to
speak playing dice with matter or
playing dice with just just by it
depends on how you mean that in terms of
what you think will become so to speak
unbalanced and what you def as the
original balance as you perceive it no
okay are the experiments that we
in in the right direction in other words
they they had they had very minimal
success they yes minimal
success is that
such maybe I'm not clear with what I'm
trying I
understand but the level of success so
to speak that they had is what has
served them and may
indicate all right to use your
terminology that where you are heading
is not exactly where you may have
thought you were
heading to indicate that maybe some
areas are so to speak dead ends but not really
are so to speak dead ends but not really
but you
understand so that you can guide
yourselves where you have chosen to
be as you make your
choices to define the path you want to
be very much the answer I expected I'm
beginning to answer my questions before
I ask them yes we do not mean to be
nebulous but in this way you are
discussing things that are a matter of
instantaneous choice and only reinforce
themselves as such they are not
descriptions of any reality that exists
apart from you like you are trying to
discover one particular true reality
rather than the ones you think you are
living is such a thing but only as you
create it so because you are creating it
there really isn't such a
thing you follow me
sure and so that is the
reason for why such interactions will or
may seem to be
nebulous okay one more question if you
don't mind that's another question
mind that's another question
but you are familiar with a Mobius strip
yes okay for those who aren't it's a a
threedimensional say piece of paper you
take a half twist put it back together
and the mobious strip now only has one
side and one Edge are
there uh threedimensional analog do you
see dimens to it uh yes you already know
you have a third dimensional analog that
is referred to as a Clin form yes how
about a fourth
dimensional what significant in a
sense to Fourth dimensional
perspective the entire third dimensional
idea is similar or vice
versa it is as if a principle that you
can demonstrate in a model in three
dimensions actually could be utilized to
form a foundation of an entire
Dimension is this making any sense it
sounds to me like it would help us
understand the relationship between
three dimensions and four dimensions if
we could establish that what you are
defining as the mob strip and the Klein
bottle or form in that way are models or
representations of a principle upon
which the idea of the relationship
between third and four density are based
the idea that the inside and the outside
are the same thing that the physical
reality you perceive to be so solid so
separated is actually all a part of the
same surface so to speak and that in
fourth density perspective you see
through the
Illusion in other words if you have a
mobus strip and you have creatures that
exist only upon the surface and you have
this half twist well to the creatures
that exist upon it it's it seems to be a
NeverEnding reality they do not
understand like you do that it is the
half twist that creates the seeming
eternalness of their
situation whereas knowing as you are
viewing it from above that it took the
half twist then in fourth dimensional
perspective you can undo the Twist and
see where the illusion was
created oh that's how oh I see that's
how you look at us yes in a sense yes
that's neat okay thank you thank you
very much
uh you have said a number of times that
a mo represents knowledge in a generally
held concept within your civilization
well is it meaningful to ask where that
civism comes from and why out of your
Collective Mass unconsciousness I have
difficulty sometimes with with symbolism
of that type well that is all right it
is not like you have to know what those
symbols meanly interesting but but I
just why would the collective the mass
Consciousness uh choose a moth is there
any reason for it is not that they chose
the moth it is that they have an idea
and it represents itself in your terms
on that level by the projection of the
animal form Consciousness you call a
moth you are putting in your terms the
cart before the
horse is there um a symbolism for
spiders and Kake snakes of the same type
yes could you tell me what they are the
idea of snake in general there can be
specifics with type of snake in that way
but in general is connected to the idea
of ancient wisdom in the same way that
the ancient symbol of dragon is
connected in that sense spider will be a
subconscious idea let us say
accessibility of information that you
feel is inaccessible to you the idea
also of the tying together of the
connections to everything in what you
represent to be a web being at the
center of it and all the connections in
that way you follow me yeah thank you
thank you you I want to ask you about Howard
you you I want to ask you about Howard
Scott who Howard Scott
he he has been dead now for about 10
years but he originated on this planet a
plan called technocracy many parts of
this plan sound similar to your Society
like no money uh people traveling around
in order to get
education uh everyone contributing
according to their ability their being
in abundance and so forth and so forth
did this being come here to put forth
some portion of this plan to lay a bit
of a foundation to help us with a
concept to help us move into fourth
density put a period at the end of that
and you will have the statement rather
than a question mark oh okay let the
physical reality be an obvious obvious
reflection of what you are perceiving it
to be if it is so obvious why make it a
question if you can see how something
fits into what you are now beginning to
perceive as a pattern why not trust that
it is a part of that pattern instead of
asking if it possibly could be or
not all right you follow me then you
will be expressing the willingness to
know that seeing the pattern in that way
and seeing how those things fit into the
pattern is a representation of the
reality you believe you want to
experience and then you will experience
it as
such you follow
me yes no
maybe yes yes but from myself so that is
all that
counts not in the sense that you ignore
everything else but in the sense that if
you are living that reality then you act
as a reflection to other individuals so
that if they like what they see in you
they can choose to live that reality too
that is how you are being of service to
them okay by having the conviction to
know that if you perceive those things
that is the reality you want live like
it live as if you understand the
patterns you are
seeing all right
sounds
tentative well I think I wondered
whether or not maybe the dissemination
of some of this information might help
some of the rest of the people get more
ideas about how we might live as we move
into fourth density then stop wondering
and do
it by you acting as someone who has
conceived of the idea that that
information can be disseminated and by
disseminating you will become the active principle of
you will become the active principle of
that dissemination and cause that
reality what are you waiting
for well for someone else to do
it no actually my husband put 20 years
of his life into getting this
information out and I free and it and it
was um no matter what form it went out
in it seemed as though it was so far
beyond the reality of people that there
were almost no people that were
interested in participating in it or
understanding or learning about it and
how many people are around you right
now oh about 50 or 60 how many groups
like this exists on your planet at this
time oh probably hundreds and you think
that that does not make a
difference and you think that the
information you have been sharing has
not found it way to some of those
individuals and made the
difference have even the idea in the
reality and whether or not it
disseminates in exactly the way you
think it should along the exact lines
you perceive the dissemination to be
taking place recognize it is still
leaking in and that the existence of all
of these individuals is a reflection of
your willingness to put that information
out there whether they perceive the
literal information or or not does not
matter the effect is the same living the
lifestyle has caused your radiation of
that existence to leak into the society
to provide an opportunity for
individuals to realize and come to
understand that type of information on
their own from their own Direction
whether it had anything at all to do or
not with the specific information you
were disseminating it is all connected this
disseminating it is all connected this
brings me to a point I did wish to
discuss with you T night so how psychic
of you allow me to say it is the idea
that everything you do is connected to
everything else whether or not it
proceeds along the paths or lines you
consciously physically expect it should
or not the sheer doing of the idea is
what makes the difference not the
specifics of the information connected
to the doing it is the essence of the
doing that is what individuals feel and
act upon within themselves you have no
idea how many individuals who never even
met you were
sparked just by unconsciously knowing
that you were doing what you were doing
whether they ever met you or
not but they felt that something was
moving that was an opportunity alive in
the world and they acted on their own
upon their own path in their own way at
their own discretion in their own good
timing with their own information that
is still connected to your willingness
to have put out what you have been
putting out whether they have heard a
word of it literally or not the action
you are doing is what makes the
difference that is why we are stressing
the action because that is what rais
action because that is what rais
mediates beyond the level of the
individuals you physically
reach you follow me
beautiful thank
you yes symbolism yes when a thought or when
yes symbolism yes when a thought or when
a symbol is is
gotten oh okay let me say when a symbol
is before one okay and and he does not
get it yes in the in the time in which
it is sparred
yes has that understanding passed him no
obviously not it is always there for you
to recreate in any way shape and form
that you wish to and you can simply know
that if you know it represents something
you do not have to Rack your brain about
what just get on with your life knowing
that whatever it represents if you need
to know it it will filter in maybe later
you'll be doing something and all of a
sudden it will remind you of that idea
and you will see how the two are
connected making an association that
serves you even further than Simply
Having recognized what it was at the
time but no more symbols will continue
in that light in that vein to to give
you what's they
can simply what we are saying is that
they don't have to continue to be
negative manifestations if you allow
yourself to know that in its own good
time you will understand what any symbol
is created by you for
okay well I didn't I I had no reference
to negative all
right okay that's good enough
thanks you um this brings me to a
question that I came here to ask tonight
I was here two weeks ago and when I got
here I got overwhelmingly tired yes and
I fell asleep in the hallway yes and
while I was
asleep um I I was listening to the Chan
yes and then when I woke up I couldn't
remember it nice and I thought well I'm
really wiped out I better go home so
went home and I couldn't go to sleep so
and I was laying in bed and I thought
well I wish I could remember the chaning
and suddenly I saw this huge Crystal
cluster and it it had it was had greens
and blues and purples and and the colors
were moving in a pattern in very slow
GLE sleeping motion and I thought um and
I saw the Crystal and I
thought oh that's my crystal and I
thought no that's not my crystal
that was the consciousness of the
channeling and I wasn't you know I'm
wondering was that a perception of the
actual consciousness of the Channon that
night or was that a
symbol of
that always in your physical reality you
will create a symbol to represented by
for nothing really has a shape you
follow me yeah unless you give it one
but you were perceive the actual energy
of the consciousness of the
interaction and you have also given a
description in symbolic terms of what
you have asked us many times how do we
see you is that how you see
yes that's it really wonderful we see
you as the
interaction of all the ideas that you
are it was the most I felt better about
that channeling that I mean I felt like
I knew more about it but I didn't know
the words that is perfect good the next
question I have is that then I was over
here at C on Saturday night and he was
channeling and when he started
channeling I did the same thing I
started passing out yes it is not
uncommon many individuals when they
allow themselves to begin to feel their
own energy as they allow it to come out
in the interaction with us or other
consciousnesses or within themselves
will simply know that in a sense they
have a belief within themselves that it
is overwhelming so they go to a place
where it is safe to absorb well let me
tell you what happened after the
channeling on Saturday night all right
after the channeling on Saturday night I
became totally aware of this energy that
I'm generating and that I can like
direct it and it's like a golden and
it's it's gold energy and it's a blue
white energy it's the first time that I
could in my life I've always known I
should be able to do it that I can
actually put it places and direct it
became aware of that during that
channeling while I was asleep yes okay
thank you very much for waking
up are you through yeah thank
you yes I would like to get more
understanding on an experience I guess
my own creation but I don't quite
understand all right share the creation
and you will have understanding um
I've been experiencing a feeling of like
I keep getting to dead ends or I don't
know what I want to do and a lot of
disappointed expectation all right very
good now first of all briefly we have
discussed the idea of what a block is a
block is not a dead end a block is an
unexpected direction that is all and
when you view the unexpected Direction
the signpost that says go left go right
when you do not allow yourself to move
within the unexpected Direction but put
a judgment upon it and the sign post
does not look like a signpost it looks
like a wall and you don't think you can
move because you think you should go
straight ahead through where the wall is
preventing you but understand the wall
is there the sign is there to tell you
that now is the time to move left to
move right and that by doing so by
moving left by moving right you will be
following the flow and that moving left
moving right is the way to actually go
straight ahead only when you judge the sign when
ahead only when you judge the sign when
you judge that it is telling you to go
in an unexpected Direction and you judge
that unexpected direction does the sign
become a wall that you stand in front of
and beat your head against and that is
when it looks like a block a block is a
signpost not a dead end it says turn
here you follow me yeah it only becomes
a block when you judge the unexpected
Direction it tells you to move in as
something that is an interruption in
your path and not a part of it it's true
I did have certain expect
I thought should happen and turned out
quite differently as we have said allow
the physical reality that does happen to
be an obvious reflection of what you
chose to
do of the path you chose to be follow it
trust it this is why we say trust is all
there is yeah right now I'm sort of making it
is yeah right now I'm sort of making it
it seems like I have a choice
um I've been making myself do something
I really didn't want to do which doesn't
seem like um the best growth potential
oh it is a very good growth potential
how so by allowing you to know you don't
prefer it yeah all right then do what you
it yeah all right then do what you
prefer but I don't know what I prefer
nothing at
all how did you decide to come here
tonight I enjoy this communication then
that is how you know what you prefer you
enjoy it why why do there seem to be so
many clouds and because of judgment well
how do you how do you start to change
that by simply as we have said trusting
that what occurs in your life is a part
of the process and not trying to get rid
of it not trying to change it accepting
it as a part of the path accepting it as
the next step not as a misst
step and as soon as you start accepting
that you are making the choice to have
that experience it will transform into
the next step on the path
clearly and your path will become more
Clairvoyant you follow me not quite not
quite where are you going after you
leave here tonight
why M good question this is where do you
have a good
answer do you have a good
answer um no it's just sort of a
predictable pattern predictable
pattern nonsense may I give you a hint
sure repeat after me I am going home I'm
going home because I want
to speak up that's the problem I'm
having I feel like I'm doing a lot of
things um not necessarily because I want
to all right do you want to go
home doesn't look like
it yes or no I guess at some point yes
never mind at some point right now do
you want to go home no all right that
was easy wasn't
it when you want to go home go
home when you don't don't
go where you want
to all
right yes easier said than done your belief
yes easier said than done your belief
your
choice you are making those decisions to
make those areas different than any
other area it is all the same understand
better don't try so
hard you are giving yourself a block by
trying so hard to understand
relax enjoy yourself lighten up on
yourself stop pushing yourself so
hard life is meant to be lived to be
enjoyed not to be
suffered you do not have to make
decisions if you are flowing the
decision the path the direction will be
obvious you do not have to make it a
dichotomy oh this or that this or that
this or that what do I do it is this and
that this and that they are all equal do
anything you
want it will all get you to the same
place it doesn't matter which way you
go that is the
point stop making one path have to be
more important to take than another and
then all paths will look equally good
and then it won't matter which one you
take because you know they all lead to
the same place
you you follow
me it is only by making the
differentiation that there must be some
path that is better than the one I am on
that is giving you the
problem do whatever you
want function within your integrity and
do what you want knowing that you are as
powerful as you need to be to have and
go wherever you wish without needing to
interfere in a sense Force anything upon
anyone else to get there you are
completely
self-empowered go where you
will and when you change your mind go
there all right okay does that make some
sense to
you yeah
yeah
yeah all right let me ask it this way
if you
were to go where you wanted to go at any
given moment are you afraid something
will happen that you won't
like I'm afraid I won't be able to pay
the r that's all pay the
r understand nothing that you consider
to be valid is silly recognize in this
way however that you are giving the
strength to that
scenario now
understand again that if you are willing
to be an idea all the ingredients are
there automatically to allow you to
continue to be that idea if money is
necessary to continue to be that idea it
will be there in the form of providing
you automatically an opportunity that
you can take to get yourself the money
but it will be an obvious opportunity
that is what we are saying you do not
have to force yourself to put yourself
in a position where you have to make a
decision it will be an obvious
opportunity you will say oh well there's
the perfect opportunity I will act on it
and I will have the money if the money
is not there allow that to be an obvious
reflection that you don't need it to be
the idea you want to
be perhaps you do not know perhaps
someone will simply come up and say this
idea you want to
be well it is something that has been
very important to me for very long and I
would like to support you in your
endeavors I'll take care of all your end
don't worry about that how do you know
that can't happen
happen
well you don't do
you speak up right all right be bold now
if you know if it is even remotely
feasible to you that something could
come into your life that you don't
expect that could provide what you need
exactly when you need it then just
simply create the reality that you can
take it for granted that that is the way
your reality will always function you
will become the ecstatic explosion of
coincidence and synchronicity always
finding yourself in exactly the right
place the right time and reacting and
interacting with exactly the individual
you need to be interacting with so that
you can be of service to them and allow
them to be of service to you
so that they can fulfill their
purpose so who's to say you're are
walking down the street you are saying I
must be about this business if I don't
do it this way it won't happen somebody
comes up to you and says say would you
like to join me for a bite to eat no no
no haven't got time must focus on this
idea or it will never come to pass oh
well well if you are so set on it but I
would really enjoy your company well
well well does sound good well well all
right well maybe it can wait for a
minute but only for a little
minute otherwise oh it might get away
from me all right I'll go to lunch but
I'll only have a little bite to eat and
then I'll leave all right well all right
oh by the way now that we are at lunch I
didn't tell you I invited another
friend and you start talking and you
find that you have something in common
what you have been trying to do is
something they want to to find someone
who has been trying to do that so they
can assist them in doing so which will
assist them in doing what they're doing
what a lucky coincidence that you
decided to have lunch instead of going
on about your focused way starving
starving
now many of you in the portions of your
mentality that you have chosen to
believe in somewhere in there say it
isn't that
simple he's just making an analogy he
doesn't really mean life is really that
easy yes I
do and it is I will this time in this
situation only give you my absolute 100%
only give you my absolute 100%
guarantee that that life works that way
when you let
it true no once you do it you will
create the reinforcement that lets you
know it's not a
fluke you follow me and you will then do
it again and again and again and create
a momentum in that
modality rather than the the modality of
reinforcing that things don't
work which is exactly the result you get
when you choose to play the skeptic and
say I Told You So told you that would
never work well you were right weren't
you well good for you I am glad you were
right you follow
me thank you you know Bashar money has
to be one of the best Catalyst for for
growth on this
planet yes that is why you have created
the idea as your medium of
exchange yeah great great but you know
cuz I've experienced like exactly how
you well you know I have I
mean I me explained it to the group
several times you know and then is that
thing of going back and saying that's
[\h__\h] that's not real and then I
create the idea that it isn't real and
then flew back in the pits
right you see what is so surprising to
us many times is that you don't realize
that when you say that isn't real and
you get the reality that reinforces the
seeming unreality of that belief that
you are creating that reinforcement
right exactly
exactly thank you once you get the
momentum of it it's it's really it's
beautiful it is simple do we seem come
iCal to your
people not in a judgmental way
no I got
safe I was not as F judgment in my
question oh Define
comical a source
of amusement and joy yes always
you have never let us
down always leave us
laughing if we were to create the
concept that you call a nightclub on our
planet we would
you every night do you
you you you and 11 others on your planet
are in are do this so-called work of
interacting with us and other with usce
do you then when you're not in that
special chamber communicating with us
when you're in your spaceship with the
rest of the crew or maybe you
communicate with other people on the
planet do you share stories about your
interaction with us oh yes in a sense it
can be done by simply becoming the idea
of the interaction and allowing any
other being who wishes to sense that
idea to Simply glean of the interaction
and then they will know is the result of
that sharing of the idea of the
interaction you have with
us um produce
Amusement yes
okay who would say telling a
joke but not judgmental just yes okay
thank
you then you is that is that the me you
you me okay thanks first of all uh the
scenario that you gave this woman here
was exactly what happened to me today at
lunch so that was good oh what a
coincidence another static explosion of
synchr very EXA okay and um the other
thing is I'd like to ask you again one
more time about Central Amer America um
I've been informed by a woman who is
works for something called the office of
the Americas that the United States
government now has set up some way to
provoke an attack by
sandinistas against American
Military that would be either Contra
American provoked on or around the 14th
of April which would be designed to put
momentum behind the bill to give Contra
Aid on the 15 are you surprised going no
I'm not surprised I'm just asking you um
if you sense that that is going to
happen you have an awareness of that
coming I will say that I sense it is
probable does not mean it is going to it
will depend again upon the degree of
willingness of
individuals who do not participate in
that reality in that way to Simply share
that idea and see if any effect is taken
up by any other individuals uhhuh not in
the sense of being paranoid or
accusatory but simply as an idea without
judgment um I have one more question for
you which is um the 14th
day
is a highly active day as we perceive
it also the
11th
now no structured
predictions no guarantees
however this nuclear
test in your Nevada desert
is beginning to build the same kind of
patterns that you built before what you
call your shuttle
destruction the constant postponements
the technical
failures the coming together of the idea
of Peace in the same
area at the same time there exists
within the same area the incorporated
city that also represents almost
everything that you consider to be polar
to
Harmony
yes your peace Marchers are arriving in
that City at the same time you are
thinking of conducting your nuclear test
which is of a great deal of in your
terms controversy between you and what
you call your Soviet
Union the idea of testing of your
nuclear devices it is all coming in you
or terminology to ahead at the same
place at the same
time there is a
potential for the same kind of effect
that happened in your shuttle accident
yes the probabilities are shifting we
cannot say what direction you will
solidify them
within but pay
attention it is hinging on the the idea
we had discussed of the incident that
can occur to allow each and every one of
you to finally make a decision for
yourselves as to what kind of a reality
you do wish to have upon your
planet we shall see what happens and as
we have said between this time the
fourth day of this month and in that way
the 11th is a high period of activity
and in this way also specifically the
14th has been
added there's a very concentrated period
on that day specifically of many things
not so much just wait and watch but act
as
well this is still an opportunity the
postponements are still an opportunity
for you to create a sharing a
communication with those individuals for
one of the reasons for the postponements
are the sharings of individuals who say
they do not wish that device to be
exploded if you are willing to add your voice to
if you are willing to add your voice to
it perhaps it will not be exploded and
perhaps it will be a step towards the
understanding that it does not have to
be exploded which can be a step towards
the understanding that you do not need a
defense which can be a step towards the
understanding that you are all in this
together all of you it is up to you we
have laid out some of the probability
lines and what we perceive to be the
energy constituents and the equations
and the formulations in your terms the
numbers are clicking and shifting
wildly we cannot see into which slots
they will fall it is up to all of you
who would we write
to there's a list there are three lists
on the table here three different lists
of addresses and names that are
available to you by the tape deck so
anybody that would like that there you
have it and three of us but three
different people brought those things
tonight talk about your synchronicity or
whatever thank you may I ask you one
more question I'd like to know if I was
question I'd like to know if I was
talking to Steve today uh about movies
and if movies would are a creative form
of expression also in the fourth density
or something like them if that's a
necessary or an enjoyable creation can
be why
not I don't know I just wanted to know
if you did it
do you mean our civilization yeah oh
no not so much in that way no there are
projections in a
sense they are not so much of that
nature or
technology but more a mental idea more
the idea of directly projecting into the
Mind mhm the
scenario you follow me mhm thank you
thank you thank you Bashar yeah yes
Bashar thank you we were talking a few
moments ago about Amusement on your
planet last week we talked about
clowning around on your planet right and
I was wondering could you relate to us
something that you on your planet would
find really funny almost anything now
understand it is not so much that we
encapsulate our humor it is not so much
that we have jokes or situations that
are specifically created that are always
taken for granted well that's a joke
that's a funny situation it is not
encapsulated in that way okay things
happen we find them amusing okay perhaps
my question would be more along the
lines of can you give me an example of
something that is happening or if you
want to refer to past that has happened
that you found really
funny what what have described at one
time the idea of the greeting of things
not going as we expected we share that
with you yes was that wildly funny to
you guys it became so do you have any other
guys it became so do you have any other
examples I I like that one
I'm simply the idea first of all before
we go on that there came a time when we
realize that in the greeting well how
are things going and the answer not as I
expected we began to realize that that
was a positive answer that when things
are not going as you expected then you
are utilizing your higher Consciousness
so to us the idea well how are things
going well not as I expected oh
congratulations things are not going as
I expected either oh
wonderful that is an idea that has come
up in that way throughout our
society now another has
been a time specifically as you would
call history when there was gathering
many individuals many portions of our
planet in a sense as you would say
shortly after we recognize that there
were other individuals and other
civilizations with whom we could form a
contact become part of an alliance as
you say an
association there was gathering and
there was in this Gathering presented
the idea of a spherical globe simply
there to represent the idea of a world
in general not that it had any specific
markings on it you follow me yes now in
this way there came all these
individuals and they regarded this globe
as a method by which to describe the
idea of how certain areas of our world could
of how certain areas of our world could
be let us say channeled toward specific
interactions with all of these other
worlds we had discovered we could be in
communication with and
with and
that as we added this idea of forming
let us
say well how would you call
them regions well all right so to speak more
regions well all right so to speak more
like well
clubs clubs to deal with this idea clubs
to deal with that idea regarding our
interaction with the different
worlds and as we formed all of these
clubs then one individual began to say
well well that club is a good idea and
and this club is a good idea and there
are some similarities in that way
between the two clubs maybe we should
form a third Club of the
similarities and then another said well
yes but then there will be many
different clubs with the idea of
similari so there'll be a separate Club
of similar clubs and then we have to
have an interactive Club between the
similar clubs and all the other clubs
out of which the similarities were
formed and well it it did not go on much
longer because everyone started
laughing and simply realized that as we
had already in a sense created ourselves
to be we were one club and that any
differentiations within it it were going
to be
malleable and were going to shift
according to the type of interaction we
would form in any given moment so we
became the club of all
clubs and allowed the membership to
change as it needed to to Define itself
according to the interaction we were
creating with any other world
club now I don't know about
now I don't know about
you but was a good one for
us SL for us too all right
King question I actually did enjoy that very
question I actually did enjoy that very
much that was that was very much fun my
other question is last week you also
said Expect Miracles and I just wanted
to say that your use of the term expect
is not the same use as you say no no
expectation right correct you mean trust
that there will be a miracle yes thank
you thank you B ni um my friend Tim and
myself made a gift for Daryl I wonder if
you can hold it maybe well if you can
Infuse some energy into it for him is
that possible it is
possible it is
done so be it then thank you thank
you you then
you I would um I'd like like to explore
a couple of things that that before you
been brought up one is the idea um of
course of of U of money of course
and oh yes I forgot of course all right
uh the the idea that I like to put out
is the fact that my excuse me what that
was a big joke too I
forgot back kept us going for quite some
[Music] time come I I'm pleased that we're
entertain all right comment on that well
simply in this way when
individuals will find that they attract
themselves to certain
situations and they feel that the
situation is worthwhile for them
understand in that way money is no
object if they find that they feel that
the situation is being presented with
what they perceive to be a lack of
Integrity then money will become
everything and in this way they will not
want to share more of it and in this
sense simply recognize there are
individuals who will in your Society
choose to create
scenarios that will be for one purpose
and say it is for another and there will
be individuals who simply will be doing
a service and will be provided in that
way by the people they are doing the
service for automatically in that sense
there are any number of variations of
that type of
exchange and you can simply recognize
that there are ways to have that
exchange by giving over great sums of
money and there are ways to have that
exchange with no exchange of money at
all and all the different variations in
between now what works for you works for
you if you find simply that the
principles in that way work for you
and in addition the principle of not
turning over the idea of your money in
that way does not work for you then
create a
scenario where you find you have the
ideas without the exchange in that sense
you are always self-empowered to attract
yourself or create the reality in which
you moderate your own level of the
exchange in that way but it is simply
representative of the idea that there is
an exchange now the basic fundament Al
idea for any so-called service in that
way that you desire to give an exchange
in that way of monetary substance for is
simply that it is based upon the
understanding that if you are willing to
give some exchange at all then you have
a vested interest in receiving the
information you will pay attention you
follow me MH but it does not take very
much of your Monetary Exchange in order
for you to feel you have have a vested
interest and individuals who simply
think that it requires Great sums of
that are in that way in a sense going
beyond the original intent of the
exchange itself and simply have an
exchange of the money and not so much of
the original information except of the
information that you are exchanging
great sums of
money is this making some
sense uh I think I had some blocks to
anything that makes sense in this
area well simply
if you
feel that the information in your
estimate is worth something pay it if
you don't don't I
understand if your exchange even needs
to be in money which it does not have to
be mhm you follow me yes simply the
principle of the exchange is
that your attention is in what you want
to learn and you quote unquote get your
money's worth it is simply an exemplification of
worth it is simply an exemplification of
the idea that sometimes not always in
that way but when the specific scenario
is created that way an individual who
goes to get information who is not
willing to form an exchange sometimes
does not get anything out of it as you
say you get what you pay for not meaning
it in the negative sense but if that you
are not willing to invest anything in it
you usually will not allow yourself to
get anything out of it
you follow me mhm but that level is
equal and in that way does not have to
become unbalanced in the sense of saying well
unbalanced in the sense of saying well
this information is worth your entire
life savings in that way now you can believe
savings in that way now you can believe
it is so and you can gladly agree that
it is so and if you trust that at that
moment it is so and you give over your
entire life savings you can understand
also in that way that you are not losing
anything and that if you need that am of
money again you will have it
automatically and probably very quickly
you will never lose anything in that
sense but it is up to you to regulate
how you feel the exchange is then equal
if you think that the idea of someone
saying well it is worth your entire life
savings and you say well no it's not
then to you it is not so don't give your
entire life
savings you follow me say I think well
for me it's oh I don't know it's worth 5
cents here
or it is worth a service well all right
if you are so eager to tell me what you
have to say or if I have attracted you
to tell me in that way well all right I
feel that some exchange is worthwhile
are you interested in knowing what I
have to share now understand that an
individual and this is perhaps where you
are sensing the idea of lack of
Integrity that is requesting from you in
that way is the idea that they are are
not taking from you what you have to
share of your integrity but only what
they think they want from you judg
mentally and that is what you are
sensing you follow me would you repeat
that quick yeah repeat that simply in
this way the scenario that has been
described is that individuals can say
well all right yes I do wish to interact
with you I will give you something and I
do in fact want something from you but
what I want from you is not not what you
have to offer but what I judge you had
better give
me you follow me making themselves and
what they have to give more important
than what you have to give to them as
well does that clarify the idea to some
degree I wanted a little bit of clarity
on was uh when you were speaking to John
about somebody breaking into his his uh
automobile after he put nice white light
in it and thought it was protected uh he
said the idea of of protecting something
was calling attention to it so therefore
it was not protected at all in a sense
it can work that way the idea that you
think you need a defense automatically
creates an attacker that can break
through it okay so if you do not if you
do not um defend in any way it seems to
me that that just gives more opportunity
to more people to take whatever they
they want easier well but it is this
way now this may seem again maybe to you
an oversimplification and again a
paradox but such as life if you don't
own anything you own
everything and nothing can be taken from
you you follow me that was my next
statement it seems like the only way to
protect what you have is to not have
anything but understand again
paradoxically if you don't own own
anything you own everything and you will
have exactly what you need to have and
it cannot be taken from you ever if you
are willing to own it with an open
hand because you are not protecting it
in that sense you do not need to protect
something that you know is there to
serve you at a specific time and no
longer for understand that when
something needs to be with you to serve
you nothing can take it from you and
when something takes it from you so to
speak you don't need
it you follow me that is the idea the
Paradox of the
situation if something can be taken from
you you don't need it you are giving
it for someone else to use
not willingly it doesn't you create the
Judgment that makes it seem so
understand again the Paradox is truly
that if an individual let us say in your
terms is utilizing this camera and to
them it is simply a temporary tool that
they are using for a certain form of
expression at that time and if that tool
needs to be with that person always it
always will be
it always will be if they simply know
that as long as it is with them that
represents the time it needs to be with
them then they will know that there may
come a time when they won't need it any
longer and so they will not care beyond
that time if it is not with them any
longer that attitude is what
paradoxically will allow that object to
be utilize lies
forever because they will not be putting
the attachment on it that says you have
to stay here you must stay exactly in
the same shape and form and situation
and relationship to me forever that you
are in now well your higher self says
change is the only constant and if you
are going to force me to force you to
face change all right
camera in the
car take it so that you will reflect to
them that on another level they know
change is what allows them to know that
they are always abundant in different
definitions of the
term so you can have an abundance of
poverty as well as an abundance of money
as long as you view them to be equal
then then
then is when you will always be able to
choose the positive manifestation rather
than the negative but feeling that oh
well if I'm not careful I could become
broke I need to protect my assets
protect them because they might leave
and then I will be broke you are saying
that being monetarily AB abundant is
better than being abundant in any other
way and you make the difference you make
the differentiation that calls attention
differentiation that calls attention
that something in your life is being
created to be unequal to everything else
so everything is going to attract itself
to that to allow it to regain its equal
status understand that when individuals
Place themselves in your terminology in
your Society at the the bottom of the
barrel so to speak then all directions
are up everything looks equally
good you follow me that is the idea it
is you simply know that if you need to
feel you have to protect something then
you don't truly believe you own
it and that is what is being
reflected that's very good how often do
you think give a second thought to
something you take it for granted is
yours never but by bringing attention oh well
never but by bringing attention oh well
I better start protecting at you are
saying to the universe you don't believe
you own it so the universe
says away it goes very obedient Universe
you have created I I don't usually think
about protecting things I just assume
everything's going to stay with me if
it's with me beine and when somebody
else comes in and takes things away then
I feel very violated then you are
playing the game of victimhood that they
had no right to come and take something
that was there understand we are not
sanctioning that they are not
functioning within their own Integrity
for it is also their Duty when you
attract someone to play victim with for
them to say no
thanks I will not be the perpetrator
that reinforces your willingness to be a
victim that is their role to play they
do not have to be the perpetrator we are
not sanctioning that they do this with
are simply letting you know that because
there are individuals who are willing to
be
powerless in that way and be your puppet
to act as the perpetrator to reinforce
your victimhood you are also responsible for
victimhood you are also responsible for
co-creating that Reality by attracting
them to begin
with by your belief that they
can exist in your reality
that you do have things that can be
taken from
you you follow me yeah well I turned I
turned it into a after replacing the
18th window in my car um I decided not
to get another stereo right and I've
used that time uh on the freeway and
going to and from uh for silent Pursuits
all right thoughts and things I do miss
listening to your tapes and listen to
music occasionally but I decided not to
provide the universe with another stereo
now understanding this way the idea is
that you can have as many stereos As You
Wish if you allow the idea for why they
are being taken to serve its purpose so
that you can know that the purpose can
be served in another
fashion and simply the purpose that is
being served is to allow you to look at
the scenario that you are creating
victimhood for yourself you do not have
to
now that you are beginning to recognize
that you do in fact own
everything and if you believe that then
you can have 50 billion stereos in your
car and they will not be touched because
you know simply that they are there to
serve a purpose and it does not matter
whether they are there or not they are
there serving a purpose if they do not
serve a purpose for you any longer you
would want them there
anyway you follow me true what
surrounding yourself with with white
light and protection of calling
attention to you in a sense it can
understand there is a very in your
Society subtle difference between simply
knowing that you are the idea of white
light and all it represents and feeling
that you need it for protection there is
a difference okay no I do it just
because it feels good and all right I
like that idea fine then it is not a
protective idea
no okay one just one one more thing U
very re recently within the last six
week or so I've been having an awful lot
of dreams about animals and I've never
dreamed about animals before I've had
elephants and Kangaroos and giraffes as
you become more fourth density you will
understand that animal Consciousness has
been created to be a reflective guide
upon your planet in this way and you are
now becoming more in communication with
that portion of the subconscious
unconscious Mass Consciousness that is
represented to you as animal life forms
they are extensions of your own
Consciousness in many ways and act as
loving Reflections and guides for you in
many symbolic Fashions you are now
simply coming into communicative
Consciousness with that level of your
own godhood excellent even the two owls that
godhood excellent even the two owls that
moved into my yard talking to each other
I would think that would be an obvious
symbol I like that what owl
symbolize the wise old
owl how about
H
keenness Clarity of insight elep now you
already know you ascribed the idea of
memory to
them they are
in history in a
sense the idea of the embodiment in that
way of that which is the foundations
upon which you are built the shess the
strength and the gentility of
strength you follow me
W wolves in this way are not dissimilar
to your Society in many ways they are
their own Society
the idea of coyotes are the idea of what
you have created to be the Renegades in
your
Society spaceship is an animal of a
different color
color
that if you wish you take it that way
and and and birds well there are many
different ideas again we have discuss
the idea of the owl the hawk the
hummingbird representing the higher
Consciousness The Accelerated r
at which you are moving in that
way now butterflies in that sense
represent the idea to you of
metamorphosis what about
a ran across that this weekend struck me
did you feel the
strength within them the strength within
yourself no actually it showed me a fear
all right
that can be
strong but in this way understand that
many of what you call the wild Predators
represent all the different structures
you have created to be your unconscious
fears recognize as we have said that the
reason that animal life on your world is
territorial is because you
are on our world it is not
territorial you follow me what about
to some degree they are very in your
terms magical beings they are bridg
Stones through archetypal
mythologies now they
now they
also by way of their environment provide
symbolism not only for you but also for
the dolphins that was my next question
dolphins that was my next question
dolphin
what about
horses horses in that way are
represented in what you call your
mythology as a new way a greater
service carrying you through life in
that sense they are similar to the idea
of what you call your dog being of
service in that way and recognize that
in that sense what you call in your
American Indian culture they recognize
the connection immediately upon
discovering in your terms the horse for
in their term what they call dog and
being of service in that way
symbolically was in their term
shanka and they named the horse shanka
wakan greater
dog dolphin is not exactly an animal as
you call it it is water
human you share common souls in that
sense now how about Cat fourth
dimensional transformation the cat
exists in third and fourth density
equally we will at this time extend to
you your ability to know that you exist
on all those levels as well and to begin
to pursue communication with all the
different forms of the Consciousness
with which you have surrounded
yourselves and with which you Embrace
yourselves lovingly the animals they do love you
lovingly the animals they do love you
unconditionally for they are willing at
a moment's notice to reflect exactly
what you
contain allow yourself the freedom of
interaction with them in that way and
allow yourself to
Marvel at the love that you share
between you we will once again extend our
you we will once again extend our
appreciation for the interaction with
you that you Beque unto us as a gift of
unconditional love we extend our unconditional love
love we extend our unconditional love
and our perception of your
acceleration as dream beings upon your
planet to continue the
sharing that exists in the Eternal now
moment forever we thank each and every one of
forever we thank each and every one of
you individually and collectively
action to you all and to all a good
night how' everything go wonderful thank
you very much darl
thank you for being here tonight
everyone thank you I don't want to what
about