All right, I'll say how are you all this
dream time?
>> Are you all alive this evening?
>> Thank you.
>> Absolutely. Every moment always. Thank
you. Recognize therefore that as we
recognize this to be your occasion that
you would call one of your holy days, so
to speak. We will thus discuss and share
with you many ideas and notions about
different perspectives and perceptions
of what the timing of this event can
reflect to you in your society in your
consciousness and can reflect to you
about your society and your
consciousness. Before we begin with that
idea, before we begin with sharing,
however, we will remind each and every
one of you that this will be the fourth
as you say installment of the awakening
idea we have been sharing with you for
the past three of your weeks of time.
We will therefore once again with you
concurrently share the technique we have
termed the awakening so that each and
every one of you may participate and
know that with your participation
you will be assisting yourselves and
other individuals in forming a type of
energy alignment that will allow you to
know that each and every one of you
individually and therefore certainly all
of you together do have an effect and an
impact upon the rest of your
civilization. Not, of course, against
anyone's will, but only within those
segments of your population that are
willing to receive from you the energy
of the gift you will be sending to them
and to yourselves. For individuals who
may not have participated these last
three weeks of your time, do not worry.
Anyone who has allowed themselves to
come into this interaction at any point
always arrives at the perfectly
appointed time for the energy that they
already know themselves to be and will
through no accident bring into this
participation the appropriately required
energy for the continuation of this
idea. No one needs to feel left out in
any way, shape or form. And everyone may
simply be willing to participate in
whatever form your imagination says is
comfortable for you. There will be no
right way and no wrong way to perform
this technique. Your way will be the
correct way. Trust and rely upon your
instincts and your imagination to guide
you in this endeavor. What we will be
suggesting to you, what we will be
suggesting as a visualization, as the
imaginational pictures you will be imaging in this
pictures you will be imaging in this
technique, in this exercise as you are
fond of calling them, will simply be
suggestive lines.
your imagination, anything you have ever
conceived of. When we say 33,
cut the image dead. Do not let it fade
out. Absolutely cut it. Go to whatever
image you need to or absolute blackness
if that is necessary to allow you to
simply cut the image. We will assist you
by providing suggestive scenarios that
can then take the place of the image of
the radiant light that you have held for
the previous 33 seconds. But again, if
you find your mind holding on, do not
worry. Simply take it for granted that
you know what you are doing and that you
will release the energy in the
appropriate manner to allow all
individuals upon your planet to
participate and partake of this energy
and to have an effect and make a
difference. You all follow along so far?
Yes. >> Are you all ready?
>> Are you all ready?
>> Yes.
>> Then by all means, in whatever way,
shape, or form you are comfortable with,
relax. >> And take three deep breaths.
You can be sitting, you can be standing,
you can imagine yourself anywhere,
anytime. Whatever is most relaxing for you, use
Whatever is most relaxing for you, use
that as your tool. You are your own
master tool. You know what you are
doing. Blend with all the levels of your
consciousness, what you may consider to
be your physical self, your higher self,
other aspects and guides that are here
to assist you. You have all the power
you need to make all of the changes in
your life that you desire without having
to hurt anyone else or yourselves in
order to create them. Glow and revel in
this ecstasy.
Begin to build the idea of the orange
emotional light within your being
and prepare to share this
unconditionally loving essence with every single form of
loving essence with every single form of
expressive light and consciousness upon
your planet
beginning now. 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11
12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24
25 26 27 28 29 9 30 31 32 33 Cut icy
blue fragments of crystallin snow
falling upon soft fields of green grass
verdant and rich in splendor and nature.
Smell the earth. Feel the coolness of
the wetness of the stones and allow
yourself to drift.
Allow yourself to feel the afterglow of
the orange emotionality within you like
a burning ember.
Allow it to make you warm, secure.
Allow that same feeling to permeate
every individual
upon your planet.
Three deep and loving breaths. [Music]
And as you take these breaths and align
yourself to the next vibratory level,
begin to imagine this crystallin blue
energy. This blue energy is the
electromagnetic and atheromagnetic
atmosphere around your planet in which
all of your mentalities are immersed and
through which all of your mentalities
communicate telepathically on whatever
level you are willing to accept that
idea. You are in constant communication,
constantly in touch with every being
upon your planet through the medium of
this ethermagnetic fluid, if you will.
And in that sense, it is much like
water. And as we have said, every motion
you make within this field, within this
fluid causes ripples that are felt by
everyone and everything,
even though many of them may not be
consciously aware of this idea. They are
aware of these ripples on whatever level
they need to be.
You can now send out a ripple
in this electromagnetic in this
etheragnetic fluid that lets everyone
know it is all right to let themselves
bring this information they are
receiving on unconscious and
subconscious levels to their conscious
awareness. It is all right to believe
that you can create the realities you
desire and that nothing is too easy or
too good to be true.
All can be created.
Allow yourselves now to prepare to send
these loving, cool, vibrant
excitations of energy rippling out and
intersecting with every other being upon
your planet. Beginning now.
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16
17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24 25 26 27 28 28
29 30 31 32 33 Cut space cold stars
brilliant sparkling gems embedded in
black velvet
drift. See the earth below you see it bathe in
See the earth below you see it bathe in
blue radiance
now as you allow yourself to gently
Gently fall towards the earth. Gently
float down like a flake of snow, like an
down like a flake of snow, like an
autumn leaf,
blown by the gentle winds of infinite
creation towards the brilliant blue
beautiful earth upon which you live.
Allow yourself to sense the brilliant
crystallin potential,
the massive and beautiful crystal that
the earth itself is shining like a gem
against the black velvet of space. Allow yourself
Allow yourself
to begin to sense an identical resonance
within you. A brilliance, a blinding
light that somehow you can still
tolerate to look at. For it is an
infinitely loving light.
And you feel it to permeate every cell,
every molecule, every atom, every
thought, every idea.
It is what supports you. It is what
creates you.
And it is ecstasy itself.
It is what you are made of. Ecstasy
itself.
As you thus now prepare
to shout for joy with every fiber of
your being, every fiber of your
consciousness, you will realize that
this shout on all levels. Even though it
may not be heard auditorially,
will be felt within every fiber of every
being upon the planet.
They will experience this ecstatic shout
as a flash of incandescent white light
for way at whatever level that means to
you. Always there is the opportunity for
blending, reflecting and sharing that
you represent by the Christmas time in
your lives.
In this way, give yourselves the
opportunity to receive the gift of the
Christ consciousness from the Christ
consciousness in whatever form you
choose to represent it. For it itself,
the Christ consciousness does not care
what you call it. It recognizes itself
to be the combined experiences of all
and each and every one of you
collectively and individually.
It loves you all unconditionally in
whatever form you choose to relate to
your own spark of divinity. Even at the
times you choose to not relate, it still
loves you unconditionally. For that is
simply the nature of the idea of the
integrated being that it is.
You all follow along?
>> Yes.
>> You are that spark.
You are a mirror which has that spark
reflected in the very fiber of your
essence. Shine forth
Shine forth
blaze brilliantly. Illuminate yourselves
and your world will be enlightened by
the light that shines from the center of
each and every one of you.
We thank you sharing
Not all at once.
>> You then you
>> Hey, speak up. Do share.
>> Time for giving gifts.
>> Give your gift so that all may unwrap
and discover for themselves their own
unique version of the gift they will
create in the wrappings you have
originated to share.
>> Yes. Well, I I have been creating um an
experience with another person which
wasn't bringing us much happiness. So,
we decided to um
to stop co-creating our experience for a
while. >> Understand that you are always going to
>> Understand that you are always going to
be co-creating an experience no matter
in what form or definition you transform
that experience. Once a relationship has
been created, it always continues. It
may continue in different forms but it
continues forever nonetheless.
>> Yes. Um we it seemed that the kind of
interaction that that we were creating
was it felt like it was a
self-destructive kind of cycle.
>> Paul, right? Were you allowing the
relationship to be what it was created
for or were you creating it to be what
you thought it should be?
Well, that was um that I'm not sure
about because I'm not sure what
>> what did you learn from it? What have
you learned about yourself from the
interaction you have had with that
individual? What have you learned in a
positive way? What have you gotten out
of it?
>> That's that's what I'm trying. That's
what I am not sure about.
>> Yes, you are.
>> You are simply not willing to look.
>> Okay, I'm looking.
>> Do not fear. You will always be able to
discover that anything you find out in
any situation will always be able to
apply to you in a positive way. There is
no need to fear that you will discover
something that will destroy you. You are
indestructible. >> Okay. Well, okay. I guess my fear was
>> Okay. Well, okay. I guess my fear was
that I was recapitulating an old
experience where
um where some things seemed to not go
well in terms of becoming passive and um
um sort of into an inertia, a state of
inertia. >> Were you giving your power away?
>> Were you giving your power away?
Um no but I felt very drained and
>> then you were giving your power away.
>> You cannot be drained if you do not give
your power away. Not that you can really
ever give your power away truly but you
can create the illusion that you are
giving your power away and that is what
drains you.
>> Right?
>> When you are centered and self-empowered
you can never be tired ever.
>> Yes. So, so that's sort of my question
to myself is how how how is this why is
this happening?
>> But that's the price that comes with
being responsible.
>> Why?
That is simply what is ingrained within
you. You believe therefore that if you
can do away with responsibility for a
while, well maybe someone else will take
care of me and I don't have to struggle
for a while. I don't have to suffer for
a while. Someone else can carry the
weight for a while. cure
when you understand that true acceptance
of total responsibility involves no
effort. As a matter of fact, it involves
great ease and joy of freedom of
expression. You will jump at the chance
to be responsible for every single
little thing. You may even want to be
responsible for something someone else
did. You'll be so overjoyed at taking
responsibility. Although that you cannot
do, you always have just enough in your life
you always have just enough in your life
to be responsible completely for and it
will always be fulfilling
and not draining.
When you choose to understand that full
responsibility is an enlightening
process, not a depleting or burdening process.
not a depleting or burdening process.
Your society still thinks that
responsibility is a burden and not a
joy. Therefore, you create relationships in
Therefore, you create relationships in
which you seek to always give your
responsibility over. And then because
that's what you are, you attract a
relationship to reflect that to you and
they are trying to give their
responsibility to you.
So, you're sitting there bouncing your
responsibilities off of each other, not
taking your own responsibilities and not
fully enjoying any other aspects of each
other because you are sitting there
bouncing something off of a mirror back
to yourself.
It cannot be gotten rid of. There is
nowhere to get rid of anything too.
Anytime you try to throw something away
to get rid of it as if it didn't belong
in your life, it is only going to hit
the mirror and bounce right back.
Everything is only a reflection in that
way. >> So where does the feeling of being
>> So where does the feeling of being
drained, how does that come into this
giving away of responsibility
and and also the the thing of
attachment? It seemed like the
attachment allow allowed this process to
happen. If if I wasn't attached, then I
was free and I was being responsible.
It was just hard to maintain that
It is very tiring
to constantly attempt
to throw away a piece of yourself.
When you throw away or attempt to throw
away a piece of yourself,
then you are not whole. And when you are
not whole, you do not have all the
energy that is available to you. And so
you get tired.
When you accept all portions of
yourself, then you rely on the energy of
the totality of your being.
Then you always find that you are able
to be supported infinitely.
Do you follow me?
The attachment to the other individual
is the attachment that you form to
attract into your life someone who would
reflect to you what you were doing. What
you were doing in giving away your
power. When you believe you are incomplete and
When you believe you are incomplete and
need a relationship in order to be
complete, you will generally only
attract in your life an incomplete
relationship to reflect your belief in
your own incompleteness.
When you know you are complete and take
full responsibility for the idea that
you are,
then you will attract a like reflection
and you will be able to share as equals.
You will be sharing but not giving
anything away. Thus, you will
>> since you're not consciously aware of
what it is that you are doing. It gives
you an opportunity many times to put
yourself in a state of rest so that you
have more than enough time to
contemplate the ideas you are changing
into rather than rushing around being too
rather than rushing around being too
busy to listen to yourself.
>> Well, I asked for a dream when I first
was coming down with this about why I
was creating this. And um
>> what did you get? I got that I used to
live in this small white wooden house
and this house and about four others had
this house and about four others had
been um condemned and that there were
toxic fumes in this house.
>> Oh, what?
>> And I went back again and I discovered
that the lady next door had moved back
into her house.
>> Nice.
>> And I decided, well, if she can move
back into her house, then I can move
back into my house.
>> Oh, what?
And >> well, I asked a man if I could move back
>> well, I asked a man if I could move back
and he said yes if you thoroughly air it
out. And uh then I realized I couldn't
remember the address and I woke up.
>> It's all right. The address is right
here. You are the address.
You are the address.
>> You are the house.
You are airing yourself out so that when
you move back in it will be slightly a
different house on a different level in
a different reality. May look like the
same street may appear to be the same
address. It won't be. It is simply a
metaphor for your own transition,
for your own being, your own body as a
house. You are airing it out. You are
maybe perhaps finding that the idea of
your diet may be changing or will soon
so that you will release the idea of
what previously would have been
considered toxins to you. So that you
will know you do not have to breathe
these ideas, eat these ideas, live these
ideas any longer. They will no longer
affect you in that way. You will have
created your own atmosphere, brought it
with you. That is what you will breathe
in the new house regardless of what was
there before. You carry your own
atmosphere with you. What you breathe is
the idea that you are.
>> You follow me.
>> Yes. Thank you. I like that. Um I was
also thinking about this idea about the
bad air that um right before I developed
this cold, I went and I had an interview
with the head hunter for um a job. And
when I went and she is on this 14th
floor of this high-rise building and I
went up there and the air inside this
building seemed very dry and very stale
compared to the air outside
>> and I was wondering if it was unhealthy
to breathe the air in this building.
>> Depends upon the belief system.
>> Well,
>> the majority of individuals may find
that it will give them some let us say
respiratory dilemma in time but it will
depend upon the belief system. There are
individuals in that building that will
not be affected at all simply because
that is not their reality and they are
not breathing that air. They are
breathing the idea that they are being.
>> Yeah, I understand that. What I was
thinking that it was is that it was like
an expression of my feelings about um
having a job.
>> Is that a question?
Okay, that's what I thought that it was
that um
>> it can be representative that you do not
feel comfortable in working in such an
environment that may represent a job in
that format to you that you do not have
to cubicleize yourself, limit yourself,
rigidize yourself and cloister yourself
away in a sterile environment in order
to produce the things that will support
you in life. You are now aligning more
with the idea of nature, that you are a
natural being, and that you can rely on
support from all of the aspects of
nature, and that you can be unbounded,
unlimited, free to move about, be very
much more constructive and creative in
many more ways other than simply a very
narrow corridor.
You follow me?
>> Yes. I like that idea a lot. And I'm not
quite creating that idea that cuz I was
thinking, well, I'm not really excited
about the idea of not having a job. And
the idea of having
>> depends on how you define job.
>> Mhm. Well, maybe that's part of
>> to do what excites you the most can
become your job.
Many of you simply do not allow yourself
to do what excites you the most because
you do not believe that this idea can
support you in life. But understand many
of the things you nowadays consider to
be jobs that everyone can do, well,
somebody had to start it. It didn't
always exist in the form it exists upon
your planet, there had to be one
individual that had that vision that
said, "Well, let's do this." Everyone
else may have said, "But that's not a
job." But the individual said, "Well, it
can become one."
You follow me? Maybe you can start
something new. Who knows? But the idea
is to recognize that in whatever way it
takes, your natural creator will support
you in the endeavor of following what
excites you the most. In whatever way
you need to be supported to allow you to
continue to do the thing that represents
the truest form of you that you are
being. Because all ideas come complete
with all the ingredients necessary to
allow you to continue to be that idea.
Nature once again does not do extraneous
and pointless things and you would not
have the ability to have a conception if
along with that conception did not come
all the ingredients necessary for the
manifestation of that conception. The
conception brings with itself
automatically on the other side of the
coin all the necessary tools for the
manifestation of that conception. The
universe does not separate. Your society
separates your beliefs separate. But
anytime nature tosses you one side of a
coin, the other side always comes with
it. You don't have to search for it. All
you have to do is flip it around. There
it is.
All the tools necessary to have the
complete coin.
And then when you know it is complete
and that both sides come all at once,
the concept and the ability to manifest
the concept,
then you will have the whole coin and
you will be abundant.
>> You follow me?
>> Yes.
>> Does that assist you?
>> I know. Yes. that I know what excites me
and it's the idea of metaphysics and
channeling which I can't do yet because
>> who says
>> I do because I have these um beliefs
that I'm still um allowing to transform
right now
>> but understand anytime you are doing
anything you truly love to do you are
channeling >> well I'm doing you know within my belief
>> well I'm doing you know within my belief
structure what it is that I believe that
I want to do and I haven't been
supporting myself so I've decided that I
want to do something different
>> all right it is up to you
>> like have a job.
>> It is up to you.
>> But it may only be a further opportunity
for you to truly get in touch with how
strong your beliefs are on the subject.
>> Maybe is another opportunity for you to
truly, as you say, get a handle on what
it is to trust unconditionally
that you will be supported in what truly
excites you the most if you are willing
to go into it 100%. The only reason that
you may not be seeing the support that
you think should be there is because you
yourself are not willing to truly be
that idea 100%.
But you will be completely supported
100% in whatever idea you are being.
Even if being that 100% idea is being
30% that and 70% this.
But if you are only being 30% the thing
that you really would like to be, then
nature will only be able to support you
in that thing, 30%. And 70% of the
support will still go towards the thing
you say you really don't want to do.
Therefore, that's where most of the
support will have to come from until you
decide that 100% can go toward the thing
you truly want to do. Then nature will
be able to support you 100% in that
endeavor as well. But only when you
determine that you have the trust and
the faith to do that thing 100%. But
that's up to you. and not doing it 100%
yet is absolutely no failure on your
part. You are learning what you need to
learn at the rate you need to learn it.
That is perfect for the being you are
being and you are doing everything just
fine. We believe in you even if you
choose not to.
>> Thank you. You're really sweet.
>> So are you.
>> Thank you for a little taste of your
sweetness. >> Sharing
>> Sharing
>> you the new
>> Sure. I just wanted to share with you
this evening um that I met the Gerald
vibration that we spoke of a while back.
>> All right.
>> And his name happens to be Larry.
>> Well well.
>> Yes.
>> You are having a good time.
>> I am. Aren't I though? Yeah. Something
I'd look forward to for the last four
years. >> My my.
>> My my.
>> And you and I have talked about many
times. >> Yes.
>> Yes.
>> And it is a future reality that is now.
>> Yay. And it's opened me up to
being in the now moment for Christmas,
but knowing uh that the future realities
that uh I'm going into are all opening
up
>> and they are all right here right now.
>> Yes.
>> Well, thank you very much. As you say,
merry Christmas.
>> Thank you. Merry Christmas to you.
>> Hey.
>> Uh yes. I've been exploring uh the ideas
of giving and receiving and how these
two can kind of interlap and
but I can see in my own life that I tend
to prefer sometimes one over the other
such as I may like to give more at times
because I feel well this is a bit more
freeing and that if I were to receive
well it may be misunderstood at times
and so forth.
>> Depends on how you look at it. One of
the greatest gifts you can give is to
allow someone to give to you because
then you will allow them to exercise
their ability to share.
It takes an understanding of balance to
allow yourself to recognize that it is
all right to receive when it is allowing
another individual to learn how to give
as well. You follow me?
>> Yes, I do. So if you are willing to
relax into that idea that this will
always come in a balanced form then
there is no need to focus or concentrate
on well what am I doing now how am I
doing this and teetering back and forth
on this very thin edge. Allow yourself
to relax into the perfect momentum of
the whole idea wherein one side or the
other will be there in the perfect
timing it needs to be there to
automatically balance the other side if
the other side is approaching an
imbalanced state.
>> Okay. It's the imbalanced state I think
which concern me. But I think as you
said before uh if I were to project the
idea of a self-sufficient uh free person
>> Yes.
>> Uh
>> then you will find yourself receiving
when you need to and giving when you
need to.
>> That would just simply take care of
itself. >> Absolutely. Automatically.
>> Absolutely. Automatically.
>> There's no need for any further uh
>> not really
>> juggling of that.
>> No. Relax.
>> Concern for imbalance
focuses on imbalance and keeps you off
balance. Relax. If you know that you are loving
Relax. If you know that you are loving
as best as you can, then you also know
that you deserve love.
Allow the love to come to you. Allow
yourself to share that love and all will
balance itself out because love is
balance and all the details will take
care of themselves automatically.
All right.
>> Okay.
>> Well, thank you very much. Love to you
>> when uh we did the beginning of the
meditation uh the white vibration.
>> Yes.
>> The words that you were saying or the
symbols or the ideas. I was curious uh
what they represented and the one that
really rang my bell was the power
numbers and I was wondering if you could
elaborate on those.
>> We simply transliterated the vibrations
of your first eight numbers into their
representational matrices
matrices
in terms of your collective
consciousness. One being the primary.
Two being the polarity. Three the triad
the polarity with the fulcrum balance in
between. Four the quadrant the way you
typically think of your physiological
world. Five the number of humanity and
the way it expresses itself in your
human being. Five extensions, five races
and so forth. Five senses in that sense.
Six being the number of technology so to
speak. Seven the awareness of all the
different levels of your consciousness.
and ate the primary octave. Bringing
yourself in a sense back to one,
the first octave, the first level.
>> You follow me?
>> Yes. Thank you.
>> Thank you very much.
>> Yay.
>> You said
>> speak up.
>> You said this was 33 seconds, but you
seem to be counting much faster than
ours our seconds. Within the idea that
we are cocreating
the 33 seconds will be relevant to the
experience whether it is relevant to
your outside sense of time.
It will be an emotional 33 seconds. You
follow me?
>> Mhm.
>> Time is flexible, malleable. It is only
what you make it to be anyway. It is
your illusion
within the experience. It was the
necessary 33 seconds. All that was
necessary to invoke the idea that you
were creating. Whether it bore any
resemblance exactly precisely to your
formerly analytically calculated timed
out 33 seconds or not is not the point.
You follow me? It was emotionally close
enough for you to simply recognize that
you were creating fluctuations
emotionally which will create
fluctuations in the time space field
that you generate as your reality
illusion. You are going to find much of
this flexibility occurring in your lives
anyway. Again, as we have said, you
already know that when you are having
fun, as you say, time flies. But it is
more than that. It is not that you are
simply having so good a time you ignore
the passage of time. It is that when you
are focused completely in the now in
that way in the now present moment you
actually do not create as much of an
experience as time. And what may seem
like 33 seconds to you may turn out to
everyone else to actually have been an
hour. And
And
>> say that one again.
>> What may seem to be 33 seconds to you at
times. Let me put it in this way as you
say in pragmatic terms. know that when
you are doing something you really enjoy
doing, many times several hours of your
time will have gone by. And to you,
well, maybe you thought, oh, if I had to
guess, I'd say, oh, maybe 15 minutes,
maybe half an hour at the most has gone
by. You follow me?
>> Understand? You for yourself literally
only created 1/ half hour of
experiential time. You literally only
aged 1 half hour to everyone else's
three. >> You follow me?
>> You follow me?
>> Mhm. That is why the more you begin to
enjoy in the moment what your life is
and live in the now, you will become
more and more ageless.
That is why your lifespans are
increasing because you're learning how
to live more in the moment and are not
creating the experience as much as you
used to of linear time.
>> You follow me?
>> Yes.
>> Does that assist you?
>> Yes. Thank you.
>> Yes, sir.
you then you think
>> we experience aside from some really
unusual dreams some body changes and
shifts. >> Oh, absolutely. Since you now begin to
>> Oh, absolutely. Since you now begin to
realize that the non-physical dream and
the physical dream, what you call
physical reality are much all the same,
all the changes going on in the
non-physical world will begin to make
themselves felt in the physical world
because you now know that the physical
world is only what you imagine it to be.
So of course body changes will occur to
become synchronistically harmonious with
the arrangement or rearrangement we
shall say of the blueprint of yourself
that you are now redesigning in the
dream state.
>> The binary code.
You can use the binary idea as a way to
represent perhaps a methodology by which
the non-physical information translates
through your physical mentality into
physical reality. It is a method of
processing the information. But let us
say in and of itself except on one level
though it may be the same thing in and
of itself for your terms it is not
exactly the actual energy change itself. It is
the actual energy change itself. It is
your representation of how you are
translating the non-physical dream
reality into the physical reality
through what you consider to be the
neuronic pathways of your physical brain
which in many senses do operate in a
binary format.
>> Eventually that will coexist on both
physical and
physical and non-physical reality will
be almost completely homogeneous by the
time you are nearing the end of the
fourth density state as it almost is for
us now as we approach our fifth density
transformational state to us physical
reality and non-physical reality I will
use your terminologies are very
difficult to tell apart
we are living in our dreams
as you are beginning to learn to do
>> is that also like being living on the
fourth dimension or is that something
different? >> The fourth density is the last level we
>> The fourth density is the last level we
shall say wherein you can experience
still the idea of a physical version and
a non-physical version of that idea. The
fourth density is the transformational
gateway the connection point between
physical and non-physical reality. That
is why third density is primarily
physical and fifth density is not
physical at all. Fourth density then is
quasi physical, quasi planer. And this
is why fourth density will be the
ground, the learning ground, the arena
in which you will fully manifest the
realization that physical reality is
simply what you dream it to be.
>> You follow me?
>> Yeah.
>> Well, thank you. Have a wonderful time.
Happy changes.
>> Yes, it is. Yes.
>> Uh living in the moment.
>> Yes. That is what we are all doing right
now. >> It allows for a complete spontaneity.
>> It allows for a complete spontaneity.
>> Yes.
>> Where does continuity fit into all this?
>> Where you wish it to.
>> What is the difference between
continuity and expectations?
>> Ah, thank you. Sometimes not too much.
Expectations can be your ingrained
belief systems that can create the
illusion of continuity. When you are a
non-physical being, let us say
colloquially speaking in between your
physical lives. For now, we will speak
that way. Or when you are a non-physical
consciousness, you will not experience
continuity in that way. All your lives
will be available to you to experience
so to speak or to view all at once.
And you will find that in many cases the
so-called order in which you have
experienced your physical lives is not
necessarily the so-called order in which
you chose to live them. In other words,
you now in what you consider to be your
contemporary physical life may find that
after you have this life, oh let us say
you decide now to have a life oh as you
say in 11 BC.
Now you will choose to create that life
and you will create the appropriate past
to go with that life. The past will
create itself to fit into the niche that
it needs to fit into in order from the
physical point of view to make it seem
as if that life came before this one
because that's what the definition of
this reality is linear time in that
format. But it is all quite arbitrary.
You follow me?
>> Continuity then is a belief system.
>> That's it.
Thank you.
>> Does that explain it for you?
>> Yes.
>> You are learning even in the fourth
density physical reality how to alter
your sense of continuity. You will find
physical objects beginning to lose their
solidity. From time to time,
circumstances and situations and what
you call memories beginning to shift
around. Many times you will find
individuals will express one of the
typical fourth density symptoms. Did I
dream that or live that?
Which came first? Is it precognitive?
Did I have a dream and then live it? Did
I live it and then have the dream? I do
not know which came first.
>> You follow me?
>> Yes.
>> These are all symptoms of going into a
fourth density reality wherein you are
beginning to realize that you are living
your own dream.
When you do not need the tool of
continuity anymore, you will dispense
with it. But you will dispense with it
at a rate that still allows you to
comfortably exist within whatever
reality you are choosing to exist. You
follow me?
>> Yes.
>> So do not worry. Things will not become
more confusing than you can handle. You
are simply learning step by step the art
of disillusionment.
>> All right.
>> Yes.
>> Thank you very much sharing
>> for sure. memory.
>> You
>> Thank you. Um could you please explain
the phenomena? I don't know if it's
called precognition, but I've or on
multiple occasions have experienced um
a reality that once certain phenomena
occurred that totally duplicated a
situation that it became to my
consciousness that I had dreamt it maybe
several weeks before or a month before.
>> There are many ways to approach this
idea. One of the simplest understandings
of this phenomena, as you say, is to
simply recognize that everything you
experience in physical reality, you have
quote unquote worked out in dream
reality first. Dream reality is the
blueprint for everything in your
physical life.
You follow me? Everything you have lived
in physical life has been experienced to
some degree in your dream life first.
Yes. >> Sometimes when a high degree of
>> Sometimes when a high degree of
coordinative or synchronistic energy is
behind a certain idea, then you will
have a flashover phenomena and you will
remember the simultaneous event of
having created it in the dream reality
as a blueprint and created it in
physical reality as an experience.
In those moments of recognition, you as
the non-physical you that created the
blueprint and you as the physical you
that is having the experience are
literally one and the same you.
You are on the threshold of infinite
eternal now present time. When you have
those experiences you are more
completely now on all levels
simultaneous with all other aspects of
yourself. You have in those moments for
an instant dispensed with continuity.
>> It is well I have two other questions.
Is there a way is there a way to develop
it? And the other thing is
>> there are many ways. Use your
imagination and rely upon the literature
that exists that describes ways in which
other individuals have explored this
idea for themselves.
>> Thank you.
>> Your imagination being completely tuned
to the vibratory energy of your being
will always be able to provide you with
whatever technique will work best for
you. Well, when it does happen, I I have a
Well, when it does happen, I I have a
momentary well, a little bit longer than
a momentary feeling of illness.
>> It is only disorientation
since you still rely heavily on your
senses to orient you in physical
reality. When you become discontinuous
for a moment, you are simply again
disoriented, disillusioned,
unlocked. You are in limbo, floating, no
footing so to speak. You follow me?
>> Yes, I do.
>> Your equilibrium physically is
momentarily suspended. That is what
causes the feeling of illness. It is
simply a habitual way of thinking of
yourself. You will get used to it in
much the same way that your astronauts
get used to the idea to some degree of
weightlessness. You follow me?
You follow me?
>> Yes. Thank you. Can you refer me to a
particular what book I could read or
would you refer to some literature? Did
you have something in particular in
mind? There are individuals who are
present with you this night of your time
who have access to many different
recommendations of literature. In that
sense, any literature that involves the
idea perhaps of what you might colloally
refer to as either out-of- body
projection or the idea of the
fundamentals of dreaming might assist
you. >> Thank you very much.
>> Thank you very much.
>> Thank you.
>> One moment.
The idea of what it is you may find
yourself forgetting
in terms of your memory patterns in
going into the fourth density state will
generally be representative of the idea
that going into a fourth density state
is the process so to speak of becoming
an individual who lives in the present
who will then in that present know all
they need to know at the moment they
need to know it to be whatever they are
being at that present moment and won't
have to rely so much on memories of the
past. So you may find many individuals
So you may find many individuals
forgetting the past in order to allow
themselves to simply know what they need
to know in the present moment to be
whatever they are being. Specifically,
those memories may be ones that many of
you may find yourselves being out of
touch with. Do not worry, you're not
going scenile.
>> Okay. Thanks.
>> Thank you, guys.
>> I've been creating an abundance of ants
in my house.
first in the kitchen and then in my
bedroom and now they're in the bathroom.
>> All right.
>> And they seem to detour around my
roommate and come straight to me.
>> And
>> are they that much in love with you?
>> Yes, they seem to just really love me.
And I'm wondering how that I'm serving
myself by creating all of these ants.
>> Well, perhaps you should ask them.
>> Well, I don't like killing the them. And
>> I did not say you had to.
>> I asked them to stay outside and they
haven't um cooperated.
>> Oh, making demands upon them.
Well, I told them if you stay in the
house, you're going to get um raided and
that'll be fine.
>> I'm sure they will understand that.
>> Understand that what we are suggesting
to you is that you ask them what they
are doing there. Obviously, they must
have a reason. You have obviously not
taken the time to find out what it is.
You have only said do this or else.
All right, ants. I'll talk to you. Get
out there. That's all the conversation
I'm going to spare on you. Ask them what
they are doing there. Ask them what they
are delivering to you as a message. Then
when you allow them to deliver the
message, they won't have any reason to
stay there. Then they will leave. But
until you accept the message, they will
keep coming. Go into your meditations.
Identify with the if you will antness
within you since you contain all
reflections of all nature.
Talk to that portion of yourself and
realize that you are communicating with
them by identifying
as them. As them become as them. Let
them talk to you in their own language
on that level. Receive the message. Ask
them what they have brought you.
When you receive the message, then they
can go on their way.
All right.
>> Yes. What I thought the message was is
that um a feeling of being overwhelmed
like with negative anticipation.
>> Oh,
>> but there I like that one.
>> All right. Very creative.
>> But they might be one aspect. All right.
Then understand perhaps you have not
gotten the whole message.
>> Allow yourself to go back into the
meditative state. Relax. Keep receiving.
For if you have learned that from them,
think of what other wonderful gems you
can learn from them. Maybe in time you
will actually, as you say, anticipate
their arrival.
>> All right.
>> Okay.
>> Co-exist.
Everything blends for a reason. Nothing
is ever ever ever
out of place.
Understand? >> Yes.
>> Yes.
>> Thank you.
>> You then you
>> uh the the
>> speak up. Speak up. Speak up.
>> The term bliss.
>> Bliss
>> is that what is happening when a person
is in that state?
>> They are completely living in the
moment. >> Oh, good. Okay.
>> Oh, good. Okay.
>> Oh, thank you. Bliss to you. Yes.
Yes.
>> Oh, the shark.
>> Um, yes.
>> Do you sense beings that are living
in the middle earth or inside of the
earth? Do you believe
>> that idea does exist, but they do not
exist in your dimensional plane?
>> Right.
>> They are not in your terms physically
there, but they do exist.
>> All right. Uh what is there
like elementals and fairies and
>> that is a slightly different idea
although some of the idea can blend with
those other consciousnesses that you
would colloally refer to as those that
reside inside the idea of your planet.
What you more often call elementals in
that way are reflections are
projections. Not that they do not have
their own consciousness of a type, but
they are mostly projections of the let
us say archetypal substream of the
subconsciousness of your entire mass
civilization communicating with a portion of itself
communicating with a portion of itself
with you perhaps and forming itself into
an identification you can relate to to
some degree but still coming with it
will be a format that will still let you
know it is not exactly precisely on the
same wavelength as your physical
reality. ity. It is a part of the
subconsciousness of the entire
civilization speaking with you. You
follow me?
>> Yes.
>> That is what elementals basically are.
Does that assist you?
>> Yes, it does.
>> Anything else?
>> Like fairies and gnomes are they in a
separate category?
>> They are variations of that theme.
Again, some of them can also be
composite consciousness or let us say
intersections of various thought projections of
of various thought projections of
different consciousnesses
using the electromagnetic energy of your
world to materialize
a an appropriate form with which to
communicate with the denisens of your
frequency. The form will be representative in
The form will be representative in
essence of the idea that they are in
emotional essence. Not that the original
consciousness actually physically looks
like what you are recognizing as a fairy
as you say. You follow me? But it will
materialize in your world in the form
that will evoke the emotional reaction
that will let you know what the essence
of that consciousness is all about.
You follow me?
>> Yes. I Are they Well, I've just gotten a
a feeling of communication on, you know,
on another level. Yes.
>> With beings of that type and I've felt
them. >> Um,
>> Um,
>> where do you find yourself drawn?
Is there a specific local you wish to
visit to enhance these communications?
>> Yes.
>> Where?
>> Griffith Park.
>> Have a good time.
Well, that's just that's one place, but
it's just that the pollution of the
earth, the pollution that man has been
um
>> we understand, but that does not have to
be in your reality. And you can do much
in the assistance of altering that in
the reality of everyone by not creating
it in yours.
>> That's what I'm I'm trying to do. But
>> you are what?
>> That's what I'm trying to do.
>> You are what?
>> You are trying to do
>> I am doing
>> Thank you.
I felt that they were trying to tell me.
>> They are not trying anymore.
>> They were telling me
>> they are giving you something to relate
to, something to identify with so that
you can utilize those particular aspects
of your own consciousness in the most
simple and easy ways to create that type
of loving ecstatic reality for yourself.
You are finding the reflections in the
mass consciousness, in the
subconsciousness archetypal substream,
if you will, that will do you the best
service that you need to see of yourself
that will allow you to relate most
closely to those aspects of yourself
that will allow you to create that type
of a reality for yourself. You are
seeing once again mirror reflection. Do
not forget whether you are interacting
with other consciousness or not, what
you are going to perceive in physical
reality is always going to be your own
version of that consciousness because
you create utterly your own perceptual
reality physically.
>> You follow me?
>> Yes. No. Maybe.
>> Uh maybe.
>> You create your own reality. You create
all the perceptions of reality that you
perceive with your senses.
You for example are not directly
perceiving the actual body of the
physical channel that we are using. You
are perceiving your self-created version
of that body. You follow me?
>> Yes.
>> Same thing with the idea of the
elementals. They are touching chords
within you on another level.
These notes that are being played within
your consciousness will evoke the shapes
you see with your senses. You follow me?
>> Yes.
>> They will be the shapes that are most
representative of the portions of your
consciousness you need to be in touch
with to give you the feeling you need to
be in touch with to create the reality
you prefer.
>> Would that be similar with um
archangels? >> Yes, to some degree. Yes.
>> Yes, to some degree. Yes.
>> Thank you.
>> No. Fine. you very very very much.
>> Question.
>> Yay.
>> Um, does that have anything to do with
uh things like uh negative entities?
>> It can from time to time
>> for whatever vibration you believe in
most strongly will be the other forms of
consciousness you identify with most
strongly and therefore you will attract
yourselves to each other. Like attracts
like. When you choose to understand that
you no longer have to believe in that
vibration as the most overwhelming
vibration that permeates your life, then
you are not able from that point to
attract them into your life and they are
not able to find you because you are of
different frequency.
>> Um
a negative entity as a as a not as a
person on the plane that I'm talking
about. >> We understand what you are saying. It
>> We understand what you are saying. It
goes across the board for anything
whether they are physically on your
planet or from some other dimensional
aspect. Whatever vibration you believe
in or fear in the strongest will be the
reality you attract.
>> What purpose?
>> Perhaps to get you to realize that
that's not the reality you prefer.
It
>> is up to you. Can be for any purpose you
have co-created.
Primarily, you will find at this time
that it will be for the fundamental
purpose of getting individuals on your
planet to realize that you do in fact
create your reality from what you
believe it to be. And that is the same
thing as saying that whatever you fear
to be the most likely reality you will
experience is the reality you will
experience. So if you don't prefer that
reality any longer, get in touch with
the fact that your vibrations are
attracting your experiences to you. If
you don't prefer them, redefine the
vibrations and recognize that when you
redefine the vibrations, when you act as
the idea you prefer to act like, then
that will be the vibration you will
radiate. And that is all you will ever
attract in life on any level, physically
or non-physically.
Nothing else will be able to interact
with you if it is not of the same
frequency you are on.
>> I see. I think I understand.
>> Nice. It is simple physics, simple
mechanics. Keep it simple.
>> Okay. One more question.
>> All right. Um do you do you find that uh
people tend to dream the same dreams?
>> Sometimes when they identify with each
other and attract themselves once again
through their vibrations to each other,
they can have similar experiences and
interact with each other on many
different levels of experience.
Sometimes they may remember this
physically when they awaken into the
physical dream and recall it as the form
of having had the so-called same dream.
>> I see. Thank you.
>> Thank you very much. You may all enjoy a
short break.
>> Can I be the next person then, please?
>> Yes. After the break, you may commence.
By all means.
Um, my basic understanding of most
mediumships to begin with is that
they're the product of an arrangement or
a an agreement that is made prior to the
physical life between the person that's
going to become the channel and the
being or the consciousness that is going
to be channeled. Your life then when
you're born into it as far as I
understand takes on whatever aspects it
needs to take on whatever occurrences
have to happen in the life uh to get you
to remember that agreement occur in the
life whether you're conscious of it or
not and um then at the time when the
time comes for you to remember that you
are given the opportunity to you know
fulfill that agreement or not. But for
me the biggest kickover point happened
about on two different occasions within the
on two different occasions within the
span of the same week with four friends
present with me the first time and two
friends present with me the second time
we had very close broad daylight
sightings of Bashar spacecraft here over
Los Angeles uh very solid very close and
there was no doubt in anyone's mind that
was with me as to what we were seeing
what I didn't understand at that point
and what I do understand now is that
those physical sightings were his way of
kicking me in the subconscious memory to
start learning what I needed to learn to
do this idea with him. So as the years
went by and I started doing more
research into metaphysical ideas, I
learned eventually what mediumship was
all about. I read books on it along with
many other subjects and eventually I was
introduced to several mediums and one of
the entities coming through one of those
mediums offered to teach mediumship to
whoever was interested. There were
several people that were interested at
the time. Even then, when I took him up
on the offer,
I um didn't think that it was
necessarily going to lead to what I'm
doing now. I just thought, well, this is
great. I've exhausted most of the books
I could find. Maybe in this class
situation, I'll learn something new.
I'll see it in action. I'll see
somebody, you know, learning how to
become a medium, not thinking that it
was going to be me or that I was going
to be one of them. When I was in that
class and under a receptive state, under
the guidance of that entity is when
Bashar and his people made the
connection. However, and as soon as they
made the mental connection, the memory
of having made the agreement came back.
Who they were, who I was to them, what
the ship sighting was all about. Dream
encounters I had had with them that I
had totally blocked up to that point,
all came back in that one memory. And
the first message that came along with
it was, "Okay, now you have the
opportunity to start doing this as you
agreed to do it if you still want to."
And obviously I said yes. And that was
about 3 and 1/2 years ago. And I've been
doing it since then.
Um now they uh you know have represented
themselves as an extraterrestrial
civilization. In my dreams I have
perceived and in the trance I also from
time to time have perceived that they
they do have a representative physical
form even though they're learning I
think their way out of it as probably we
will eventually. Um but they still do to
present themselves to some degree as a
physical being. They are mostly
telepathic in their civilization. Bashar
is not his name per se. It's a it's a
term that he chose out of one of our
earth languages to represent um his
identity basically. Now I have I had it
was funny this evening uh somebody came
up to me during the break and who had
some familiarity with Arabic. My uh half
of my my ethnic background is Arabic and
I didn't even know what the word was
when Bashar chose it to represent his
name. It is an Arabic word. But one
person had told me and a couple of
sources had told me that one variation
of the term Bashar in Arabic actually
means commander. What was interesting is
this person um came up to me tonight who
was a little more familiar with the
language and also said that in Arabic El
Bashar actually means human being. So
that's something I didn't even know at
this point. So he also there's al
obviously a multi-level connotation you
know to what it is that he chose to
represent himself and um you know even I
am still learning about all the
different reasons for why a lot of this
is going on but that's uh sort of in a
nutshell a recap of how this happened
for me and and basically speaking the
idea is not so much that that I think
that uh anyone has to necessarily
channel in this way but the idea that
they're helping us to remember is that
we all do channel in our own ways and
that you know Bashar has said many times
that he knows he's doing his job best
when we really don't need him anymore or
when we can really interact or begin to
interact with him as an equal and when
their civilizations can blend with ours.
Um so anyway um at the request and
there's there's the recap of sort of how
it happened and everyone's path is
different and if any of you are you know
feeling like you're moving in this
direction then uh have a great time
cuz I know I have even though there's
been a lot of things to learn about and
and sometimes some moments that were
touch and go you know with regard to
whether I'm going off my nut or not but
uh I'll just uh say that you know I have
one thing I have learned is that the
more I have trusted it, the more
beneficial it has become and the easier
it has been for me to see um I guess you
would say positive feedback in my life
that constantly reinforces that that the
path I'm on or the track I'm on or the
way I'm presenting it is the way I need
to do it at least for me for now
regardless of you know what anyone else
gets out of it. So, I um would like to
hope that you all continue to have a
good time and at this point because just
in case anyone takes off early, I would
like to uh thank you all for being here
for the amount of time that you have and
wish you all a very merry Christmas and
happy new year.
>> Merry Christmas to you.
>> D was the ships that you saw, were they
the triangular?
>> They were the equilateral triangles
about about 40 ft in on a side and about
8 ft thick.
>> Yeah. uh when you as Daryl want to
communicate with when you're in a trance
then >> I have my communication with him when
>> I have my communication with him when
I'm in the trance
>> separately from whatever he's doing with
you see that's why I don't remember so
much of the conversations that we have
in terms of you talking to him the
dialogues don't really register for me
the experience is like being lost in a
daydream it's very over
>> what they could do to make their
relationship better.
better.
>> Now, first of all,
does this individual, this friend,
does this individual
feel that there is something that the
other individual should say?
>> Yes, I think so. what
>> um sharing uh what is occurring on the
business cycles and also being
interested in what's going on at home
with her and with their children.
>> All right. Does this individual feel
that this situation
allows her to begin to become aware of
other aspects of her own consciousness
that she may not have realized are there
and that she can begin to pursue on her
own right
>> because she needs to look for other
things if she cannot find it in him
within herself.
I find that the conversations we've had
because of this has bought out these
aspects in various things and I think
she's beginning to be aware of that too.
She's had conversations with you
concerning aspects of herself that are
developing and expanding and uh coming
to force. She's a person that had had
intense um uh migraine-l like headaches
when she was uh beginning to and that
just before big events would happen and
you had told her that as she began to
open up and
>> sensitive to the electromagnetic field.
>> Right. Recognize also that the
individual you may call her husband in
that way in the relationship may also be
reflecting from his point of view that
there is a fear within him that the
sharing of certain information
will be let us say perhaps overstressed
overanalyzed or demands will be made
upon him for things he does not perhaps
feel he can deliver if he shares much of
this information. This is an opportunity
for both of them to realize that
openness and honesty and communication
will alleviate any so-called
self-created problems rather than
complicate them. But at the same time,
it is an opportunity for the friend to
recognize that there are many forms of
communication and there is much support
in silence at times.
>> You follow me?
>> Yeah, I do. In this way therefore it can
be an opportunity for that individual to
support the other individual
unconditionally in the way they are
choosing to be for they can function as
a reflection for each other in that way.
She can support him to allow him to know
that she will not
let us say twist the ideas into
something he does not feel he can live
up to. In a sense creating within him a
need to guard himself for fear that
there might be portions of himself that
he is letting get out of hand that he is
not in control of. You follow me?
>> I do.
>> He knows he can do this in the
relationship because they are close in
that way and he is in a sense
unconsciously relying upon her to
recognize that at this point he may have
a need to experience this fear so that
he can come to terms with himself that
there really is no need to feel that
anyone really can take anything away
from you including the idea of
controlling your life or that you are
somehow enslaved or that he is somehow
enslaved to someone else and that he
only lives for someone else and not for
himself. You follow me? I do.
>> In this way, at the same time, it will
allow the friend to get a handle on
certain ideas that she can also pursue
to replace certain ideas, so to speak.
not utterly replace them so that she
will no longer experience these ideas
from him, but at least for herself
create her own versions of the things
she thinks she needs to learn from him
so that she can learn some of these
things on her own from herself by
herself in her own avenue in her own
point of view without relying upon him
to supply her with some sort of stable
foundation she cannot discover within
herself. >> You follow me?
>> You follow me?
>> I do.
>> It is an opportunity for both of them to
use perhaps in that way. There are many
more levels and many more facets. This
is very intertwined in many different
ways which we cannot go into completely
right now. Allow her to rely upon her
own higher self in her dream state and
ask for assistance and guidance from
those that are there to assist her and
rely upon her own imagination in her
relaxed period of our being at that
moment. And it does not have to come
through the idea of the compilation of a
series of discrete discontinuous
compilations of study or remembrance. It
does not have to be a collection of
memories that creates knowledge. You are
understanding that from the point of
view of making knowledge a collection of
memories. Well, things perhaps can get a
little weighty from time to time if you
have to carry all those memories around
in order to know anything you need to
know at any given moment. But if you are
willing to simply recognize that the
baggage so to speak is always with you
when you need it that it is more in the
form of let us say a device you have
used in your society many times that you
may refer to as a magic bag that really
while you carry it around is quite empty
but when you reach into it for the thing
you need that is what you pull out.
You follow me?
Therefore in that context it need not
weigh anything. Knowledge can be looked
at as the potential to know what you
need to know when you need to know it.
And it does not have to contain anything
at all until the moment you need it.
>> You follow me?
>> Yes.
>> Also, I want to say um merry Christmas
in that way.
>> From you. Merry Christmas in this way. you
>> venue
>> venue.
>> Um u about a year and 3 months ago, we
talked about uh the possibility of me
having an experience when I was about
seven and having an exchange with uh
ETSs for lack of a better
>> longer word. Um
and that within 3 months or certainly
within this year I would remember that
lost time.
>> Nice.
>> And and I have yet to do so. I realize
we have a week to go.
>> Anything can happen.
Now do recognize first of all that you
have had some recollection in dream form
but you have disguised it according to
things that make sense to you according
to the things you are working through in
your physical life.
You simply have not recognized some of
the communication for what it is. But
you will awaken into that as well. Also,
the environment
towards what you call the end of the
year that you will be placing yourself
into will have a lot to do with opening
up some of those doorways even though it
may be within the last as you say 2 or 3
days of your year.
>> You follow me?
>> Okay. All right.
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you very much. Simply allow
yourself to understand the things that
come to you in dreams in a different
way. They will begin to be a little more
apparently different when you place
yourself in what you call the Hawaiian
environment. And the last time you were
there, you in a sense set the stage for
what it is you will make a connection to
this time.
>> Oh, okay. All right. Understand that
even though it may seem certain changes
may wait as you say till the very last
moment, it is always the precisely
perfect moment. And it does not really
matter how much time preceded the
change. We know that to your eyes many
times it may seem that well the longer
it takes to get to that point, the less
likely it seems that that change will
ever come. However, understand it only
takes a moment for that change to occur.
So when it does occur, it won't matter
how much time it took to get there.
Things will still be different.
And you will not relate to the time it
took anymore.
>> Every moment is zero.
Every moment is zero.
Zero. Zero.
Zero.
You follow me.
>> Mhm.
>> Pleasant bream.
>> Thank you.
>> Sashar.
Um, recently I have become very aware
that there is a new well new 2 or 3
years old influence in my life that I
that I am attracted to and that is to um
a homosexual men and I've never um well
I wouldn't say never but it does seem to
be a new focus for me.
>> Nice. And I'm wondering if
>> as you are now beginning to blend with
the idea of your own masculinity and
femininity within yourself and allow the
marriage of the masculine principle and
the feminine principles to take place
with equaleness within you. You can be
of assistance to individuals to allow
them to blend the ideas within
themselves in that way so that they no
longer necessarily not that it is right
or wrong but need to manifest the idea
of an imbalance in one direction or
another. therefore recognize even though
someone may not be in your terms
homosexual, they can still reflect an
imbalance. And this is what your society
has basically done for many thousands of
years is reflected the imbalance and not
been willing to understand that each and
every individual does contain the
potential of the balance of the
masculine and the feminine principles.
It is a denial of that equality within
the self that has created the need for
the tool of homosexuality because those
individuals were willing to reflect in
no uncertain terms to the mainstream of
society that each and every individual
regardless of their physical properties
contained masculine andor feminine
principles completely diametrically
opposed to what their physical
reputation was. The mainstream of your
society still did not get the picture
and still to this day bequeaths the idea
of judgments and invalidations upon
those individuals which then taking
those judgments to heart have created
the idea of many of the diseases they
are now experiencing in the idea of your
society. But these diseases in that way
are still a reflection of the
opportunity that your society has to now
in being forced to drop its barriers of
immunity to new ideas now must face the
idea of the blending of the male and
female principles within each and every
individual. They must now force
themselves to be open to these ideas and
that is what they are doing. You can be
as you are beginning to learn to
identify with these individuals. Of
great assistance to them in learning
with them how to blend your own aspects
further and teaching them by seeing in
you this reflection of the blending, how
to blend their masculine and feminine
aspects in a more balanced state. So
that they will understand that when all
individuals marry those two aspects
within themselves equally, both what you
call the homosexual society and both
what you call the heterosexual society,
learn to balance these ideas within
themselves equally, then there will be
no need of any form of disease in your
society whatsoever. And you will find
once again, not that it is right or
wrong, that there will also probably
most likely not be any more
homosexuality in your society simply
because it will no longer be necessary
as a tool. Because the society when they
choose to be born as either a male or a
female will still as a male or a female
exhibit the emotionally androgynous
properties of the balance of both while
still expressing themselves
fundamentally physically in the form
they consciously chose to be born in.
>> You follow me?
>> Yes, I certainly do. You can be of great
reflective assistance in aiding these
individuals to balance this idea and so
allow themselves to balance across the
board by recapitulating many of the
different experiences that many of them
have of all of you has had the idea of
male and female lives alternating back
and forth many different times. Allow
them to know they contain both. And when
they can allow themselves to be both
simultaneously, then they will allow
themselves, not make themselves, not
force themselves, not take themselves,
allow themselves to go back to the zero
rest balance point.
In which definition, no imbalance can
exist? >> All right.
>> All right.
>> And I am a Libra.
>> As is the physical channel.
>> Oh. Oh, very good.
>> Thank you. A one moment. Are you
through? >> Uh, well, there was one other thing I
>> Uh, well, there was one other thing I
wanted to ask.
>> All right. Can you wait?
>> Yes.
>> All right.
>> Um, some some weeks ago, um, I mentioned
u negative relationship that I'm now u
moving away from.
>> At least distancing enough so that I can
>> You are transforming it into whatever
format is necessary for you to learn the
next thing you need to learn.
>> Exactly. And uh about 2 weeks ago uh the
man that I'm living with had a really
really violent dream after we had had a
a particularly nasty argument.
>> Perhaps he has been hanging around with
that other individual over there.
>> And in it he he was carrying a severed
head under his arm
>> and it was dripping blood and gore all
over the place. I wondered if you could
shed a little light on this dream. Uh I
I'm sort of he does seem to have a
violent nature but not that violent
>> again recognize this as an opportunity
to know that many things are played out
in the dream reality that perhaps let's
say would be socially unacceptable in
physical reality. The idea at the same
time that he can use this as a release
is also an indication that perhaps he is
not within a belief that he is connected
to the portion of himself that controls
his life. You can allow this individual
once again to understand that he is
simply reacting to beliefs he has bought
into and that you can teach him this.
Every individual is as strong as they
need to be to create whatever reality
they desire in their lives without
having to hurt anyone else or themselves
in order to create it.
They do not have to cut off their own
head. They do not have to spite
themselves in that way. They do not have
to feel that they are disassociated with
the portion of themsel they think runs
their life.
>> Wow.
>> All right.
>> Uhhuh.
>> Share your unconditional love. The
experience you have had with other
individuals that may have seemed to be
negative also gives you the tools you
need to work with this individual.
You follow me?
>> I think so. If you find that you have
been able to identify in other
individuals patterns of what you would
call violence, then you now have in your
tool box a recognizable model through
which you can assist other individuals.
>> Uhhuh. Yes, I see.
>> Thank you.
>> Don't lose your head. >> Ace.
>> Ace.
>> Okay. I have a couple sharings.
>> All right. Uh two weeks ago I shared a
dream about a u a suicide nice that I
participated in and there was no uh ill
feeling or uh anxiety or whatnot. Last
week I created in my physical structure
a uh very acute uh low back disc
syndrome uh
uh
which was so very intense for 5 hours
that I actually contemplated uh going to
a hospital. Uh but it was the sense that
um I couldn't find a place to sit, lie,
walk, stand, anything for more than
about 15 seconds and I vomited for uh a
great number of times and uh a friend, a
fellow chiropractor came over, couldn't
touch my back, but ended up after an
hour of frustration basically by
adjusting my neck and alleviating about
70% of the in about 20 minutes.
>> All right.
>> Which I then have in the last week gone
to about four different people each, you
know, seeking a certain um aspect of
their their ability.
>> Yes.
>> To bring me back to a much more stable
place. >> Okay. Now
>> Okay. Now
>> now,
>> now the question and that's the
scenario. >> Yes.
>> Yes.
>> My perception was and I'm going to use
terms of like uh
>> from the Bailey books that I'm uh
accustomed to
>> that there was
>> a certain tension in my lower chakras,
>> the solar plexus, sacral, and uh root
chakra. >> All right,
>> All right,
>> that directly related with some type of
agreement or a movement that was going
to be connected with my throat chakra or
an expression. So there was a tension
that I've been holding.
>> And during my life, I've always I've had
sort of a cutting edge to my words.
>> All right.
>> And so the way I look at it is that
there had to be a shift, an actual
blending of the lower centers to be able
to bring more of the next center up,
which would be the heart center
>> into my expression, my communication.
>> All right.
>> Um, and it was funny that my back went
out while I was creating a Christmas
card. Did you laugh?
>> Yes, I laughed a lot. I went out uh for
about the first half hour or so and then
the next four hours I was crying. But
>> all right.
>> Um so I wanted to share that with
everyone because
>> why do you
>> I didn't I don't really you know I
wasn't I was I was anxious for those
five hours until I could finally find a
place to to lay to lie. But it it seemed
like there was
you know I have a I've created the need
in my life to bring through a physical
experience to represent change to
myself. Well, in that one instance, yes.
The idea also of the connection to what
you call the suicide scenario
now allowing you to represent the idea
that you gave yourself a strong enough
focus and an urgency to understand that
you are connected to other individuals
and that they can be of service to you.
They can support you. That you do have a
connection to life. that you are capable
of attracting into your life. Those
things that will allow you from the idea
or the scenario of death and running
away in your terms to come into a new
birth. Christmas after all is a birth.
And in this way allow yourself the
experience that while suicide usually is
the product of belief that you are
disconnected from reality and have not
got the resources to create the life you
want. You gave yourself the opportunity
through that focus of intensity to
realize that you were able to attract
into your life all the connections that
you have to be able to support you and
alleviate any tension that you do have
within you.
>> Right? And it happened so quickly. Most
of my clients takes three months for
this type of event to go. did not need
it to hang around very long.
>> Exactly.
>> It served its purpose. You wonder
>> each individual fell in
synchronistically. >> Absolutely.
>> Absolutely.
>> All right. Thank you. I have one
question about someone else.
>> All right.
>> Thank you very much for that sharing
though. >> Thank you for yours for you only unfold
>> Thank you for yours for you only unfold
more and more of yourself and allow us
to reflect what you already know. We are
teaching you nothing new.
>> Okay. I have a friend, her name is
Michelle Iverson and she's had three
surgeries. uh concerning her uh
reproductive organs uh scar tissue and
blocked uh fallopian tubes and she's
really wanted to have a child and her
husband has really wanted it. So they
went through all this expense and
surgeries, two surgeries first to do
this. And she really was focusing on
drawing together her relationship with
her husband um by giving up some of her
work in in the aspect of a photographer
and being an artist to be more with him
and be more conscious of of uh a union.
>> All right. And then she proceeded after
working this past year very hard of
getting uh a tubal pregnancy which is um
well she didn't lose her tube and I mean
she didn't lose her life or anything
like that but she's really confused as
to all the work that she's put into her
life >> all right
>> all right
>> to this point and to still come up with
something that's now put back into the
bed basically for four or five more
months. Some of this in our immediate perception
Some of this in our immediate perception
perhaps is a remnant idea of guilt from
something that she may have felt she was
neglecting in another life and now
creates for her a sensation of being
drawn close to this other individual
that she may have felt she abandoned.
The idea in this way therefore is that
in her own mind this abandonment of this
being now her spouse then her child
now her spouse then her child
has allowed her to remain fixated on
this struggle to give birth while at the
same time creating baroness and a great
deal of struggle and complexity in the
process of getting closer to the
individual she abandoned before.
She does not need to carry this idea in
this way anymore.
Perhaps even the simple relating of this
idea to her will unlock certain ideas in
her unconscious that will allow her to
see that she no longer needs to create
punishment upon herself and that the
idea of karmic balance can always be
created in positive ways as well. Just
because you may have done something
negative in one life does not mean you
have to perpetuate upon yourself
negativity in this life to balance it
out. It can mean you can be of
assistance in positive ways and that
will also balance out the momentum. For
do remember karma is self-imposed and in
no way, shape or form truly represents a
retribution or a punishment. It is
simply the indication of a balance of
polarity and momentum that you desire to
experience from one life to the next.
But in this way she is exploring this
idea of abandonment. And so she finds
that the idea of childbirth abandons her
so that she will be forced in a sense to
let go of the things that truly are her
children, the things that excite her the
most to adhere to the individual she
felt she abandoned before. But this is
not about needing to abandon the things
in life that truly are her children,
which are her interests, which are the
things that excite her. that will only
compound the difficulty. She can simply
forgive herself and recognize that
because this individual is in her life
again and in a position to be of support
to her that this individual loves her
unconditionally regardless of the
relationship and regardless of the way
she treated this individual in the last
life. >> You follow me?
>> You follow me?
>> Yes.
>> She is already forgiven. Allow her to
forgive herself. Then she will in many
ways give birth on many levels. So she
should return to what excites her the
most, her creative aspect.
>> Allow herself to recognize that there
really is nothing to forgive. Then she
will sense within her the urge to return
and at the same time she will become in
a sense pregnant on many different
levels. >> Pregnant with new potential and perhaps
>> Pregnant with new potential and perhaps
even in what you call the future
pregnant physically.
>> All right. Thank you very much for her
and myself. I will also add this at this
point. When in her physical future, she may
When in her physical future, she may
choose to cocreate a physical pregnancy
with another consciousness now that she
already has in her life the child she
had before as her husband.
She does not need to worry that what she
is going through now will add physical
difficulty to the birth.
>> All right.
>> All right. She can completely
retransform her cellular structure by
getting back into what it is she enjoys
doing. >> It will rejuvenate and refresh her
>> It will rejuvenate and refresh her
entire body because she will be giving
birth to her energy children, the
aspects of herself. And this will
prepare her for any physical birth that
she might agree to have.
Thank you. Thank her for us and share
this information. It will make a
difference in her consciousness and open
many doors that she has held tightly
closed simply out of fear and self-doubt
and guilt.
>> I will share
>> one moment. Ace.
>> Yes, Michelle. I've got a I have a uh
young female client who is
u heavy drug user.
And uh
>> are you teaching this individual that
they have what it takes to create their
reality without relying on outside
tools? I have shared that idea.
>> All right.
>> Uh
she um makes in
in the general sense makes improvement
in this area and then uh relapses and
continue and goes back into heavy drug
use and it's been a quandry for me.
>> Do you know what this individual does
wish to do in life?
>> Is there anything at all that excites
this individual? That's funny you
mentioned that because that's exactly
what we've been talking about the last
couple of sessions.
>> All right.
>> And she's not coming up with anything.
>> All right. Perhaps you can suggest some
alternative exercises or techniques that
will allow this individual to get in
touch with that they can create similar
experiences to what the so-called drug
seems to give them, but that they can do
it without the drug since they are doing
it anyway. and the drug is not really
doing anything for them,
>> right?
>> You can initiate from your imagination
and through your own research a series
of exercises that you can feed to this
individual that they can gain the same
sense of empowerment out of that they
think they gained from the drug but will
allow them to begin to rely upon their
own energy bolstering their cellular
structure bit by bit as they proceed and
progress through the series of
exercises. One of which will be the
technique we have shared many times with
getting in touch with the blue
crystallin sphere of energy that is your
oric field and beginning to identify
with that energy. And one of the
assistive techniques in getting used to
dispersing yourself through that energy
or identifying with that energy is the
idea of the immersion in the body
temperature water.
>> Mhm. and extracting from the water the
crystallin power potential that will
allow for identification to take place
within the cellular structures of the
body so as to realign and become a more
clear conductor for the fact that she
herself is creating the empowerment.
>> You follow me? Use your imagination.
This is your opportunity to discover
your own creativity. You are right on
the threshold of allowing yourself to be
able to in your sense invent a package
of tools that can be very beneficial for
many individuals that will touch them on
many generalized levels. Taking them
through these techniques will allow them
to wean themsel from the externalized
addiction and begin to rely upon
themselves by feeling within themselves
the spark of power they always assumed
came from the drugs.
>> Then they will discover it exists within
them and then they will know the drug
never did anything for them to begin
with that they did it.
>> Thank you. I just got that on several
levels. Thank you.
you all.
[Laughter] There will be but a few moments
There will be but a few moments
remaining for this interaction this
evening of your time.
>> I sure
>> one moment you then you
>> you've discussed this topic several
times but uh it's it's concerning sleep.
Hey. >> Um, at at various times it seems like I
>> Um, at at various times it seems like I
could be driving down the road and I
have a suggestion to myself or something
that the the word sleep will come across
my mind and it's like I have what's the
term narcolepsy or something?
>> Ncolepsy. Yes.
>> Yeah. It's like I just drop into a it's
not like normal times like uh the
afternoon uh thing that you've discussed
you know in our bodies. Now, in a sense,
your own time is your own normal time.
>> Okay. But it seems a little more if
abnormal, if you will.
>> I understand.
>> And uh it seems to be the only thing
that I'm really having difficulty with
that I have not seemed to get some kind
of uh
>> Have you had your physiological body
checked out by the belief systems that
you might call your medical
practitioners? >> Yes. Oh, yes. Yes.
>> Yes. Oh, yes. Yes.
>> Have you?
>> Yes.
>> And have they bound anything?
>> Nothing.
>> Nothing at all.
>> One moment.
>> Have they given you what you call EEG?
>> Uh,
no, I have not. We would suggest that
for they may discover certain patterns
within the neuronic paths of your brain
that will be indicative of certain
chemical states that may be being
created by your belief system within
your brain that may cause this fusion to
take place and in a sense remove you
from conscious reality.
This is nothing serious but we would
suggest that you go and see what you can
discover with this tool. Well, just
recently they did find that I do have a
abnormal, if you will, heartbeat that is
just it isn't
a regular heartbeat and several other
things. This is don't worry about, you
know, it's just kind of indicative of
you as an individual.
>> Yes, in a sense that is correct. But it
is also indicative of this particular
anomaly pattern within the way your
neuronic circuits fire in your brain,
the ones that automatically regulate
your heartbeat. Well, I have spent quite
a lot of money lately going to medical
uh things
and if you will, I'd like for you to
suggest something outside of the
medical. >> Thank you.
>> Thank you.
You can begin to first of all when you
place yourself in a meditative state to
realize as you already well know that
individuals upon your planet have
exhibited many times that when they
place themselves in certain states of
meditation they utterly have the ability
to regulate what you call their
heartbeats and brain wave activity. You
follow me? Mhm.
>> Therefore, we would suggest that perhaps
very beneficial for you would be
allowing yourself to get in touch with
methods that will allow you to regulate
what you call your BOF feedback systems
to allow you to get in touch with what
type of brain waves you are producing
and when you are producing them so that
you can learn to recognize them when you
feel them and learn how to transform
them into what you need them to be when
you need to maintain certain states of
consciousness. >> You follow me? M
>> You follow me? M
>> what you call BOF feedback techniques
may be of assistance to you. You may
find that there may be many quote
unquote clinics which exist which are in
your terms are not the idea too much as
you say of expensive if you explain the
idea that you desire to get in touch
with learning how to control the idea of
your different brain wave frequencies.
They can perhaps point you in the
direction or be of some assistance to
you as to different methodologies to go
about learning how to do so. Well, for
some reason I I understood that wherever
we're going, things are happening and to
to get us there.
>> Yes.
>> Okay. And but you see, the idea may be
that you're giving yourself an
opportunity to explore an avenue that
will allow you to gain the type of
conscious awareness and control over the
variances in your brain activity that
you need to to do what it is you're
going to be doing.
This may simply be one of your methods
and one of your tools to get in touch
with the fact that you can regulate your
body systems. Even the ones you think of
as automatic and unconscious. Exploring
the idea of what you think of is
unconsciously regulated in your body,
such as a thing like your heartbeat,
will put you squarely in touch with the
blending of your conscious mind and your
unconscious mind.
>> You follow me?
>> Yes. Explore the idea of your alpha,
theta, and delta brain wave rhythms.
Research your literature. Research your
techniques. Many are available simply
through the idea of what you call your
books and do not involve the necessity
of the purchase of expensive equipment.
>> Okay. Under the look under the heading
of bio feedback
>> ace,
>> okay,
>> or brainwave activity.
And there are once again many
individuals now that you have in a sense
put it out there that are around you
even right now that may be able to as
you say turn you on to some of these
directions. Do remember every thought you have
Do remember every thought you have
actually physically changes the neuronic
structure of your brain. So when you
start thinking in the ways you will be
thinking when you explore the idea of
blending the different areas of your
brain, then your neuronic pathways will
begin to indicate and reflect that type
of thinking which will put you squarely
in touch with the blending of your
conscious, subconscious, and unconscious
reality, which is what you have desired
to do.
>> Holy
>> It just occurred to me I'm going to have
dinner tomorrow with a surgeon who is a
neurosurgeon. Well, well,
Well, well,
thanks. Okay,
>> thank you. >> Thanks.
>> Thanks.
>> Nice.
>> I um very rarely remember my dreams and
I'd like to find out what this is all
about and what I can do to remember
them. First of all, recognize it is not always
First of all, recognize it is not always
necessary to remember them. You can and
many times you will. However, you do not
necessarily have to put upon yourself
the demand that you do. For many times,
you will find that certain things you
learn about in your dream realities are
quite a distinctly separate lives from
what you are doing here. And there
really is no need to mix the two in that
way. Also, you will find there are
certain things you do in your dream
realities that even though they have to
do with this physical reality, you don't
want to necessarily have absolute
conscious analytical awareness of until
you spontaneously live through the
experience you have set up from the
dream reality. So, you will learn what
you need to learn rather than simply
intellectually know it already and not
get the spontaneous experience of life
out of it. You follow me so far?
>> Not exactly. Let me put it more simply.
Everything you do in physical life in a
sense you have worked out in the dream
state. You follow me?
>> Yes.
>> Sometimes what you work out in the dream
state, you don't want to remember when
you wake up so that you will remember
what you need to remember after you have
lived through the experience you set up
in the dream state. So you don't have a
memory of the dream because it would tip
you off.
>> Uhhuh. I get it.
>> So it wouldn't be spontaneous.
>> Okay. Now also another reason why you
may be creating the idea of not
remembering dreams. Although we do
understand that in your society there
are things sometimes which you do not
want to face and sometimes when they
come out in your dreams you will not
remember them because perhaps you fear
to face them. All right, no big deal.
Allow yourself to simply recognize that
you will learn what you need to learn
when you need to learn it. But also
recognize that the fourth density
reality is the idea of living your
dream. And what you colloquially call a
dream is a symbolic tool to form a
connection for you between a physical
and a non-physical reality that you
don't believe are connected. When you
therefore wake up into physical reality,
you have a dream memory to let you know
there is a bridge and a link and you
were doing something when you were
asleep. When you begin to blend your
dream reality and physical reality into
more of one reality, you don't need that
link because you're always aware of the
fact that you are awake and dreaming at
the same time. So in fourth density, you
will find that people will not so much
wake up and remember a dream as much as
they will simply know they are always
awake and always dreaming at the same
time and don't need to create the
separation of physical and non-physical
reality and the link of the dream to let
them know that they are aspects of the
same reality. You follow me?
>> Yeah.
Okay. >> At the same time,
>> At the same time,
simply as soon as you lighten up on
yourself with regard to needing to
remember these dreams, most likely you
will begin to understand this first of all
begin to understand this first of all
and take this to heart.
Are you paying attention?
>> Yes.
>> Repeat after me if you will. I
>> I
>> am
>> dreaming
>> now
>> now.
>> Okay.
>> This is a dream
>> in a sense.
>> Therefore, very good. Therefore,
when you understand this is also a
dream, this physical reality is also a
dream, there will not be as much
separation for you.
>> Mhm. And therefore, it will not be such
a big deal. Oh, I'm going into the dream
reality now. Well, big, dark, nebulous
place. I probably won't remember
anything about it because it's so unlike
my life.
When you understand you are dreaming
right now, you will allow the dream
reality to become familiar to you in a
way that will allow you to think of it
as a normal experience and not something
so esoteric that you can't possibly
apply the idea to your physical life.
>> Mhm.
>> Then you will begin to let the two
blend. Then you will have whatever
memories of it you need to have.
>> Okay. Thank you.
>> Thank you very much. At this timing, we
will once again extend to each and every
one of you our deepest appreciation and
joy in your willingness to allow us to
share and experience with you your gift
of consciousness.
Remember, you are creating in more ways than one
you are creating in more ways than one
the idea of a completely new year, a new
orbit, a new life, a new you. Yes.
>> In which you will all be able to learn
how to express yourself in more
spontaneous, loving, and
loving, and
childlike ways.
Our deep and unconditional love to each
and every one of you. When we speak with
you again, once again, you
and us, the channel and the world that
you live within will no longer be the
same.
Wake up and dream.
Merry Christmas. Happy New Year. Our
love to you all.
>> Christmas.
>> Good night.
>> Thank you.
[Music]
How did it go?
>> Wonderful. Thank you.
[Applause] >> Thank you all for being here tonight.