All right, I'll say how are you all
receiving of your time as you create
time to
exist? How's the dream going?
All right, nice reactive. Let us begin with
right, nice reactive. Let us begin with
an interaction based on the idea and
this is also the title if you wish for
tonight paradox. All right. All right. In this
paradox. All right. All right. In this
way, the idea once again that we have
illuminated and outline to some degree
within many of the interactions we have
had with you from time to time is that
when you find yourself coming across the
expression in your lives you call
paradox, then you know you are dealing
with the higher consciousness more
directly. For you will find that the
higher consciousness has a tendency to
be in your terms broken down into
seemingly seemingly
diametrically polarized occurrences in
physiological reality. Therefore, when you begin in
reality. Therefore, when you begin in
your expansion in your so-called search
for your spirituality, you come across
more and more and more understandings of
more and more situations that seem to be
in your terms
paradoxical expressing what you call
dichotomy or polarity.
Then you know you are standing firmly
and squarely at the center of those two
seemingly opposite events and that means
that they both come from you. They are
both projected from you. You standing at
the center are the very example and the
very indication that both of those
things in coming from you because you
have the ability to see what appears to
be both sides means that within you they
are blended. They are one concept. They
are one event. They are one idea. They
are one thing. Within that blending,
there is no
dichotomy. Polarity,
Polarity,
paradox are expressions of the
manifestation of the unbroken wholeness
of your higher consciousness in physical
reality. Because by definition, physical
reality is that which separates. so that
you can see the components so to speak
of which the higher homogeneous
wholeness is created. Thus individuals
for many tens of thousands of years in
your society have gone about living
their lives and according to what they
have bought into in terms of a belief of
what that life should be. Many of them
will find no paradox occurring so much
in their lives or if it does they will
have a tendency or have had a tendency
to ignore it because it does not fit
into what they have been taught is the
life you are quote unquote supposed to
live the way things are quote unquote
supposed to be. Now that you are
expanding in your awareness, now that
you know that there is no one way but
that each and every one of you is your
own path towards the understanding of
the infinite creation, you are going to
run into more and more of the idea of
paradox and you are going to see it not
only expressed in the daily events in
each individual life but in mass events
as you find different quote unquote
factions within your societ. society
becoming more and more
polarized within their estimation as to
how to relate to the reality around
them. At this time there are three once
again a triad three basic groupings of
mass consciousness upon your planet that
we perceive. The dynamic interactions of
these three are what are spurring you
forward. Whether at times it may seem
like it or not into the fourth density
higher consciousness reality, it is the
interaction and the momentum created by
this interaction playing off of one
another that is allowing you to examine
all the different facets of the paths
you have lived for many thousands of
lives, many thousands of years and now
are allowing you to be capable of
integrating these reflections you are
getting from each other so that you can
come to a clear and conscious
understanding of the fact that all that
seems to be paradoxical within life is
in fact blended and contained within the
one higher consciousness that you are.
The three
basic divisions shall we say that now
exist upon your
planet are individual. Now before we
begin, in no way, shape or form is any
of the following definitions meant in
any way to indicate that something is
better or worse than anything else. You
follow me? These are simply distinctions
as we perceive the conglomerate energy
of your society. And they are in their
own right completely and totally valid.
for each is playing its part in the
spurring of the momentum towards force
density. One will be and again these
definitions are very general very
general one will be those that generally
generally recognize
themselves to be the creators of their
reality. What you may generally lump as
you say under the term metaphysicians so
to speak. This is a very loose
terminology. One will be the idea of any
individual following in any way, shape
or form in accordance with what you
would call religious
aspects. the individuals in this way who
in your terms follow a schematic they
believe to have been laid down by one or
more facets or reflections of the
infinite creator in that
way. The third will be what you
generally term the scientific approach
and into this will also fall any
sociological structure that is so based
including what you refer to as
politics. These
three ideas are playing off each other and
ideas are playing off each other and
allowing there to be the foundations of
the three aspects of
physicality, mentality, emotionality and
the spirituality in life.
spirituality in life.
In this way, the
idea is to recognize that many
paradoxes, many polarizations will
continue to increase between these three
factions for time. Although you will
find that there are, as always, hints
and clues as to where each and every one
of these three blend with all the other
two. You are beginning to see that ideas
that have for a long time been held to
be religious or metaphysical are
cropping up in science. Ideas that have
for a long time been held to be
completely scientific are cropping up in
religion and
metaphysics. And ideas in this way that
have been long held to be simply
religious can also be shared by the
other two ideas. They are now beginning
to form the foundations for the blending
of the three. But at first, at first,
primarily for one reason, they will
continue to separate a little further,
gaining dynamic tension for a while.
This dynamic tension is building up for
the purpose of creating there to be a
very strong springboard once the dynamic
tension is snapped. So that you will go
through the doorway into fourth density
in a very dynamically propelled fashion.
But you are beginning to recognize that
there are underlying foundations into
which each and every one of those three
aspects all have a degree of
commonality. They are of course simply
different aspects of the same one thing
but your society does not realize it
yet. The one reason the primary reason
that this is not realized in your
society is simply because of what you
call definitions. That is it semantics.
That is it. the idea of the definitions
of what you think you believe. For you
will find that one faction will say,
"Well, that other faction or this other
faction, they say this and this, and
therefore I do not agree with them, and
I will fight them to the death."
However, recognize that all that is
being done is that what is being said by
one faction is simply being interpreted
by the other factions in their own
terminology. And according to only what they
And according to only what they
understand or what definitions they have
applied to those particular aspects of
life that will determine how they choose
to understand what another faction is
saying. Therefore still quite often you
will find that one faction while they
may think they understand what another
faction means very often only
understands what they themselves mean by
their definition. the definition they
have been taught to believe about what
another faction means and not really
what the other faction means at all.
This is why we have discussed with you
of like the idea not that you have to
analyze this into oblivion but the idea
of being very concise and very clear in
your communication with any other
individuals in your society about what
it is you believe. For in this way you
can then provide for them the clearest
and concisest definition of how it is
you actually mean what symbols you are
using. For meaning once again will vary
from individual to individual. And the
biggest assumption in your planet is
that what one thing means to another
individual is the same for everyone. And
this is nowhere near the idea. For do
not forget no symbol comes with built-in
meaning. They are all blank. You fill in
the meaning. the meaning that has
relevance and significance to you. Your
interpretation is what you experience of
life. The idea
therefore fundamentally of the expression of the
fundamentally of the expression of the
paradox will be first and foremost in
the creation of a blending in
recognizing as we have shared that the
paradox of what an individual may say to
you. There is only one truth. All right.
There is only one truth. And the paradox
is that that one truth is that all
truths are
true. That is the
paradox. So you see it is not something
that has to be a conflict, something
that has to be contradictory in that
sense. Each and every faction simply has
their own way of saying it for
themselves. They know what they mean in
their own relative point of view. But it
is still all the same information
because it is all the same
universe. It is simply that as a
co-creator with the infinite creator,
you are creating your version, your
interpretation of the one creation. And
that is how you create more creation.
Even though everything already exists,
there's another paradox.
You follow me? Allow yourself
therefore as these things crop up in
your society to not necessarily have to fall
society to not necessarily have to fall
into the idea of battling these other
individuals to stand up for what you
know to be true. But simply recognize
that if you truly do believe what you
say you believe, then simply continue to
live your life in that manner. And if
you change your mind, change your mind.
Ultimately, it doesn't matter. You follow Siri. [Music] [Music]
Another paradox.
Thanks. Um, it has seemed over the last 20, 30,
Um, it has seemed over the last 20, 30,
40 years, that crime is on the increase
throughout Western civilization in
general, certainly in the United States
where when I was a child, you could
leave your door open. Now you have to
lock your home and your car. Yeah, I've
discussed this to some degree. Could
Well, okay. I wasn't here. I'm
interested. The idea is analogous to the
fact that you are now bringing all the
different ideas of negativity to the
surface and allowing them to run as you
say rampant because now you are forced
to deal with them. Now you are forced to
deal with the reasons not just the
surface effect. It is so prevalent that
you can no longer ignore it, let it
pass. It is no longer just a surface
effect. You must now deal with the core,
the heart of why these traits exist in
your society. And the basic foundational
reason as to why they exist is because
your society has been taught to believe
it is
powerless. The idea is not so much the
idea of being powerless against other
individuals. No, but that those
individuals expressing the criminal
activity believe they are powerless. And
that is why they attempt to make
everyone else around them equal to
themselves, just as powerless. The idea
is that you have been taught that you do
not have the ability to create the life
you want, the life you desire. And so
this creates a great deal of frustration
in many individuals in your society.
They feel therefore that they must try
to control other individuals to get what
they want because they themselves have
not been taught that they are themselves
in control and can have anything they
desire without having to hurt anyone
else or themselves in order to get it.
When you now begin to teach the
individuals in your world that every
single person is that powerful is that
powerful and through the functioning of
integrity you can create whatever
reality you desire then they will be
self-empowered and they will not have to
force their points of view or their ways
of life on anyone else which is only a
sign that they believe they are
powerless.
Thank you. Guys,
I have a question. Uh, a friend of mine
who's not here tonight. [Music]
Before you speak, allow me to remind
once again each and every one of
you that anything that you have
co-created and attracted yourself to
hear being said from anyone else is
there for a reason.
There is always a way with
the creativity I know you possess and the
creativity I know you possess and the
imaginations I know you express. To take
what anyone else has to share or say and
apply it to yourselves so that
everything can be a learning, a sharing
and a growing. Different things may have
what you may term relative degrees of
significance or importance to you, but
you are still participating just by the
very fact that you are where you are and
by the very fact that you are able to
hear someone else say something. That
means it is a reflection of a part of
you. Once again, there are no boring
situations, only bored minds.
Let yourselves expand within your
curiosity and your excitement and let
yourselves be fascinated by everything.
For nothing happens by accident.
Everything that is said, every nuance,
every subtle shading has a reason. It is
completely orchestrated by all of you in
tandem. It is a co-creation. Be absorbed
in that and you will have the
fascination of a child.
Continue. Yeah. Well, this friend of mine, uh,
Yeah. Well, this friend of mine, uh,
Kim, she comes through a lot. Anyway,
she said she wants to know about drugs
and alcohol and the different effects
that they create. She's noticed that
sometimes some people who are drunk get
real silly and some people get real
belligerent. Nice. And she wants to
know, is this caused by negative ego or
is it a magnification of their true
feelings? In a sense, both.
In a sense, both.
The idea many times is that an
individual has not felt that they could
be communicative in their society. And
when they allow what you may call the in
taught the
inbred inhibitions to drop, they may
have something they wish to say and they
may have been taught that there is no
easy way to say it. So they will wait
until they are about to explode.
Then once they let the barrier drop, the
only way they know to say it is to
explode, is to become belligerent in
that way. That is the only way they
believe they will be heard because your
society has taught you that only if you
shout loud enough do you get paid
attention to. Therefore, there may be just as many
to. Therefore, there may be just as many
reasons for the different various
actions as there are individuals. But in
general, any
individual who in that way ascribes the
idea that the
drug is what is letting them say their
peace is simply not realizing that they
are the ones creating the opportunity
and they are using the drug as an excuse
for the drug has absolutely no power.
You give it the power. The drug is there
and it can be a tool in what you may
call extreme
moderation to allow you to know what
abilities you do have. From time to
time, there are ways in which a
so-called tool such as a drug, so to
speak, can allow you to recognize that
you can go beyond what you believe you
couldn't go beyond. Once that has been
accomplished, you no longer need the
tool. You no longer need the drug. But
because your society once again has been
taught that the power is not there
within you then it is simply your habit
to put the power outside of you in the
tool in the drug and thus you think well
that was wonderful allowed me to really
get it off my chest. Therefore, the next
time I have something to get off my
chest, I have to use the drug
again. And thus builds the idea of
dependency and addiction. Because you do
not realize that what the drug was
showing you is that you had the
capability all along and you don't need
the drug. It was only a reflection, a
momentary reflection. It was the tool
you were willing to allow to be the
reflection that showed you you have the
power. You follow me? Thank you. Does
that assist you? Yes. Thank you very
much. Thank you. One other question. I
have a sister-in-law who uh she had a
tubiligation a few years ago and now
she's married to a guy. They want to
have children and she's tried various
things to undo this. It is not yet
timing.
This individual may also
find we perceive the energy now. Does
not mean it cannot change. We perceive
the energy now, right
now, to be most likely in the direction
of what you call
adoption. For there are individuals that
that individual can hook up with, as you
say again, that have already been
born. So that they do not
necessarily have to have the idea of the
physical birth themselves to have
contact with the individual that in all
senses of the word has agreed to be
their child. You follow me? Yes. If that does
child. You follow me? Yes. If that does
not occur within what you call the next
three of your years, then we sense there
can be a physiological change that may
allow a physiological birth within the
individual. But you may find that the
idea of an association and an attraction
of an already physicalized child may
occur within the next three years. All
right. Thank you very much. Thank you.
Sure. For sure.
you then you
uh do you have animals on your planet?
Speak up. Yes, we have animals on our
planet. Okay.
Uh, I was curious
to I'm very involved with animal rights
on on this planet and
um I would be interested in anything
that you can share to assist us uh
simply show everyone how much you love
them. Teach everyone that they are extensions
Teach everyone that they are extensions
of your consciousness and that anything
anyone wishes to learn about an animal
can simply be learned by identifying
with the animal, by asking it, by
communicating with it, or by
communicating as it. That is what your
imagination is for. You have the ability
to create a synchronous harmonious
identification pattern. And in so doing,
you can literally become your version of
the animal and learn everything from a
very intimate point of view that anyone
would want to learn about the animal.
Okay. Well, I'm deal I'm talking from
more of a societal standpoint that uh
that wants that believes that
vivisection is necessary in order for
them to learn. We understand the way you
say it exists, but that has nothing to
do with anything. The way it exists is
not a reason for you not living the life
you believe to be true for you.
You follow me?
I follow how my being in contact and
with you being the example of how to
communicate with animals and learn from
them what you need to learn can teach
other individuals that they do not have
to kill the animal in order to learn
what they need to learn.
Open up your communication and be an
example to your society that there are
other ways. Then they will see within
you another
choice. Bold.
Okay. Um I Why are you hesitant?
I guess I Do you think it will be a big
battle, an uphill struggle?
Well, cuz I'm not in I'm not ex my
presence is not exposed to the
scientists that need to see the
reflection of me with the animals. Well,
why not?
Whose creation is that?
Do you understand that if you truly are
the whole idea of expressing that to
your society, you will automatically
attract yourself into whatever
environment you need to be attracted in
order to show whoever needs to see it
that they need to see the idea being
expressed within you. Just because you
aren't there now doesn't mean
anything. Live the idea. And if showing
other individuals there is another way
is what you wish to do, you will be
attracted into those environments so
other individuals can see that there is
another way, you are holding yourself back from
way, you are holding yourself back from
being the idea because you are not
seeing the end result before you
begin. Be begin and everything will be
there at the same
time. You follow me? Yeah. You are
creating stipulations. I can't do that
because I can't do this
because be the idea that you are.
Interact with the animals in the way you
know expresses your unconditional
love and simply share with any other
individuals you come across the idea
that they can be learned from without
killing them. recognize it is a
scientific principle already that you
cannot really observe a process by
stopping
it. So perhaps you can take that
particular tangent. The idea is very simple.
tangent. The idea is very simple.
However, you do not have to make a very
complex idea out of it. Simply be the
individual you are moved to be and you
will wind up in the circles you need to
wind up in.
I have some information on that. See see
me afterwards. Okay. Um what I what I
guess I was um looking for was like uh
if you knew of alternatives that the
scientific community uh would want to
hear about um so that they don't feel
that this is the only way for them to to
practice that they're looking for it in
black and white and they want the
scientific like I went to a cosmetic um
I was in Merl Norman's today and I was
talking to the chemist that moral
moments and studies about tests
and they want to know what they can do
specifically so that they don't have to
um so that they feel they don't have to
do the DRA test and they don't have to
do the LD50s and kill these animals. I
know that it's wrong and that it's not
necessary but I don't it is not right or
wrong. Well,
it may be a negative expression. Yes,
it's a very negative expression and I uh
negative not in the judgmental sense
just in a definitive sense. Negative
meaning separative limiting.
Okay. Well, the idea still may include a
necessity on their part to adopt at
least a bit of a belief system that in
general your scientists do not believe
exists. For if they were willing to recognize
For if they were willing to recognize
that every being has an atheric and an
astral counterpart, they could glean all
the tests from that. But they are not
even willing to admit that that
exists. They must
somewhere restructure the basic
foundational understanding of their
beliefs in order to take advantage of
what they desire to take advantage of.
It will not occur within a framework
that has no room for the ability to be
able to get the information from another
source other than the
physical. If they wish another
methodology, then they must expand their
definition beyond the framework they
have already invested in.
Then they will give themselves the
ability to tap into the information they
seek still in a very seemingly
scientific way with all sorts of
instruments and the
like but they still have to understand
that there are ways to read the magnetic
and electrical energies of a
being. There are methodologies that can
be created now through what you call the
polarity potential. the electromagnetic
polarity potential of the cellular
structure of any body while it is alive.
Each and every cell functions like a
gate in many different ways expressing
itself almost like a very tiny battery
and the entire body of any living
organism expresses itself totally like a
battery in that way. By reading the
so-called amperage if you wish of the
flow within the cellular structures of
the body, they can take let us say sounding
body, they can take let us say sounding
and they can catalog lists of the
different types of sounding and create
an entire energy picture of the body.
And by reading how the energy flows once
they map the body out electrically that
way, electromagnetically in that way,
then by simply taking a reading at any
particular point, this is where the idea
of acupuncture originated a long time
ago in your term. By taking a reading in
that way, they can turn what they
believe to be an esoteric idea into a
very scientific one by simply reading
the electromagnetic potential of the
being and the flow of the energy through
that being in very specific ways.
Because there are specific gates,
meridian points that define and describe
the energy pattern that a physical being
is. They have been known for quite some
time in the idea of acupuncture. But
many scientists simply again do not
believe that that has any validity and
so don't pursue
it. You follow me? Yeah. That is one
way. It is up to you. Do your own
research based on your own excitement.
You will find what you need to find. And
again, synchronistically, you will
attract, as has already been pointed out
to you, individuals who can supply you
with information. If you feel at a loss,
just because you have now put out with
your vocal conviction and communication
to the rest of the individuals that
surround you, what is the idea you wish
to do, then you have gotten an automatic
synchronistic response from an
individual that can be of assistance to
you. That is all you need to do. The
more you put it out, the more
individuals will know what you are all
about and the more information will come
to you along the path of least
resistance. You follow me? Yeah. Simply
continue in that way.
Thank you. Thank you, Michelle. Guys, um
I just returned from a trip to the
southwest in which I went to the healthy
reservation. Good. And I spoke with um
an elder grandfather David. Oh, what?
And did you have a good time? Yeah, I
had a great time. All right. And um I
asked him about the four aspects of the
feminine. All right. And he didn't I
don't think he understood, but I'm not
sure. But he didn't really want to talk
about it. He understood.
[Laughter] But I don't understand. I don't
But I don't understand. I don't
understand why I why I was unable to
have a
dialogue with
him. You have had
dialogue not
physically. The idea in allowing
yourself to integrate the idea of the
four aspects as you tournament is to
recognize that you are having dialogue. Now, an
Now, an
elder to some degree generally will
choose to play with you a little bit,
lead you on a little bit, see exactly
how serious you are, how persistent you
are. You follow me? Yes. How persistent
are you?
Very. All right. Did you share with that
individual your
understanding of the concept? No,
because I felt confused as well. Well,
there you go. You got an exact
reflection. All right. I I more willingness on your
All right. I I more willingness on your
part to
recognize that you know what you need to
know and to put it out will give back to
you the reflection in life kind
well I was thinking I was thinking when
I spoke with you a while back about um
speaking to an elder you you had said to
me um have you thought about going to
you know to this area seeing an elder
and then you said go they will know what
it is you're asking well right and I did
but you in a way I felt I was kind of
blindly following the suggestion why did
you follow it then if you felt that way
well I yeah you're right okay then I had
one other I had one other question that had
other I had one other question that had
to do I felt for some reason during this
trip that mo a lot of work went on at
that time in my dream. Yes, that is what
I just told you. You have had dialogues
not in the physical reality. All right.
Well, I remember one uh one dream in
which I was being um instructed by a
hoping man. Well, Giz,
what a surprise.
But I can't I was I can't remember what
I I was I can't remember the exchange.
Well, relax.
The information is within you. You have
made the
journey. You have made the journey and
you have had the dialogue. Just simply
now live your life knowing it is within
you and you will see it come out in your
actions. All right. All right. All
right. I I had another question. All
right. I was wondering um what kind of
work you were doing with the cacinas.
Oh, very exciting.
As of late, as we informed many of the
individuals on your planet recently of
your time, we are connecting with five
different civilizations to undergo what you may
civilizations to undergo what you may
colloally term an expedition of sorts
into that particular dimensional
framework in which we perceive their
consciousness to be infolded or
intertwined. The idea for us is that we have
The idea for us is that we have
recognized communication with aspects of
the consciousness you would refer to as
Kacina consciousness or cacina energy.
But now we are beginning to delve into
the very heart, the very core of their
existence. And we find them to be very
intimately intertwined with the very
fundamental fabric and structure of
physical reality itself. This is very
exciting for us.
intertwined with the structure of
society of all physical reality. They
of all physical reality. They
are all right. Now you may have heard
this term. We recognize it as an entire
phrase in your
society. This term does exist in your
culture and it has been used from time
to time. It is in this light appropriate
and appropriate analogy to refer to the
kacina by considering the entire physical
by considering the entire physical
universe to be so to speak a
machine. The kacina being heavily
intertwined into the very structure the
very skeleton if you will that gives
form to the machine makes the cacas
ghosts in the machine.
They are the spirits of the machine.
They are
archetypal representations of the very
structure of the consciousness of
creation itself in physical terms. That
is what we are beginning to discover
about them. We won't be too posted.
Okay. Could she just ask the spirit
guides? No. can in a sense more like
true reflections of energy of combined
reflections of energy of combined
conglomerate mass consciousness energies
in
embodiment spirit
forms symbolically presented based upon
whatever way is comfortable for the
particular culture that chooses to
perceive that particular facet of them
at any given moment or time. Could you
define the five pieces of five aspects?
Five different
civilizations that we are exploring this
idea with as what you would call one
project. Define most civilizations.
Define most civilizations.
One is
serious. One to some degree is arturous
energy. There is some intermixing with
what you may call reticulum.
The others you do not
know. Not yet.
Thank you. I I had one last question.
All right. Um, this was a question a
while a while ago I talked to I asked
you about a dream and it was was a dream
that had to do with a Thunderbird or
connecting with a Thunderbird energy and
I I interpreted the Thunderbird energy
as being the
higher self. All right. Is that
accurate? Can you It is valid for you.
If it will allow you to soar. Yes.
Um, there was a portion of the dream
that I had not remembered until I went
back later and read it. And I was wanted
to ask you about that because in the
beginning of that dream that we talked
about before, there was a scene in which
I was playing with a boy who I realized
was my son. And we went, we were walking
together and at one point he said to me,
"Be careful or you will not have a child
in your womb."
And I remember in my dream I thought
about this very intently and I was
wondering well what what was it that I
needed to be careful about and was that
more a symbolic rebirth or was that
actually to some degree? Yes. Understand
that the idea you call the Thunderbird
is also analogous to the phoenix rising
from its own ashes rebirth. In that way,
the idea is to simply recognize that the
power that you feel in that
symbol is something that does represent
the being, the creator that you are, you
do not have to feel that it will burn
you out, make you barren. You follow me?
Yes. You can connect with that energy.
Simply recognize
that from the belief structures of many
different lifetimes, the degree of let us say
lifetimes, the degree of let us say
reverence and respect you have treated
it with has also brought with it some
modicum of fear rather than
equality. Let yourself be
equal and you will in your own terms be
the fruit of your own womb.
All right. Yes.
it.
Related to what you're just talking
about. Number one, I have I just I got at a
Number one, I have I just I got at a
garage sale a u uh this week a cacina
doll that I'm not sitting up on the
counter, a small one.
Um and
um also two days ago I went for a
wonderful glorious ride in red state reticulum
glorious ride in red state reticulum
mothercraft and got the whole tour. Very
exciting. Thank you for the creation in your
Thank you for the creation in your
energy state and the
intertwining and the blending of your
dream and imagination reality with your
physical reality. For then you are
shortening the
bridge a bit at a time and bringing the
two sides of the apparent chasm closer
and closer and closer together so that
there will be no need of a bridge
because there is no chasm. Right.
Exactly. Thank you. Thank you. You
venue. I would like to ask some
questions about dolphins and I might All
right. Speak up. Should I ask you or
should I ask to speak to the dolphin
question? We have to some degree the
idea of a blending. It will remain in
the fashion you are perceiving it now,
but there will be a blending, a
connection. Continue. We're working with
with autistic children and dolphins and
there seems to be extraordinary
communication between the
children and so you will recognize first
of all once again that the idea to some
degree of what you call autism is that
those individuals are still very highly
focused into many different realities
that your civilization may call dream or
imaginary realities that are no less
real and of course the dolphins exist in
dream reality very consciously. So they
are finding simply that they are
speaking in many ways the same language.
They live in the dream reality. They are
very highly focused in that sense. We
we're using we're using the dolphins to
heal the children. Yes. Are the children
going to be similarly a path for us to
understand the dolphins? Yes. Of course.
Everything works both ways. They are
doorways. Depends upon who is willing to
walk through them.
Earlier I we looked at a picture of some
islands where we hope to establish a
base study. Hope hope hope why hope in
Canada then that is different.
Do you do you feel with your dolphin
consciousness that they're correct? That
those islands are correct?
They are in their configuration what you
turn the yin and the yang
right. They are the polarities in a
spiral motion and in their center is a very
motion and in their center is a very
strong gate that will be the creation of
the participation between your two
species. [Music]
[Music]
Is there a is there an Atlantean link in
Oh yes. Oh
yes. Very strong. Understand that that
particular area was the embodiment of
the southernmost island of
Atlantis. The northernmost and larger
island was off what you call the eastern
seabboard of your present day country. A
little further north. There was a
separation between the two islands.
But the entire area you called the Hamas
was the southern island area of
Atalantis. Work with the children of the dolphins
Work with the children of the dolphins
going to lead the discoveries in that
area of the islands themselves can be
of the islands themselves can be
fashioned into very small artifacts
whether pyramidal or spherical in nature
that in and of themselves will carry a
high magnetic charge in the atheric
sense in the astral sense.
They can be very strong identification
tools for the Adalandian
consciousness and assist with very very
little exposure the unlocking of many Atlantian
exposure the unlocking of many Atlantian
memories and traits within any
individual. More the island itself can
be utilized in that way.
The idea is that there are artifacts in
that area and some of them have already
been discovered. But you will find that what
discovered. But you will find that what
you will
create will be a reflection of the new
age in which you exist. For the precise
old tools that you used to use in
Atlantis will no longer exactly apply in
the same way for you are not the same
individuals. You did work with them before in
You did work with them before in
Atlantis and you are working with them
again in New Atlantis which is what you
call your United States of America which
is an almost exact historic parallel of
Atalantis. You are retrieving many of
the traits that existed then. the
understanding and the fascination and
utilization of crystallin forms
communication with your brethren that
all interchange in that way and the
experience at the same time of what you
call a very high physical
technology. All of these were concurrent
in Atlantis as
well. It is simply slightly different
now. And the idea now is that the energy
you are putting into these endeavors is
what is allowing you to experience as
you say the flip side of the entire
event now that you are at the other end
of the cycle begun by destruction and
now ending in the opportunity for
integration and harmonious resolution.
Follow the last question. Oh, Mike. Uh,
there's a man in San Diego who's doing
some extraordinary work taking human
saliva, putting it into a solution,
connecting it to a computer, and can
monitor the the the functions, the
bodily functions of the person from whom
the saliva was taken, regardless of
where the person is. One moment. Are you
paying attention?
I don't understand.
Just pay attention. What do you
understand about what has been said so
far in terms of applying it to the idea
you desire to apply it to?
That there is a way to extract
ingredients from a living being that can
be the encodification of the entire
being without harming the original
being. You follow
me? Perk up and pay attention.
You are getting your answers. They are
all around you blossoming like a garden
in synchronicity.
[Music] Atlantis and I know that in Atlantis
Atlantis and I know that in Atlantis
they used a lot of vivid section and
that was a part of um the synchronicity
of this when you mentioned the two
countries. So I Oh, but that was in your
terms later in their history not at
first. There was also the idea of
genetic engineering and many negative
expressions were created that way as
well. Not that you have to imply that it
is negative
that it didn't work in Atlantic.
Well, what are you learning now?
I'm learning that that there are
alternatives. All right, then you are
learning. I was just curious if that society
I was just curious if that society
learned before it was correct.
Many in that society
understood and were not in the
destruction having long since left
before it. Those that were in the
destruction have spent many thousands of
lifetimes learning. They are now beginning to
learning. They are now beginning to
understand. Continue.
The my question is I I spoke with a
gentleman today with an idea of using
saliva from a dolphin in the same
experiment. All right. My question is do
you will we get something beyond the
physical state of the dolphin from this
is it possible that with this saliva and
with a with an analysis of it we might
get something multi-dimensional and not
just well to some degree. Although what
you will find
is the non-physical dimensions of any
living being do make their impression on
the molecular arrangement of that
substance. And so what you need to do is
learn how to read where the impressions
have been made. So that if you find a
particular molecular bonding that
indicate certain consciousness
interactions with physical materiality,
then you will know that non-physical
consciousness has been at work here. But
the idea is that you may still have to
find the physiological symbol in the
molecular bonding the enzyatic action
that represents that non-physical
interaction. You follow me? I understand. Could be
You follow me? I understand. Could be
the medium for that impression.
Now I have discussed your device and
according to the way we have discussed
it in terms of the cycles per second,
the rate of electric flow and all of
that in that manner can you still once
again tap into the etheric nature of the
dolphin or the human or any other
consciousness within creation. But that
is a slightly different idea.
You may be able to get a very
rudimentary etheric field from the
saliva with that device but it may not
tell you anything
coherent. You follow me? Because in that
format though it will represent let us
say a nucleus
packet of
energy. The idea of learning how to read
that energy is still most easily done
with your own intuition rather than any
device.
Does this assist you? Yes, indeed. I
have one last question. Right. I was
told to ask, are there are there any
messages that the dolphins might have
for me in connection with the work that
I'm I'm doing? Well, we have in a sense
shared some of them with you in the
understanding of the energy of the area
that we have spoken of. One
moment. We are scanning at this point
many of the symbols that you have
utilized in the Atlantean
life. Gold played in your terms an
important part. We perceive it is not
necessary in this particular
incarnation for you to have a symbol
made of that substance.
Though it can function to some degree as
a balancing agent, if you wish to create
a symbol that can
represent the
interaction of human and doll, they
would suggest that you go into your
imagination and
represent in perhaps what you call the
yin-yang format, a symbolic interaction. action
format, a symbolic interaction. action
between Schuman and
Dolphin in a circular
format. It will thus represent the
accelerated momentum, the spiraling accelerated
momentum, the spiraling accelerated
momentum of that interaction. In your
terms also the interactive
interdependency in the expression that
you are no matter what your expression
of it one basic species overall in soul
form and
that in the
area in what we term the yin-yang symbol
where there would
be the
dots. You follow me?
that perhaps they be represented
by
stars so that there is also the idea of
a stellar
connection in that you are beings of
light together. You follow me? I do. They
together. You follow me? I do. They
simply offer this as a
suggestion as a symbology that in and of
itself can function as a meditative
tool. which when the meaning is understood and
which when the meaning is understood and
focused on in a meditative
state can actually function as an
intercommunication device between your
consciousness, your mentality and their
mentality. Now the
idea that will occur in any way, shape
or form that you choose to create this
interaction of allowing humans to focus
upon dolphin consciousness is that what
will be created is as follows. to set up
this mental
communication. In being given an
opportunity to see, to
feel the dolphin's form of
expression, the human will create in the
mental field an identifying vibrational
frequency that will actually allow them
to feel what it is to be a dolphin and
thus be able to quote unquote think like
a
dolphin. You follow me? Yes.
The dolphins are already doing this in
order to think like a
human. They simply form an
identification pattern. They are already
very used to working with
frequencies, especially in the mental
plane. And they form an identification
model, a pattern through which they can
then feel you, hear you, so to
speak. You can do the same. The more you
identify with them, the easier it will
be to
understand so to speak their thoughts
because you will be simply creating the
same thought patterns for
yourself. It is simply another example
of to love them is to know
them. You follow? Yes.
Folding. All right. Zoomer, I want to
share with you my excitement. Um, Suz,
speak up if you are. I'm so excited.
Okay. Um, I just met Boris last night
and we're working to feels like the
Lamuran side of this Atlantean Dolphin
Connection, working with Jim Lumis in
Maui this um, coming December. We're now
talking about um, actually making making
the Maui part of it a sub part of the
Dolphin Perspective Company, which is a
nonprofit company. This will enable us
to do our project with Jim Moon within
Maui and take the whole thing to New
Zealand. Yes. More synchronicity, more
integration. Once the momentum is begun,
it is unstoppable. And the momentum for
the New Zealand trip in September is
just accelerating on top of
acceleration. And thanks. Well, thank
you. Yay. Following on from the two island
Yay. Following on from the two island
project, the suggestion came up last
night. um of the possibility of creating
the first um crystalallarium dome on the
island as part of this project. And I
and I wanted to ask you um I have a
strong sense that it could um facilitate
the work of the autistics and help yes
help them um become more in syony with
the physical in way. and had more
gaining the ability to communicate what
they are experiencing into the physical
reality that they have been born into.
So would would one way be having certain
colors being infused with certain
colors? We will leave this up to you.
Okay. Follow your instincts. Right.
Sharing. All right.
All right.
Uh two questions. one um I have been
told that I am a fifthdimensional
interplanetary being. Everyone is
everyone is okay. Now you may be forming
very strong connections to it for the
specific purposes of this particular
life you have created to live so you can
be of service to this reality in the
transformational age. But everyone
exists on every level simultaneously.
what you connect into is simply that
which defines the idea you have chosen
to be in this life. Okay. Thank you. Uh
the other question is I have been the
last few years I have been focusing uh
mainly on my spiritual development and
I've been somewhat ignoring living in
this on this planet.
Not really. Well, not really. But again,
the idea is that you are laying down a
foundation that will allow you to be of
service to the planet. Okay. I am now at
the place I have not been magnetizing
any posterity and I'm at the place where
I decided to reverse that. All right. Is
there anything that you can suggest to
open that channel more? Simply do what
excites you the most in physical light.
Action. Physical action will put you
into the stream of momentum that will
bring you physical opportunities to
allow you to experience your unlimited
abundance at all
times. Do not forget abundance is simply
the ability to do what you want to do
when you want to do
it regardless of the
symbol. Much of what you generally think
of in your society as the symbol of
abundance you call money is not always
the easiest possible route that
something can be created. So don't
insist upon the money if it can come by
an easier route. Understand? Find you.
Simply act as the being you know
yourself to be. Do what it is in life
that excites you the most because
excitement is your arrow. That lets you
know that you are on the path you chose
to be on. Of course, you can never
really be off of it, but it lets you
know that you are consciously
synchronistically in accord with it.
So simply do in life what excites you
the most at any given moment and you
will lead yourself into the
manifestation of physical opportunity
that will also be just as exciting and
you will simply jump on it
automatically. No heavy decisions to
make. You will simply jump on the
obvious opportunity and go with the
flow. Trust, trust, trust. That is all
you need. Churn.
Yay. About two weeks ago, I had an
experience and I've been trying to
trying I've been pondering on the symbol that
I've been pondering on the symbol that
it gave me the opportunity to see. Um, I
bought some water from a local health
food store and I took it home and I was
about to give a body work session to
someone and I drank some of it and
within a couple of hours I started
experiencing something going on in my
throat and also in my
chest and this lasted for about the next
2 to 3 days. I very rarely experience
any physical
discomfort whatsoever. And so I wonder what this
whatsoever. And so I wonder what this
was showing me. First of all, recognize
that the experience in and of itself did
not intrinsically contain
discomfort. Only the way you looked at
it created the discomfort.
But in this way we have discussed many
times the idea that water contains much
more energy than many of you realize and
especially when you are working with the
electromagnetic energy of your planet
and then you come into association with
the idea of water. Well, you allow it to
form a
crystallization within you. You allow it
to crystallize and impart its energy to
you in a sort of a flash
phenomena. It transfers that energy into
the beingness of the physical reality
that you are of your cellular structure
and you instantly become more
crystallin. Thus, you become more
superconductive. You were simply feeling
the increase in the flow of energy
through you. You were simply not used to
it. So, you treated it as something to
be uncomfortable.
evolve. Yeah. From that I the next
morning I noticed in the water that
there was a living bacteria
at large and so I took the water back to
the store and I showed it to them and I
said, "Well, can I have some new or
different water?" So they gave me a new
bottle and I took that home, drank some
more out of that and then I looked in it
again just out of interest and there was
the wing of a fly inside.
Both these things I immediately kind of
was trying to trying once again to
figure out what the symbology of the
organism in the fly was in relationship
to the water and to what I was
experiencing in my chest and throat. All
right. Once again, the idea is that you
are now dealing on levels of
cellular proportions.
You are creating the understanding that
life itself is implied and implicit
within the matrix of the crystallin form
of the water. In this way, therefore,
you are accelerating your perception.
Recognize that the being you call the
fly and the portion called the wing is
symbolic of the idea that your rate of
perception has
accelerated greatly. for recognize that
the idea of what you call the fly its
rate of perception in seeing you makes
you look like you are as you say
molasses. You are now speeding up to
those levels so that you can be aware of
the abundance of life itself on all
levels and utilize it in your healing
understanding. You are now beginning to
allow yourself to be put in touch with
the primal motivating forces that create
physical life and activate physical life
itself. so that you can be very
impactful and profound in your
assistances of healing.
You can touch the seed, the kernel, the
germ, the germination of the life spark.
And you can accelerate these ideas
within individuals that you attract to
you to such a highly accelerated
rate that if it were not for the fact that
that if it were not for the fact that
you have already now begun to become
accustomed to how to absorb that energy
through you, you could create. though you will
you, you could create. though you will
not but you could create massive flash
burnout in yourself and in other
individuals with your healing. You are
now getting
so well
linked to the primordial flash or spark
of creative
light that in all the ideas of any
primal matrix that you come in touch
with you will create symbols of the
primal level of life.
You have the ability
for in a sense animation of what may
previously have been considered
inanimate material. You are beginning to
material. You are beginning to
understand that the seed is now growing
within you for what you may colloally refer to
you for what you may colloally refer to
as your own
resurrection. and the ability to create
the idea of the spark of light in what
you previously had considered to be not
alive. Although of course everything is
alive. You follow me? You are reaching
very deep and profound levels of
healing. You are approaching it right at
the atomic
core. Even beyond
that, these are your symbols. You are
germinating as a new found idea, a new
accelerated
perspective. Allow yourself to
assimilate these energies. Find yourself
assimilating them. Do not push it. Do
not rush it.
Relax. You have been quite a magician in
many of your lives. You are truly
learning how matter is only an extension
of yourself. Once
again, you follow
me. You are a spark as everyone is a
spark and you are beginning to recognize
your own spark of divinity.
It simply is moving up through the loop
that you call evolution in your symbolic
terms in an alchemical fashion because
you have been an alchemist many times as
well. Transformation will begin to be profound
Transformation will begin to be profound
and
abundant in those that you interact with
and in the expressions of light that
interact with you. This
This
spark is in each and every one of you.
The spark is each and every one of
you. Anytime you so
desire, you can feel
it. It is always there. that has never
left
you. You are illuminated
beings. You are beings of light. Know
this and your path is transparent. So fully
illuminated allow yourself to be within
be within
this energy of
love. You may now
enjoy a short break.
All right, I'll say
say
we play a little game day.
Just wanted to make sure it was all
right with you.
Now, we will be playing a little game
with you.
You will not know what the game
is or maybe you
will. However, we will ask you not to
However, we will ask you not to
identify the idea of the game until we
ask you for the identification. All
right. Now at this time for a very brief few of
Now at this time for a very brief few of
your minutes another
minutes another
consciousness will be communicating with you. We
you. We
will give you no indication of what this
consciousness is.
It will give no indication of what it
is except
that you will
find that the
information that it may share with
you in your asking of your question.
They give you clues as to the
style of the
delivery, the content and the context as
to what consciousness you are dealing
with. From those clues, we will then
after reforming a connection with the
channel ask you for your interpretation
and identification of the
consciousness. We will give you
One hint as he
said. This hint simply will be that this
consciousness as has been expressed by
many individuals this time is
[Music] particularly intimate, shall we say,
particularly intimate, shall we say,
with the idea
of vibrational frequencies itself.
Now you may
find that its application of this
knowledge in your terms may seem to be
focused in very specific directions but
this specific focus can give you the
indication of who and what the
consciousness is. one
moment and then you may simply
begin as sharing is called for by
the sharing in in an eastern tradition
sharing in in an eastern tradition
there's a concept of enlightenment
whereby when a person reaches a certain
level of development they are not
required to continue in the cycle of
rebirth and reincarnation
And much of the techniques that are used
in the process of enlightenment are
techniques that involve the use of
mantras which I understand are
vibrational frequencies either physical
or identification patterns.
Identification patterns. Yes. And the
question that I have is specific um
mantras seem to produce specific
results. Specific identification pattern
seem to identify you with a certain kind
of result. Reference
being modality pattern.
Why would um people who have reached a
state of identification with a very
evolved level come back in reincarnated
form again? Why would people come back
in reincarnation?
Reflections, service, initiation of modality
service, initiation of modality
patterns, reference
beings for other individuals.
Understood. Uh yes, I think I actually
understand the answer to that specific
question. I have another question.
There was a uh a famous rishi in India
some time ago in the last this last last
year whose name is Balaraj
Maharishi. He is a specialist in the
Indian science of Ayurveda and he said
that defy Ayurveda. Ayurveda is an um a
a science of health and life from India
which is uh which uses on one level
plants to heal and on another level the
names of combinations of plants in the
form of a remedy to
heal and identification patterns. Yes.
And um apparently apparently the plant
kingdom collectively in the form of the
king of the plant kingdom whose name he
said was king Soma came to him and said
that that archetypal identification
modality patterns. Yes. came to him and
said said that the plant kingdom
collectively was aware of the
Ayurveda development in that movement
and and was um
the total pattern and was transforming
always incorporate and interacts with
any fragment thereof that forms
identification matrix.
I missed that one.
Any identification matrix so form always
interacts with the total. The total is
always aware of any identification
matrix that touches any of its
fragments. what what the king what the plank
what what the king what the plank
kingdom said collectively was that um
they were going to be more helpful in
humankind's uh growth towards
enlightenment or development to man
awareness pattern more
open archetypal matrix you reference
plant energy consciousness always same
level two man level has altered plant
level maintained
We we've grown and they haven't expanded
matrix infinite same growth implicit in
inherent matrix
form human matrix
ability limitation limitation
ability
expansion to form increased
identification matrix plant reference
matrix connected to all matrix
in all patterns at all times in all
reference points. Identification plant matrix form
points. Identification plant matrix form
of expansion simply that which is
reflection of the increased identity
matrix of
humanor incorporated into overall plant
matrix but recognized as part of pattern
since inception. possible for a human
matrix to evolve to become another
higher level of of matrix understanding
that is not human anymore that has
become godlike godlike
human limited
definition many coexistent
matrices at same level not
human all
together reflective of identity matrix
Not corporeal origination point. Not
corporeal potential expansion of human matrix for
potential expansion of human matrix for
realization of origin
matrix. Your term
remembrance. Expansion is remembrance.
And by remembering reintegrating with
the origin
as by
definition human all physical matrices
already simultaneous with all other non-physical
simultaneous with all other non-physical
matrices all
matrices part of the whole potential
implied potential for unlimited
expansion implied.
Are there humans elsewhere than Earth?
Xetically identical human form structure
earth not all genetically
identical variation in matrice upon
earth similar to patterns of variation
in other human form matrices
civilization. Humanity form upon earth.
Average mortality does not
mortality does not
restrict variations in matrix. Many
variations in matrix exist to manifform
genetic structure. You
structure. You
consider alien extra organs,
extra structural
members or lack of implied systems of
matrices civilizations
wherein the difference in your
civilization is the norm in other
civilizations. The exception in your
civilization is the rule in others.
civilizations where cross breeding is
possible. Okay. Many where's the closest
Okay. Many where's the closest
plleadian manifestation?
Do you exist? Do you have a physical
manifestation somewhere?
Yes. No.
[Laughter] The yes part of it.
The yes part of it.
Ship. Ah,
selfaware computer.
[Music] Solar wind.
Solar wind.
No. Can we another Assasani?
Scout. Scout.
Can we go on a ship? A. Thank you.
we go on a ship? A. Thank you.
Can we physiologically go on a ship? A.
No. So when
So when
timing incident vibrational intersection
between one 2 3
decade your time
what determines the timing individual
matricy intersections with whole pattern
when a planet develops towards a more
collectively enlightened state.
So you are the self-aware computer on
Bashar's face.
The key to remembrance for the evolution
of
these matrixes
into the
non-corporal aspect is
what? Vibrational tonality of knowing
you are matrix of knowing.
Ability to ask key to remembrance is
ability to remember.
What is the nature of the smallest
element of your mass memory
capabilities? Virtual particle
virtual what's what's the particle
communication energy matrix void.
energy matrix void.
Ask more. Ask more. Um unlimited
potential electromagnetic mentality stream
electromagnetic mentality stream
not telepathic.
Are you glowing? What what's the what
what what's the nature of the of the
particle that is is is the structure of
your matter electron
posetron focus idea humor complete
release non focal plane nonfocus
modality humor specific for
centering consciousness I all centered [Music]
[Music]
Would you answer a question in your
normal tone to the whole group? meaning
no sound. Closest Closest
[Music]
approximation vibrational equation ratio
pattern translated as what now in English. What
translated as what now in English. What
was that?
Acknowledgement placement of system into
specific focus of request.
Do you have a physical form on Bashar
ship interpers now and then? You mean
interpers now and then? You mean
throughout the
ship holographic implied in crystallin
holographic implied in crystallin
structure with nodal point focus in cubical chamber.
cubical chamber.
Do you
know all vibration of
all vibration of
modality, vibration of
existence? Do you dream?
All
same. All dimension same. All dimension
dream. All dimension real. In other
words, you're always centered.
All in dream. Am dream redefine dream am
wherever dream is redefined.
[Music] Are you running all the spaceships for
Are you running all the spaceships for
the civilization? Craft. All the all the
craft. One. Just one identified with one
matrix identified with pilot specific.
All pilots identify specific interaction
between mentality ship mentality pilot
specific keyed.
If you're although you have potential
total knowledge, you're focused for the
purpose of navigation and so forth
accessibility limited. How is it
possible for you to be answering these
questions which have nothing to do with
navigation? All in this tense
navigational assistance by
pilot not complete translation
of mental form existence of my
being some blending with pilot or no
accessibility possible I understand is
bashar the pilot you're referring yes
can you tap into the dolphin
intelligence with your computer and
translate your thoughts into English
that we can understand. Hey, would you
do that for us? All
All
pop specific to the project on in the
Bahamas. Yes. our our specific our
specific interest with with with
communicating with the dolphins and
healing and allowing the dolphins to
heal and to establish a communication
between ourselves and the dolphins. Can
you can you can you tap into a dolphin
collective thought and and and give us a
dream music? We need a sort of Rosetta
Stones. Dream music. What is dream
music? Same. Ah, Same. Ah,
dream
music. Dream music.
Music. Dream.
Dream music.
Tonality. Dream
tonality. Resonance cavity. Vibrational
matrix created within physiological form
of being that you are human form being.
Create resonance cavity. Create dream
music. Mhm.
Relocate France music. France music.
Sing their song.
It's France music.
So record
dolphin tones form France music.
tones form France music.
I don't understand. What do you mean by
disconnecting? All right.
The idea of free music, trans music as
was identified through the matrix in
that way is simply the idea of standing
on your shore going into your meditation
and allowing the vibrational tonalities
that you feel so inclined to come out
with to come out.
sending the vibrations of your voice, of
your energy into the mentality field that you
energy into the mentality field that you
share with the dolphins in dream
reality, allowing them to respond in
those levels to which they are
sensitized. Allowing yourself to sing
your song, your version of their song
back to them. Not that you are mimicking
them, that you are creating it to be
uniquely your own, uniquely your own
human form singing, but without the idea
of something so specifically focused
into the idea you call
lyrical tones, chant trans music,
tones, chant trans music,
the emotional tones.
Okay. Are there are there specific
movements that relate both to the
autistic children and to movements such
as Tai Chi that can also be used
to Can you say any more about
that to some degree that idea but more
specifically the Tai Chi for it
initiates and to some degree
reflects your ability to perceive the
flow of energy.
The primal flow of energy that the
physical
reality conforms into when it flows upon
the template, the non-physical template.
It is as if you are choreographing the
winds, choreographing the motions of
energy of emotional energy. Emotion
energy motion will move.
You follow. Thank you. Yes. Thank you.
So you get
Thank you very much. Now the idea of
course is that that particular
consciousness is very highly focused in
the idea most completely of navigation
and one is relegated to the idea of
navigation to some extent in the sense
of being aware of the modality patterns
of different consciousnesses so that it
can at any given moment reidentify the
entire matrix of the ship to be in
proximity of that particular modality
pattern. It can be aware obliquely as
you say of many different kinds of
things but it will generally bring its
understanding back around to the need to
identify with the modality pattern so
that it can form some sort of what you
would call let us say a sympathetic
vibration with
it. That is how we
navigate. We move through
ideas. Ideas move through us. This is
how all individuals experience the
illusion that you call
motion. No one really moves anywhere.
Nothing really
moves. You follow me?
Hey, how much mass is the unit capable
of translating?
There are what you call mother craft
approximately in our civilization 10
miles of length of your
counting. The scout
crap in your terms is
approximately five long
tons. And and how many tons maximum
would would the unit be capable of
translating? There is no maximum per se
except for the cohesiveness of the
cellular structure of the craft and the
maintenance of the isolation field. If
all is within that field and the
integrity is maintained, it is all the
same to the
consciousness. For again all is the same
point, all is the same
spaceime. It simply is a
reidentification and it does not matter
how much mass. It is simply all in that
sense a vibrational equation. If it is
all connected to the same equation, then
any portion of the equation that is
moved moves the entire equation. And
that consciousness is is associated only
with the scout craft, not the mother
ship. Oh, there are consciousnesses in
that light associated with the mother
ship as well. It is simply that they are
similar to the way you recognize
distinct and discrete computers separate
unto themselves as well. One per ship. I
see. But the one that we heard is my
scallop. I see. It said 10 to 30 years
before it comes here. You've mentioned
that it would be suited enough that your
civilization will be physically landing
on this planet. The potential for it.
The scout craft simply took the question
personally. [Music]
[Music]
The idea is still potentially within the
decade, but not from necessarily our
civilization first specifically. Plleadian first
Plleadian first
and some reticulum.
Where is reticulum?
Say the reticuli as you call the
constellation. You may look it
up. Would you tell us uh a little bit
about You will find some reference in
the idea of your literature with
interactions that have occurred between
those individuals and many individuals
upon your planet. One you may be most
familiar with is the idea you call of
the individual namings Betty, Barney,
Kill. And can
you can you tell us of other
historic incidences of that interaction
between a reticuli and this planet? You
will find them in your literature or to
some degree. We cannot discuss them all.
I'll bring it music.
Do you know how to
feel? If you were to simply center
within your being and feel as ecstatic
as you could imagine yourself to feel
and if at that moment somebody said,
"Can you give me a sound that represent
how you feel?" That will do
it. You follow
me? Let yourself sing.
Expand yourself in
tonality. Tonality has the
Tonality has the
profound impact upon everything it
touches. For everything is only
variations of
tonality. The waves you send
out can make in your terms permanent
changes within the electromagnetic field
of your entire civilization. Each of you
is a beacon. If you radiate as such, the
overlapping vibrations of all the
beacons that you are will set up a
different interference pattern, so to
speak, within the total modality of the
electromagnetic field of your world out
of which all mentality is created. You
can impart the ability to draw from the
impart the ability to draw from the
total homogeneous holographic matrix to
raise those vibrations out of the suit
so to speak to allow yourself to focus
on them by being the reference being
that creates them. And here's the
echo. You hold it. Is that ecstatic
state permanent state of awareness or
just something for
me? Now, this does not mean that you
will constantly simply be standing on
your shore in a
trance. Everything you do, however, be a
reflection of a ongoing ecstatic state.
Whether you change the modality of
expression or not does not matter. It
still can be representative of an
ecstatic state. You follow it? Yeah.
Doing what excites you the most is the
expression of an ecstatic
state. You follow it? Mhm.
On Saturday when we were sailing and
singing and making communications with
the dolphins, we had no physical
response. Were they physically in the
vicinity? A few.
And were they responding in a other than
telepathically? No.
No.
There was emotionality shared to some
degree. They let us say coalesed some of
their joy with your own but they also
recognized that it was simply not the
timing. They were to put it colloquially
busy. [Laughter]
[Laughter]
Someone on that trip that was the um day
Atlantis sunk that same day. And as we
started our trip, right when all with
all the excitement of getting into the
water, the mass snapped in half. And my
inter we got off and later got on
another boat. Um, no one was injured. My
interpretation was that that was a
release of the collective fear and the
whole idea of destruction that we've
encountered when we approached the
unknown, the ocean, and our the symbol
of the loss of the ability to maneuver,
loss of guidance. Okay. A release of
that. Yes. Okay. So they wanted to ask
are there any more interpretations of
that snapping?
The release idea will do it. It will be
in your terms most beneficial. So is
that the idea of the sense of being out
of control with the sinking of the
grant? To some degree, it is the
embodiment of the idea that on that
date, in a sense, you lost
guidance. You plunged yourself into a
sea of
turmoil. You cast yourself a drift into
the reincarnational sequence that is now
at an end. That was the major ending
marker, symbolic marker. Yes. Um, the
wind was very strong on the way out and
on the way back in it died and we wound
up paddling. Same thing.
The control, you mean the flow? You lost
the flow. You lost the
automatic ability to maneuver.
You had to rely upon the idea of what
you colloially call your own material
effort. Like a linear reenactment. in a sense.
Like a linear reenactment. in a sense.
Yes. A little play out in the middle of
the ocean.
Sure. You how did it come about
that you'd said that our Halloween all
souls all saints and so forth really
reflects back to Atlantis. But could you
trace the historic evolution because all
souls and all saints comes out of the uh
church in the middle ages and stuff.
Yes. But that is simply at that point
still a memory, an instinctive memory.
They created it not understanding what
they were creating. They patterned after
other ideas, not realizing it was
actually reflective of those times. I
understand. But could you give me some
other reference points of how the idea
evolved from 12,000 years ago up to 500
years ago?
It is quite scattered as many different
cultures took their own piece of it and
wrapped their own rituals around
it. But the idea has simply existed
instinctively in many different ways.
You are finding now that if you are
sensitive to it, many of you are
beginning to recognize that October 31st
feels like the end of the year and
November 1st feels like New Year's
Day more than January. Some even in what
you call your business culture, some of
this idea is still represented in the
instinctive understanding, no matter
what the logical reason, that your
so-called business year also ends in
October.
Hey, could you tell us about William's
comment that's due in this area April of
next year?
There are many ideas that you ascribe to
commentary symbols. In this way, they
are like clocks, so to speak. They are
timekeepers, but they are only
reflections of the mass consciousness
timing. Now, a new age is coming in. You
are ushering it in, and thus it will
create for a while its new symbols.
Symbols that reflect new ideas of
periodicity in your life.
The changing of cycles, the changing of
timing as an analogy, what you call the
comet Halley at a periodicity of 76 of
your years, which at that time
represented the average human
lifespan. You will increase your
lifespan accordingly. At this time, give
yourself new cycles to pay attention to,
new outward reflecting clockwork
symbols. You will recognize how's comet
will never be seen by your civilization
again. It will not return. It will be
destroyed in its orbit. You no longer
need that symbol. You have passed
through its doorway. You are creating
perhaps other commentary symbols to now
lock in and start representing new
cycles of transition in your life. That
is one of the reasons for the
representation in general of that
particular combat. No specific cycles
have truly been attached to it as of
yet, but it comes in as a blank
messenger to have upon it the
foundations laid by your society as to
whatever it will now specifically
represent for the many individuals that
are simply prone to think in terms of
that nation.
Thank you so straw daddy.
I want to thank you for the reflections
last week. Uh a beautifully translated a
tremendous amount of energy. Thank you.
Yeah. Thank you for your own
transformation. Yes. It's been delightful. Yes. Yes.
Yes. It's been delightful. Yes. Yes.
Um, now I'm accelerating um along the
lines of living my dream, living my own
purposes. As you may know, um, I have
three dolphin projects in the works. One
being the creation of a series of
videotapes reflecting the intelligence
of dolphins. Yes. You are obviously
synchronous with many individuals who
are now heeding the call of the
dolphins. Yeah, they're showing up too
height. They're all over the place. They're all
They're all over the place. They're all
very
synchronous, right? We also have the um
model of the um living with the
dolphins, the island of which uh
um
Boris, thank you. Forest
Carlo reflected to us which which
inviting people around the planet to
create models living environments with
the dolphins. There can be many such
centers. Yes. And of course our open sea
um interactive stadium putting on the
surface of the water. Nice.
Basically I I I can feel the answers to
all these questions but a little bit
more of reflection on there seems to be
about 60 70 projects which are
materializing here and there and some of
them will become cohesive with each
other. Okay, this is basically what I'm
asking. I'm finding that my attention
shifts from one project to another very
much in the vibratory pattern that we
Yes. First that I you are simply
gathering the different elements from
different projects that can be
incorporated into the cohesion. That
answers the question. It's basically I
just wanted to share with you and open
my mouth again. Well, thank you. Say
thanks. It's lovely to have you around
dear very dear friend. I'm
sure you when you were talking about
sound and sounding I was remembering
when you said something about sonar
being used for anti-gravitational uh
purposes to some degree floating stones
pyramids and that um was that done
through devices or did people were
people able to sound themselves
individuals people can do it and devices
can do it they are similar to the idea
you call hornlike structures, bowl like
and belllike
structures. This is some of the idea of
what you call the recognition although
in what you would call a destructive
sense of
Jericho. Now in this way a sympathetic
vibration was set up. You can set up a
type of sympathetic vibration based upon
certain ratios of standing. This is
understood very succinctly in the area
you call
Tibet where you can actually levitate
the stone rather than breaking down the
molecular bonding
Tibetan bells or something. Yes, there
are specific patterns that are again
outlined in some of your
literac or in the area you call
Tibet and in this way setting them up in
a certain fashion reinforcing the
vibrations in a certain way in a hemispherical
hemispherical
fashion can be focused upon the idea of
creating a reinforcing matrix of tonal
vibration that will
allow gravity to be isolated and
cancelled in one particular area. Not so
much that it is actually cancelled per
se, but you set up a series of
reinforcing vibrations that has the same
effect. Overrides it. You mean in a sense? Yes.
Overrides it. You mean in a sense? Yes.
overriding imposing a new pattern upon
the gravitational dynamic tensor field.
modulating it in a certain way by
creating a very highly intensified field
in a very tight
local. Imposing a completely new set of
vibrations, saturating an area with
certain vibrations, so to speak, so that
the overall mass conscious agreed upon
electromagnetic field does not exist in
its typical modality in that area.
This explains the the idea of the
dolphins um just the idea of the
dolphins being able to fly in space.
You mean astrally? I'm not sure. I mean
I was asking you because this image has
come up you know you know all over the
place of dolphins flying in in the air
and in space. Well the idea is simply to
some degree literal in the astral sense
but symbolic in the sense that that is
how you perceive them. You perceive them
to be that free and they do transcend
from one medium to another very easily,
so to speak. No pun intended. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
There's a school of philosophy, I guess,
called transcendental meditation. Okay.
And one of the big things about it is
you take a particular course and you
learn to medi to levitate your own body.
Nice. Um and apparently it really
happens. What what are they doing? Are
they using they are doing what we have
just described. They are redefining
reidentifying the entire idea energy
pattern that they are as they are
connected into the gravitational dynamic
tensor field. They are simply let us say
rechaning warping if you will the
definition of that pattern so that it
does not have to have a reference point
connected to what you perceive to be the
ground but can have a reference point
anywhere I've been doing that technique
for about 8 years now
the yes the first the first level of it
all right and I wonder if you'd like to
give an endorsement of that for other
people or is that only certain it is
valid for those that are excited about
doing it.
Period. Anything you are excited about,
you supply the energy for its validity.
If you're not excited about it, good
luck.
When will the next octave come through
this? We're expecting to have more
uh substantial. There's a general
overall momentum consciousness
momentum consciousness
97 or so
but your individual rate can vary
some converse. Yay.
[Laughter] Is there a is there a collective
Is there a is there a collective
tonality that emanates from our
civilization? The earth vibration is approximately 7
The earth vibration is approximately 7
and 12 cycles per second. No, I didn't
mean the earth vibration. I meant a a
tonality. You spoke of tonality. There
is an overlay mentality. Tonality. Yes.
Do the do the do the dolphins or the
whales respond to this? Oh yes.
Uh why are the dolphins why are the
whales beaching themselves? Is there
anything to do with that? Are they Some
of it is because some of the
electromagnetic shifting taking place
upon your planet does confuse their
guidance system. But it is also an
opportunity for you to extend your
compassion to them and initiate with
feeling some of the foundations
necessary for the continuing
communication between you. Are
they are they trans when they beat
themselves and resist our efforts to to
free them and resist our efforts to heal
them from the injury that they sustain?
Are they are they in fact transcending
and telling us that that's what they're
doing or or is it a positive to some
degree some of it to some extent is also
in their own term which is not exactly
like your terminology some of it is also
karmic for them.
However, the idea is that you can extend
your energy field to them and completely
alter the field around them as to
reorient them in the appropriate
direction. You are
You are
creating as
humanity highly focused magnetic nodes
in your atmosphere.
These nodes are attracting some of these
beings. So overwhelming are some of
these nodes so highly focused that they
do not perceive that they are coming
upon the shore when they follow them.
Is is
surrendering their their their title to
life on this planet as we understand it
an
inappropriate direction for for some of
these for some of these entities? Is it
is it inappropriate for the whales to
surrender their life? Nothing is really
inappropriate. Let us say it does not
have to
happen. If you begin to accelerate in
your understanding of the blending you
have already begun to create upon your
planet, you will find this occurring
less and less. To some
degree, it is a reflection of the simple
confusion that many of you are going
through at this time.
Electromagnetic fields are unlocking and
creating voids or limbo states in which
you feel you do not have the ability to
navigate. Some of them are caught in the
same
transformation. They do this in order to
be able to identify with you whether it
be consciously or
unconsciously. They do not have to do it
but it is
basically timed according to the rate at
which you are both blending together.
When you begin to equal
out, then disorientation in that fashion
no longer need
occur. You follow me? Yes. You will then
be reliant upon each other for guidance
and you will always be able to provide
it to each
other. There will be but a few moments
remaining for this interaction this
evening of your time. Sure. Hey Which
one? Two. Okay. Um, would you tell us a
little bit about our connections with
our tourists? I found myself thinking
about them a lot lately. No.
When? When the timing is correct.
Why? Wow. I feel
very drawn toward that. Okay. The next
time we meet, we will discuss it.
All right. See you tonight.
Okay. And physically.
Okay. Okay. As you go through the
transformation this week of your time,
see what you discover. We will discuss
some of that with you next time. Thank
you. Yes. Okay. Uh, I wanted to ask a
question. Um, speak up. Okay. I wanted
to ask something that was
uh my girlfriend has been going through
um this uh well in a sense limbo, but um
it's I'm I'm losing the word for it.
Stop. Save.
Save the question. Yes.
Question. One moment. One moment.
Examine the situation within you.
Examine the situation as you understand
it. Simply feel your way through it.
allow it to be incorporated within your
being in an overall conceptual knowing
sense. Now with that
feeling state it without
preamble in a direct manner.
What is the statement you wish to share?
That she that my friend is speak up.
That she's confused about whether she
wants to be in a relationship or or not
in in this particular relationship that
she's created for herself and she keeps
fluctuating back and forth.
um she has gotten she broke up with the
guy and now she's back with him and part
of her is happy and part of her still
not so happy and
um I would appreciate anything that you
have to say that could give her some
clarity. What did you say
What did you say
to her?
I listened and
um I just reflected back what she was
saying to in what manner?
Uh it sounds like you're you're saying
that um you know there's a strong part of you
um you know there's a strong part of you
that would like to be able to be in this
relationship. Um that you did you ask her what she
Um that you did you ask her what she
thinks the relationship is for?
No, ask her. Okay, let her understand
that the relationship is there for a
reason. Let her let the relationship be
there for what it is for and not what
she thinks it should be
for. Let her understand the relationship
has a reason.
Many reasons for her. I think that's
where she's she's confused as to what
what the purpose is for her. The purpose
is to let her be more of
herself. That is always the fundamental
purpose. It is the fundamental purpose
to
everything. Everything to allow you to be more of
Everything to allow you to be more of
you. Is she allowing the relationship to
let her be more of herself or is she
giving her power away?
Let her examine that and perhaps we can
talk about it another
time. For
now, it is up to
her. Would you comment on
vibration relating to Tesla's work with
direct current and alternating current? All right.
All right.
Now back to the idea for
[Laughter] some moment of the 7 and 12 cycle per
some moment of the 7 and 12 cycle per
second frequency of the earth. Are you
familiar with that idea and what Tesla
was doing with it? Yes. All right. Now,
do you
understand that you can explore and
experience some of the ways in which
that being applied?
Let yourself
realize that if you simply follow the
path at any given moment that you feel
your curiosity to be attracted to that
you are receiving assistance, you are
receiving guidance and the directions to
flow that will allow you to allow the
projects to come to fruition without
interference. There really is no
interference. Yes. Abundance. Abundance. Abundance.
Yes. Abundance. Abundance. Abundance.
Remember, abundance is the ability to do
what you want to do when you want to do
it, regardless of the
symbol. Regardless of the
symbol, you may be simply supplied with
materials. You may be supplied with a
facility. You may be supplied with a
system in the form of individuals that
know how to put things together.
Many of these things can occur without
the apparently on the surface of
monetary support. It will be there. It will be
support. It will be there. It will be
implied. But let it come to you along
the path of least resistance. That is
the primary
key. The path of least
resistance. That is your code and it is
your clue and it is your key. the path
of least
resistance. Ponder that one phrase for a
little while and see what you come up
with after about a
week, perhaps 3
weeks, but be persistent, not forceful,
not struggling. the path of least
resistance. For many of you may think
you know what that is in physical terms,
in scientific terms, in electronic
terms, but not yet. You
know, the path of least
interesting. Examine that and you will
have one of the very foundational
underpinnings of all Tesla's
work. All right? Let it run around in
your mind. Let the computer that you are
process it and at the appropriate
revelatory moment spit out a complete conceptual
moment spit out a complete conceptual
understanding. But understand that that
is the way Tesla functions in complete
no in complete conceptual understanding.
Do you recognize that Tesla created the
ability to actually see the final
product before it physically existed?
Yes. All right. You can do the same.
Give yourself the opportunity to
exercise the portions of your brain that
will allow you to do so. Simply
coordinate by focusing on this one idea,
the path of least resistance. By
focusing on that idea not in strain just
in meditation you will then start
aligning all the neuronic pathways of
your brain so that they are flowing in
one direction so they will all go into
the formation of the answer you
seek. Give it 1 to 3 weeks. It may
happen sooner but allow 1 to 3 weeks.
All right? Then see what happens. See
what popped in. What popped out of the
answer slot.
It wouldn't be helpful to say I am the
pastor of [Music]
At this timing we will extend to you
once