All right, sir. How are you all this
evening at your time as you create time
to exist?
We will begin with an interaction with
the idea of energy. Energy. The energy
that you are, the energy that you feel
yourself to be. In this way, recognize
that incent you are a part of the
creation of the physicalized universe.
The physicalized universe's first state
of being. After all, it takes its form
and function from the idea that we have
referred to as the template, the
non-physical template upon which the
idea of physical reality is built or
based. The first manifestation of the
physicalization of the universe in this
way will be the homogeneous energy field
that you call itself the primal
fundamental energy of all that is. Out
of this primary energy field, all that
you refer to as material is created, is
manifested, is formed, transformed,
reformed into many different concepts,
many different reflections, and many
different ideas of the primal energy
idea itself.
In this way recognize your
consciousness projects itself into that
primal energy field in a sense impresses
itself upon that primal energy field in
a sense and whatever idea you are being.
Whatever pattern you imagine yourself to
be, that is how your consciousness
projects itself into the idea of the
primal energy matrix and allows it to
take for substance gives it in a sense a
shell, a cloak to represent in physical
reality in material terms the idea you
are being as a consciousness.
Therefore, do recognize that the idea of
everything you are experiencing in your
physiological reality is once again not
so much
some different than yourself that you
are experiencing but you are actually
experiencing another version of what you
are who you are. You yourself are the
experience that you are
having. You are the experience that you
are having forward. In this
having forward. In this
way, all the physical reality, all of
the emotional atmosphere in which any
particular manifestation or experience
does occur in your life in a seemingly
objectified manner. All of that
materiality, all of that atmosphere and
all of that projected
emotionality, every subtle
nuance, it is all you in different
manifesting forms, different manifesting
reflections back to
yourself. You have created the idea of
yourself to be what you call physical
reality. In this particular
manifestation of physical reality, there
are many, but in this particular
manifestation of the idea, you are
being, you are playing out as your
particular unique physical
reality, physicalized realization.
You simply have created a great deal of
what we have discussed to be limitation,
separation, so that you could
explore all of the ideas of what it
means to be limited, which if you do not
forget that you created this reality,
you would not be able to do.
Therefore, you have created yourselves
to be the idea of a
reality whose only
cognition basically fundamentally
immediately is a material reflection
seemingly outside yourself. So that you can in
outside yourself. So that you can in
fact feel as if you are in a material
universe rather than knowing that the
material universe is what you
are. But that is what you are now
beginning to explore from the idea of
integration because this as we have said
many times is the end of the cycle of
limitation. You are beginning to
experience integration blending more and
more and more awareness of more of
yourself. And in this way you are
beginning to blend the dream,
imagination and physical realities into
one to experience all the ideas of this
transformation. experiencing the
experiencing the
disorientation, the confusion, the limbo
state, the seemingly
surrealistic attitudes and atmospheres
that you may encounter from time to time
that allow you to feel disassociated
from the material physicality that you
have been used to experiencing for so
many hundreds of thousands of
years. Now you find yourself integrating
and beginning to see through the
illusion that you have created a
physical materiality. It has served you
and served you well. But an illusion, a
tool, and a creation it is
nonetheless. Now you will continue for
some time based upon your choice of
course to experience another type of
physical materiality. what we have
referred to as fourth density, a little
bit more
rarified, higher degree of energy
expression. And thus many of you now are
finding that as you are beginning to
acclimate to the idea of the new
accelerated energy, but are still
thinking that you exist in the old
terminology of foot density. Many of you
may begin and have been feeling this
energy in different ways as long as you
are attached in comparison to your body
and what you think your body can and
cannot tolerate. Many of you may feel
the acceleration of this energy in many
different ways according to what we have
described as fevers, flushings,
adrenaline rushes, anxiety rushes.
Many times pain in the spine, the
shoulder blades, the base of the neck,
migraines, sinus, pressure, palpitations of the
sinus, pressure, palpitations of the
heart, rushes of anxiety in the solar
plexus. All of these ideas are forth
density symptomatic. in this way simply
of new awareness of new levels of energy
that you are but still couched in old
terminology. You will assimilate, you
will acclimate. Do not fear it. It is simply
acclimate. Do not fear it. It is simply
one of the ways you can begin to
consciously be aware that you are
changing. You are
transforming. All of these different
manifestations lets you know something
is going on.
because you have created yourselves to
be a reality that has relied upon the
need for a process in order to become
something else. Then many of you still
have a little bit of the remnants of
some of these processes and that is the
only reason why you are feeling some of
these ideas to be taking some time and
working themselves through. But work
themselves through they
will for you are the idea of the
transformation itself. So transformation
is now what you all are all about. You
all follow along. Yes. Sharing. Lashar.
Yes. A couple of weeks ago you said that
third density is where we experience the
illusion that the objective
circumstances and people around us
create the subjective feelings within
something like that. I kind of in a
sense. Yes. The idea that your life is
affected by seemingly externalized
forces rather than the truly subjective
understanding that you are creating
those affectations within yourself and
projecting them to seemingly come from
somewhere outside of you. Okay. If if a
person reaches the stage where he no
longer blames or points fingers, does
that mean he has more or less achieved
identity? In a sense, a that will be the
beginnings of the fourth density
experience. There can be and will be
according to your choice of how long you
wish to remain in the fourth density
experience for the approximately 2 to
3,000 years it will last. There will be
more and more changes, physiological
changes, energy changes, sociological
changes that you will be able to witness
as you go along in Fort Vincent. But
that will be the beginning of your
willingness to consciously know that you
are now in fact in fourth density. And
is that how you would sum up the fourth
density where the subjective creates the
objective? Yes, in a sense. Knowing that
there really is no such thing as
objectivity. Knowing that you create
your reality totally. Fourth density is
taking responsibility for the creation
of your reality. acting like you
actually do in fact create your reality.
That is for density. Recognizing that
everything as we have said is
synchronicity and acting like it.
Everything is interconnected
holographically. Everything is the same
one thing manifesting in all the different
thing manifesting in all the different
multiaceted multi-dimensional ways that
it can simultaneously with regard to any
particular event.
Everything you experience is the same
one thing. Knowing that and acting like
you know it is living in forensity.
Living in the now. Living in the moment.
Forward. Yes. Thank you. You then
you have some experiences in my
dreams where I feel like I'm conscious
in my subconscious. Yes. I'm literally
having dreams where
I'm asking myself what the
interpretation of the dream is in the
dream while I'm in the dream
consciousness. You are recognizing that
there is only but one consciousness and
that the terminology of subconscious and
unconscious have simply been convenient
separations to allow you to remove
responsibility for the creations in your
life from you to someone else.
Therefore, now that you are all willing
to take responsibility, you will not
need the sub and unconscious
because you will know consciously that
you are creating your reality. And you
will not believe that there needs to be
any portions of yourself that are not
worthy of being completely out in the
open, outront, and equal with any other
portion. They do not necessarily now
need to be buried anywhere because you
are willing to face the total being that
you are. Well, then what is been the
difference between the subconscious and
the unconscious?
In this way, let us say it is simply a
matter of degree as to what you are
willing to face. You may say in that
sense therefore that the let us say
unconscious is where you bury the things
that you don't want to deal with right
now. The subconscious is maybe where you
put things that you are willing to deal
with a little
bit like what you might call the
clearing house. See if it is safe. Test it out in
house. See if it is safe. Test it out in
the subconscious before you truly let it
into the consciousness.
And then when you are through with that
one, you pull another idea from the
unconscious, plop it into the safety
zone of the subconscious. So you have
time to deal with it according to your
own pace. Then when you are ready, it
goes into the consciousness and so on
and so on. But now is the idea of
knowing that there is nothing you can
discover within your unconscious that
could possibly be of anything but
positive surface to you. So why allow it
to take that long? Well, then will this
all clear out? In other words, we
dissolve with the unconscious as we move
into this fourth density. By the time
we're completely in the fourth density,
will the unconscious be completely
dissolved or how is the correlation? In
a sense, you will simply know what you
need to know when you need to know it.
You will be living in the moment and you
will fear nothing.
So you will be consciously aware of
everything in your life as your
creation. Nothing mysterious, nothing
hidden, nothing oult.
Then you'll eventually move into
integrating with your higher self. In a
sense, that is still a form of
integration with your higher self, but
remaining in physiological terms. Fifth
density is the expression of synchronous
harmonious congruency with your
so-called higher self while still
remaining to some degree separated.
Fifth density in a sense then is
actually becoming the higher self.
Yes. Um I this was very interesting to
me the fact that uh the observation that
the third density appears to be composed
of dichotoies and polarities and these
various things. It is one of the
definitions that creates third density.
Right. Now it is not so much that third
density contains it. That is what
creates third density. Right. Okay. Now
what's interesting to me is that the
fourth density appears to be a dichotomy
of the third density. An opposite of it.
Is that was that the end? No, no, no,
no, no. Does not have to be. Do
recognize that even though you may be
able in third density to recognize
polarities, that does not necessarily
mean you have to experience the
negativity. Right? Therefore, it does
not have to be an opposite in that way.
I see. But it is, so to
speak, an opposite in terms perhaps
simply of the idea of going from
Not knowing you are creating your
reality to knowing that you are.
Yes. Um this this week I've experienced
a great deal of anger almost uh and
anger. Yeah. And and I have it's been
very very powerful anger. And anger is
powerful. Yeah. Well, uh I and I have
strived not to judge it. Strived not to
judge. Strived not to judge. That's rough. Oh,
Strived not to judge. That's rough. Oh,
you are judging so you will not judge.
Yeah, it's really rough. You know,
rough. If you say so. May I remind you
that natural quote unquote as you say
anger does not bring a negative feeling with
does not bring a negative feeling with
it. That's true. But if it lasts longer
than 15 seconds judgment that's right.
Now anger in itself truly is not so much
the idea to change the terminology of
anger but it is alignment. Yes. That is
all. When you see something that you
know is not the vibration of your
reality, you align into the vibration
you know to be true for you. Yeah. Now
when you judge what you are witnessing
and what you are aligning to then it
becomes negative. Then it becomes what
you usually refer to as
anger. But anger is only alignment. It
is that surge of knowingness that when
you see something, you immediately align
yourself to see how it is you relate to
that where you stand with reference to
that particular reality, that particular
belief. That is all. That does not mean
that you need to judge what it is you do
not prefer for yourself.
That is the only thing that creates the
negative anger is judging what has so
lovingly given you an opportunity to
understand what your reality actually is
very clearly. Yes. Uh what I've observed
is that there's a certain third density
viewpoint that certain people I have
come across oddly enough in this past
week um to reflect back to me. I I found
that I was actually irritated with them
and I and I thought Pamela I got I
thought of you and how lovingly you uh
are so willing to listen to everything
that we say and and I thought I always
have fun. Yes. Yes. I know you do. And I
was just noticing that I was it was an
honest feeling that I had and which I
don't particularly consider wonderful
but there's some judgment on it. Okay.
Um is simply that I was it almost
appeared so-called selfish and um uh
even though I understand that these
everyone is wonderful and all the all
those aspects we've discussed I
understand all of that. Nevertheless,
the honest gut feeling was one of
irritation and oh for God's sake, why
don't you just if you want to do this,
don't ask me to do it for you. Do it
yourself. Why are you looking to up to
me? All right, that sort of thing. And I
found myself really really angry about
all right. But once again, you do not
necessarily need irritation at the
understanding that individuals that come
to you in that way. Trying to give you
their power, you do not have to take it.
And in this way, in a sense, being
irritated is simply doing what they are
doing to you back to them. giving away
your power to them to give them the
ability to make you irritated rather
than simply reflecting to them that they
are just as powerful as you are and do
not need to approach you in that way by
giving their power away. Yes, I I
mentioned it. I see what you're saying.
All right. Thank you. Is your choice.
Thank you.
Go ahead. Um is there any truth to the
idea? Is there any truth?
Before you go on, allow me to remind you
the truth is composed of all truths.
Okay. Now, I know how to ask my question.
Now, I know how to ask my question.
The way to understand everything is
simply that what is true for you is just
as true as what is true for someone
else. Even if they are totally
different, they are both true.
There is no one background against which
to measure something for its
truthfulness. The truth, the only non
background truth is that it is composed
of all
truths. Simple. Obviously if you have
conceived of an idea for you it is true
or you may simply recognize that for
someone else it is true if it is not
true for you
then if I have a truth that I have
decided to be true in my life yes that I
don't like and I would like to make it
into another truth how would you go
about doing that in this way do you
recognize that it is simply something
that you do not prefer yes or something
you are judging
When you say you do not like I don't
prefer and I think I'm also
it is one or the other. Okay, then I
it's something I don't prefer. All
right, then if you know you don't prefer
it, then you're not it. You're something
else. You follow me? Not really.
If you can even have the conception
that there is something else you would
rather be. In order to have that
conception, you must already be that
other thing. Otherwise, it never would
have dawned on you that there was any
other way. You can only observe the idea when
way. You can only observe the idea when
you are already something
else. You follow me? Yeah.
Just knowing that there is something you
do not prefer means you are already
something else other than that thing you
do not prefer. Otherwise, you would not
be able to know you don't prefer
it because you would not have a
seemingly objectified point of
view. You would not know there was
anything else to prefer. If you know
there is something else to prefer, then
you must already be partaking of that
vibration in order to give you the
perspective that what it was you were
doing is something you don't prefer
anymore. You simply do not believe that your
You simply do not believe that your
imagination, your conceptual abilities
are as real as the thing you were
doing. But as soon as you even conceive
of an idea, you are automatically on
that vibratory wavelength. being on that
vibratory wavelength is in and of itself
being the idea you prefer.
So then I'm conceiving of something that
I really do prefer and I'm witnessing
something else that I don't prefer. You
are witnessing it. So what? Well, what
has that got to do with the idea you are
being? What if it's like all around you?
All around you. So what?
Then just be in it. Understand you are
living in a transformational world.
Yeah. Any reality you are desirous of
experiencing, you can experience. At the
same time recognize all the other
realities everyone else is having. That
does not necessarily mean it has to be
your reality.
You follow me? Yeah.
So in this way, do not give your power
away to anyone else. Know what is true
for you and act like it. That is the
only thing that will affect you are the
things that are true for
you. Anything else that affects you, you
are choosing to allow it to affect you.
And therefore, you are saying that you
are not truly being what you prefer.
Yes. Does that assist you? Yes. Thank
you. You sure? You sure
uh carry this idea a little bit further?
I want someone to explore something with
you which I seem to be a little bit
confused about.
about.
Um if an individual is creating their
entire reality, they are their reality.
Okay. And there are other
consciousnesses supposedly that are
doing the same thing in in in a
producing environment. Okay. Um so you
have let's say that one has in their
life that that they don't particularly enjoy
that that they don't particularly enjoy
yet they are creating that whole thing
right and so but someone else appears to be
and so but someone else appears to be
there it's like it's like a the set that
Daryl makes you know it's like they're
they look real from from from the inside
of them but when you get behind them you
can see that it's just a set it's a
cardboard set so so the consciousness is
behind the set
only because you believe it to be behind
the scenes. That is the idea of the sub
that unconscious you have created.
When you take full responsibility and
blend them, then the set will be the
consciousness. It says, "Okay, all
right. I can see that." Now, if there
are other individuals being their own
sets as well, you still have these
coions. You're saying that according to
what you believe to be true for you, you
will create co-activity with someone
else that fulfills your level of belief.
Okay? So if you have something in your
life, let's say that you you know you're
not enjoying, you have to be
responsible, take responsibility for the
entirety of it. You know, the the not
enjoyment. Yes. But that does not mean
blame. No. No. No. I Okay. But
meanwhile, this other individual is over
there creating this co- circumstance.
Yes. So, well, there's something in that
I'm not getting. I don't. Well, simply
in this way, you think you are anchored
to the idea of what it is they're
creating. You are not. You are not
responsible for their part of the
creation. That is what you are missing.
You are responsible to them to be
completely your part of the creation. If
your part of the creation
changes, then you are acting with an
integrity to act like it has changed. If
that removes you from the coexistence
that so be it. Okay. So
Okay. So
then that is also what they have
co-created. the potential to interact
with someone who might have changed
their reality enough to vacate the set.
Then that becomes the set.
Yet in the overallness that one is
actually the other consciousness as well
only it's not really apparent so much in
this kind of a reality. state.
So you don't really take responsibility
for that view. You allow that view to be
to create what it creates so that you
can you are responsible to that you by
being completely who you are or choosing
to be at the time. In other words like
who one is now the moment. That is what
I
said by being completely who you are.
There is no other way to do that other
than being in the moment.
Does that clarify the idea to some
extent? It does. I have one more. All
right. Um I've been interested in this in the
Um I've been interested in this in the
idea of alchemy lately.
Transformation. Transformation. Yeah. It
seems like
that looking at it from the standpoint
of of a physical reality that it is
basically allowing the the self to
become the master of the self uh to a
certain degree. Uh
knowing knowing more about yourself and
what your your being is capable of
transforming into more of yourself. Yes.
Great. Sure. Sure.
I'd like to add something perhaps to
Cena's question, right? Uh it helps to
remember that we're
multi-dimensional and that doesn't mean
dimensions that are vastly different
from our current reality. It means
dimensions within our current reality.
So in uh in one respect, a person could
select to associate with other beings
as multiple dimensions or other
dimensions. um and experience their
negativity if if he chooses or witness
his negativity or he can actually choose
not to um associate with those
dimensions of those beings at all and
his reality will be entirely positive.
He won't even see u any of the
negativity. So it's really a matter of
choosing the various dimensions of the
individual beings that that you're
associating with. That helps clarify it
for me. Anyway, thank you for your
sharing and clarification. Great. I have
another couple of sharings. Uh we had a
really neat earthquake a couple days
ago. 22. [Music]
[Music]
Oh, that's right.
On 77.
The gateway that we spoke of last week
of 77.
In this way, it is a representation of a
transformation of an entire body of
consciousness that was in this way
channeled in a shift in your
electromagnetic field and therefore your
physiological plate as well. Its
specific merit in the area that you call your
merit in the area that you call your
bomb
springs has to do with ancient
energies that arrived upon your planet
in that area long ago. And because of
this doorway, because of this
release, it has now been crystallized.
Do you follow me? No. Yes.
Yes.
The idea we have discussed of much of
the Orion energy
arrived upon your planet at that
point. And in this way, the
exemplification of the crystallization
of the electromagnetic field in that
area has now allowed much of that energy
to be completely and totally balanced.
It was a very widely spread earthquake,
but it didn't seem to do much what we
would call damage. I mean, there's some
damage, but not really severe life loss.
It was mostly for the idea of a
physiological reflection of the
crystallization of an ancient energy
that now allows for balance. It was on
78, not 77. Close.
My my my girlfriend and I were feeling
tired. We took a nap that evening prior
to the earthquake. And I really I didn't
tap into what was what was happening,
but she kind of had a uh pre-stage of of
the earthquake happening. And it
happened. Many individuals have
as you become more and more connected to
all that is, you will be able to always
read any type of communication.
I have another sharing. I had an
interesting realization and you've been saying that
realization and you've been saying that
you can take any event which is
fundamentally neutral and perceive it as
negative or positive. I realized that at
that moment where you
decide whether to perceive it negatively
or positively that is the choice point.
That's the fork in the dimensional road
where you decide which dimension you're
going to go into. Yes. And if you decide
a positive dimension, you will literally
be going into the positive
realities. It's not a matter of
experiencing the negativity in the same
dimension or the positivity in the same
dimension that you would have got
anyway. It's really a different reality.
Yes, absolutely.
Thank you. Thank you. Crystal clear.
Yes. on the earthquake. There was an
interesting news clip where a a fellow
who whose house actually was was damaged
was talking about he was dreaming while
it was happening and as he woke up and
the the h the room was falling apart
around him he really felt he continues
to be in the dream and I thought it was
a very interesting um reflection on what
you've been talking about that dreams
and realities are blending into one.
Yay. Thank you.
Thank you.
Excuse me. What did you mean by the
energy was crystallized?
In this way, the idea we have expressed
many times of one of the reasons of the
Orion energy in this way becoming physicalized
energy in this way becoming physicalized
in your sphere, your earth sphere in
this way was for the purpose of learning
the balance of the positive and the
negative. This idea has now been
crystallized. Meaning that within
individuals who are connected to that
energy in specific ways, they now avail
themselves of knowing that within
themselves is all the opportunity of all
the balance and all the acceleration
they desire from this point forward. For
the idea is that the road is clear and
that energy is now completely and
utterly connected back to the original
system to also create a balance within
that system.
What would be the opposite the condition
prior to the crystallization? How would
you describe that? Silly limbo state
uncertainty. Energy in a sense what you have already
Energy in a sense what you have already
described as just before the fork in the
road. Now the fork has been arrived at
for that particular consciousness
manifestation and has crystallized into
the positive reality.
There are many
systems. One of the ideas and
understandings would be associated with
what you refer to in your language as
one of the stars in the belt called
Mntapka.
The planetary system associated with
that or closest to that stellar grouping
in the language of the original system
would be kuva.
I have a question about past lives. Yes.
If it has if that's part of the
different dimensions that have the
different realities, are they maintained at the
realities, are they maintained at the
same time? Yes.
All is simultaneous. Linear time is an
illusion, though it is real while you
are in
it. And once again, to utilize a phrase
that one of your own has recognized
already because you were desirous of
experiencing limitation and keeping
everything separated, then time is one
of the ways to keep everything from
happening all at once.
As you have said on your own planet, it
is a convenient way of allowing yourself
to become
objectified, but it is all occurring
now. The past and the future are created
in the present.
You follow me?
Thank you very much. Yes. It seemed like
the the picture that we're painting of
whatever we're creating, the energy that
we're creating. It would seem like the
energy that we're creating whether we
can choose to play the third density or
the fourth density or the fifth density
or the second or whatever it would just
be what process we decide to run at that
particular point in time or what game we
decide to play.
Period. So you get tired of it, try
another one
in a sense. Although it is not so much
the idea of getting tired of anything
but simply recognizing that you have
fulfilled your particular needs along
that line.
Thank you.
Yes. Um, I had a question for the past
almost two months. I've been getting
this picture over and over again of my
father in a car kind of over the
steering wheel. It wasn't as if he was
physically dead or anything, but like in
a state of not knowing or confusion.
And it had been coming back and more and
more. And lately there have been some
talks about changes and some things that
might be changing in my family. And I've
been getting this picture more and more.
All right. And I was wondering about it.
You were wondering about it. Why wonder
when you can simply understand your own
symbology. Do recognize first of all the
understanding of the car, the vehicle
that moves you in which you travel.
Confusion once again is not necessarily
a negative thing. co-fusion fusion with
more of
yourself. In this way, recognize that
the changes that are occurring may be in
this case being created to be part and
parcel of energies you have shared
before in other lives. And you're simply
taking turns at making shifts and
transformations, acting as each other's
anchors at different
times. So that one at a time will
experience the unsettling quality of the
transformation and not both. Okay. Thank
you. I have another question. All right.
Um Also, sometimes I've been um able
to get a picture of something that's
going to happen like within like 5 or 10
minutes down am time. And I was just
wondering if there was anything you
could tell me about that. How I could
You are beginning to live in the now and
recognizing your own probable choice
futures. The one that you are giving the
most energy. Okay. Thank you. It allows
you more conscious recognition of being
able to choose what you prefer.
rather than simply feeling like you are
being steered at the whim of fate. Okay.
Thank you. Steered.
All right. Yes. Thank you. Thank you.
Yes. The sharks, guys. Yes. I'm an
actress in New York and I believe that
you create your own reality for a long
time. Our perception is that you are in
the city called Los Angeles.
Right. Okay. But anyway, um I want to
know what I can do to speed up my career
progress. Speed it up. Yes. Well, I want
it now. I want to do films now. I want
to do television now. I don't want to
wait 20 years. Go ahead. But what do I
do? What do I physically do in my being
an actor?
Are you? Yes, I am. Are you sure? Yes.
Really? Yes.
Then if you are an actor work at it I do
work at it but I don't earn I I do work
in the profession but I don't earn my
total living doing it. So what and I
would like to I would like to do that
and I would like then do so.
What are you holding on to? I don't
know. That's why I'm asking for your
help because I'm doing everything I know
in my power to do and I get jobs here
and there. Here and there. Yes. But not
consistently. not enough to support
myself just acting which is what I'd
like to do. You are missing the point.
When you trust that you are an
actor, then there will be nothing else
that you will want to do and you won't
do anything else. That is what will give
you the opportunity to be supported only
as an actor.
Okay, you follow me? Yes, I do. It is a
matter of trust. Once again, the idea is
that you are always a 100%
idea. If you are doing something else
and you wish to be doing the acting and
you say, "Well, all right. I will work
as hard as I can at being an actor. I
will be an actor
100%." How can you be an actor 100% when
you are still 30% something else? You
follow it. Yeah. Yeah. So in this way
recognize that you are always a total
100% idea. If you are still 30%
something else then the most you can
ever become an actor is 70%.
So does that mean that the survival job
that I have on the side is that is what
it may mean. It is a matter of trust.
Now understand it works. I guarantee it.
understand it works. I guarantee it.
The understanding is that every idea,
every idea comes complete with all the
ingredients necessary for the
manifestation of that idea and the
continuence of you being that idea. You
do not have to do anything special. All
you have to do is act like you are the
idea you believe you are.
If you are willing to act like the
idea, then the universe has no choice
but to support you by giving you a
reason to support the effect you have
created. The cause does not have to come
first. Okay. You follow it? Yes, I do. I
have another question for you. Um,
fulfilling relationships with members of
the opposite sex have eluded me for
years. I I I get love and intimacy or I
get like sex and I want to know what I
can do so that I can get all of it in
one person and have you know a life
partner. Be
that understand once again this is an
idea of attracting a reflection of your
own belief in your own
incompleteness. The understanding that
you think you need a relationship in
order to be complete.
That means you can only attract a
relationship that will only reflect your
belief in your
incompleteness. If you already know you
are complete and do not need the
relationship to complete you, then you
will be of a vibration that contains the
totality of all that you prefer in
someone else. And by being that
vibration first, you will then attract
someone who will reflect that vibration
of completeness back to you. So it was
not so much that the relationship is
there because you need it, but it is
there so you can share each other's
completeness. Okay. Again, the idea is that you are
Okay. Again, the idea is that you are
looking for a reason before you will
allow yourself to be the effect. Cause
and effect are the same
event. Be the effect and nature will
supply the cause automatically.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
are you? Um, how do you stop letting
fear uh control take over at moment?
Know that it is your friend. It is
giving you
messages. Tap tap. Look here. Part of
yourself you didn't know existed. I'm
bringing it to your attention. Isn't
that wonderful? Now that you are aware
of it, you can integrate it into the
rest of your being and be more of what
you are. Haven't I done you a wonderful
service? No. You didn't want to see that part of
No. You didn't want to see that part of
yourself. I thought you wanted to see
everything there was to see. Experience
every facet of the multi-dimensional
existence that you are. Do you not want
to integrate yourself so that you can
accelerate in that way? You're not
sure. Well, all right. I'll hang around
until you are sure. Until you allow me
to deliver the message, I will hang
around. Of course, as long as I hang
around, you might as well feed me, pay
for my meals, allow me to grow, become a
living, get stronger and stronger, nag
you constantly until you allow me to deliver
constantly until you allow me to deliver
my message so I can get out of
here. That is the only reason fear is
there because you do not allow it to
deliver the message that it brings.
because you attempt to reject the
message because you think it is
something that is not worth having.
Does that assist you? Yes, it does.
Thank you. Chris, um when you use the
word you, I owe you, you're speaking in
an overall sense. Uh sometimes, not at
all. Uh well, let's say if I said I
wanted a million dollars and I don't
have it, you'd say, well, you don't
really want it.
But the me that I know myself by wants a
million dollars. What does it matter
what you want?
Do you not prefer what will truly allow
you to be the idea you chose to be? Yes.
Yeah. Then there may be a situation
where there is another way an easier way
to be that idea rather than the symbol
of the money. Now if you are
concentrating on only the symbol of the
money as being the only valid way that
you will accept delivery of the
situation you want then you are shutting
the doors on all the other ways it could
be delivered to you because you are
refusing to acknowledge that there may
be other ways quicker way easier ways it
can manifest rather than through the one
symbol you are willing to recognize that
you call money. It is not the only
symbol of abundance.
I guess my question really is that was
just an example. My question really is
is the me that I know myself by there
are elements missing when you look at
the overall picture from from your
viewpoint you can see probably more of
me than I can see of myself. Not really.
But okay, if I if I could see everything
about myself Yes. I wouldn't be down in
scrabbling around in the third density
would in a sense. Yes. No. In this way,
first of all, you would not necessarily
think that third density was such a bad
place. I don't particularly think, but
but you said before that in the fifth
density, you know what? Fifth density,
you will not be physical. You can know
in fourth density. You can even know in
third density. You say something about
you know
what you need to know and anything else
that comes in is more of what you need
to know and not something to reject.
What is the lady asked a question about
fear though? fear is delivering a
message. Now I have fears myself but I
don't always know the message. I would
rather have a message in the fear simply
in this way recognize in this way simply
that now I am not
saying that this is
something that carries any more power
than you do.
But many of you have put much stock in
the belief of
habits. And so because you believe that
things can happen in your life
habitually, second nature without even
knowing you are doing it, then many
times you simply do not even realize
that you are before you can even think
about it. Rejecting the message that
comes from the feeling because you
simply do not pay attention that
quickly. following.
following.
Therefore, it is simply a matter of
allowing yourself to know that the
messages are there that you can hear
them. Even allowing yourself to be
fascinated by the fact that the fear
might be bringing a message can even
curtail the
negativity, can dull the negativity.
Just because you might be fascinated
enough to say, "Well, what is the
message?" The minute you become curious,
no more fear.
Could you give an example of what a fear
what kind of message a fear would bring?
Well, in this way you are walking down
one of your
streets, someone walks up to you and all
of a sudden you are fearful. What do
they want? What do they want? Why are
they bothering me? I do not want to be
accosted. Are they going to rob me? What
do they want? Excuse me. Do you have the
time? Oh, well, yes. Oh, thank you very
much. Goodbye.
Why was I so fearful? Why was I so
fearful automatically without knowing
anything at all in that
way? Assumptions and structures that you
build, habits that you believe in, the
message is there that lets you know that
that reaction lets you know you have beliefs
reaction lets you know you have beliefs
within you, structures within you that
you may not prefer. That may be the
message. If you do not prefer to live that
If you do not prefer to live that
way, then you have now allowed yourself
to let the fear show you that these
beliefs are within you. Now you can
change them.
That is one way you can allow fear to
deliver a message.
Will that serve you? To a degree. Of
course, there is a situation where a guy
does have a gun under his coat. Fear is
really telling you get the hell out of
there. All right. Now once again
understand that that situation can occur
that way but it also does not have to.
The idea of
knowing your
reality and knowing it without fear can
give you the cognition that that event
is there but you know it will not affect
you in any negative way. That's the way
I generally approach my life. All right.
And I'm wondering cognition of a
situation does not have to create fear.
True. Well, what I'm saying is that sometimes
Well, what I'm saying is that sometimes
the sensation of the fear comes up and I
go, "Okay, oh, look at that. That's
neat." Um, and I just find that I'm able
not to feel fearful because I'm in the
moment with it and I know that uh that
there will be a positive outcome. Yeah.
So, how is that different from what we
are saying? Well, I'm saying if that
does occur, then what is the message? Is
it have I just made the message
unnecessary or have I? Yes. The minute
you begin to become curious, you have
gotten the
message. The idea of many of the fears
is to simply spur your curiosity to
begin exploring that facet of yourself.
That is all. It is a gentle reminder.
add the more you are willing to explore
the gentler and gentler and gentler the
nudges become you can do not experience
that fear
anymore again it is simply the idea of
little bits and pieces of beliefs and
remnants that is all little twinges of
old habits that is all but as soon as
you acknowledge that it is something
worth exploring no more habits so in the case
exploring no more habits so in the case
where the guy does come up and he's got
a gun His initial intention was to rob
you or whatever and you experience this
fear. You go, okay, but I don't have to.
I can just do this this as a positive
thing that will flip you and him into
the dimension where you co-create. It
can happen that way. It can also simply
allow you to not come anywhere near that
individual and vice versa. I'm saying
he's two feet in front of you. But
understand you are missing the point.
Okay? Not that it cannot switch in the
middle of the idea, but generally
speaking, individuals do not necessarily
need to have that particular type of
reference to simply know that if they
create their reality in a certain
vibration, then you will never meet the
individual at all. They will take
another street. You will take another
street. You will not have to come down
to the idea of the confrontation at all.
Although that may be one way that
individuals may find an exciting way to
come to terms with what they believe in
the moment, it is certainly valid if they
moment, it is certainly valid if they
create it and it has happened. That
sounds like what you're saying is
that where where you go down and treat
other than what he goes down, it's as
though you've already dealt with your
fears in a way that you that is the
point. Okay. But I mean yes yes if you
are using the situation to allow the
fear to be there to deal with it then
yes you can transform the situation
right in the
middle and therefore recognize that if
that is what you are willing to do then
the individual you have attracted is
someone willing to change with you.
Therefore, in a sense, it has already
been changed.
Exist already. Let me just
Can I just finish the thought? Uh the
judgment seems to be the common
denomination. If you judge, you
immediately create
polarity which seems to create a
magnetism. Yes. You become the
vibration. You are what you judge. So
rather than try and polish up the
magnet, the best way is to blow your own
polarity by becoming static, which is
like pure love. In a sense, you become
polarized in your own
reality. That is all. Your frequency can
only therefore attract the same
frequency. You can only experience what
is on your wavelength and vice versa. Yo.
Yo.
Oh, hi. Um, hi.
Um, the when the uh two people before
spoke of fear, let's say for instance,
you experience the fear and then you do
become aware of beliefs that it points
to, right? How do you then change the
beliefs? Once again,
Recognize that it is not a matter of
needing a process. Although your
imagination can supply you with whatever
process you think you need, that is what
it is for. It is tuned right into your
vibration. Anything you can imagine
therefore that might work as a process
for you in order to create that idea
will work for you. If you change your
mind, then that is an indication that
you are supposed to. However, you do not
necessarily need a process if you are
willing to understand that once again,
once you are cognizant that there is
another way to be, you automatically
already are that other way. And all you
need, the only process you need is to
act like you already are that other way.
Then your reality will be able to
reflect the way you are now acting.
That is it. Thank you.
You You have a fear of ghosts. Ghosts?
Yeah. Why? You have been one many times.
What kind of message? I mean, what do I
learn from it? How would I cope with it?
Oh, in this way the idea may simply be
that it is an
indication of an extension of your power
and also perhaps a memory of an
experience of another life wherein you
allow yourself to
feel the limitations and restrictions
that go along with that particular
vibratory energy. For in this way, what
you usually perceive as a spirit or a
ghost or a haunting, so to speak, many
times are
individuals that are still very very
close to the physical vibration yet have
in your terms died. One of the reasons
that they are close still to the
physicalized vibration may be that they
a do not know they have
died, b have died in a self-induced
violent manner that allows for a lot of
attachment to the earth plain to still
exist. And so from time to time, the
vibrations of that non-physical
individual slow down enough to be
perceived by individuals still
physically living. This may simply be a
reminder for you of a time that you've
created in a similar way that was
unpleasant for you. And also now a
reminder that as you now are extending
your senses to go through that level and
beyond, you still must encounter that
level again. And you are simply fearful
that you will become stuck there again.
But you won't be because now you
understand that that is only part and
parcel of the idea of a specific belief
system and that you now already are a
different belief system and you will
sail right through that
level. Now understand you can also be of
assistance to these individuals because
you have had the experience of being
there before. And the original idea, as
we have said many times, of your
so-called exorcist is not the idea of
the banishment of evil spirits, but what
you would call a ghost psychologist to
allow them to know that they are in fact
dead. That they are just fine where they
are and they do not have to remain
attached to the idea of the physical
earth plane and can get on with their
lives on whatever level they want to. So
you can assist any ghosts you come
across in that way because they will
recognize you are speaking from the
heart from experience because you have
been there and you are simply
recognizing that you may have a fear
that you will be there again but you
will not because that is not the belief
system that you are right now. And
interacting with the ghost in that way
in the dimension of your imagination can
also alleviate that fear for you because
you will become more and more familiar
with that realm. It will become your
friend and you will sail right through
it. You follow all I have been saying a
little bit. I my fear is I haven't had a
confrontation with the ghost yet. It's I
have a fear of it being there because of
course but that is what we are saying.
We are not saying you need the
confrontation. We are saying it is in
your terms a memory of having been quote
unquote stuck in that place
and so you fear to face it again. Right.
In this way we are saying you will not
be stuck there again because that has
nothing to do with the beliefs you have
in this life. It is not what this life
is all
about and it can be something you can
utilize in a positive way because you
are experienced with being in that
state. Therefore, should you do run
across something the idea you call a
haunting or a ghost, you will be able to
communicate with them at the same time
alleviating their fear so they can go on
alleviating your fear so you can go on.
Yeah. I just I just don't trust myself
thinking that if a confrontation comes,
they'll just go crazy or fear and be
paralyzed or something. You are not
paying attention. You have already been there.
attention. You have already been there.
You don't need to be there
again. The
idea of your paralyzing fear is only an
exemplification of the idea you
experience already in that state
before. That is the only thing you are
remembering. But that is not who you
are. You can choose to recognize that
that vibration has nothing to do with
the idea you have created this life to
live. Now your
Now your
imagination is a dimension unto itself.
It is the dimension in which you exist
as
consciousness. In this way therefore
trust and rely upon your imagination to
provide for you
scenarios right now or whenever you feel
so inclined and so comfortable in your
imagination. Talk with ghosts. See what
it is like right now. What would you
imagine it would be like talking with a
ghost?
Create a ghost in your
imagination and talk to it. What would
you say? Let us say you are walking down
your hallway and there is a
ghost. What do you say? I'd say, "Who
are you?" All right. Nothing hard about
that, is there? What do you want? What
do you need? What can I do for you? All
right. What's so tough about that?
Well, um it's not just because I'm
surrounded by people, but when I'm alone
and it's dark in the house.
You are always connected to all that is.
Do not forget. You are simply confused
in a negative sense with the idea of
what being vulnerable is all about. You
think vulnerability is weakness and
exposure and therefore susceptibility to
negativity. Vulnerability is being
willing to be open to all that is. Being
open to all that is is being connected
to all that is. Being connected to all
that is is being infinitely
selfmpowered and strong.
So be vulnerable when you meet that
ghost. You will be infinitely supplied
with infinite
strength. Vulnerability is not weakness
nor susceptibility to
negativity. It is strength. It is love.
It is
willingness to be all that you are. And
that is what will give you the ability
when you need it at that moment to deal
with that ghost. And let them see in you
the reflection of your life, the
reflection of your love and your
connection to all that is. So that you
can remind them that if they can see
that in you, they can turn around within
themselves and see their connection.
That is what will let them go on.
Yes. Thank you. Feel the vibration of
your love and share that with them. That
All you need
uh I've been playing with astrology as a
way of rediscovering dimension.
Are you having a good time? Yeah, I'm
having a very good time. Well, thank
you. And um I've gone through the
planets and the science enough that I've
been using points beyond the solar
system, including galaxies and stars and
holes and things. And I've also been
having a very good time with the images
of the
constellation and those images those
imag those images have been around for
thousands of years and I was just
wondering if you could um share some
information about the many of them are
intuitive interpretations about the
consciousness that is connected to those
systems such as Sirius being represented
as the dog star the dog in your society
being the symbol of service serious the
consciousness being the highest idea in
the triad that forms the consciousness
of your planet our planet and their
planet. So they are in ultimate service
to
you. That is one
example before. Okay. Orion being the
hunter in this way a recognition of the
idea of the polarities of the
suppression that went on in those
systems intuitively.
Yeah. Are are the images of a terrestrial
Are are the images of a terrestrial
source or are they from an
extraterrestrial source? The symbology
is of a terrestrial source. The energy
is of an extraterrestrial source and a
terrestrial source because everything is
always the combination of the experience
you are having.
Yes. Were these images projected out by
a certain group of men or they've been
gradually unfold? It is simply a
cognition of the mass consciousness
according to the relationships that you
have formed with these other
consciousness endings. What I am saying
therefore it is the interaction itself
on their part and your part as a
civilization that creates the intuitive
symbology. It is the way you have linked
yourselves with those consciousnesses
the way they have linked themselves with
you. It is the interaction that supplies
the symbology that you are referring to.
But much of the symbology basically
stems from your point of view
physiologically. For while the other
consciousness may recognize that
symbological interaction, they may also
have their own quote unquote perspective
of the interaction. and it is not
necessarily exactly the same as your
perspective of the interaction. So they
would not necessarily have the same
symbol, but fruitful nonetheless, right?
Bashar, the uh idea of atoms and little
tiny particles,
uh I've had trouble getting into that
agreement. Is that a third density
concept? Because to some degree, yes.
Because I look at a wall, to me, that
wall is just a wall. I don't uh if I
look at it as an illusion, it's a it's
a projected illusion in a sense. Now,
understand that at this time, even many
of what you call your own physicists
understand that what they usually refer
to out of symbological convenience as an
atom is also only symbolic.
They know it is an illusion. At least
some of them. Okay. So the the wall
there is an adjustable thing. Depends on
what absolutely. Okay. One other thing.
Um I used to have a problem. I always
wanted I'm very willful. I always wanted
my own way and I was I would tend to
force I would tend to force what
experience I wanted and say it has to
happen right now. That is the shest way
not to get it. Right. I' I' I've found a
better way. uh a different way. A
different way, brother. It seems to work
now. Is is just allowing. Yeah. Is just
uh uh waiting. I I hope I'm not coping
out, but I see
waiting doing what needs to be done at
any given moment. Not waiting for
something better, but allowing
allowing. It is not so much exactly
waiting. It is doing but it is doing the
unexpected at any given moment
that allows itself to approach you as an
opportunity. You are not waiting for
something better to come along. Okay.
Well, that is paradoxically the way to
allow all that you desire to be there as
quickly as it can. Right? Well, let me
explain. Like today, I had to get
through to somebody on the phone. I was
busy. Okay. So, I sort of intended for
the lining to come clear and I tried it
again. It didn't work. So, I decided at
that point to just appear at the time
when the communication would occur. Ah,
but that is not waiting. We understand
what you mean. That is the cognition of
everything as synchronicity.
Since you are still going on about your
business, you are not waiting. You
simply know and trust that you will
always be in the right place at the
right time for what it is that needs to
occur. That is not
waiting. There's certain things goals in
my life that I've been I guess I would
say I've been waiting for them. Waiting
for the timing. And what I guess is is
disturbing is the time that passes that
I'm aware of that between now and that
event to come to pass. But understand
once again just like the call you can't
miss it by definition you can't once you
are that idea you can't miss it. So you
simply take it for granted that whatever
is going on in your life whether it
seems to have something to do with this
idea or not must be something that has
to do with that idea since you know that
that is the idea that you are. It is
what excites you the most. Therefore you
simply are being shown what
opportunities what paths to take what
roads to walk down. No matter how long
it seems to take, it is what is
necessary for that idea to come about to
find itself right place and right time
to be exactly in touch with the timing
of that manifestation. The only thing
that makes it seem like it takes a long
time is you do not think that the roads
you are walking down have anything to do
with that idea, but they do. Oh, that's
beautiful. Thank you. Which you um back
on fear. Oh, not going to be an old
lady. I don't know whether I'm fearing
um dreams, but I'm I'm having a
difficult time. Um I know I dream, but I
just don't remember. All right, one more
time. The idea, first of all, maybe this
does and maybe this does not apply to
you, but pay attention. Another fourth
density symptom is that as you are
blending your dream and physical reality
into one reality, you do not need to
create the memory of a dream bridge to
link the two realities that are no
longer separate. Remembering a dream is
only there because you believe that
physical reality and dream reality are
not the same reality and have to form
some sort of symbological interpretive
link to allow you to know that they are
connected. When you begin to live your
dreams and allow your dream reality to
become your physical reality, you will
not need to remember a dream because you
will constantly be living the dreams.
You will always be awake and you will
never wake up. You are dreaming right
now. You follow me? Yeah. There is nothing
You follow me? Yeah. There is nothing
wrong with not remembering your dreams.
The idea many times of negativity that
causes that is refusing to look at
certain portions of yourself that you do
discover in the dream reality when you
are keeping it separate from the
physical. But the idea of not having a
memory of dreams is not necessarily an
indication of that. It may simply be a
fourth density symptomatic indication
that you are blending your dream and
physical reality into one. So there is
no need to create something that reminds
you that they are separate.
Okay. Um, another question. When the
earthquake came, um, I guess was at 220.
I mean, dogs were just barking all over
the place and I had a real difficult
time getting back to sleep. So, I know I
just put some energy out and I I don't
really remember what I said.
After that, the dogs stopped. All the
dogs just stopped.
Do we have the power within ourselves to
Absolutely. But it is not control over
things. It is cognition of your
connections through
everything. That power you have always
had. That power is what you are.
Thank you for recognizing the connection
and allowing the
gateway to open that up to you as a
reality.
Sure. Um yeah, I wanted to ask you for
some clarification about what you say about
clarification about what you say about
doing what excites you most. Right. Uh
uh and what's more like you talked about
doing what that excites you most and
doing it you know like with an init.
Well sometimes to do what excites them a
a could look like you know like you
uh well you know like
total IS you know to uh
That is why we stay with integrity.
Yeah. But yeah, now not that you have to
do it that way. If you wish to explore
negativity, that is your choice. But do
understand that in that way the idea
will once again create more separation,
more limitation and more judgment and
not allow you to recognize your
connection to everything as
synchronistic. Uhhuh. So you will not necessarily
Uhhuh. So you will not necessarily
experience an acceleration of anything
positive. Uhhuh. Uh well you know like
all I can say is that sometimes various
temptations are quite what is
temptation? What is temptation?
What is temptation?
Is that another excuse for something
that you say is outside of your power
beyond your ability to take
responsibility for the creation of
it? as if the idea of temptation had
some sort of innate power that you no
I'm saying it's your choice and all
right then then that is another way to
say temptation translate into what I
choose to do that is all temptation is
uh
uh uh uh uh just let me give you a
concrete all right
concrete a moment for instance say a
person may be into hot
um date and hot fudge Sundays really
excite them. However, they know that you
know they what they may know that to
partake of a hot fudge Sunday may
produce various consequences.
They know that they they believe that.
All right.
Well, they have observed that
from you know like from observing the
effect of hotness. Once again,
understand in this way that it is still
an understanding and an opportunity to
learn more about the beliefs that you
have and to recognize that when you are
in the positive synchronistic momentum
of doing what excites you at any given
moment and you have created that
atmosphere for yourself, then should
that be something that comes up that
excites you, it will not have a negative
effect because you know that your
recognition of your excitement only
leads leads to positive effects. You
know this. If you
this. If you
know that following that urge is going
to create in you something
negative, then all you are saying is
that what you are excited about is
exploring negativity. So you are
following your true uh uh that's a good point. So
your true uh uh that's a good point. So
that is why we have suggested not
telling you that that is the way it has
to be but suggested that you do
recognize the idea of integrity
integration the positive aspect of the
excitement to allow yourself to know
that should you partake of that
so-called Sunday and you allow to create
the negative effects within you then
your excitement was to explore that to
find out what you believed in what you
believed would be the negative effects
that would happen to you. That can be
exciting as well. Thus giving yourself
an opportunity to become excited about
the possibility of not necessarily
needing to experience those negative
effects ever again because now you are
aware of them and know why they happen
and then you will not necessarily have
the urge for that any longer or if you
find yourself in that way partaking of
that it will no longer have a negative
effect. Uhhuh. Well,
um, well, that all went by quick, but
like I think I got the gist, but
uh, you know, the thing is uh, you know,
the thing is maybe you could say a few
more words
about, you know, like
the excitement of the negative. In this
way, recognize that the idea
simply is to know that many times when
you sit down and you think of all the
things that excite you, we are not
necessarily saying that you have to
think of the thing that could be the
most exciting thing you will ever do in
your life at that moment. We are simply
recognizing that the idea is that there
are many opportunities that have
presented themselves to you already.
Yes. And if you act upon the most
exciting one, it will lead to more and
more and more synchronistic
opportunities. Do
recognize that if the idea of all the
ideas you could possibly even conceive
of that are available for you to act
upon, if the idea of eating that Sunday
does turn out to be the most exciting
thing you can imagine out of all the
things you can conceive of to do that
are available to you, then obviously it
has a reason for being so. So go ahead.
Discover what you discover by doing it,
right? Because it may be that getting in
touch with the negativity you might
create is what you need to do. That is
still acting through integrity. Uhhuh.
Um. Okay. I do that. You understand one
Okay. I do that. You understand one
other
idea. The idea of functioning within
integrity. Not that it has nothing to
do with the idea of respecting and
loving yourself, but it more in a sense
has to do with the idea of not forcing
your viewpoint on someone else. But in
this way, the idea is that if you are
choosing to experience the negativity
only upon yourself and are not forcing
someone else or let's say attempting to
force someone else to experience it with
you, then in a sense it is
self-contained within your universe and
can still have a greater leeway of the
idea of expressing integrity even when
it may result in a negative
manifestation because you are simply not
allowing anyone else to be affected.
Right? in following. Yes, I do. Does that
in following. Yes, I do. Does that
clarify it to some extent? Well, it
does, but I haven't heard proceed. It's
a good question. Thank you. Um, so
um Oh, God. Question. Uh, so therefore,
um, say the thing that happens to be in
front of your nose that excites you
most, you know, like, uh,
you know, happens to be an uh an
experiment or an exploration of
so-called
negative. Remember, that's what's in
front of your nose at that moment and
that's what excites you the most right
then. Okay. Speak please. With
integrity. Yes.
If you recognize and understand the idea
that you are going to experience that
negativity at the
sake of your
integrity then you are not fulfilling
the idea that we discussed. Okay. If you
recognize that you are going to take
that excitement and use it negatively to
impinge upon someone else, then you are
not functioning within the idea of the
integrity that allows you to maintain a
conscious connection to your own
positive excitement and synchronicities.
Of course not. That is all there is to
it. Okay. You
You
um is it important to know about
reincarnation? No,
no. Live your life. Do recognize that it
is a tool of understanding like anything
else. You do not have to understand.
There are many individuals who are
living as fourth density individuals
have never even heard the term
metaphysics, reincarnation, life after
death. They are simply living the life
they know themselves to be and are doing
it in a third fourth density way. In
this way, you recognize also that many
times the exploration, wild ballads of
all of those ideas of past lives, future
lives, alternate lives usually always
lead back to how they can assist you now
in this life since this is where you
are. So if you are simply there to begin
with and recognize that you have other
ways of recognizing that, then it does
not matter what tool you use since you
are creating your connection to the past
and the future from the present. Anyway,
thank you. You may all take a short
break. I'll say first of
all that the
idea of the
title for the cake this evening of your
time can be energy gate. Sure.
Sure.
do we talked about the crystal skull and
uh I've been getting some information
that indicates that some people surmise
that it origins are pre Atlantian even
pre- Lamaran we've discussed them in terms of
Lamaran we've discussed them in terms of
the origin being the Tersian being Mayan
did you comment on
that in this way you will find that
there is some
is some
reality in the sense that it predates
the mind in that way. But mostly you
will find that there have also been
other crystallin artifacts in that way.
It is mostly the idea of the technology
itself and the utilization of the
technology in that way that predates the
artifact. It was in this way simply that
It was in this way simply that
technology, that understanding, that
information that allowed that
civilization to create such an artifact
that carries with it a
sense of ancientness about it by its
very nature because of the blueprint it
was fashioned from. It carries with it
intrinsic connections to ancient times.
So that each and every artifact that is
created in that manner can be perceived
or would by nature by definition be
perceived by those sensitive to it as
something that is quote unquote older
physiologically than it is.
Is that connection made simply to the
technology of craft crafting?
In a sense, yes, because of what it is,
because it does function as a
dimensional energy gate, then any
sensation, any perception of it as an
artifact will always bring with it an
understanding or a perception of the
fact that is connected to all places and
all times. So it will feel older than it
may physically be. Oh, I see the concept
of energy gate predates that and
but anytime such an artifact is made
following that pattern following that
blueprint and function as an energy gate
it may to certain sensitivities seem to
be older than it physically is. I
understand. Thank you. Also last week um
I asked you if I had appeared as virtual
personality on your planet and you gated
uh basically yes and you mentioned you
perceived energy of my working with
crystal sheets and when you and what I
my response was um I'll take your word
for it and the reason I responded that
way is because my perception was that I
did that in my dream state right
therefore I didn't I don't call my
dreams generally therefore I didn't I
would make recollection of it. Although
it seemed fitting, it seemed just fine
to me that that's what I would have
done. All right. Um I wanted to find out
what what the crystal sheets do, what
they are, and what way. Now, we have
described them to some degree. They are
in a sense what you might call a
technological manifestation.
They are imbued in a sense with a type
of loosely termed circuitry that allows
them to perform many functions according
to how they are applied in connection to
other manifestations. In a sense, they can be
manifestations. In a sense, they can be
utilized as remote
computers which can also attach
themselves to other crystallin forms and
allow transformations of those
crystallin forms according to the
programming in the crystallin sheets.
They can be broken into different sizes.
They can actually perform the function
of the idea of becoming a hole where
necessary upon a craft in that way if
such as necessary. And in this way they
can allow themselves to be reprogrammed
for many different ideas, many different
understandings that have to do with both
physiological technology and mental
technology. They are in a
sense the skeleton keys of our
technology. They are multi-versible,
multi-licable. Is it quartz crystal we
have on this planet? Not exactly though.
It is a combination metallic crystallin
substance that is a combination of
something that you might recognize to
some degree as combination of crystallin
structures of magnesium and
iridium. Okay. What is the thickness of
this crystal?
Not more in your counting than a prior.
There will be some variation between
what you call 14 to 1/2 in. Uhhuh.
Now um what is my function in dealing
with it? Simply you are there to understand
it? Simply you are there to understand
the idea of the
malleability of such a device as it
points out to you the relationship of
technology and consciousness.
You say malleability refer to the
physical malleability or the yeah
programming malle put this way what you program it
malle put this way what you program it
to be allows it to become also
physically
malleable let us say that you had a
sheet and you were upon a planet that
you were
exploring in this way the sheep a large
sheet So aptly programmed could become
the idea of what you would call a
shelter and certain portions of it could
also function as the exploratory devices
that you may need to analyze what you
are exploring. Does that mean it will
take a physical shape? Yes.
Without mechanical um all the mechanics are
mechanical um all the mechanics are
built into it circuitry.
It simply will respond according to the
energy matrix the circuitry gives it. It
will take that forward. Well, does that
mean that let's say you
um as I as I continue this in my
imagination, you land upon a planet with
a craft. Okay. You got this uh hole or
this uh stock load of crystal sheets.
You take a bunch of them out. You say,
"Well, this one is programmed as a
shelter. This is a programmed as a
exploration vehicle." And they just take
shape right before your eyes
any wild. You are simply understanding
that there can be simplification of your
technology to represent the multiplicity
of ideas. Yeah,
this you are beginning in your society
to explore with new combinations of
metallic plastics that are also
conductive. Yeah. Well, we haven't, as far as I
Yeah. Well, we haven't, as far as I
know, we haven't really tapped into the
idea of self
self transmogriying. or just beginning
to just beginning to.
For now, one of the first primary steps
is the recognition of what you call
metal memory or plastic memory. What do
we use it in? Not many things right now,
but a few devices. Well, if you if you
would name one, I'd probably draw my
memory and give me certain types of
energy engines, but again, most of these
are in the experimental stage.
on your planet. Yeah,
it is not in what you call widpread use.
Although there is one idea that let us
say it is a sort of precursor to this
understanding and it is what you may
refer to as the bi metallic strips of
what you call your thermostatic
controls. When a certain temperature is
reached, it takes one shape, another
temperature, another shape and performs
the function of the switch on and off. I
understand that was I would think that's
a primitive form of that. It is. Let me
be because I would think that what
you're talking about in crystal sheets
is something which uses
um interdimensional functioning to to
change form. Nice. In such much the same
way you move your spacecraft, right? It
is simply interdimensional engineering.
Yeah. So it just goes into a different
dimension which which in which it has a
different shape. Now does it go into
that different dimension um in a step
function so it goes instantaneously to
its final shape or does it go through a
sequence in which there's a process in
which it takes you would observe there
to be a smooth transition a small
process in actual fact it's changing
different dimensions Hey,
Hey,
you said earlier tonight that a bunch of
symptoms which you mentioned which I've
had all
of symptoms of moving into the fourth
dimension. There are symptoms of moving into fourth
There are symptoms of moving into fourth
density while still retaining some
connections to third. Okay. I have a
little confusion on relating that to
another thing at another
time being created by judgment. Yes,
thank you. The idea is that you have a
habit of thinking of yourself in a
certain way as a third density being.
When you begin to have the notion or
become aware of the idea of fourth
density, then in this way you will find
that you usually begin to explore that
understanding from a third density point
of view. One of the things that you have
created in your society to begin the
exploration of fourth density from a
third density point of view is the
creation of a so-called belief that as a
third density individual, you have a
slower vibration than you will have as a
fourth density individual. But this is
still the remnant of a judgment. The
creation that the idea or belief that
the third density is somehow less than
the fourth density. So in this way you
created separation while you are quote
unquote forcing yourself to explore
fourth density and therefore allowing
yourself to experience some
accelerations of energy in that way. You
still hold on to the idea that while you
are doing the exploring, you are still
somehow something less than what it is
you are becoming. You are moving at a
slower vibration in that way.
Therefore, as long as you are exploring
the idea of higher vibration as you
create the idea for density to be
represented in your mentality as a
so-called higher vibration and at the
same time still retain a notion that
while you are doing this you are a
slower vibration. This judgment and this
comparison of
separation then creates the scenario
wherein you have two different
vibrations within the same body. This
causes friction which causes pain.
When you simply know that you are what
you are at any given moment and what you
are at any given moment is what you need
to be, you will then accelerate as a
smooth oneness of vibration in that way
and not create compendance between
something you think is less to become
something you think is more. You will
become one vibration. You will erase the
friction. There will be no pain.
That helps so much. Thank you. I do have
Thank you.
Uh In this lifetime, I I had a son that
died at age 32 about 10 years ago. I
have had some communication that I feel
that he would have indicated he was
waiting. All right. And his sisters,
many individuals who choose to form life
bonds with certain other individuals and
then partake of a transformation into
non-physicality before, so to speak, the
other individuals do so to function as
spirit dies. for those still alive. For
in that way, many times you will find
that your desire to communicate with
that individual will then be what lures
you and spurs you on to extend your
senses to reach into different areas and
different levels of yourself in a sense.
Therefore, they by having gone to
another level are luring you to extend
your senses to that level of yourself as
well. Okay. Well, he didn't seem to be
doing terribly well in his lifetime
here. Nevertheless, he could be in a
fourth density at this point.
Nonphysical form.
Now, at this time, there is also a
perception on our part that as we
perceive the energy of that individual,
there also opportunity for an aspect of
that individual to also have already
formed a
reincarnation. This does not mean you
cannot still be in communication with
another aspect of them. For on the level
of the fourth density non-physical, the
idea of who they used to be no longer
strictly applies. Therefore, many ideas and
applies. Therefore, many ideas and
counterpart formations can be
accomplished and other aspects of the
soul can be incarnating while different
aspects still carry on a communication
with you.
Yes. Yes. Yes.
Um, whenever it was break time, I
was I had a real loose tooth. It was
about to come out
and at my last bite, I was eating the
cookie and then it felt weird where my
tooth was almost coming out and then it
wasn't there. But then it was in my
mouth no more. I didn't know where it
was. All right. So, could you tell me
where it is?
But you do not need
it in this way. Recognize simply that
the idea is you are giving yourself an
idea is you are giving yourself an
opportunity to change one idea for
another idea which will grow in its
place. And as that idea grows to
recognize that you with the same natural
smoothness change the entire being that
you are. In this way you don't have to
search for aspects of your past. For you
are creating your past from now. Allow
what has been in your life to serve you.
Allow what you are now to be just as
beautiful as anything you have ever
been. There is no need to look back but
simply recognize that you are always in
the process of becoming something new
always being a new
idea. Go on
forward. All right.
Crazy is if at this moment in time on
our planet transitional phase third
density fourth density is the planet
itself going through a similar change
will there be physical changes expressed
on the planet that we can see some like
what some of these
some of these
manifestations you have expressed as
some of the ideas you call your
earthquake. Some of them are changes in
your electromagnetic
field. Some of them also in this way are
changes in the type of atmosphere you
may be
breathing. Some of them in this way will
also be the sensations of different
types of pulses going on in your planet.
Some of it may also be the cognition
that certain ideas and objects in your
planet may be giving off more light than
they used to, may seem to be brighter
than they used
to. You may also find that there will be
some fluctuation in the idea called
temperature. Some ideas may be the
cooling of certain areas to allow the
energy to crystallize and become
superconductive. Okay. Will there be
like is if it's affecting this planet
would be also affecting the solar system
like sunspots stuff like that. Yes. But
again understand it is not so much that
one thing affects another in that way
but that everything you are witnessing
is simply different manifestations of
the same one interaction
all interrelating.
Okay. And you also mentioned that the
fourth density experience would be a 2
to 3,000 year approximately as we
perceive your energy at this time. You
do not need as much time for integration
as you have created for separation
experiences. So we would be using that time to move
So we would be using that time to move
to a fifth density.
More and more integration,
unification, harmonic resonance upon
your planet. Ecstatic joy.
Thank you.
I was thinking about what you said about
relationships, people having
relationships that they are the
relationship. It's not something they're
having. Yes. And it occurred to me um
the relationship my soul is having with
the all that is right now. Would that be
me? Yes.
Thank you very much. You
You
I've heard it said that um when
projecting from say the mentalities of
the athetheric universe projecting on a
curvature is is more accurate more more
effective than projecting in straight
lines. Is that does that make any sense?
perhaps for the individual that
suggested
it. But it is simply one
representational way to understand the
relationship of yourself to all that is.
If it makes sense to you, use it. If it
doesn't, don't. It is simply a
definition. Well, is is space itself
course this gets back into
physics. Space is space itself built on
a circle or curves. Is that how you see
as a sense? But again, spacetime is also
an illusion built on this
is just to saying well it's this way or
it's this way could it could be both
would be quite true. There are mass
conscious representations that are
created to be generally applicable
throughout any given universe. And in
that sense there is a degree of
recognizable spiraling curvature that
energy will represent itself within in
this physiological universe. Okay. One
question I have um different subject the
subject of law law which law which in in
my interpretation governs the world of
create creation itself. Let me express
this. Why? Um for example, there is a
law. It seems there's a law which says
that if you are in your own domain,
you're creating your own your own
dominion so to speak and your own
reality, then there there is this
tendency that other outside vibrations
will not interfere with you. It will not
be be u negatively affecting you. Do you
do you see what I'm saying? That is
because there is no outside.
Whatever you are is it. You are your own
entire universe.
Okay. So is that a law right? Is that a
law which affects all beings? It is an
agreement. Is an agreement. Okay. But
the the real core of the question is um
I have experienced a sense. It's very it
was an abstract sensing of not actually
perceiving but a sensing of elders
elders outside this this reality
structure. We understand you are simply
in touch with different levels of
consciousness as you interpret them to
be on different levels.
Uh elders which which would appear not
as any um manifestation but only as
perhaps a law the law of order the law
of evolution. We understand what you are
saying but you are only recognizing the
agreements of all the consciousness
within the idea of that particular
universe you are perceiving. So you're
saying it's nothing more than that. It's
all it has its own self-awareness. But
that does not mean it is not a
cocreation with you.
You are all cocreations with each other
and yet you each have your own
self-awareness. Yeah. Is that where it stops? There's
Yeah. Is that where it stops? There's
that's where it begins and ends.
There are
elders. There are you. There are the
idea that you are both a single
cocreation that defines each other. Oh,
I
see. Okay. Because there seems to be
worlds that will
defy naming, defy definition only
because that is the definition of your
reality to not have those definitions.
Okay. The idea on those level is that
definition is simply
knowingness, not analytical.
Yeah. Um there's a a thing in the Bible
where God does not want to be named,
doesn't want to be marked. You see what
I'm saying? Oh, what is not that God
doesn't want to read. It has nothing to
do with the idea of wanting to read. It
is simply the idea of recognizing that
there are the ideas of levels, so to
speak, levels within all that is for
which your particular level of
experience does not create a
recognizable conscious definition other
than the actual direct experience of
knowingness itself. I see.
Okay. Thank you.
Um, I I learned last night uh that Jane
Roberts died of cancer and uh
I bothered me a little bit. I wonder why
someone would uh because each and every
individual no matter what service they
provide is always their own individual
and controls their reality utterly.
That is why. So it's a choice that she
for some personal reason. Of course.
Thank you.
For sure.
You about a week ago, I had a dream of
of
of doing some some sort of a healing
with a
pale green crystal about 8 in long. And
I was I was I was wondering what
that was a life and and where and and
what I I was doing with that. It is
mostly a representation of your
recognition or your cognition in the
present that the vibration that most let
us say quote unquote accurately
represents the transformational fourth
density earth is the emerald crystal
because it is the green vibration of the
transformation. In this way you are
simply recognizing your ability to
channel the energy in healing ways.
with the use of a symbolic
wand that represents an octave of
reality.
And to another you know question uh with
your triad of of a planet that
is associated with this planet earth.
What
what a density would asterius be in in
your uh in
your start system be at this time in
comparison to earth working from third
to fourth. How is it? Our system is from
going fourth to fifth serious the
portion of serious consciousness that
has been involved in the interaction
with the triad is in sixth. Thank you.
Thank you.
Now one idea before we proceed in this
way at this time not so much the
exemplification of the energy
itself but communication a message that
we will deliver. Now we have already
shared the idea of the energy gate that
connects up to the idea of the Orion
energy. As of last week your time, we
said there would be a brief
understanding in this way. Also a brief
understanding of Arcturus energy at this
time very brief not so much an actual
communication but through us in this
way. For now, this is a seed which can be
For now, this is a seed which can be
embedded in your mentality and allowed
to
blossom. And recognize it is once again
simply a symbol, but valid nonetheless
for the certain portions of your
mentality that it will touch. The
representational symbol of our octurus
is a 12ointed
star, white on black.
We will let that sink
in for
about a a
week. And there are
connections in another
type of
association, another type of
triad, to use that term loosely, between
Arcturus and the star you recognize to
be
Polaris, for it is in line with your
magnetic north in this square, and thus
is connected to the idea of some of the
shiftings that will take place
electromagnetically for your balancing
of the polarities within your
system. More doorways to
come. Each with its potential for
expansion, acceleration, and blending.
acceleration, and blending.
and ecstasy. Sure.
Sure.
You um my the cat that lives with me
um uh killed a baby's rat and uh brought
it upstairs and put it in front of my
neighbor's door. I was just wondering, I could not
door. I was just wondering, I could not
quite grasp what that represented. Did
you ask a neighbor? Uh, no. Why don't
you? Maybe you will explore something.
Maybe you will find that the cab is
being of service to more than just one
individual.
Have a good time.
And do not forget that the animal is
only representing the idea that many of
your individuals in your society think
that you need in terms of the idea of
protection. Okay. What would uh cats represent the
Okay. What would uh cats represent the
transition into the fourth density? What
would rats would rats have a similar
type of representation? And if so, what?
In this way, once again, there may be a
tie to some of the ideas of your
subconscious fears.
Okay? But it may also have different
But it may also have different
validities for different
individuals. One connection may be more
colloquially what you call panic.
Okay. Thank you.
Yeah. Um, a little while ago in answer to your
Um, a little while ago in answer to your
question, you said that one of the
physiological manifestations of the
transformation might be a cooling of the
Earth. Does that mean that we may be in
for another ice age?
Not exactly an extensive idea, but there may
exactly an extensive idea, but there may
be the lowering of temperatures in
various areas, but there may be first
fluctuations in
temperature until it evens out
overall. It may be more of a pendulum
swing. Thank you. Thank you, Michelle.
Thank you. Thank you, Michelle.
Um, our grandfather just died and while
he was uh his last, I don't know, few
hours alive, he seemed to be wanting to
say something and I was kind of
wondering what it might be and if we
could communicate with him and how we
would do so. Your imagination once
again, where is it?
Where is what? Your imagination.
in my head.
You think so? I I don't know. I've never
been asked that question before.
Oh, so now you ought to be now.
so now you ought to be now.
Where is it? Do you suppose
I feel like somewhere in the upper half
of my body?
I don't I don't know my heart.
Are you guessing? I Yeah.
All right. You have guessed your head.
You have guessed your heart. Where else?
in your laughter too. Okay. What else?
All around me. Ah,
since you know that your physical
reality is a product of your
imagination, yes.
Why should it stop
there? It is not only all around you
physically, it is
everywhere. You are it. It is you.
Therefore, you are in
communication. Open your imagination.
Feel the communication that is going on.
Feel it. You do not necessarily have to
have an analytical interpretation of it.
Just feel it and act accordingly as you
feel yourself to be. So moved
down. All
right. Now, what ideas do you
Now, what ideas do you
think would be being shared at this
time? Do not think about it. Just feel
it. It may in your case sound like something
It may in your case sound like something
you are thinking about
yourself. It may come out in your
mentality as a self-proclaimed
statement. But don't think about it.
Don't say, "Well, it sounds like I'm
saying this about myself, but that can't
be right." Don't think about it. Don't
judge it.
Just what do you feel
that he's saying? What do you feel? Just
what I what do I feel right now?
That's a little vulnerable.
Vulnerable. All right. Then you are
open. You are open to infinite strength
and infinite communication.
How does it feel to be vulnerable?
Do not think about it. A little scary.
All right.
right.
Now, imagine that while you are
exploring your
vulnerability, imagine that
your recently transformed friend
is participating with you from a vantage
point wherein he knows beyond the shadow
of a
doubt that you are
doing just
fine in your life.
How would you
feel if you could receive that
information from him? Why?
I would feel that he was present with
me.
Do understand something. In the
dimension in which he
exists, he can always be present with
you. In the dimension in which you
exist, you can choose to not be present
with him.
So anything that does not feel like you
are with each other is from your end,
not from his. Forward. Yes.
Forward. Yes.
So comfort
yourself and relax into the
communication that is always there.
All right. Okay.
Send love. You are receiving love. It
will be felt both ways.
Trust that any assistance and
communication that that individual is
going to give you is going to come
through the synchronistic experiences of
your physical
life. That is the way they can best
serve you forward. Yeah.
you forward. Yeah.
Let it be unobtrusive so that it can
paradoxically become more
apparent in unexpected
ways. All right.
Also allow that individual to go through
whatever changes they need to
make.
Simply expect that the communication is
there. When it needs to stand
out, you will receive an appropriate
letter. All
right. Sleep on it.
All right. Okay.
Pleasant for you, please.
Um, realize after my question, there's
more to my question about
Robert that I
feel about.
I'd like to explore what I'd like to
explore what might be the service or
motivation for leaving the body that
way.
It might. Now there may be many reasons.
This is one that we are allowed to share
with you at this time. Recognize that at
this time that individual is in a sense
not responsible for but in your terms
responsible for the idea of many
individuals now getting in touch with
the idea of channeling their higher
selves and channeling many different
energies. That individual opened many gates,
That individual opened many gates,
opened many doors. At the same time, you
will find that there is one very strong
belief system in your society about
channeling and that is do you as an
individual retain
control? Well, I would say that Jane has
shown you beyond a shadow of a doubt
that your life is always your life
regardless of the agreement you make
with spirit.
So you know that if something like that
can occur to someone who was of such
positive benefit through the channeling
itself, then you know beyond the shadow
of a doubt that the polarity that that
represents in your mind shows you that
an individual's life is always an
individual's life and the way they
choose to live it is completely up to
them regardless of the services that they can
regardless of the services that they can
also become and provide.
That is one way you can look at it. You
may not see it so strongly at this time
simply because you may not be in the
midst of that particular exploration.
But for many individuals to whom it is
of a great concern so to speak to know
that while they are making their
agreements with other levels of
consciousness that they do retain the
right to control their own lives. It
might come as something of a pleasant
surprise to know that that could
happen. Not that they have to exemplify
it negatively in that way, for the idea
now is that Jane has done so. No one
else needs to take it to that
extreme. But it does show that you are
in full
control. In that way, she was of service
by allowing herself to take it to that
extreme. for now that extreme is played
for now that extreme is played
out. You follow me?
Yes. No. Maybe. Uh maybe that will do
for now. Perhaps you will find more
understanding in it when you yourself
key into a particular type of frequency
or a particular type of endeavor wherein
you may then need to understand it.
Perhaps now you simply do not need to
understand it any further than you do.
Thank you. Sure. Uh I have a question
about crystals. First, I just want to
thank you for sharing. It's wonderful.
Well, thank you for co-creating this.
Thank you. Uh I just recently became
involved in crystals and I I really
enjoy it and I just want to You mean
again quartz crystals again? Again.
Absolutely. Uh what I wanted to ask you
was from I was thinking of something and
then with what you said about them
tonight are they really
uh a crystal gives you acts as a
catalyst to get you in touch with
vibrations of what you're working on.
You have a term in your society. I
believe it says
bingo. Thank you. You are your own
master crystal always.
The crystals are symbolic
representations of the primal energy in
an ordered state that reflects to you
your conductivity and your relationship
to the matrix of all that is.
Yes. Thank you.
Uh just to continue what he was saying.
So a person could achieve whatever
recognitions or cognitions they wanted
to or needed to with or without the
crystals. essence. If they believe that they are
essence. If they believe that they are
their own crystallized way, if they
simply act like the vibration of the
reality they know to be true for
themselves, they have the cognitions
they need.
Okay. Thank you. No tool other than what
you were born with is
necessary though it is not invalid to
explore yourself in that way. Yeah. U
for it is all you. Okay. One thing I
have a a sub on the subject of death.
For me, it's a little confusing. I'm not
sure sometimes if I'm physically dead or
not because or or cuz I think I there's
times when I've already
when I've already
u reached that timing in a sense that
um uh I be I'm having a hell of a lot of
fun. I'm having a good time. Right. I
had a lot of fun and it seems like the
body of a little dog behind me I'm
dragging along and I sometimes forget
that I've got that with me and it
becomes a little bit of a an
incumbrance. So here you are once again
finding yourself fluctuating between the
idea of less materiality and more
materiality. It is again a typical
symptom of the transformation. You are
exploring the idea of the transformation
itself and recognizing the polarity
within it.
I find myself wishing sometimes that it
would just get it over with. I just I
feel more about twothirds spiritual and
one/3 physical. Little bit of as if
being physical was not a spiritual
thing. Well, no, I'm not saying that. It
was just there's the certain certain
weight there certain ways that we
understand what you mean. It is still no
less spiritual. Okay. All you are doing
is experiencing some ideas of judgment.
Okay. Again enjoy everything for in that
way you have created it for that
purpose. All right. Thank you. It is all
created from the substance and fiber and
essence of your being which is
unconditional love which is what you are
made of on every level. All right.
All right.
Thank you. Yes.
Uh would arthritis be a condition of one
of the conditions of the transformation?
It can be an opportunity to exercise
your knowledge of the transformation and
not necessarily need that tool. In this
way, it may be reflective of
beliefs that there is a lack of
flexibility in you.
Could you explain that again?
The idea may for some individuals be a
reflection of their belief that they
lack flexibility, the flexibility to
change, that they believe that
The rigidization of a structure is a
natural natural end result of certain processes
natural end result of certain processes
in a
rather entropic
way. You following? Yes. Okay. Why why
would this only occur like every few
years? Why instead of why would it go
away and then come back? In this way you
are simply exploring the variations
simply exploring the variations
psychically in this way when in your
terms it does not manifest. You are not
the individual. You are not the idea and
you are not the vibration that contains
the possibility of
that realization.
When it is there you are because as you
are accelerating you have a belief
within you in this way that you wish to
explore a stable structure around which
you feel you are orbiting from different
points of view. So you dip back into
that belief system become that
individual again to see where you are
relative to that concept.
So you reintroduce the effect over and
over again so that you can understand
yourself from all the different points
of view and recognize the
homogeneousness no matter where you are.
So it is simply a matter for you to
recognize that you do not have to
continue to orbit that structure and
keep dipping back into it to see if
there is any appreciable difference but
that it is simply representative of a
structure you do not need. turn the
other way and go outward into space and
expand by going within yourself in that
sense. Thank you. Do you follow her?
Thank you.
I thank you. Uh in your opening dialogue
and you mentioned all of the
characteristics of going through the
transformation from the back pains the
silos etc. Um
The last couple of days it seems like
everything you mentioned I wasn't going
to come tonight by accident I'm here
right oh yeah h
you you suggested research the plleades
which I've been doing for the last
couple of days and I don't know there's
any connection on that and all the
very this transformation of everything
you mentioned and a couple of new ones
that were coming in
um
rather well what I kind of would like to do if
well what I kind of would like to do if
possible is to go over so it's as we're
going through these stages of some of
the more attractive things that we start
coming through into the fourth density
and I know you've commented on these
lightly before but I could you go over
lightness of spirit oh I'll take
this free of charge
I think that's a good
Right. And I'll take more.
And I'll take more.
More what? Anything. Just anything.
No,
not it's not the most attractive thing
to etc. When your back is out, your
sinus is going, your back, your neck's
hurting, and etc., etc. Do you like to
dance? Yes.
Yes.
When was the last time you did? Oh dear.
10 years ago.
Would you take it as a suggestion to
dance a little more often?
Um, sounds good.
Then you may find that that may be one
way you can quote unquote symbolically
of course stabilize your electromagnetic
field and balance your entire system.
The spinning motions of the
dance, the lilting lightness of spirit,
heart and soul,
can transfer ever so
transfer ever so
smoothly into the path you are to life.
Thank you.
Find you, butterfly.
Oh, very good. Very good. Thank you.
Do you remember?
You may. Yes. Um, you said something
very fascinating at another time about
the the skull in that one could gaze
upon it. It had some intrinsic
characteristic which uh one gazed upon
it they would integrate somehow I got
the idea more quickly than
uh it would give you an opportunity to
do so. If you could not do so, you would
not be able to take advantage of the
dimensional gate it would provide to you
if you did. Gotcha. So, you don't need
really even need it for that then. Oh,
not necessarily. Although it may be one
tool that someone may find fascinating
enough to interact with. Yes. There was
some some part where you mentioned that
if uh there were certain characteristics
of it that a person could do it to the
degree that they could not handle it. In
other words, it would be beyond their
control, which conflicts with what we
the idea we've been talking about. Not
beyond their control. They may create a
scenario in which it seems it is beyond
their control, but the usual effect will
simply be to turn away from it. I see.
Okay. It brings up ideas that if you
fear them can create a scenario in which
it seems you are out of control.
All right. Thank you, Mayor.
Mayor.
Is there a correlation between the the
model the physical astral causal mental
and the various density densities that you
the various density densities that you
talk about guys they are all counterpart
energy representatives of the different
octaves of universal reality all
exemplified in a manifestation of layers
within each and every individual
um I don't follow that totally They are
energy models of all the different
dimensions in which you exist.
Do they do they do they relate directly
or correlate directly such as the astral
might second level density
like that fourth density astral fourth
density causal fifth ace and mental sixth
causal fifth ace and mental sixth
ace okay thank Sure.
Sure.
I hear that you've been talking about
the new children that are coming to this
planet soon
off and on. Off and on are going to have
a baby in February. Can you tell me
anything about these souls that you're
talking about? Simply that the idea once
again is that many of these individuals
will not forget so
much and many of them are forming
associations to a type of pattern energy
from the idea of
Arcturus to assist them to be able to
remember more of who they are once they
are physical in your plane.
Many of them will be reminding the
parents of what the agreements are all
about. It is now that these children are
being born into an atmosphere that
allows for the possibility of the
expansion of
consciousness that will show.
They in a
sense will become and are not so much as
you have termed it in the past, not so
much just another
generation, but truly and distinctly
they are a completely different culture
altogether.
Will that do?
Yes, I've been studying astrology and I
noticed that Spya and Arcturus are at
the same part of the zodiac and many
people in their charts have wonderful
experiences when they have
planets in this position. Can you tell
me if this has something to do with the
manifestation of these new beings? Yes.
How how does it work? connections of
consciousness, cognition, electromagnetic cognition, electromagnetic
balancing,
restructury in a sense,
identification patterns,
congruency, overlapping vibrational
patterns that represent also the release
and expression of the child within each
and every one of you. in joy and ecstasy
and growth and curiosity and excitement
and imagination. Once
imagination. Once
again, perhaps a reflection might be the
12ointed star pleasant.
I have a couple other things to share.
All right, by all means. one is another
realization that I've had in the
last I had a purpose and a connection
and I and I
didn't and um you almost wouldn't
discuss it with me which was of course
the right action and um since then I've
realized what my connection is
I don't know how many other people
experienced this but maybe you'll find
out maybe I will almost After every
channeling session, one or two or more
people come to me and thank me for my
questions. It gives me a very warm, very
connect kind of feeling to know that you
have been of service simply by being who
you are. Yes. Yes. And it's very
heartwarming to me and I appreciate
their expression of something that I'm
doing because I enjoy it and I I I am
glad to be of service to them. I
realize that
the connection that I have with you and
that the group is to be of service in
that way. Oh, thank you. And I realized
that the reason I didn't feel connected
is because I didn't have a sense of the
agreement that was
made which defined that purpose or
defined that connection simply because
perhaps it was always right under your
nose. Yeah. And once I realized that my
activity in the group was the purpose
I real I I I gained a sense of that of
that agreement. So the understanding
came with the term catalyst.
Um actually no it only I see the
connection that you make right now with
that. Yeah. But the understanding came
that just as I gradually began to
realize, oh, I function here to do this
and I'm being of service to myself and
to others. And it is something that it's
not just a fluke that people come up to
me and say this. It's not just a fluke
that I'm coming up with questions that
really tune in to a lot of people. The
only flukes we know of are on the tales
of whales.
[Music]
So once I perceived that that was my
purpose, I I just gained that sense of
the agreement.
May I take this opportunity to thank you
for allowing us to endure you.
Thank you.
Yes.
I I wanted to discuss the idea of using
the 100% of your energy or yourself in
an idea for what um if I understand
correctly often times when you make
reference to that idea you're suggesting
that people have an idea that they want
to do and they're still hanging around
in something that they don't want to do
say 30% and they're doing what they want
to do 70% therefore that idea is not
going to manifest 100% % because they're
still hanging around in the other idea,
right? Because they are creating the
idea of both to be representative of one
idea and not truly a different idea,
right? Okay. I don't know if there's any
difference. What if somebody's doing
three things that they are really
excited about? Does that mean that each
idea is only going to develop a third of
the way because they're involved? But
that may be the definition of the 100%
idea that those three things go into
supporting each other to form the 100%
momentum of the total group of things
they are
doing. To do it that way doesn't
necessarily mean that you have to
eradicate the different elements. It
simply is a matter of looking at the
idea positively or negatively. And if
the one idea you are being is enjoyable
to you doing this and that 3070 or 33 33
33 then that is the one idea you are
doing and that is the way it can be
enjoyable if you recognize that all the
different pieces go into making up the
whole and the whole is what you do enjoy
doing then everything is in your terms a
positive outlook. The idea simply is is
when you have within you the belief fact
that two things you are doing within the
one idea are not both just as enjoyable.
You follow me? In other words, if to do
this job 30% and this job 70% is the one
idea you enjoy 100%.
Then there is no need to change it.
Okay. Does that answer your question?
Yes. Thank you. Thank you very much. Um,
there's a sort of belief on this planet
that anything that is a sort of belief.
Well, I don't maybe my belief, but what
I see
is anything that's primitive or natural
is more spiritual than anything that is
synthetic or modern. I see. And well,
people sort of go off into the desert
and ask somebody who lives in a tepee,
secrets of the universe or something
like that. They already think that
eating an apple is more spiritual than
eating a Twinkie.
Now there are symbolic representations
of the choices of positive and negative
synchronicity. And in that sense we
understand that one may be more
positively representative of the
connection of your spirituality and one
may be more negatively representative of
the connection of your spirituality. But
in this way it is mostly the belief that
one is more spiritual than another that
creates the reality of experience that
that is so. So this is you will already
be aware that there are many what may be
called fables in your civilization in
your cultures wherein the so-called
master wise person or magician may
utilize many different objects that are
not normally considered spiritual and do
spiritual things with them and in so
using them that way allow the so-called
apprentice to understand spirituality
through the use things that are not
normally considered spiritual but which
are when used that way. It seems like an
irony that we sort of go in both
directions like we'll go to the more
primitive and we'll also come to the
more advanced like yourself rather more
advanced. Well, if you're up in a 6,000
ft spaceship and technologically you're
more advanced. Well, we understand what
you mean but it is not so much truly the
idea of advancement in that way. It is
simply a different point of view of what
it is you already are too. From our
definition, are you living what we would
call a completely synthetic life? In
other words, you are you eating foods
that are completely synthetic? We do not
really eat. Oh, okay. In this way, it is
almost a combination of both though when
the symbol was there. In that sense, the
idea is that what we did eat was not
quote unquote natural to our planet.
However, our combined mass conscious
mentality is what created it and it grew
naturally from that point. So even
though it was synthetically created out
of our electromagnetic reality of our
mentality, it also had a natural aspect
in that it was created to be
representative of our connection to
nature in that way.
There's just one more thing. I suffered
from uh arthritis until about 6 months
ago. And I was sitting in a cinema one
night and I suddenly realized that I was
holding on to a position of rightness.
Oh, and the whole thing lifted off and
just went up through the roof and I'd
never had arthritis since. Thank you,
Lord. for being of reflective assistance
in synchronous occurrence this evening
of your time.
There is a few moments remaining for
this interaction.
There's a something I've been wondering
about um somebody brought it up once
before in in magic or wiger there are
certain laws and one of them is that um
If you are in the process of creating
something, you don't talk about it. But
you've also talked about
conviction. I have wondered how that
should be uh no shoulds. Once again, it
is simply another way to understand that
when we say talk with us equally, we are
actually saying do what excites you the
most. Right? But if you do, okay, let's
say I'm It is not that you cannot share,
but what is being said is that the
talking about it many times may take the
place of the doing.
You may be using your energy to talk
rather than to do the idea. That is all
that is being shared. Thank you.
Hey, I've had some real funny pains in
my teeth. Are you laughing? I know, but
I was kind of excited. All right. I
don't have very weird things happen.
I wonder if you had any insight on it.
Well, maybe you created it so that you
would have some weird things happen. You
could be excited about it. I know, but
I'm a little worried, too.
I see kind of
in what way do you think your belief
system will allow you
to transform the idea?
Well, whatever happens to me is all
right. So, I could just All right. But
that does not mean you do not have
choice or preference.
Right. But I What is it doing for you?
What are you learning?
Well, that that there's things outside
of the ordinary that I can connect with
myself that all right. Usually don't
happen. Do you find
that when you explore some of those
things that now and then you might feel
you have but not more than you have to
or are you comfortable with the amounts
that you take?
Um, sometimes my ideas I think are
greater than I can handle. How can they
be? If you if
If you if
you are able to conceive of them, how
can they be bigger than the one that has
created them?
Well, if I don't want to let go. Let go
of what? Well, my other ideas.
Let them go. Yeah. Where will they go?
There is nowhere for them to go to. They
will always be there if you want them
again.
You are free to explore anything.
And always every other idea will be just
as equally within your reach.
There is nowhere for anything to go.
If you explore one idea and find it is
not to your
preference, then you will choose another
one. That is
Do you like blue light?
The color.
Blue the
color. I don't like how do you
perceive blue the color if not quite
light? Well, the color of the sky. Is
that not lit up? Oh, yeah. But I mean,
there's red light and I like I did not
ask you about
like white light and I like the color
blue. I see.
Will you shine some blue light on your
teeth? Okay, you will. Yeah.
Okay, you will. Yeah.
Why? Because I
Why are you going to do it? Because I
said so. Well, because I said you're uh
you said that thinking maybe it would
change something.
Oh, is that why I said it?
Oh, you imagine that's why I said it.
Oh, thank you.
Then you are vibrating in resonance with
your own reality. No.
Allow your imagination to alter that
suggestion of mine in any way, shape,
and form it so desires.
I like it. Have a good time.
you have um referred to the use of uh
crystallin blue white
light and you you use it as a suggestion
in
the the
imagination. What exactly do you mean by
that? This that the light itself which
you don't see necessarily is white. That
particular vibration that you call blue
white is very closely associated in your
mass consciousness to the
electromagnetic field that represents
the balance of your system. Therefore to
infuse your entire system whether in
your imagination
of non-physical reality or your
imagination of physical reality with
blue white light or blue vibrational
light in that way will be a
representation generally speaking in
your mass consciousness of the
rebalancing of the electromagnetic field
you are and therefore a realigning of
all the original 0 point blueprint.
print definition patterns that you
created yourself to be.
Okay, I understand that. It's more of a
um a functional question that I have
here though. When I look at an object in
physical reality, the object appears to
have color. It might be white or it
might be
blue. Blue white might be more of a
faded blue or it might be um both colors
intermixed on the same object. But I
feel like I don't actually see the
light. Although my eyes
do receive the light and transmit
translate the light into a perception of
physical objects. Oh yeah, but I don't
see the light, you know, going across um
the space. It's only when it enters the
eye and therefore
um however there are ideas of lasers
wherein you can apparently see the light
but what it's actually doing is it
illuminating some floating substance in
the air smoke or whatever. So when you
say imagine blue, white light, are are
you referring to some kind of imagined
object which has that color or any way
your imagination wishes to perceive it?
We are simply giving you a very general
concept and allowing you to alter it to
whatever form you are comfortable with.
It can be an object. It can be a
crystal. It can be light itself. It can
be a laser beam. It can be an animal
that is blue. It does not matter.
Whatever you relate to when you think of
that idea as we have suggested it to you
is the way your imagination needs to
translate it. So one of the ways would
be for instance that you say imagine
blue white light and using your body you
can literally imagine yourself looking
at your body and your body creating as a
source of light blue white light. Now my
next question is how can you have blue
and white light at the same time? You
can have the variation of the different
overlapping vibrations. In that sense,
we are simply using a reference point to
allow you to make connections that will
be made whether it makes any analytical
sense or not. I understand that I was I
just I was I created for myself the idea
of difficulty in imagining exactly how
to use this tool you had suggested. All
right. But you can have blue white light
in the same way that you can have the
idea of orange light recognizing it to
be the idea of the vibrations of red and
yellow combined. Okay, that that I
understand. Thank you. Thank you. Sure.
Briefly. Yes. Briefly, I would like to
thank you for uh once again calling to
our attention the fact that indeed our
imagination is the perfect tool. And I
have been noticing in contacting
different portions of my life this time
and probably parallel times as well that
indeed that's what I have done over and
over again and it worked beautifully but
I didn't happen to notice it. So I want
to thank you for reflecting that. We
thank you and we'll remind you once
again that it is not only the perfect
tool, it is what you are.
We extend our unconditional love and
appreciation to you all once again for
the sharing that continues forever. The
interaction that we are. We bid you
exciting dream life and life dreams. We
bid you a fun and loving grief. Wonderful. Thank you.
Thank you.
No, thank you.