All right, sir. How are you all this
evening of your time as you create time
to
exist? We'll begin this evening's
interaction with the idea of the
continuation or we have spoken of
recently of your time. Conclusive and
inclusive of the idea of synchronicity
and symbology in your physical reality.
The idea we have been discussing with
you of what you call synchronicity or
coincidence, recognizing, as you have
said and discussed, that it is not
accidental in your terms, but that
everything that
coincides does so for a reason. that
there is nothing in your terms that
happens by accident, but simply the
recognition that everything is part and
parcel of an orchestration, if you will,
an identification with a series of
events that are all from one particular
point of view. the same one event
manifesting in a multi-dimensional
number of ways simultaneously within any
given moment in spaceime to allow you
the opportunity to see reflected in that
event the different portions of the path
you chose to be so that you can always
know you are creating for yourself in
physical reality the type of feedback as
you call it that is necessary for you to
understand that you are always on the
path you chose to be on a path is what
you are you can never be off yourself in
This way the idea is to simply recognize
that synchronicity will bring with it
the idea of symbology. Many times you
will find that everything in physical
reality what you call physical reality
will be symbolic of the actual idea of
the actual interaction that you are of
the exact fundamental energy exchange
that you are creating within your being.
You will always create as long as you
are in physical reality an identifiable
symbol to reflect the idea going on to
you. Since you have created physical
reality to be something outside
yourself, you will then understand that
everything you perceive in physical
reality is a physiological symbolic
extension of processes, interactions
which are actually going on more or less
inside yourself. Not truly outside
yourself but inside yourself. You are in
and of itself the actual interaction.
You are in and of itself the actual
process. You are the experience that you
are having. You are the experience that
you are having. Anyone that you imagine
yourself to be interacting with in any
symbolic experience is in your terms not
that you are not interacting with other
consciousness, but the only thing you
perceive in physical reality generally
is your self-created version of who you
are interacting with. And that
self-created version that you are
interacting with is created by you in a
particular manner necessary and
containing the exact specifics to allow
you to see in that other individual the
things you need to see reflected by that
individual about yourself so that always
in that interaction you can understand
that you are dealing with different
aspects of your own consciousness. Is
everyone following along? Yeah.
In this way, therefore, simply recognize
as we have said that the idea of
coincidence and synchronicity is when
you allow yourself to recognize that
life works when you let it. That
everything that you attract in your life
is the product of what you believe your
life to be. That you can only attract
the vibration you are equal to. And that
synchronicity, therefore, whether it is
manifested positively or negativity in
your life, can only be a reflection of
what you believe your reality to be.
Therefore, it is up to you once again in
recapping to treat every situation in
life as fundamentally neutral. No
situation has intrinsic built-in
meaning. You give it all the meanings.
You you you create the idea of the
attitudes, the meanings that you wish to
impart to any given situation and it is
your attitude that determines the effect
that will manifest in your physiological
reality. Therefore, the idea is to
simply trust that what comes to you in
your physical life is symbolic of the
path you chose to be and simply take it
as something that can synchronistically
serve you. Do not assume that it is
fundamentally automatically negative.
You will allow yourself then to take
advantage of any fundamentally neutral
situation in a positive way by simply
understanding that every situation that
you create and attract into your life
can serve the path you chose to be. And
therefore as soon as you adopt the idea,
the perspective, the point of view and
the attitude that every situation can be
viewed as a positive situation and
therefore can create a positive effect
in your life, you will
understand how you relate to the
entirety of what you call the
multiverse. In this way, by recognizing
that everything, every object, every
person, every situation, every
interaction is the same, including you.
one thing manifesting itself in all the
multi-dimensional ways that it can
simultaneously
shar you Ben. Hi Bushar. It's
Strawberry. Thanks. You mentioned it uh
on a couple of occasions that the
dolphins have been in telepathic
communication with other civilizations
for some time. Could you expand on the
details of some of that a bit for us
please? Simply this way you will find
that much of the dolphin consciousness
is relegated to the assistance of the
awakening of your awareness upon the
planet. Therefore, the idea of many of
the communications while they have in
your terms also reveled in interesting
information that has to do with their
own civilization are now partaking and
participating in giving over their
consciousness and their assistance and
their unconditional love to you so that
you can also recognize that you are in
touch with many other forms of
consciousness as well.
Thus, much of the communication you're
receiving from many different
civilizations, primarily Sirius at this
time will have to do with ways in which
you can be
assisted by them. Very nice. Thank you,
Bashar. Do the dolphins have any kind of
a cultural manifestation like we do in
terms of cities and technologies? Not
really. They have no need of the high.
Okay. Very nice. Thank you. Thank you
guys. Uh I want to ask you a question
about where conscious cause intervenes
over higher cause. In other words, if uh
for instance you're in contact with
somebody who's making your life
miserable, you can say, "Well, this is
miserable, but at least I know it's
synchronized." At what point at what
point do you consciously stand up and
say, "Okay, you son of a [\h__\h] out of
it." Never. For the idea of what you have
Never. For the idea of what you have
just expressed is a judgment and that is
what keeps it around. For it keeps you
connected to the event you do not
approve of. The idea is for you to
recognize that any event that occurs in
your life whether you may perceive it to
be negative or not is an opportunity for
you to know that you can now reinforce
whether you are negative or positive.
And if you simply allow the interaction
to form a reflection for you to allow
you the opportunity to decide what you
want, positivity or negativity, then if
you choose positivity, the situation
will either in your terms not appear in
your life any longer or will appear to
you to be something that will be of a
positive nature. For in this way
recognize many individuals will still
form synchronous interactions with
negative individuals even though they
are expressing a positive reality simply
because they as they have chosen to
express a positive reality are now
willing to function as reflections and
examples for other individuals so that
they can also choose positive reality.
Right? Uh I guess my question really is
that it seems that when something takes
place and you judge it, the sequence is
really an apparent uh in a potential
sense. You have a judgment within
yourself first and the person will then
come along and show you that. Correct.
That is why we say the idea of your
physical reality is always a symbolic
reflection of what you already believe
it to be. Okay? So if you were going in
and looking at your face in the mirror
and you saw it was dirty, it would be
ridiculous to wash the mirror. Yes. Very
good. Very good.
Very good.
Thank you. Thanks.
Uh with respect to synchronicity, uh
granted that every everything is one
idea that happens. Uh but there are only
out of the all the factors there's only
some that we perceive that become those
that have in your terms relative
importance to the path you chose to be.
Right. Okay. Now of those that we
perceive um are they related to areas
that are I don't know how to say that
improving in our lives for example again
not necessarily for in the example we
have just discussed you can recognize
that many times you will attract a
negative individual or a negative
situation so that you perhaps can have a
positive influence on it. Oh well okay
right but I was thinking about little
little things like um
The day the day all things are equal.
I agree. The day after last Wednesday uh
I happened to decide I wanted some
breakfast. So I stopped at Jack in the
Box and and ordered something and
without knowing it was on sale and I
thought, "Oh, what a happy coincidence.
It was cheaper. It was one third cheaper
than I expected other." We understand
the idea. Okay. So
then so I thought uh does that because
there is a coincidence in the area of
finances does that have an indication
that it might yes it can and
particularly if your imagination chooses
to become excited about taking it in
that manner. Yes. For you can recognize
that many of you may form the idea of
monetary abundance by simply attracting
yourselves to things that cost less.
That may be your way to begin to
understand that you are as abundant as
you need to be. Not that you have to
have more money, but that you will buy
things that are cheap.
Or if you if you happen to have a number
of coincidences that you perceive with
respect to to people or old friends,
that would indicate that things are
uh coming together as far as your
relationships are concerned. can be
again allow whatever your imagination
locks onto with excitement to be what
the situation represents. Okay, great.
Thank you very much. Thank you. Yes, you
do. When one has um achieved a positive
outlook and are that they may also
achieve that. Aren't they putting
themselves in some sort of danger? Why?
Because If that is what your idea definition
If that is what your idea definition
contains then yes I am acting as an
example for other individuals and this
is dangerous. That is one idea.
You follow me? Yeah. I am acting as an
example for other individuals to choose
the same reality if they so desire. And
doing this is perfectly wonderful and
not dangerous at all is another idea.
Which idea do you prefer? Second, then
in this way simply recognize that there
is no need to form connections where
they do not automatically exist. This
must lead to that. No, no, no. Why?
There is no such rule in the universe
that says this must lead to that. Cause
and effect are the same
event. One thing as you define the
particular interaction that is the only
cause and effect you will create.
One effect that has no business
connecting up to the cause you are
creating will not manifest. It is not a
foregone conclusion that a particular
effect must be a result of a particular
cause or vice versa. Okay. As you choose
to define your idea of yourself, that is
the cause and the effect that you will
manifest. Okay. I've been in situations
where um I've been around people who are
being very negative, right?
Trying to do me harm. So rather psych
psychological or physical and did they?
Well, I tried just being myself. Tried.
I was. You are yourself. I am. Do not
forget that no matter what you choose to
be, you are always yourself.
I was I was just Now the question is
what you were you being were you being a
you that decided to also believe what
they believed and adopt for yourself the
same belief structure. Yes, you are
right. You can affect me negatively. I
will believe and co-create that reality
for myself. Is that the you were? No.
All right. I was being strong and
saying, "Okay, I'm going to grant you
the space to be however you want to be
and look at the situation how you want
to." Yay. And it's not going to affect
me. Oh, why did that not allow you to
feel self-empowered?
Well, after the bombarding didn't stop it, it
after the bombarding didn't stop it, it
then perhaps you are that strong.
So if I were stronger then it would have
lasted longer without it affecting you.
You may be strong enough to be able to
accept that kind of bombardment for a
long time because it will not affect
you. And in the duration of the
bombardment, you will function as an
example to those individuals who will
simply recognize that your seeming
persistence is an indication that you do
in fact believe what you say you believe
and it might change their mind about
what you say.
Beautiful. So if you find yourself under
what you assume to be an attack, simply
take it for granted that you are
obviously strong enough to endure it.
I like that.
I'd like to see a a spacecraft. Are
there any in the system that come that I
could actually see?
The opportunities are always there
depending upon what vibrational
wavelength you happen to be on at any
given moment and what the purpose for
such an interaction would be. Uh well,
I'm interested in the extraterrestrial
perhaps. Again, you may or may not
cocreate such an opportunity, but
recognize simply that if and when it
happens, it will happen according to the
timing that is necessary. If it does not
happen, the timing is not necessary.
beyond about your life. Recognizing that
whatever interests you have do not
necessarily mean you have to have that
particular experience in order for you
to continue along the path you know to
be true for you. Okay. Thank you. Many
of the ideas of these so-called
interactions. It is not that they cannot
occur but simply many times they will
not occur because you are requesting
that you will not be complete unless
they do occur. And therefore we would
not show up and reinforce your sense of
incompleteness.
Also, do not forget that in any given
area of your planet that contains to a
certain extent, it be to their best interests to
extent, it be to their best interests to
see what you are seeing. Therefore, we
will also not show up if you are in a
populated area where it would not be of
service for the other individuals to
partake of the experience. Are there
certain areas that have more sightings
that uh what you call your deserts for
obvious reasons
about Atlantis? Is there any connection
in uh is there any underwater going on
in Atlantis? It is not so much that it
is going on in what you call Atlantis or
in that way that civilization has been
destroyed. Recognize that the idea does
exist of what you call underwater bases.
They are temporary bases in that way and
many times the crafts in and of
themselves may function as those phases.
So they are not always where you think
they might have been.
Thank you.
Are there other reasons for some people
who get diseases? Yes. Many reasons. As
many reasons as there are people.
The idea is that each and every
individual for whatever reason they have
created within their aware conscious
mind or unaware unconscious mind so to
speak will choose for one reason or
another to create for themselves a
disease.
That's right. I'm thinking that maybe
some people get diseases and they die
and that's that's might be because they
don't need to live anymore. That is
correct. Very good. There are many other
reasons. Sometimes it is for the purpose
of the individuals around the person
with the disease to come to terms with
something within themselves. Therefore,
sometimes the individual with the
disease is doing a service for them.
Many times the individual will then once
the service has been done not need the
disease and quote unquote get better.
But recognize that whenever an
individual gets a disease and whenever
an individual becomes cured that
individual is doing it themselves. It is
not something else doing it, but that
the individual is
allowing it to seem as if the other
doctor or medical, chemical or machine
or situation or circumstance is doing
the curing but the individual is curing
themselves always. They will cure
themselves according to what they
believe in. So many individuals who do
not believe that doctors can cure them
will never be cured by a doctor.
Okay. Thank you. The shark
um what and where was I last to? Where
do you think?
Put it this way. We will always find
that if you express a curiosity to know
these things, you have the information
within you.
Oh, really?
We will be willing to explore some of
the details with you, but only if you
are willing to take the first step.
Right? What attracts you?
Is that a
question? No. Why did you pick that?
Have you had in your terms memories of
things that do not fit into your present
life? feelings that would seem to be
feelings that would seem to be
familiar that you cannot explain with
regard to the life you have lived now
such as I can't
see me not knowing could you speak up me
not knowing of what I am thinking about
not knowing what you are
thinking understand one thing before we
go on with the connection of a past
life what you are living now each and
every one of you is referred to by many
individuals as the age of
transformation. This age of
transformation means many things. One of
the primary things it means is that you
are all beginning to learn how to live
in the now in the present. Therefore,
many of you are realizing that you no
longer need the idea that you call past
memories and no longer need to the same
extent you have utilized it analytical
thought. Many of you will simply begin
to realize that you know what you need
to know when you need to know it and do
not have to think so much.
Therefore, it is not necessarily an
indication of anything having to do with
the so-called past life to simply
recognize that you may be consolidating
the ideas of lack of need of thought,
lack of need of memory in the present
life. You follow me? Yes.
Now in many ideas in exploring the
blending of your consciousness in the
present life of delving into what you believe to
life of delving into what you believe to
be past lives can be of assistance to
you. But you will usually find I am not
discounting the idea of learning about
the past life. But you will usually find
that the reason you are interested in
searching that past life is only to give
yourself the abilities you are
experiencing right now. The idea of
blending yourself all the lives you have
ever been into one now, present single
moment so that you can simply live in
the now. The idea of researching your past
now. The idea of researching your past
lives has value and merit. But what it
will usually lead to is simply
understanding that you are creating your
reality in the present, including the
past and the future. You are creating
the past and the future from the present
because the present is the only time in
which you ever exist.
We will get into that in a moment. Now one
moment. Do you like to sculpt?
No. Do you like rock?
Yes. The feel of it.
Yes. What do you think if you had a block of
What do you think if you had a block of
rock you would like to do with it?
Shape it. Then that is sculpting.
What would you shape it into?
Usually a man or a person. All right.
What color would you prefer the rock to
be? Blue. All right. And blue gray,
perhaps. Do you like a blue gray? Yes.
All right. Do you like the feel of the
cool smoothness of the rock?
Yes. Do you like its hardness? No. Why? No. Why?
because
it prevents you from sculpting it
easily. Yeah, it doesn't it doesn't feel as good
Yeah, it doesn't it doesn't feel as good
as soft things. All
right. Soft things are smooth to you.
Yes. Yes.
in this
way. Then allow yourself to
Then allow yourself to
recognize that our first impression and
this is only our impression. Your
opinions in a sense are far more
important about you than ours are about
you. But recognize our perception of one
of the
ideas of the connection that may be
perceived to be what you call European
in that way perhaps what you call French
maybe of that as a sculptor.
Thank you. In this way, out of
perception would
be what you would call
perhaps 30s to
40s. Within that relative time span as
you count time, 1,930s to 40s in terms
of when you did the idea of your most
ambitious works.
That is what we can share with you at
this time. If it has been of assistance to
time. If it has been of assistance to
you, so be it. But simply understand at
this point our perception reveals to us
that what we are allowed to share with
you is simply for the purpose of
activating your own imagination and
trusting that what you find in your own
imagination is always valid and true for
you in whatever way, shape, and form it
needs to be. Accuracy is not a
consideration so much as validity.
You follow me? Yes. Thank you. Now, the
idea of creating the past from the
present is to simply recognize this
simple understanding and this is not so
much an analogy as it is literal. Can
you remember a time any time ever when
it was never not now?
Yeah. When when have you ever existed
that you could not say it wasn't now?
Whoa. Never. All right.
Then understand this is not simply a
play of words. The only experiential
time frame you ever experience is the
present. It is the only place you ever
exist. Now therefore recognize that this
is a reflection of the way the universe
actually is. All time, what you consider
to be time and space all exist
simultaneously. But you have created the
idea, the illusion of linear time. To
put it very colloally, as many of your
individuals have, time is simply for the
purpose of keeping everything from
happening all at
once. But everything does exist all at
once. The idea that you have created time for
The idea that you have created time for
is so that you can experience reality as
a linear progression. But everything
exists now. The past exists now. The
present exists now and the future exists
now. But you have created them to exist
in separate nouns.
But the idea simply is is that you only
always experience your empowerment and
your existence in the present.
Therefore, all that you consider to be
the past, you are creating right now.
Recognize that anything that you call a
memory, you are not actually existing in
the past in order to have a memory of
the past. You are creating the memory in
the present.
And also you can recreate the past
differently every time. Yes. Very good.
It is as easy as that. And what you call
your collective history is simply the
product of the agreement of all the
individuals or at least most of them
upon your planet. When you change your
mind about what has happened in the
past, you rewrite your history book.
Now many things may seem to be generally
unchanging but that is simply once again
because in an unconscious way let us say
telepathically you are all simply
agreeing to maintain a certain
perspective of the past. But it can
change very abruptly and many times
often does and you will find that as you
go further and further into the
transformational age the idea of the
past may begin to change very abruptly
for many individuals.
You may find
situations where you have recreated
events in the past so distinctly
different from the way they used to be
that even other individuals that come up
to you will also bring with them. The
memories you have changed the memories
into
this is my first time meeting you. I'm
an I'm concerned with world peace.
How how can we create to use your terms
how can we create or recreate? Has there
ever been a time when the world was not
at war? Yes. And how and that's one
question and the other is how can we
then recreate that time? Thank you. It
is very simple. Act like your world is
at peace. live in peace within yourself
first. Then you as an individual will
set a shining example for how other
individuals may be able to choose to
live as well. One individual makes a
difference and the fundamental idea that
we have shared with many of your
individuals many times. Let us say to
render it down into a basic formula if
you wish. You do not get peace by hating
war. You get peace by loving peace.
Therefore, the idea is if you know that
peace is the way you wish to live, then
live as if that is the only way there
is. When you place judgment upon what is
happening in your world, you are
reinforcing the idea of all of the
negative occurrences by being worried
about them. you are sending them
reinforcing negative energy because what
you are doing when you worry about the
negativity is you are saying you believe
it has more ability to be more powerful
than peace. So you are worried that it
will get the upper hand as you say when
you simply know that peace and harmony
and the vibrational resonance that goes
along with it is to you the most
powerful vibration that there is. Then
you will simply recognize that you as an
individual are as powerful as you need
to be to have anything you desire
without having to hurt anyone else to
get it. And therefore you can radiate
this belief to other individuals who
then if they decide to can also choose
for their own right to share that
similar belief with you. All that is
necessary is to begin to reflect to the
individuals in your society and to teach
them that every individual is already
complete, has already all of the power
and the abilities that they require to
have anything they desire without having
to forsake their integrity and harm
someone else to get it. Recognize
this when you observe the idea of the
warfare over ideologies going on in your
planet. view this
understanding. An
individual who truly believes in
something doesn't have to force that
belief on anyone for they know the
belief in and of itself is worthy of
merit and manifestation. Therefore,
recognize that if you find individuals
and or societies and or governments and
or religions and or any other
sociological system in your society
forcing a belief on someone else, they
obviously do not believe in the power of
that belief themselves.
[Music] That is our suggestion. The idea of
That is our suggestion. The idea of
course is to teach your people that but
not that they have to choose to
understand you or believe you but simply
that you are willing to function as a
reflection of the fact that you know
that peace is power in that way and the
granting of equality and validity to all
unity. Unity is the product of the granting of
Unity is the product of the granting of
equality and validity to the infinite
diversity within creation. In other
words, there is no one way. There are
many ways to recognize one's
relationship to all that is. If there
was only one way, there would only be
one person.
Therefore, it is in recognizing that
every individual has chosen what they
have chosen because they are learning
what they think they need to learn by
granting them the right to do so. You
then reflect to them an opportunity that
you believe that what they are doing is
right for them. At the same time along
with that message comes the polarity
message that since I am supporting you
just the way you are, you now have the
opportunity to see reflected from me an
opportunity now that all choices are
equal to choose what reality you prefer
to
choose. Before we Oh yes.
Does this assist
you? Well, not exactly. Why not? Is it not?
Well, not exactly. Why not? Is it not?
Because what you're what you are saying
no. Uh what you're saying is that we are
all in total control. And I can't quite
agree with that. Oh, but you are
anyway. The idea is simply that because
your society has made a determination as
you call it so many thousands of years
ago, so long ago as you count on to
explore every single nook and cranny of
limitation, separation and
judgment. The idea that comes along with
the decision to explore limitation,
separation, and judgment is the fact
that you have forgotten that you have
chosen to do so.
Therefore, it is only the fact that you
have forgotten that you chose this
exploration of limitation, separation,
and judgment that does not let you think
or remember that you are in control even
when you create situations in which it
seems you are out of control. But you
are in control of creating that
situation of creating the out of control situation
of creating the out of control situation
is what you're talking about. Yes.
Your physiological situations are the
product of what you believe andor fear
which is a belief that your reality is.
The idea that if you fear something will
happen is the same thing as saying you
believe that that is the most likely
occurrence. Therefore, that is what you
attract to show you synchronistically
that that is your strongest belief.
Those situations come into your life to
afford you the opportunity to recognize
that you have that belief and if you
don't like it, change it.
Then you know you are in control. The
universe does not do pointless things.
There are no ultimate victims in that
way. The universe may not do pointless
things. You are a part of the universe,
but people do. No, not really. Again,
the idea is recognizing that everything
you create has a reason. It may be only
for the reason to show you that you do
not like what you have created and
therefore can choose something else, but
that's still a reason and it is not
pointless. It is up to you to understand that you
It is up to you to understand that you
have that ability. Let us render it down
to the let us say most basic common
choice. You have the choice as you say
to believe that you do in fact create
your reality or to believe that you do
not. If you choose to believe and it is
your choice to do so that you do not
create your reality then every single
thing including this conversation is
absolutely pointless because at any
given moment according to the belief
that you do not create your reality and
are not in control of it anything could
occur to wipe out anything that you try
to do. Therefore you might as well do
nothing. If on the other hand you do
wish to do something, you might as well
believe you are in control otherwise
doing something is
pointless. That is the most basic common
denominator that we can create for that
scenario. You either know you are in
control and know that you can have an
effect or you believe you are not in
control and therefore why bother? You're
saying in control of your own life,
right? Yes. What about the things that
are going on elsewhere? But you have
chosen to interact with these things.
And the idea is that while you can
project yourself into a reality where
you have the ability to recognize that
these other choices are going on all
around you, they don't have to
negatively affect your life. Okay? So I
can see from them that that's not what I
choose. What I prefer. Correct. And
therefore, by being fully the being you
chose to be, you can therefore set the
strongest, brightest, and fullest
example to them that they have an
opportunity to choose something else
which they can see in you if they don't
prefer what they are doing. What if they
don't choose to? That is up to them. Do
not forget one thing.
Everyone is
eternal. You are indestructible
forever. Therefore, what's the
rush? There's no need to worry
ultimately about anyone else because if
they quote unquote choose not to do it
this time, they may choose to do it next
time. and they have an infinite supply
of next
time. Now, the idea is simply deciding
whether or not you want to wait that
many next times or choose to do it
now. That is all there is to it.
Therefore, if you take the pressure off
of your need, your need to have them
make a decision that's all right with
you, then you will fully grant them the true
then you will fully grant them the true
ability to choose to change their minds.
As long as you think they must change
their minds in order to find benefit in
the situation they are living, you are
only reinforcing that the reality they
have chosen is in fact something worth
less than your reality. and you're only
supporting their choice of negativity
and reinforcing it by judging their
situation to be worth less than yours.
Okay. If if man is eternal, a nuclear
and woman and woman,
the generic
Okay. If the human being is eternal and
goes on forever and ever, not the human
being. All right. the idea of your
consciousness which has been many things
besides the human. Okay. All right. I'll
accept that. Then a nuclear holocaust
really doesn't matter, does it? Not in
an ultimate sense. However, the idea
simply again is that you have the
opportunity to recognize that that
particular type of physiological
annihilation will co-create imbalances
in many dimensional rifts and will not
remain as you say in your own backyard.
Therefore, the idea is simply that is
the one manifestation you will not be
allowed to manifest at this time because
you are too closely connected to many
other civilizations at this time. You
may annihilate yourselves in any other
way as long as you keep it to
yourself. Now the idea is again that we
are not here to run your lives. It is in
a sense the only exception that is made
simply because it affects more than just
your immediate sphere of influence.
However, it is our perception and the
perception of many civilizations as we
read the energy of your mass
consciousness that you have already as
of what you call 5 to seven of your
years ago decided on mass though it may
be mostly unconscious at this time to
not annihilate yourselves in that way.
Much of the accelerated negativity you
experience upon your planet at this time
is actually the result of knowing that
it is safe to blow off the steam because
you will not destroy yourself. You are
giving yourself an opportunity to
accelerate the experience of this
negativity and purge it from your
reality. Because once you live through
it very quickly and very abruptly, you
will know you have done it all and you
will not have to go back to any of those
experiences in your new integrated age
of awareness. The idea is that
transformation is not the product of
mediocrity. And as far to the negative
as you have allowed yourself to be
experiencing life, that is how far to
the positive you will experience the new
age. It is like a slingshot effect. So
you are speeding yourselves up,
accelerating yourselves, and all of the
negativity you are experiencing upon
your planet at this time is the product
now of bringing what was formerly hidden
and covert in your society and making it
overt and obvious so that your
civilization as a group can decide is
this what we want or not.
Do you follow? Yes, I follow you. I I
could extend it but I'll let someone
else have an opportunity. All right.
Thank you for your sharing and your
choice to be alive at this time of
transformation in the civilization you
have chosen to do for as we have said
every individual no matter what your
point of view makes a difference. Yes.
I want to share this is one of the one
of the most magnificent evenings and I
realize that it is my husband is
still my pleasure and I realize that it
is because I'm simultaneously in
communication with so many people that I
really love and it's just beautiful.
Thank you. Thank you. Um Um
well earthquakes
do you enjoy them?
Many individuals
do. They find that the energy excites
them and spurs them to creativity. That
is why many individuals choose to
congregate in areas of high seismic
activity because they like as you say
living on the edge.
It allows them to feel their own
creative energy and recognize that how
once again they have the opportunity to
recognize it does not have to manifest
negatively that they can through their
own consciousness re channel the energy
in positive ways could kill though I
that is up to you. Well um I just wanted
to know if you knew when we should take
any precautions cuz this when you feel
like it. Well, people said that people
on the news and stuff that we're going
to that we're supposed to have a real
big earthquake here. Let's put it this
way. Okay. If you simply find that it is
something that does not have relevance
to the vibrational life that you know
yourself to be, then whether it occurs
or not, you will not be there. You will
be somewhere else.
Now the idea is also to
understand that to fear something is
what attracts you to it.
Why is that? Because as we said your
reality is created from what you believe
it to be. And if you fear something will
happen you are saying that you believe
that is the most likely occurrence to
happen. And that is where you are
putting the highest amount of your
momentum energy. Okay.
Therefore, the idea of fearing it is
simply judging the vibration of energy of
judging the vibration of energy of
excitation that you feel coursing
through your being when you think of
that idea. Fear and anxiety is only
excitement that you judge.
Well, sometimes I can be afraid of
something, but I don't really believe
that it will probably happen. I think
this chance, though. All right. But
again in
all possibility that such a thing might
occur. Take it for granted that your
ability to be aware that such a thing
might occur is a sign in and of itself
that you are aware that you do not want
it to occur, that you do not need it to
occur, and therefore you will
automatically guide yourself to where it
won't occur. Otherwise, you wouldn't be
aware that it was a
possibility. You would simply be caught
in it without any forewarning or
knowledge at all of such a thing. The
idea that you can be aware of such a
thing and recognize it is something you
do not prefer is in and of itself a sign
that you can take yourself beyond the
occurrence. Are you saying that my
unconscious? Yes. Yes. Oh, okay.
Thank you. I have nothing. Yes.
Um I have a a relationship with my
eating in my body that I would like to
stop. I um eat or rather binge when I'm
not hungry physically and I tend to do
it sometimes until I throw up. All
right. You have a good time.
Oh. All right.
May I ask you a question? Yes. Are you
doing in your life what excites you the
most? No. Why not?
May I ask you another question?
What right now excites you the most that
you would rather be doing in your life?
Playing the piano. Why aren't you?
Um, here it
comes. In no way, shape, or form am I
denigrating or being demeaning to you.
But recognize that many individuals when
they create the so-called reasons for
why something is not going on are
basing these reasons on foundations they
think to be solid but carry more weight
than any of the reasons themselves.
Now truly is there
truly one I'll accept one good reason
for why you are not doing what you
really want with this just one. I'll
make it easy for you. Um
one good reason. Okay. Um I need u
enough money to that doesn't do it.
I'll tell you why.
Because money is only a tool like any
other tool. It is only one way to think
of and manifest what you call abundance.
Only one way. Recognize that every idea,
the idea that you are a pianist is an
idea. Every idea comes complete with all
the ingredients necessary for the
support and manifestation of that idea
automatically, synchronistically. Now
the idea is is that if you are willing
to be that idea and act fully like that
idea that excites you the most, you will
then automatically synchronistically
coincidentally attract
whatever ingredients, situations,
relationships are necessary to support
that idea. Whatever is there is what is
necessary to support you in being that
idea. Whatever is not there is not
necessary. Therefore, you may find that
you are only creating an expectation and
an assumption that money has to be
necessary in order for you to do this
idea. Now, if it is truly necessary, the
moment you start acting like you are
already a pianist, the money, if it is
necessary, will automatically flow to
you or an opportunity that will allow it
to flow to you will flow to you. The
idea is is that you do not simply trust
that you are that idea that it will not
support itself automatically like every
other idea you are willing to be
supports itself automatically and if I
start doing more of what I really want
to be doing I'll stop eat that you can
for you will recognize that many times
the idea it is somewhat connected to the
idea of what you call overweighteness in
the sense that many individuals will
find that they will create that scenario
Ario for similar reasons and that is
that they are by a coincidental cross
reference in your language find that
they are overweight because they are not
doing they are waiting to
do. When you begin to do what you know
you want to do you stop waiting.
The idea is that you are only replacing
all of the energy with some substitute
symbol. You know it is not what you
really want. Therefore, you get rid of
it just as quickly as you pile it in.
But the idea is to simply know that all
you are reflecting is the idea that you
do recognize that there is a flow of
energy going through you, but you are
not placing it in the direction you know
is true for you. The way to tell which
direction is true for you is to pay
attention to your excitement. Because
excitement is the physiological
translation of the fundamental
vibrational energy that represents the
path you chose to be. Follow your
excitement. You will always be exactly
in synchronous harmony with the person
you chose to be in this
life. Follow your excitement.
Then you will be feeding yourself in a
spiritual way that will nourish you in a
way that the physiological food
cannot. You simply find that the food is
a substitute for the symbolic reflection
that you feel you are starving
spiritually not
physically. Do what excites you. You
will be supported. This is one of the
few things I can guarantee
100%. That goes for each and every one
of you. Wow. When you do the thing that
excites you
coincidentally, synchronistically, and
automatically, all the necessary
ingredients to support you in continuing
to be that idea will flow into your life
because you have been willing to be
completely vulnerable. Being vulnerable is not
vulnerable. Being vulnerable is not
being weak. Being vulnerable is being
completely open to all that is. Being
open to all that is and willing to
receive all the ways in which all that
is can manifest in your life is being
connected to all that is. Being
connected to all that is is being
ultimately strong. So vulnerability is
infinite strength.
I will assume of course that you are
applauding yourself. Sure.
Sure.
Yes, sure. I would like to ask some
questions about walk-ins. A few
a few questions or a few walk-ins. A few
questions. Okay. I uh found one book and I read
Okay. I uh found one book and I read
what I could read and it was not very
very helpful. It was by Ruth Montgomery
and they said at that time in 1979 when
the book was written that tens of
thousands of souls were walking in to
some degree. It still represents a small
fraction of your population however and
usually will remain so. Please define
walkin. the idea that an individual
finds that they have come quote unquote
to an end for the need of a physical
life, but that another individual that
is non-physical that needs a life does
not need a whole life. So, one
individual quote unquote leaves the body
and another one comes in to continue for
the amount of time that is necessary for
their purpose to be fulfilled.
Now, this is occurring a little bit more
often than it used to. But again, you
will also find that many individuals are
simply the same quote unquote souls
ascending into higher vibrational states
of themselves and remaining in the same
body. Sometimes this can appear to be
what you call a walk-in but it is not.
It is an ascension in a sense within the
same body.
The idea does not really need a
confusion of labeling for simply again
the entire idea no matter what version
no matter what type of vibrational
change and personality shift has
occurred is all for the purpose of the
blending into an idea of the assistance
in the transformation taking place
when born again Christians get what they
call a new spirit is that a walk-in they
do not define such a thing in that
that does not fit in with what they
believe to be their
reality. In this way, it is simply
looked upon more or less as a new
creation in a sense of a new
soul. But the idea also of the idea of
transformation is more connected to the
idea we have described as ascension. the
shifting and the changing of the
identification of the an individual's
vibration so that there is a personality
shift a reidentification of
themselves in the
universe but that is going on all the
time you are constantly reidentifying
yourself every moment of time that you
create to exist
always you are new every moment you are
new
um so in Uh, I had a walk-in experience
from February until June 5th, and I felt
that it was completed on June
5th. And um, do you mean with you? Yes.
So, where were you? Well, that would be
another question then because I just
asked it.
Oh, what? Where were you during that
time? During that time, yes. I believe
that from February to June both of us
were in here then it is not technically
what you call a walk-in. Again
understand one thing. Now we do realize
that because you come from the idea of
the physiological state you are in. You
generally consider that the terminology
that something enters the body to be
literal. But your body is also a
projection of your soul. The idea is not
so much that something can enter a body,
but that there are only identifications
with different frequencies of
consciousness and vibration. So to us,
walk in, ascension, changing your mind
in a sense is all the same thing. A
shift in vibrational frequency that
redefineses the identity consciousness
that you are. To us, the creation of
different separate labels only confuses
the issue in a negative way.
The idea simply part and parcel is take
what you feel to have happened and
simply act upon the essence of the
feeling without necessarily needing to
label it to understand
it. How did it create you to feel? What
do you want to do with the feeling? That
is what will benefit you in your life.
You follow me? Yes. Simply function in
that way and it will slide a little more
smoothly for you. Okay. Okay. Well, I
was interested in some facts because I
thought about writing a facts are
relative. Yes. There's a I understand
there's a man in New York that's doing
seminars on the fact that he's a walk
in. All right. If that excites you, go
see him. Well, no. Yeah. I would like to
meet him, but I have a good time.
Okay. Again, the idea is simply to act
upon what excites you. Now, once again,
let me remind you and point something
out. a little bit of a
redefinition. Many times we have
discussed the
idea although of course questions are a
valid way to share that when you are
willing to make statements and
convictions of equal sharing then you
will be more willing to recognize
yourselves as equal to us and equal to
any level of consciousness within
creation. One thing about the idea of
the equal conversation, however, is that
the idea of conversing as equals with us
is actually more the idea of actually
going and doing what you know is true
for you rather than talking about it.
Doing it is the conversation that
creates the equality.
Therefore, simply act upon your
instincts. Act upon your feelings, move
yourself or let yourself move in the
direction your feelings and instincts
and imagination and excitation takes
you. The idea of thinking about it and
analyzing it is fine on its own terms.
But in this way, we do perceive that you
are requesting the idea of being able to
feel it in your life as a practical
thing. Therefore, live it as a practical
thing. Trust your imagination. Trust
that it is valid for you. And it is
creating the symbols that relate to you
most necessarily at this time. So do not
put so much stock in what the symbols
mean for the symbols will change from
time to time. Simply trust that whatever
symbols are there for now are there to
create the feelings that give you the
opportunity to act. It is the action
that is
primary. Not the understanding
specifically of what does this symbol
mean? What does that symbol mean? What
is this terminology? What is that
terminology? It is how it makes you feel
that gives you the opportunity to move.
That is why the symbol is there. You
follow me? Yes. Slinky.
Nice. You sure? Nice. Thank you. but one
who speaks first again. Thank you. Um
made the design of the uh levitation
disc generator we've talked about. Yes.
And I'm to the point now I'm building
the coils. I envision them uh 21in cores
by 2 in tall. All right. With 28 gauge
copper wire. Is that sufficient to
produce the effect?
How many in your terms wrappings can you
achieve around each core? It's a great
question. Uh let's see. I was thinking somewhere
Uh let's see. I was thinking somewhere
between 3 and 4 ounces of wire. I'd have
to calculate exactly how many turnings
they used. Is there a number you
suggest? If you can
approach what you call
300 that would be sufficient. Is the
diameter of wire sufficient?
Fine. If you can approach 300 wppings.
If you can't then no it is not. Okay. Uh
one more thing then uh on the drive
shaft a half inch of what material?
It can be what is called steel. Okay.
Okay, very good. Thank you. That's
enough for the next stage.
Uh, obviously it is possible to be the
idea of a lot of different things at the
same time. Right. In a sense. Yes. But
what do you mean in a sense? In the
sense that if you know you are an idea
that contains the opportunity to do many
different things, then they will simply
flow into your life in a manner that
will allow you to accomplish them in
sequential form. So it's not exactly
that you'll be doing them at the same
time, but you can be the idea all at
once. Okay, that's what I was asking.
Uh, one of the ideas that I have been
creating for the last number of weeks,
months is to to create a fourth density
atmosphere in my backyard. All right.
And as I was sitting thinking about what
that entailed, I thought, "Oh, I have
those king snakes and if the king snakes
don't get a go for a squirrel once in a
while, they won't live. And if the
squirrels, you know, don't eat whatever
and if the earwigs don't eat plants,
they will die." And this whole uh and
even if I, you know, don't pull weeds,
they will which kills the weeds. Uh
other plants can't live. And so that um
I don't know exactly how to think about
it. Do you mean that you cannot imagine
that you can sustain all within your
realm upon the energy that you vibrate
that they cannot partake of the
manifestation of the energy of your
eternal consciousness and so remain in a
state that that always allows them to
know they are sustained in whatever
manner they need to be. Can I do that? I
mean you tell me. Well, I do you believe
that you can. Yes, I do. But then you
have done it. I I think that you know
the ladybugs still eat insects and and
that is your choice.
You are creating third density
definitions of what? Yeah, I realize
that then simply redefine the idea that
they can exist in the state that they
are in by simply receiving direct energy
from you. Then they will simply lose the
urge. Okay. What? What happened? Let us put it
Okay. What? What happened? Let us put it
this way. Once again, remember that the
animals upon your planet are territorial
because you are.
I've been communicating with a lot of
the animals in my backyard and I think,
you know, um it seems to they seem to
pick it up. I mean, of course they do.
But they will always, however, only
reflect the degree of willingness that
you express in your own beliefs.
Therefore, they function as a very
accurate barometer for So, for example,
this if those king snakes that are up
there remain in my backyard, they will
not kill squirrels and gophers. But if
they go, they do not have to. If they
move somewhere else, they will perhaps.
Oh, what what do the animals on your
planet eat? In this way, again, it is
mostly energy and it is mostly through
the exchange you call symbiosis.
At times, in what you call the past, so
to speak, there used to be some
predatory forms, but no longer. Anything
you would now perceive as a quote
unquote predatory form always leaves its
prey alive. Taking an exchange of energy in a
alive. Taking an exchange of energy in a
certain way that benefits both. Oh, I
can do that in my backyard, too. Oh,
wonderful. I love it. As an
example, there
is a being, a creature, an animal as you
would call in this way, that would be
similar as we have described it to what
you would refer to as a slug-like
creature, but it will be a bit more
flat. It will have upon the top
side plates for the direct conversion of
sunlight into another type of energy. As
this creature crawls upon the skin of
another being, it will convert the
sunlight into a type of energy that when
it is projected into the cellular
structure of the being it is on, will
release a type of energy that the slug
feeds off of. But the conversion will
also regenerate and rejuvenate the cells
of the creature it is on. Oh, wonderful.
So, it is symbiotic in that way.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
Um recently you said that all pain med
mental and physical was spiritual and
emotional. Yeah. Was as a result of some
kind of disconnection from all that is.
Yes. Um can you recommend any process by
which a person can get more in touch
with all that is process? Well I don't
know. Um now we can recommend many
processes but recognize that your
imagination will alter them to fit you
and your vibration accordingly. But
again the idea the idea of believing
that a process is necessary is a
continuence of the separation because
you are not saying that you believe you
are connected now
and you are. It is trust that is
necessary. Knowing that you are connected acting
Knowing that you are connected acting
like you're connected acting like you
believe you're connected then you will
be. Yeah I get it. Thank you.
Bashar. Thanks. There's a Spider-Man
here. Several weeks ago, you you asked me a
Several weeks ago, you you asked me a
question about if there was any work
being done by myself or others on my
brain, and I answered no. I have
re-evaluated that uh question and have
possibly come up with a yes. I wonder if
you could give me any information on
that. Share what you feel.
Well, like a possibly a primary psychic
attack attack.
Why would you choose to interpret it as
an attack? Well, because if somebody is
uh doing something in my brain, it's
it cannot be without your agreement.
Right. Therefore, how can it be an
attack? I guess that answers my question.
Sir, one moment.
What we can perceive is that you are
cocreating an
allowance for you to be able to
perceive. There is no real terminology
in your language, but perhaps we can
refer to it
as the ability to create a core of
revelation. or the recognition or the
or the recognition or the
cognition of a fundamental primal
doorway gateway fusion point if you will through
gateway fusion point if you will through
which you can create a symbolic
connection to more of yourself. Mhm. An
alignment, a compaction, a fusion so to
speak has taken place to some degree. a
crystallization to some extent. You may
find at this time that there may
actually be a slight percentage higher more
be a slight percentage higher more
silica in your brain cells than
previously existed.
Does that assist you? Yes. Thank you.
Thank you, Bashar.
Rashar, um I'm very curious about
something. I'd like to reflect with you
for a moment on what I guess I'll call
um the power of the spoken word. All
right. And I was wondering um now that
we're going to be transitioning from
third density into speak up third
density into fourth density power of the
spoken word and all.
Thank you, M.
Right. Think of how best to say this,
but the way you say it will be the best
way for you to say it. Um, it it seems
to me that our language is going to
become very important in a sense,
although you will also find that you may
need language less. Well, what I was
wondering also is that you say on your
planet you communicate telepathically.
Yes. Well, um, this might be an
allegory, but like in the Bible where it
says, "And God said, let there be light
and there was light." And there was
obviously no one else there. So he
didn't have to use spoken word. So I
wondered do you It is the idea of
vibration. Vibration is what you are referring to
Vibration is what you are referring to
in your biblical literature as the word
that was spoken. It is the recognition
that out of the primal fundamental
energy every material universe is the
product of a variance in the vibration
of the primal fundamental energy. In
other words,
consciousness, the vibration of
consciousness is the word of God.
So you don't use words at all ever to
like an ritualistic form or words to
help manifest something like it is not
in this way necessary. You will find
that for the most
part the only remnant utilization that
our civilization now finds for the
language we once had maybe simply for
the enjoyment of what you call singing.
But in this way it is mostly vibratory
integral connections from one
consciousness direct to another. So then
it might be not so much our choice of
words as uselessness like too many being
wordy when it's getting an essential
word. It is not that your choice of
words cannot assist you in this way. For
many times you will realize that while
you think things are happening to you in
your reality unconsciously, if you would
but listen to the way you say things,
you will understand that they do very
often reflect the way you do believe
things to be. Therefore, when you begin
to listen to what you say, you may
recognize that your choice of words is a
symbolic reflection of your choice of
vibrations. Yes. I I think I've been
conscious in directing on that,
listening to what I say, listening to
what others say and how they say it.
choice of words. It gives you an idea of
where they really are at that point.
Yes. But recognize that while you are
listening so intently to the words, you
are also feeling them out which is more
of a telepathic idea. Okay. Do remember
that telepathy is emotionally activated.
Empathetic. Yes.
Okay. Thank you very much. Oh, and I
wanted to tell you the tape from last
week on synchronicity. I've been
listening to it all week while I paint.
I paint for a living and I've been
listening to the tape. Okay. I just love
it. It's been so helpful. Thank you very
much. Thank you for creating the
reflection in your life and allowing us
to reflect it to you. Thank you.
Rashard. No. Yes. Could you give me some
ideas perhaps on um why I may have
chosen the disease asthma and I'm having
difficulty curing myself of it. How is
it serving
you? What does it allow you to learn
intellectually? Things like the lungs
are the shape of butterflies. It has to
do with freedom. Um, I see. Very good.
What do you do with this knowledge?
Uh, I don't know. Oh, I'm having
difficulty translate, you know, acting
on it emotionally or um physically. Do
you feel that in your terms again to be
colloquial in your language that you
have connections to other places, other
times perhaps including ones off of your
planet? Do I feel that I have a connection to
Do I feel that I have a connection to
that? Yes.
I don't see it so much as another
planet. Sometimes I have the feeling I
think that um you know I'm not of this
planet but there is a feeling of not
being connect I I interpret that as not
feeling connected perhaps. All right.
But can it not be that you are feeling
connected to somewhere else rather than
simply interpreting it as not being
connected here? Yeah, I guess that could
be. All right. I have recollections of
feeling like I could fly. All right. Now
that is typical and does not necessarily
have to be a connection to another
planet as that will be a typical
experience that you will translate in
physiological terms in what you call
astro projection. But in this way simply
recognize that since you are
translating the idea of any other
connections you may have in terms as you
have shared them that you feel that you
are not connected to here from time to
time. Then you may have brought with you
a belief system that lets you think you
are quote unquote breathing alien
air and can't breathe it deeply.
No, the idea also can come hand in hand
many times and in this case our
perception is that it also does come
hand in hand with some of the
experiences you have created in what you
call your past life phenomena so to
speak with regards to suffocation
there. You will find that it is not
unlikely that many of what you call
azimatics are carryovers from
suffocation
death. As you are hearing what we are
saying, what feelings are occurring
within you?
Uh we are not expecting that you believe
us but simply what feelings are
occurring within you? Sadness.
Oh why?
Uh
well well aside from the feelings I've
I've had thoughts of actually a
relationship I was in where someone
tried to
um choke me. All right. So I'm thinking
that perhaps I manifested that as you
know trying to act out that somehow
since I mean that came up. So I'm
thinking maybe in your terms the idea
you would call a repetition of a
scenario you have lived through before.
So then of course thinking of that
particular thing that actually happened
physically here is brought up to
sadness. All right. Do you recognize
that sadness as you are experiencing it
at this point can also be
releasing? It is centering from a
negative point of view just like
laughter is centering from a positive
point of
view. Crying, laughing, the same thing.
One negative, one positive. Both of them
are centering
phenomena. Therefore, what you are doing
right now in the experiencing of your
emotional status is releasing,
centering, and opening up the
understanding that if you have created
these scenarios in your life, you are
once again in control of them. You have
drawn them into your life for a reason.
And the reason may simply be to allow
you to examine what you are examining
right now and to choose to connect and
link to the reality you have created in
whatever way you now prefer to because
this is the transformational life.
Therefore, any
idea can be allowed by you to be
deserved by you. Ecstasy is your
birthright. You do not have to do
anything special to deserve it. You do
not have to do anything special to earn
it. You are it automatically because you
exist. Therefore,
Therefore,
relax the judgments upon yourself and
the constrictions you have placed upon
yourself. Breathe deeply of the self and
the energy that you are. Know that your
oric field, your electromagnetic
spectrum can energize and oxygenate you
in whatever manner is necessary.
Take it for granted that the atmosphere
of your existence is worth breathing for
it was created of the very joy of
unconditional love of all that
is and if all that is created
you all that is obviously thinks you
deserve to
exist. So once you center after you
release recognize that in being
centered you are allowing yourself to
blend within ecstasy
ecstasy
energy from this point forward will open
doorways within your sub and unconscious
realms as you have created those levels
to exist within your consciousness. And
from this point forward, much can become
more conscious. And you may find that
your dream activity will accelerate in
various ways starting this night of your
time. Thank you for allowing us and
allowing yourself to touch those
doorways within you. For now, you will
find that many of the energy vortices
you call chakras within you will
expand, particularly the solar plexus, which is
particularly the solar plexus, which is
the chakra of
intention. Now that you are centered in
this way, you may allow yourself to
breathe more freely with who you are. As
you breathe freely and more freely into
your life, as you take in the atmosphere and
life, as you take in the atmosphere and
breathe out the new
reality, the reality you prefer to be,
recognize that you will then begin to
breathe together with others of the same
vibration. You will
You will
conspire to create a reality of peace.
You may all take a short break. [Applause]
All right. Say continue.
I bet you
um I heard about the blue light and uh
you said
uh manifesting any type of energy or any
type of of uh the idea may seem to be
that you are putting expectations on the
way you think it should manifest and not
allowing what manifest in your life to
be the way the energy has
to make that if I believe nice I would
just believe that Your total reality is
nothing but the product of what you
believe it to be. Plain and
simple. The idea of utilizing the blue
white energy is still only a symbol that
we have suggested to you because many of
you may find that it befits the modality
of your mentality. But if the symbol
doesn't work for you in that way, create
your own if you need one or simply
believe. Okay. I have a All right. How will we
Okay. I have a All right. How will we
die?
Okay. Uh I simply project within your
imagination the idea and you will find
that you can create the experience in
whatever way, shape and form is perfect
for you now. Or you may in your terms
quote unquote wait until you are in your
dream reality where it may be easier for you
reality where it may be easier for you
if you believe it
is. The idea again is that you do not
need so much of a pinpointing but simply
recognizing that when you attune
yourself to a particular idea it carries
its own vibrational wavelength. Simply
being tuned into that vibrational
wavelength will deposit whatever portion
of your consciousness needs to interact
with it wherever and whenever it is.
Time and space are not barriers to
consciousness. Thank you. Oh
Thank you. Oh
you sure you um is it I want to know how
Ouija board work in this way. It is like
anything else in a sense a tool. It is
an object. It is a symbol that allows
your own power of connection and your
own levels of awareness to be manifested
in physiological terms. Your own
connections to other consciousness can
be symbolically reflected or represented
by the action of that tool. But like
anything else, it is a tool. The power,
the communication, and the interaction
is from you. Oh, okay. Yeah, that's what
I was saying. I was thinking that that
maybe um people will believe that it'll
that some ghost or something will move
it for you. So then they move it
themselves but aren't aware of it. Oh
that can occur. Now this is not to say
that you cannot co-create a reality
wherein you will allow another
consciousness to activate the
physiological mechanism. This is not to
say that what you call disembodied
consciousness cannot act that way. Many
times it can. All we are simply saying
is that it is neither just it that is
doing it neither just you. It is a
combination of both that creates the
interaction. You are both doing it.
Oh it doesn't work in this way then
simply it does not carry through your
belief system but that is a tool that
will work for you. Oh the communication
can occur and does occur in many other
ways. It is a tool to let you know
something is going on that you are
creating with another consciousness. Oh,
there's a person that uses a Ouija kind
of levels of spirit like fourth level
old spirit and like anything about that
guys. You are referring to the entity
consciousness that refers to itself as
Michael. Oh,
Oh,
in this way again simply recognize that
it is a tool that many individuals will
find useful because it is a tool that is
fashioned in a shape that is reflective
of the way their mentality works. So
they will let the tool work for them.
Just like other individuals will avail
themselves of the idea you call cards
tea leaves. Many of these ideas are simply
leaves. Many of these ideas are simply
different ways that your consciousness
is comfortable in allowing a
manifestation to project into physical
reality. So they are all tools.
That that um idea kind
of breaks the theory of how how time
does exist in this way. Again, simply
recognize that time does exist when you
create it to exist. You are creating
yourself to exist within it. When it is
said that time does not exist, it
doesn't mean that you do not create a
reality in which it doesn't exist. It
means that beyond the reality in which
you experience time, it is not
experienced. And that time is created
within existence. Time is subject to
creation. Creation is not subject to
time. Time is one of the creations of
creation. Creation is not a creation of
time. Therefore, time does exist when
you create it to exist. But if you do
not create it to exist, you don't live
in it. Many consciousnesses that
communicate with your level of time
track awareness do not exist in a time
frame. They only seem to and they use
terminology that makes sense to you
because you can only understand things
from a time frame point of view.
So it translates into terms you can
understand. This does not mean that the
reality is that way for
them. You follow me? Yeah.
It is simply like learning to translate
from one language to another. You may
have a word in one of your languages for
an object. That word may not exist in
another language, but you can find some
way to refer to it by using terminology
that may be common to both languages. Okay.
Okay.
Uh that's that's it.
Can you channel for me and
uh talk to Ford?
to Ford?
I'd like to know why she's
uh attempting to get in touch with me or
why I want to get in touch with her and
and have not uh consciously been able to
do so.
All we can perceive at this time is that
there may be
diverence within the idea of identity
consciousness life
paths that may be necessary to be
brought to your attention.
It does not necessarily
necessarily
prognosticate a negative event, but in
this way simply may be indicative that
your vibration and the vibration of that
consciousness to some degree may be
diverging for various reasons personal
to yourselves independently.
Could you put that in plain English?
Are you waiting, guys? Well, you told me
no already, guys. Okay,
we are waiting for the one who can put
it into plain English to do so.
I don't get it. I
know. I'll keep waiting until you do.
Can you repeat anything that I said at
all?
Not really. No. Anything at all? One
word. Yes. We
Yes. We
Anything else?
Any other concept at all? Were you
listening at all?
Thank you.
Using your imagination right now. Are
you willing to do this? Yeah. All right.
with your imagination, fully trusting
the capabilities of your
imagination. Go within your imagination
right now and
imagine what I
said. What come to you? Well, the the
two of we were working on something
that would perhaps be somewhat of a
diversion. Uh well what I got is we're talking
Uh well what I got is we're talking
about some a similar thing that might
take us a different path. Now what was
so difficult about that? Oh well I got
that but
then you are just being stubborn
perhaps. Perhaps I
am that much of it I I got. Uh, however,
it's still I guess it's there's more desired
still I guess it's there's more desired
more desired. Okay. What makes you think
there is more? You feel like there's
more. Well, yeah, that's my judgment. It
is not a judgment. It is a feeling.
Well, that's how I feel. Then if you
feel like there's more, you must be
aware of what it is.
Since you are sensing that there is
more, what is it?
May I ask you a question? Well, you
don't have to ask me a question to ask.
Thank you.
Does anyone ever
understand that sometimes the dialogues
we have with you, the very mode of the
dialogue is in itself the answer?
What does that tell you?
Well, for some reason I just wanted to
get more. I wanted to hear more. Then
you know that there is more. What is
it? Trust that you're sensing that there
is more to hear is an indication of your
ability to know what it
is. But you are just being stubborn with
yourself.
Let it go. That in itself is a help.
Very good. We are attempting to show you that
good. We are attempting to show you that
what is being done with that
consciousness energy as well. And what
we are reflecting to you is that we are
luring you into more of your
selfawareness. Okay.
Okay.
Well, there is a tendency to not want to
get into the d the the dissecting of any
pattern or anything because I'm I'm just
separating more. Now, in this way, the
idea of the willingness to extend your
senses does not have to manifest as an
analytical process. You can simply know
there is more, say what it is, and not
feel that you are dissecting your life.
Well, that is in itself
uh somewhat of that part of me because
saying what something is and feeling it
is two different things. Yeah. In a
sense, you know what I'm saying? Uh I
know what I'm feeling from a feeling
viewpoint from a from a from a soul or a
beingness viewpoint. Then you have the
complete answer within you in a feeling
sense. Is that what you are saying? Yes.
But but often times it's it's I find it
difficult or my laziness or whatever you
want to say to reflect back to you
verbally what you're
asking. You understand me? Then in this
way, why did
you create the
connection of reflective assistance in
terms of something that you could have
dealt with yourself?
Well, there was a bit of uncertainty in
that. Is there now? Yes. Can you deal
with it? Yes, I always do. All right.
Are you happy about that?
I know it'll come out in the wash, you
know? I mean, I have no doubts about
that. All right. And I know that my
trust level with myself
is is perfect. Perfect. It is. It is.
Because that's the way I get what I
need. Then based on that definition of
your reality, what can I possibly
reflect in you that you do not hold?
Well, you sped the process up just now
by making some statements that uh then
as I said the modality of the exchange
is all the answer we can give you. Okay.
Thank you.
Yes. Um I have two two questions. Well,
one is about
um um well the pain I've been having in
my
spine of my very lower back for how long
in your terms of time? One week and a
half. One week and one half hour. Yeah.
And and I was wondering and I've been
having dreams during this time. And they
are of what nature?
Uh well, one was a there a a flying
dinosaur uh called a a pterodactyl flying through
uh called a a pterodactyl flying through
the window. And another was of a dragon.
I was a Chinese dragon flying. And then
last night,
um I'm supposed to buy a reptile
um
handbag. So, but meanwhile, my back uh
when I when I move from under. Okay.
How does it feel when you bend over
forward and exhale?
I now or now? Then sit up and inhale.
Bend over forward and exhale. Sit up and
inhale. How does that feel? [Music] over. Yeah.
How do you feel? Very warm. Very hot.
Yes. And can you direct that heat into your
And can you direct that heat into your
spinal area with your imagination?
Yes. No. Maybe. Yeah. question.
question.
How does it feel when you do so? Um, Um,
what else?
Do you or can you or have you during
this time sensed the manifestation of
let us
say a smell an
odor that is different than anything you
have sensed
before. You may only be smelling it in
your imagination rather than in what you
call your nose. But in this way do you
sense an odor? Um,
I'm seeing something. All right. What?
It's like a thick flower. Thick flower.
What's color?
All right. How many paddles?
Well, it's like a lotus. Yeah, it's all
right. Very good.
Relax. What you are beginning to release
is the idea that has been for quite some
time in your civilization referred to as
the kundalini energy at the base of your
spine. You are beginning to align many
different levels of yourself and you are
forming particular connections as you
have symbolically related in your dreams
to ancient wisdom which is what the
symbol of the dragon
is. ancient lives, ancient wisdom, and
ancient connections to many other
universes that in a sense first
manifested themselves in your particular
earth frame reality as the concept that
you call a dragon or that is perceived
by your earth consciousness as what you
call a dragon.
It is simply the release of the
weight and the exploration of the
releasing of the weight and the
exploration of the opening up of the
different channeling energy within your
spine in the connection of all the
different levels upon which you exist
that is causing some degree of the pain
you are talking about. Or you will find
that you have reached a point in your
life where this integration can take
place and there is still some small
degree shards remnants of judgments of
habits within you. It is only those
shards and remnants that are allowing
the pain to be felt at all. Recognize in
other words it is still a perfectly
timed event. Let us put it this way. If
this were to occur three years of your
time ago, you would have been almost
crippled. You can handle it now. It will
acclimate. As you simply do more of the
being you know yourself to be, as you
simply let the energy of your intentions
flow through you, you will continue to
align, blend, assimilate, and acclimate
to the energy. It will level out.
Yes, I do. I do. Thank you. That um I
have one other question. But I have one.
Okay. What's yours? Oh, you
both about serious
in that I
um like the word and I don't know what
it is. I
mean it's it is your name for a star.
Mhm. Around that star is a multi-level,
multi-dimensional consciousness,
civilization if you wish, that has been
in contact with your civilization for
quite some time and forms the upper
level consciousness of the triad energy
that is formed by them, us and
you. They are very strongly connected to
the dolphin consciousness upon your
world as well.
You will find that because that energy
is blending with your civilization now
that as you form connections to many
different levels, you may contain an
essence of a connection to that idea as
well. It will be experienced as the
polarity between the positive, the
negative, the light, the
dark. So my question to you is what
color is the dragon?
Well, you see the first word came as
green, but I don't
Well, that's all I in terms of seeing
it. All right. Then trust the first
thing that comes to mind. Mhm. For it is
representative once again of the
blending that is going on now because
the idea of green the emerald vibration
is the symbolic vibration of the fourth
density transformation taking place upon
your planet now. So you are blending an
ancient symbol the dragon with the
polarity of the white light in this way
forming the blending of the polarity and
being completely in the moment the green
vibration of the earth emerald crystal.
So now you are a green dragon
symbolically as opposed to the black
dragon that you parttook of in the past.
Not necessarily saying that that is a
negative thing in and of itself, but it
is simply representative of the time
tracks that do to some extent define
some negative polarity. The white lotus
in your terms is the other symbolic end
of the spectrum. You are blending the
two together in the green vibration of
assistance with the transformation.
Sleep on it.
Thank you. Fine.
Yes. Um I have my attention on a
spiritual matter in communication with
some friends elsewhere off of this
planet. I see three beings bald heads
out there somewhere. And I seem to have
attention on who these beings are. Can you speak
on who these beings are. Can you speak
up a little bit? I have attention on who
these beings are. And I get a sense of
friendship and peace and pulling me that
way. Skin color radiation sort of gray.
White.
Have we ever told you what we look like?
All the males have no hair. Fox skin is
white whitish gray.
Yes. And is it discerned? Um almond
shaped eyes go up.
You sense a largeness about the eyes.
Yes. Thank you. But the ones I I sense a
Thank you. But the ones I I sense a
delicateness somewhere. Oh yeah. And I
guess there's an aesthetic quality
there. And I want to know
I feel like they're my friends and I
felt this for some time, but I'm not
quite sure why I see three. Because we
form the idea of a triad and we work in
threes all the time.
The idea once again as it has been
expressed is that a triad formation
triangular formation first of all is the
primary fundamental geometric that will
always occur in second density and third
density. The tetrahedrin is the most
basic fundamental form of manifestation
in third density that you can have in
physical reality. The idea of serious
consciousness, our consciousness, your
consciousness forms a triad
consciousness. So that the idea is that
two are always supporting the one. In
that way our civilization works in
threes in networks of threes in that way
always upon the principle of forming the
triad for support in that way the two to
the one.
I see. And in terms our craft scout
craft are also triangular.
Okay. One more question. I see. in terms
of this feeling of wanting to go there
or feel or having been there or having
been there.
It's just sometimes I feel like I'm not
something about an uneasiness with here
in terms of even my body and its
function that it's a little alien in
terms of being comfortable. But do not
judge it. You have chosen to be where
you are to be of service in the way you
wish to be. You simply now as you are
forming more awareness of the
connections may at first because of the
habit remnants of judgment that you have
picked up in this
society. You may form an
uncomfortableness for a while simply
because you are now making connections
to other places that you also are. It
will pass. The more joy you put into the
recognition that the connections you are
realizing is of service on this planet
you find yourself to be on now, the
easier you will fit into the clothes.
Okay, that's good because I really feel
there's a communication that helps
between the two points and I think I
want to just bring them together as a
purpose or a goal. Thank you.
Many of you once again visit our level
of consciousness many
times and bring back what you need to
bring back. Sometimes that is simply
more awareness.
Thank you. Oh, thank you. One moment. [Music]
What you call in terms of your
counting? July 7th.
Oh, July is my birthday. 7 is my
favorite number. Uh, it's the seventh month.
number. Uh, it's the seventh month.
Have a good time on that day.
Thank you. I will. Oh, thank you.
Um, I want to ask you another definition
of an emotion. Oh, right. I noticed that
you're sharing with us is different from
say Americans sharing with the starving
African. What is the emotion
pity? Pity is
judgment. It is not an emotion. It is
judgment. Okay? It is the consideration
that something else is less.
Then
you recognize once again simply the idea
of the interchange you are defining and
describing that though they have created
for themselves the idea of physiological
starvation. Your willingness to interact
with them allows you to feed them
physiologically while they in turn allow
you to fill in the gap in the spiritual
starvation you have created in your
society.
You are feeding each other.
So there is no need for pity.
Is it possible that we might have a
communication from Mark Turos tonight? in dream state
particularly within each and every one
of you that creates the manifestation of
the portion of yourself that you call
the child. Sure.
Yes. Bashar, can you tell me how um on
your planet you take care of the raising
of the young?
In this way, you will find that first of
all, we are in communication with the
consciousness before it is born, during
birth, and after birth. In this way, you
will find that we are always in touch
with the understanding of why that
individual has chosen to manifest within
our society to begin with. Therefore,
any raising that is done is only an
orientation process into the dimension
that that consciousness has projected
itself approximately up to what you
would call 3 years of age. Then they are
on their own for the most. Do they age?
Do they reach full what we would
consider adult height? No. But in this
way at what you call three they have
developed the idea of the ability of
interaction necessary with an honor
society to simply attract themselves to
wherever they need to attract themselves
to learn what they need to learn.
Thank you. Fascinating.
Bashar, in uh in your
in uh in your
society, you travel through physical
space in a
in a
sense. We do have a type of physical
nest that you would call fourth density.
When you come visit us, do you travel
through space to here or do you
just appear? Now the idea of the
communication you are perceiving this
night of your time is not quote unquote
traveling in the usual sense in this
way. I have not come to your sphere
except by the projection of my mentality
my consciousness in that way. The idea
of traveling in what you would call our
spacecraft also was not exactly
traveling as you understand it. But the
idea is not necessary for us to travel
in this way for this type of
communication to take place. The idea of
consciousness takes place above so to
speak time and space. Therefore, any
connection of this sort needs only the
belief and the trust and the faith
within the mechanism of the dimension of
the imagination to occur. Now, this is
part and parcel of how spacecraft work
as well since they are also only
projections of consciousness like
anything else in the physical universe.
But in this way, many times we have the
distinction of communicating with you
this way. Whereas I am in my spacecraft
in my own system, not in your system. Or
I have the opportunity in this way of
moving as you would say my spacecraft to
your system and interacting with you
that way.
Um do you follow me? Yes. When when you
do come in your spacecraft, can you
exist in our atmosphere? Yes. For there
will have been the slight vibrational
shift necessary to exist in your frame
of reference at all. You would find that
with a similar slight shift in the other
direction, you would be able to survive
in our planetary atmosphere as well. It
is not dissimilar physically. Okay?
Recognize that when you travel in our
spacecraft, you automatically almost
unconsciously would make a shift you do
not think you are making. You are
adapted during the journey because the
idea is that to exist in our
civilization to even be able to perceive
any other civilization on any other
planet, you have to change the
vibrational frequency of your
consciousness. Anyway, doing so can
allow you to adapt to the existence of
that civilization.
If it is necessary to change my
frequency to perceive you, is it
possible for you to come in your space
and only have certain individuals
perceive? Yes.
That happens quite often as a matter of
fact. For you will find that because of
the vagaries of consciousness because
you are shifting all the time. Many
times there are simply ships around you
all the time you are not aware of. And
sometimes certain individuals because
they simply for a moment for some reason
tune into a certain vibration will
suddenly have it seem as if a craft has
appeared when it has been there all
along.
Follow me. Um yes I have one more
question. All right. Um is
Um is
matter does matter contain
consciousness? Yes. Matter is
consciousness. Energy is consciousness.
All energy, all everything is
consciousness. All that is is consciousness. So um
All that is is consciousness. So um
since everything is consciousness and
it's everywhere
and everywhere
then you can that that's how you can
tune into a different. Yes. The universe
is as you call it holographic.
Do you understand the terminology? No.
holographic as you have created it to
understand your civilization simply is a
reference to the idea that any one point
in the universe contains the probable
whole universe.
How does that work?
Very
well. The idea can be expressed this
way.
There is once again in what you call
your earth mythology the idea expressed
as Indra's net which is simply a net of
pearls. Now each pearl being round and
reflective has the ability of reflecting
every other pearl in the
net. Therefore it can be said that each
pearl contains the information of the
total net. That is the way the universe is
net. That is the way the universe is
built so to speak. That is why we can
travel as we do because the idea is
simply that we do not think of
spacecraft or any physical object as
something that exists within space and
time but we consider spacetime to be
properties of the object itself. Thus,
when we change the particular space-time
coordinate property, vibrational
signature property of an object and
replace it with another vibration, then
by definition, the object must cease to
exist at its former location and take up
residence at the second one, no matter
how far apart in space or time that is.
I'm traveling in between. Correct. Yes.
Now understand this is what you are
doing anyway even when you move through
a room for every moment is its own
unique moment and is not connected to
the next moment until you form a
continuum in your mentality. So you are
constantly redefining the property of
space and time for yourself so that you
create the illusion of motion.
Nothing really goes
anywhere. It is all right here.
If only. Yeah. So that means I can stop
creating that
continue. Yeah. Yes, you can.
Does that exciting you? Yes.
Yes.
Then you may find yourself creating less
time which will seem like an
acceleration to you. But that is what
you are literally doing when you are
accelerating. Living in the now creates
less time.
So things seem to be sped up.
took care of all those questions.
Sorry. Um Oh, yeah. If there if there's
a tree out in the middle of nowhere and
nobody's around to see it, okay, and a
leaf falls, does it make a sound? Maybe.
Now recognize this. When you say no one
is around to see it, that does not mean
that your telepathic mass collective
unconsciousness is not aware that it is
there and is not aware of the fact that
you have created a universe in which it
must make a sound. That does not mean it
has to. And in all reality, if no one is
creating that idea to exist, then not
only does the leaf not make a sound,
there is no leaf and there is no tree.
you decide to perceive as human
um sometimes I get very strong images of
um I say
um of people's thoughts or or
things of that sort and and sometimes I
meditate in large groups and I and I
don't get visuals at all but sometimes I
do is there any way that I and use some
exercises that would help me to be more
visual. But why do you think that not
having visuals is a deficiency?
I just enjoy having them. I'm artistic.
I like to see them. All right. Do you
like to feel them? I Yeah, I feel all
the time. I mean that that part I get
emotions all the time, but I don't
always get the visuals with it. And I
But you don't always need them.
No, but I get a
I want them. But create them.
Back to my question. Are there any
exercises I can do that can create them
more often? I find that I often don't
have them when I would like to. But for
you don't No, you don't have visuals
when you would like to. Right. For
example, should I give an example? All
right. Um I was recently um May I
interrupt you for a moment? Certainly.
Chair, I get those visuals.
I get those visuals.
So, what is the difference? Well, I'll
tell you. All right.
I was in Sedona recently in a um an
archaeological um like a cave dwelling.
Okay guys, and I was inside a um a
shaman's um room where he did some I
didn't know what he had done there, but
I was in there alone and I was feeling
these very strong emotions and I was
trying to get pictures and or or I was
wondering why I wasn't getting pictures
and I wasn't. I just felt the emotions
and I did not know how to connect them
with anything. It is very simple. You
are not creating any
pictures. Being in that type of energy
is being in a vortex. the center of
creation, the center of all probable
universes where you need to take action
to create the realities you want to
experience. You simply were open,
waiting to receive, but not recognizing
that in that particular type of energy,
you don't receive what messages you
don't send.
Okay. Well, I don't understand that
because what the archaeologist said was
that a number of different psychics had
been in there at different times and
they had all
experienced or told him about the same
the same picture. Yeah. So, I don't know
that. Well, anyway, what it was was
something to do with with the shaman
that was in there and what he did to
some women that were there at the time.
Yes. So,
and why did I just get the emotions? I
felt I I got some very strong emotions,
but I didn't get pictures. I don't what
did they do differently than I did? They
may have within their belief structure
an automatic mechanism that allows them
whether they know it or not to project
and then trust that whatever pictures
they project are the pictures they need
to receive.
In other words, perhaps you are trying
too hard in the sense of or you are not
believing that the pictures you would
create in your imagination consciously
would be as valid as something you don't
think you had anything to do with
you follow. I do except that sometimes I
get very vivid pictures you know
sometimes. Well then you are not trying
so hard. I just I do the same thing. I
close my eyes and just let it come. Then
it comes. I I'll ask a qu Oh, I'll ask a
question. Maybe you can ask a question.
The idea simply is from our point of
view that if you find yourself in a
situation where you get pictures, that
is what you need. If you don't get them,
that is what you
need. Again, it may simply be that your
automatic expectation is so quick that
if you don't get them exactly when and
as fast and in the way you think you
should, then you cut off the flow that
might come in the very next second
because you are too busy looking for
them to see them when they come.
Relax your expectations and then
paradoxically you might offer yourself
more opportunity to receive them, but
recognize that if they're not there,
they don't need to be there. Why make
the assumption that something is wrong
if they're not there?
It's not wrong, but when it's But you
are assuming that you are somehow
deficient by comparison. I suppose yes.
Then that is in your terminologies
translated as wrong.
Yeah, I'm missing some of the fun. You
are not. You are having fun in your own
way. in the way you will add to the
overall experience in your unique
way. Now do not
Now do not
assume that every single one of those
individuals who got pictures then always
gets pictures.
Perhaps for you, the feelings were more
important because maybe the way you
translate feelings is quote unquote more
appropriate to the overall scenario than
the way they would have translated
feelings. You follow
me? In other words, whatever you
experience, it is a reflection of what
you can bring to the event in your own
unique way.
So if you don't get something then
assume you don't need it to share in the
event. Translate it in whatever way you
do get it. That is how it needs to be
gotten. So lighten up on yourself
you in my dream state lately I there are
two dichotoies occurring. One, I feel so
unconscious that if a biological urge
turns on, like to go to the bathroom, it
takes me so long to compute where that
feeling is and what it is I'm supposed
to do with it. And it's it gets kind of
hairy. I've had it happen several times.
And the other is that I my dreams keep
repeating themselves of unlimitedness,
going back to the same places and going
through the same things over and over
again and nothing ever resolving. Nope.
Never the same place, never the same
dream. Only your assumption that it is
makes it seem
so. You are never the same you. You are
never in the same now. How can you
possibly ever go to the same place?
That is true. So it's an apparency. Yes,
it is something that I am trying to work
out by the apparency of it being the
same place with similar circumstances.
Many times you will find that as you
continue to change and become different
new you. You will reflect on a similar
circumstance from different points of
view. It may only be that you are
judging it as the same circumstance over
and over and over again when in actual
fact you are viewing an idea from many
different perspectives because you are
now new. so that you can come to an
new. so that you can come to an
understanding from a variety of points
of view, an all-encompassing idea.
Simply remove the expectation that you
are repeating something and you will
allow the information that represents a
new focus to come through.
I see. and being so disoriented with the
body and trying to regain some memory of
what the body is even doing. That is all
right as well for recognize that
disorientation is exactly that you are
disorienting from one reality and
reorienting in another one. Confusion
that limbo state of disorientation is
simply being connected to all the
different points of view that you are
confusion.
Allow it to be an all right state and
you will become comfortable with it and
always know where and when you have to
be. Okay. The only negativity you are
Okay. The only negativity you are
experiencing is because you think you
are losing track or losing control
because you are not used to the limbo
state. The limbo state is there now because you
The limbo state is there now because you
have the ability as many of you now have
to consciously perceive when you are
changing from one belief to another. So
it leaves you hanging for a while. But
that is all right because that state in
and of itself is a place to learn
something from. And it lets you know you
are in control because you are
witnessing firsthand consciously the
unlocking from one reality and the
reorienting and relocking to another
one. Whereas before this was mostly an
unconscious process. These are only
symptoms of the blending and the removal
of levels from your consciousness which
is truly only one consciousness.
Subconsciousness and unconsciousness are
convenient terms, but they do not really
exist unless you create them to.
I see. Thank you.
I've been
u playing with the idea of
u over the past few months uh the
ringing and the the clue sounds at
various times that would come
in. I have had tooth
well say sensations around the teeth.
All right. Okay. And here of late I
have I guess about a week ago I've come
up with this excruciating toothache and
uh it was about 2 days after leaving the
dentist actually
and and I associated at first I
associated the uh pain with some sort of
cosmic connection but now the pain has
begun to be so excruciating until it's u
it's got to be something that needs to
be handled right away.
Have you gone back to your dentist?
Why not?
Well, one reason was because I wanted to
I'd like to really
just handle it without going to the
dentist. Right. That is all right. You
may try whatever your imagination
suggests. But recognize that if that is
the way your belief structure is set up,
then I would suggest you avail yourself
of your belief reality.
Your belief reality may be that you have
to go to the dentist and that is what
will cure you. That is what will let you
cure yourself. However, feel free to
experiment with whatever your
imagination comes up with. One of the
things we have suggested from time to
time is that blue light shined on the
teeth can alleviate some of that idea.
Mhm. Now, well, does that this specific
pain in this specific,
you know, You you can stop that.
Okay. Anyway, I have gotten sensations
in and around the four. Okay. And that
has occurred that has been occurring for
months now. Yes. Okay.
Um, and for some reason I want to
associate that with some realization
that I'm having or some connection that
I'm having. But this particular maybe
just the realization that you have a
toothache. No, that's that's the point. All right.
No, that's that's the point. All right.
The other sensations was never
crystallized into one specific tooth as
it has now. And even now the things will
will vary all around
the you understand and I'm
wondering what is that symbolic of if
anything other than my having to go and
get this thing taken out you know the
the movement of having various
sensations all
around what
K9 next to the K9. It's next to the
K9. The fourth tilt to the
right on top. Do you
Do you
think if you go to your dentist, he will
create for you what is called a crown.
Well, for this particular tooth, well,
if you can, okay, I don't think he can.
Do you think there will be a process to
call root canal? No. Oh dear.
I am simply asking you.
Has that cost you a lot?
Well, for this particular tune, I just
thought it would have to be taken out
period. Taken out. Yeah.
Taken out. Yeah.
All right. Why?
Because it it does have movement. Shaky, shaky.
What this comes down to is the fact that
I have had sensations all around the jaw
at various times.
Now the fact that it's crystallized in
this particular tooth has brought up
it's more or less prompted me to ask the
question the question of why or what or
is there some sort of symbolic there is
always some sort of symbolic something
obviously everything is a symbol of
something
well I've been playing with the idea
that this particular tooth is bringing
all of this to a head. All right.
How will you feel if it is removed?
Mine is mine, too. How will you feel
about that? I don't want to I don't want
to take it out. All right. Thank you. I
really will. All
right. Then will you do me a favor?
Sure. Maybe you
We'll see. All
All
right. Will you tonight of your
time? When you go
home, take take
one
glass of what you call purified
water. Place it before
you. Allow it to be cool, not too cold.
In other words, room temperature. Is
that It can be a little cooler if you
desire it, but not too much. Okay.
Can I purify this myself with my own
thoughts or do I need to go to the store
and buy some?
What you call purified water? That is in
your terms purchasable. Okay. Okay.
In this way, set this glass before
you now.
Yeah. At the same
time, do you
have acquisition in this way of
substance that you refer to as primary?
No, I guess I would have to stop and
die. All right. When
When
you will then place some of this also in
what you call a glass that's designed
for the holding of that liquid. What you
refer to as snifter.
Follow me.
Snifter. Oh, okay.
Place small amount of bran in the bottom
of the glass.
Place the glass in your line of
sight behind the glass of water with the
brandy in it. Behind the glass of water.
You are looking in a sense past the
glass of water to the brandy and
following. Light through it. Yes. In a
sense. Okay. Over it is sufficient.
[Music] Then in your terms,
Then in your terms,
light the
branding. You follow me?
light. Okay, Okay,
then
look look at the color of the flame.
That color is what I would suggest you
imagine the water to be imbued with that
color energy. Seeing it in flame form
will create it to be easier for you
physiologically to imagine
it. Imagine that color going into the
water for as long as the flame shall
last. That will be
sufficient. Assume that the energy of
that color has
completely saturated the
water. All right. Mhm. Mhm. Then
Then
after the fire has gone out in the
branding, bend down and
inhale one deep breath of the aroma. Do
not drink it. One deep breath of the
aroma. Then slowly and
Then slowly and
comfortably drink the
water, allowing it a little bit of time
to sit in the mouth and wash the tooth
and then go down your
throat. Then relax. Do nothing
active. You may go to sleep if you
wish. and simply know that that energy
is now infusing the cellular structure
of your body and will go to whatever
portions of your body require it the
most. If that is your tooth, so be it.
It will even out the electromagnetic
balance of your oric field and allow you
to know that when you awake, you can
create yourself to be a totally new
individual at whatever rate is
comfortable for you. so that you no
longer necessarily require the idea of
that pain and the need for extraction in
that way. Thanks. Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Nice luck for sure.
I think he deserves it.
[Music] After all, he has put up with me for
After all, he has put up with me for
super long. Yes. one.
one.
Do not be sorry. Oh, she can go there.
She's way in the back. You okay? Then
you ma'am.
First, uh, I love you very much. I love
you. Second, I like your title for
Second, I like your title for
under control. Okay. What was the
question? want a title for tonight for
the tape. Oh, I had three. Um, you said
that um if you would laugh, we would break
um if you would laugh, we would break
the
channel and I was just wondering if you
could just maybe laugh totally at the
end of the channeling. We could see see
you know you would not experience it
though in that way. No, this is as close
as it can get for now.
Who are you?
We'll see.
start made some suggestions to me in
regards to delivering my baby and so I I
followed that and uh it worked perfectly
and I
coincidence I wanted to thank you for it
but also it's like everything went so
perfectly it was practically painfree
and it was outright exciting yeah right
and the um my baby did help me
throughout it and from the moment I woke
up she um gave me an idea I experienced
which I don't even know how to describe
that experience but you have done so
perfectly oh thank you and every
everything went perfectly the whole
thing was completely
everything was like being in a exciting
movie may I congratulate Thank you on
the creation of that vibrational reality
for yourself and the allowance of
someone who
is much more used to that reality to
help you.
I've been finding that quite true. Yeah.
Thank you. Okay. For the expression of
your love to yourself and therefore to
all that is.
Oh, you're welcome. Good. Two things.
Uh, number one is um some channels can
break the connection. So, it just has to
do with you and Daryl
in a sense. Okay. And also another thing
is talking about teeth. Is there
something um you suggest for the gums?
Um sometimes my gums get irritated.
Would there be something good for me to
apply or rinse my mouth that way? I use
salt water in that. Is there also
anything else? Mint. Mint.
Mint. Mint. Now
you don't mean the form of like mint
candy stuff like that. More
[Music] making like a
making like a
leaf. Wait, wait, wait. Okay, great.
leaf and but can there also be made like
a mouth wash out of those or something
adding water or steeped steamed then
cooled. Okay, thank you.
One moment.
[Music] If you wish, if you are so inclined, you
If you wish, if you are so inclined, you
can follow what we
suggested a while ago. Okay,
and begin. Why do you think I should
have
because you enjoy my biting
commentary? I I have a difficulty in
hearing sounds. What? I have a
I have a difficulty in uh in hearing
everything that is around that I should
be hearing and should be well if someone
is communicating to me and I do not
perceive that verbal communication.
Okay. Then what is it that you think you
might not want to hear?
It's not a matter of what I don't want
to hear. It's just a matter that I don't
hear it. What do you think you are
missing? Well, I'm missing the communication that
Well, I'm missing the communication that
was directed to me. Not really.
Understand that sometimes many
individuals will create the
idea of the seeming blockage of one of
their external physiological senses so
that they will give themselves the
opportunity to utilize that sense
inwardly and begin listening to
themselves since that is where all your
answers come from anyway and all your
information. Anything that you would
hear from someone else, you have to
create internally your version of it to
be able to listen to
it. This simply may be an opportunity
for you to recognize that you have
access to all the information you need.
So maybe you blocked your lines of
external communication so that you can
get used to listening
inwardly and realize that that is
something you can rely on. You are not
disconnected. You are not out of touch.
You are not missing out on
anything. Listen inwardly. You will know
all that you need to hear.
The sort of I I get what you're saying.
But right, the next step is to also
recognize that as soon as you know that
your hearing inwardly is crystal
clear, your hearing in your dimension of
imagination is crystal clear.
The next step is to know that your
physical reality and your imagination is
the same
thing. So that your external reality is
no longer
external. If it is one in the same
thing, you will hear and
see as crystal clearly outwardly as you
do inwardly. When you allow the inward
reality to be the outward reality,
is there something within you once again
that you may desire to do that you are
not doing? An expression of your inward
reality that is not being projected into
the outer
reality. Many times if you hold
something within you that you desire to
do, you do not then create an atmosphere
around you in which the appropriate
sounds can
travel. Simply it is a reflection that
the sounds you are hearing in the
reality around you have nothing to do
with the reality you would rather
be. We all fine. It's very true. the uh
reality that I find myself in just being
here on this planet is uh very
unsatisfactory to me and yet I'm here.
So obviously you chose to be. Now when
you begin to function as if it truly was
a choice and that you knew what you were
doing and still do, then perhaps you
will give vent to some of the things you
wish to do that represent the ideas that
would exemplify your vibration
regardless of what anyone else says.
Create this to be the home you are
familiar with by living like it.
create this to be heaven on earth.
Okay. Thank you.
And um do we choose our parents? Yes.
And they choose you. Okay. Um I have
another question. You said before that one of
question. You said before that one of
the things that separates uh whales and
us from our pets is that we think and
they just know. Um, what about apes?
The idea is that you are projecting a
portion of your consciousness into that
animal fragment of your consciousness to
represent and exemplify connections to
the basic fundamental foundational
physiological form that you extracted
your present model from.
Thank you. the show. I was wondering if you
you. the show. I was wondering if you
enjoy physical pleasures or hobbies as
we do. Like I like to go scuba diving
and go swimming and things like that.
Everything that I partake of, I enjoy.
The idea from time to time is that there
is interaction of a sort with other
individuals. Spontaneous interaction
that you might call play. But then
again, everything to us is play.
I am in your terms playing right now. Do
you have limitations as we do? Only
those that are designed to define the
beings we consider ourselves to be
through the job we want to do. I'm not
sure I understand. We have self-imposed
limitations like any reality within all
that is to simply allow us to exist as
something distinct from everything else.
Okay. [\h__\h] you.
Dice. Um, do you are you familiar with Mount
Um, do you are you familiar with Mount
Shasta?
Dice, what what meaning does that have
for you? It is what you term in your
vernacular the crown chakra energy of
the earth.
[Music] The vortex and the
The vortex and the
doorway of multi-dimensional connection.
First to be man in the body. That is the
heart chakra. How about you? Third eye
chakra. What is your back? How about
Israel? There is energy vortic there, but it is
There is energy vortic there, but it is
not in your terms one of the major
chakra points. Where's the condolin?
The idea of what you call north and
south poles will function much like the
spinal column in that way.
Does that answer your question as to
Shasta or would you wish to continue with
or would you wish to continue with
something? I'd like to know if I have a
special connection with Shasta being
since you have asked obviously you do
otherwise it probably never would have
occurred to you to ask. That is what we
mean by allowing your physical reality
and the imagination and excitement you
create within yourself to be an obvious
reflection of the connections you have
formed. If it did not interest you
enough to ask, then there would be no
connection that you were
forming. You follow me? Yeah. Act upon
your intuition. Have you been there
intuition. Have you been there
physically? Yes, actually. Uh I went up
there on the weekend but never actually
got there.
and was quite happy to stay distant from
it. Um why?
Because there were other spots there
that were um beautiful and and quite
enjoyable to be at. Right. But I still
wanted to do you also understand at this
time that because this is the
transformational age, all of the chakra
points are beginning to blend. So the
idea of one or the other having a more
distinct energy is not so definitive
anymore. and that each and every one of
you are energy vortices as well and
contain the totality of all the chakra
points on your planet. Therefore,
Therefore,
you as you create the identification,
you are
shast or Tibet or Hawaii or wherever you
wish to be or whatever you wish to be.
Channel the energy through you. Use it
as you will.
Make your connections
accordingly. It is up to
you. All is becoming one.
Um can I just mention a dream I had last
night that was connected with Shast.
Um in that dream
uh I was dying nice and transformation.
Yeah. I I was sort of awake and asleep
having this dream blending of the dream
and the physical reality. So I was able
to talk about it as I was having it. And
what was happening is I was having cold
rushes coming right up my from the my
feet to the top of my head.
And um polarity connections south nor I
was very energized by the feeling though
and I I didn't worry about the fact that
it was death.
It was transformation.
Yeah. I didn't It didn't feel like death
at all. It felt transformation.
Transformation, which is what death is.
Transformation does not always have to
mean physiological
death. But once again, in a sense, since
you are recreating yourself every
moment, you do die and be born every
moment of time.
In fact, those were almost the same
words that were coming to me that death
was with me all the time. Yes. So is
life.
Yes. Thank you. What are our
responsibilities to others? To be
yourself completely
because you cannot be responsible for
someone. You can only be responsible to
them by being the most complete version
of the individual you created yourself
to be. So that then when they interact
with you, they are interacting with all
of you. So they get a complete
picture. That is what allows them to
also see in you the opportunity to be
complete within themselves. That is your
responsibility. told you. Yes. I want to ask a question
told you. Yes. I want to ask a question
about the speed of spiritual evolution
speed. Well, um does the striving to go
to other words? If you if you pursue
spirituality as we call it, like
channels and we read books, try and
realize things about things. Does that
speed up spiritual evolution or is it
taking place in a natural way? Anyway,
both in a sense.
It is your own
cognizance of your conscious awareness
of your connections that allows you to
create less time and make it seem as if
time is accelerating. Because your
conscious recognition of your connection
to everything allows you to exist in the
now which creates less
time. But there is no striving
necessary. It is not wrong. It is
indicative of the state of mind you are
in.
So just coming here in itself
just coming here in itself does not
necessarily give one
that speeded up. No, it is an indication
that you do desire to recognize those
connections not because it is us but
simply because you have cocreated this
type of interaction to represent those
connections. So it can make a difference
but it does not have to unless you
decide that it is making a difference.
Once you decide it is making a
difference the difference is made.
Period. just to not even going and
making that decision is just as yes
because that is the idea we have always
said you do not need us when you are
willing to simply live the lives you
desire to live you are in the moment
that is it
it is that simple
that me or someone else
yeah I also had a baby a few weeks ago
and um although I did practice many of
the of the tools that you mentioned and
they did help, my child at the last
moment decided to um to exit by
non-traditional means to be a ceerian.
Uh can you tell me why she decided to
enter that way? Surprise.
Yes, it was. perhaps to let you know
that there is still room for the
unexpected even when you know everything
is under control.
Is isn't it the least dramatic form of
birth? And wouldn't a being choose that
if they have a choice? Not necessarily.
Again, as you have understood, the
method you have created to be quote
unquote natural does not have to be
dramatic. But in this way it may simply
have been the root desired by the
consciousness for its own conditions and
the agreements it has made with you.
Simply on an emotional level it is as we
have suggested at least from our point
of view the idea that having everything
under perfect control does not mean that
you will have a boring predictable
existence.
There are many ways to enter different
realms of reality. Many ways. Learn that
from the
child. Many ways.
Are are the chirping sounds that she
makes that sound a whole lot like
dolphin sounds any connection to
dolphins? Yes.
Yes.
For there is much in the way of
assistance of birthings from the serious
dolphin consciousness and Arcturus at
this time. You will find that many of
the children now being born once again
will remember who they are, will
remember their connections and will
bring forth quote unquote abilities and
talents that have not been seen upon
your planet for quite some time. In a
sense, they will come through with those
conscious recognitions if you will
continue to provide for them an
atmosphere that will allow them to
continue to remember it.
Since we had an underwater birth plan
for her, wouldn't that have uh helped
her remember the dolphin
uh energy a little bit better than the
way she came in? in a sense, but perhaps
it was more for you
than her
so that you can remember your
connections. In other words, she didn't
even count to remember that. Correct.
Is there a connection between water and
transformation? Yes.
Yes.
For it is recognized by your
consciousness as being the life creator,
the life
sustainer and always constantly shifting
and malleable
and purifying.
Yes, it represents birth and
transformation to
you. It is in of
itself a form of crystalline
consciousness. that forms the
that forms the
matrix and sustains and supports the
matrix of your electromagnetic
consciousness upon your
planet. That which you call mind or
mentality is connected to water very
closely
through the idea of the exemplification
of electromagnetic wave structures. Thank you.
Thank you.
Yes. Yes. Bashar, a friend of mine uh
was in San Francisco this last weekend
going to the first world crystal
conference. And when he was there, he
saw the crystal skull that you mentioned
that I asked you about before that came
from Machu Picchu or that area and wound
up somewhere in the Aztec civilization.
Was that the same one?
May. Mayans. Okay.
Um, he also met the lady who's I think
in her 80s now who was along with her
father when he found the skull. Nice.
Um, and I was wondering if you could
tell us a little bit more about that.
Um, about what about the crystal skull?
How
uh I don't know there's something I want
to know that I don't know how to put in
words about it. And it's connected to
the whole idea of crystals and also the
the fact that the Cherokee Indians have
in their legend that they dreamed
themselves here to Earth from from the
uh planet that circles Sirius. Yes. With
the aid of crystal skulls. Yes. For as
we have said the idea of the crystal
skulls is a representation of
dimensional doorways.
those that can learn to read them can
cross through. That is what the Mayans also
through. That is what the Mayans also
did.
Okay. Well, that particular one that
um that was discovered
uh in South America among the Mayan
ruins was that that was one that
originally came from Peru.
It has been
around. Some of the technology is also
Adalandian. Was the skull itself not old? There were
Was the skull itself not old? There were
others. Oh, okay. Oh, also um
um
I there's something about a pair of
hands that held a crystal from Atlantis.
And I've I've heard two different things
I've I've heard two different things
about that. One about the the
crystal. All right. Um in a channeling
last Saturday night, a girl asked why
she didn't like crystals. And the
channel told her that she had been part
of a group of 31 people in Atlantis that
removed this crystal from a pair of
carved hands that hold it. Understand
that the idea of the carved hand will
have been the connector and supportive
base. There will have been the direction
of what you call solar energy onto the
crystal held in the hands in the
pyramidal temples.
There's a connection here with Egypt as
well. Mostly at this time at analis. All
right. And the idea of the destruction
of Analis through the crystal
technology. Yes. Um I heard the very next day
Yes. Um I heard the very next day
synchronistically from a friend of mine
that she had heard on um a a talk show
that some diver had discovered this pair
of hands when he was diving and he felt
they were a remnant of Atlantis. As in
the area you call Bahhat Moss.
Would that be Biminy? Yes. That was a
mountain top in Atlantis at one time. A
plateau. A plateau.
One of the
islands referred to as
Poseidia. The larger island is further
north, what you now refer to as the
sunken Bermuda rise area off of your
eastern seabboard.
Yes, it was mostly those two islands, though
it was mostly those two islands, though
there were smaller islands in the chain.
Atlantis is not the Atlantic Ocean
filling continent that you might think,
but it was large islands closer to your
Americas. Okay. Can
Okay. Can
you would you be willing to give me a
little of my personal connection with
Atlantis and also with Sirius? I feel a
tremendous connection and I whatever you
can tell me about it I would be willing
to hear. At this time all we can share
with you is the idea that your
imagination can delve into gold, white
linen and crystallin forms in circular
fashion. jade, blue
jade, blue
crystals, water, pyramidal
structures and what you call the art
form fresco
which originated in Atlantis
and then showed up in Greece. Yes.
Yes. Yes. Okay. and what you
call Portugal and
Spain and Morocco.
Ah, how about Mayorca in Spain?
[Music] Well, that's good because I'm going
Well, that's good because I'm going
there this summer. Follow your
instincts. Retrace your steps.
Thank you, Michelle. I love you. You may
find that it may feel
more natural to walk in sandals.
True.
There will be in your terms a few
moments remaining for this interaction
this evening of your time.
You find out something about it. Define
local. Uh Canadian Rockies.
one of the beginnings of what you would
call a geomagnetic
anomaly under the surface of
your crustal plates.
defining some of the electromagnetic
properties of one of the main energy
vortices that swing
from. what you would call northwest to
souththeast Canada more parallel across the land
Canada more parallel across the land
mass towards what you call the Hudson
the southern
portion it is highly electromagnetic
geomagnetic in nature a concentration
point there are other
connections that have to do with
interdimensionality alities and different
alities and different
phase shifts of your planet in other
times in other plains of
existence. We can delve into this at a
later date.
You sure?
I have a couple of questions. First one
deals with wavelengths. Little louder,
please. A couple questions. First one
deals with wavelengths.
How would
you invite others
to share certain wavelengths that again
all you need to do is be the idea you
wish to be and you can only experience
those on the same wavelength
you will attract them
automatically by your simple actions by
the simple acting out of the wavelength
you are. You will then radiate a beacon
at that wavelength that will attract all
others so inclined to interact with you.
Okay. Thank you. The second question
deals with this level of density. Yes.
The I believe it's this planet is the
third and if you could give some
indication of the transformation to the
fourth. Again, the idea as we have
discussed is simply that you will
recognize that third density offered you
an opportunity to consider the idea of
the universe existing outside yourself
remote from yourself so that you could
create what appears to be an objective
point of view. Fourth density will be
the blending of all the polarities in
that way so that you will recognize that
this objective point of view has been an
illusion. You will see through the
facade you have created for the purpose
of experiencing limitation and you will
now begin to experience integration in
many ways. You will accelerate in many
different ways that will allow you to
know you can partake of the substance of
energy itself that creates the dimension
in which you are transforming. And in
this way, let yourself know that you can
become more accelerated. The effects
that you may perceive will be the idea
of the blending of the lack of memory.
The idea of the creation of knowledge in
the moment, the idea of living in the
now, the idea that your physical form
may become a little bit more brilliant,
may reflect more light, be more of a
light body in this way. You may require
less physiological sustenance that you
call food, less sleep. In this way, as
you are blending the different realities
into one reality, you will find that you
are always living a waking dream. These
ideas will also allow you to radiate at
the harmonic vibratory level that will
invoke a harmonic resonance of love,
unconditional love and peace upon your
planet and create a scenario in which
you can allow once again for the
creation of unity by the granting of
validity to the infinite diversity
within your civilization. And these are
all as you say hallmarks or earmarks of
fourth density reality plus many other
exploratory ideas and blendings. At the
so-called end of fourth density reality
in approximately what you call 2,000 of
your years, you will find that you will
no longer need to be at all within the
earth plain physiological
reincarnational cycle and you will no
longer manifest as physical beings.
Perhaps someone else will utilize the
idea after you.
That's what I was wondering. 2000 year
2000 other words for this particular
planet this these societies you see the
transition to the fourth the idea of the
overall beginnings of the transformation
are occurring have been occurring and
will continue to occur for approximately
the next 30 of your years of counting.
In this way you will understand 2,00 as
you count it the year to represent
simply the transformation point in a
linear time frame referential state.
There will be a high point of activity
also within the idea of what you call
2011 to 2013. In this way therefore you
will create the beginnings of awareness
that will allow you to build a society
that functions within peace and harmony
for approximately 2,000 years more. then
you will no longer need to remain as a
physiological society. Thank you so
much. In this way, once again, we will extend
In this way, once again, we will extend
our unconditional love to each and every
one of you and thank you for allowing us
to experience the gift of your
consciousness to allow us to experience
that much more of all that is and expand
our awareness of creation. We send you
our energy, our unconditional love and
bid you an exciting dream life and a fun
and loving good evening.
Thank you. Thank you for being here
tonight. [Music]