I want
all we will begin this interaction this
evening of time with the notation night
of Dreams this is also your title thank
you in this way the idea as you turn
make dreaming is now something that is
Bec more and more common place in the
dream reality's ability to begin to
blend into the physiological reality
recognizing that what you usually
experience as a physiological reality is
but a dream anyway an extension of the
dream reality given a certain degree of
solidity the illusion of solidity
because it is the particular aspect of
the dream world the dream self the dream
reality that you wish to experience
yourself to be this is for the purposes
as you have created them of growth of
experience of a particular facet a
particular Avenue a particular angle if
you will of yourself a particular IDE a
particular notion point of view an
aspect of the overall multi-dimensional
being that you are so you create the
solidity the limitation the isolation of
a particular portion of the overall
dream that you are so you can focus upon
that one particular aspect and so see
yourself through that particular
reflection to learn about yourself as an
aspect of creation through that
particular Avenue so that you may expand
the understanding from many different
points of you about the being that you
are this is what is part of the ongoing
creation the idea that as creation
continues to unfold the way it unfolds
generally speaking to use your
colloquial terminology is that different
aspect of creation create different
points of view about that aspect of
creation so that it is not so much the
idea truly let us say of addition to
Creation in an actual mass energy sense
but addition to Creation in an expansion
sense an awareness sense an experiential
sense a sense of creating a new a
completely different and new unique
point of view through which creation can
thus experience that much more of itself
and expand into that much more of itself
it is all the idea of of view
experience and in this way therefore
recognize that dream reality now that
you are recognizing the third density
physiological reality you have existed
within for hundreds of thousands of
years to be an extension of your belief
system to
be the result of what you believe your
reality should be to recognize that you
are in fact creating your reality to
recognize that it is only a point of
view of yourself that creates what you
interact with as this supposedly
exteriorized reality this exteriorized
reality only being a reflection of the
idea you are being in the moment and
exploring within yourself you can now
recognize that these physiological
realities these illusionary
physiological realities are extensions
of the dimension of imagination in which
you exist are extensions of what you
normally refer to as the dream reality
that you have for so long considered to
be something quite have apart from the
physiological reality and now are
beginning to understand that they are
one and the same as you allow yourself
more and more
cognition that the dream reality
imagination reality and physiological
reality are different aspects of the
same overall reality then you will begin
to recognize your physical lives more in
a dreamlike way there will be more
things seemingly possible in your
physiological reality and they will be
more effortlessly created with the same
degree of effortlessness in which you
change your realities in the dream state
in this way you can begin to recognize
that as you begin to blend the dream
reality and the physiological reality
you will be surrounded in your life with
more and more of what we have spoken of
that you call synchronicity more and
more coincidents not accidents
coincidents there are no accidents but
co-incidence will allow you to know that
you are now consciously becoming aware
as you say of the warwar and the Woof
and the fabric The Weave of the web of
all the interconnectedness of all that
is you are beginning to recognize that
everything is linked to everything else
and thus when you allow yourself to
exist in a
synr harmony with the idea that the
reality you experience is an extension
of you then you can begin to experience
how it is an extension of you you can
begin to see the ideas you are exploring
very clearly very transparently very
clairvoyantly which is clear sightly you
can begin to see all of the different
paths and avenues you have created
projected out there for yourself you can
begin to see how they all feed back to
you how everything in that way feeds
back to you and through you and it is an
extension from you in that way you can
see how all the paths you have created
in your life extend and interact and
intersect with all the other individuals
in your life you can see where the
overlaps occur and why you can
understand the entire idea of what has
for so very long seemed like a very
random series of events to be one very
intimately tied together intimately
interactive with everyone else orated to
a very fine specific degree and in this
you can begin to recognize the idea that
in there being no accidents then you can
begin to allow all that you experience
in your life to be there for a reason to
be there for a purpose to be there to
allow you to explore more and more of
what what it is you are discovering
yourself to be and in this expansion and
in this ringness to know that as you
interact with all other individuals you
are being given an opportunity to view
and explore that much more of yourself
by seeing in them a reflection of you
and allowing them to perform that
service for you as you perform the same
service for them then more and more
ecstasy will also filter into your lives
floods reality in which you exist and
your physiological reality will become
very much like the idea you call your
dream you will begin to live your dreams
very literally and you will find that
what has for so long been relegated to
the non-physical realm the blueprint
realm the templet realm upon which
physical reality is formed will begin to
filter down leak in and imbue and Infuse
with physiological reality and your
ability to cause much more
instantaneous physiological changes will
then occur in your reality because the
mechanism that causes that change the
non-physical template will be that much
closer to you will be that much more
immediate within you will not carry with
it the degree of separation you have
placed upon it will be well within your
hands and in causing any change within
that normal physical dream template the
physical reality must follow suit it has
no choice physical reality is the shadow
of the soul the shadow of the dream
reality the shadow of the non-physical
total Consciousness that you are that
you are creating physical reality with
are you all following
along therefore in this way this night
of your time the night of
Dreams there will be in the interactions
we will be having with you this evening
of your time and the interactions that
others will be having with you this
evening of your time
these interactions according to only your
interactions according to only your
degree pace and level of willingness
nothing will be forced upon you ever but
in your own degree of comfort your own
pace whatever rate you are already
doorways and gateways will be opening
within your levels of consciousness this
night of your
time many of the so-called barriers
between the different levels will now
begin to dissolve
and allow your Consciousness to
homogenize into more of one
Consciousness that allows you to act and
function as a conscious conduit between
the non-physical and the physical
reality an open and clear tunnel Channel
conduit for that which you relegate as
your higher self to allow it to come
through and flow into physiological
reality so that the physical you can
also act as a synchronistically
harmonious component of the total
Consciousness that to are for many of
the ideas of the energies we are
exchanging this day of your time this
night of your time will have to do with
the opening of those vibratory doorways
within you and you may begin to find
this night of your time and from this
point forward many many many changes
within your dream realities and
therefore many changes and much degree
of more momentum acceleration within
your physiological realities again
according to the level of willingness
you are creating in terms of allowing
those gates to be open allowing those
barriers to be
removed but you will feel a
difference there is
now in a perception of your overall
energy the overall energy of your entire
civilization that is our perception of
yet another energy gate approaching this
gate is an opport Unity like all energy
gates for the total civilization wherein
aspects of the non-physical total
civilization will be harmoniously
aligned and much of that will then begin
to filter into your physical reality and
you will see more and more examples of
the gate you have passed through after
you have passed through it you will in a
sense therefore accelerate through this
gate onto another
level another level that will allow you
to know you have control over the
realities you experience over the
reality you desire to experience this
gate exists approximately in your terms
of tting between the dates you call the
27th day of the presence of your month
to the fifth day of the next month
following within this time frame is a
very very strong energy date that has to
do with allowing many things from your
past to come bubble into the present and
allowing many ideas for the so-called
future to become far more
clarified than they have seem to be many
of you as we have discussed before are
now having been existed in what you call
a limbo state where you feel everything
to be unplugging in your lives and
spinning around you and do not see them
plugging back in they are starting to
plug in now this represents a thickening
of the atmosphere a thickening of the
energy around you the energy atmosphere
and this represents this thickening
represents that you are pulling more and
more of your energy into the present you
will acclimate to this thickening and
then it will not seem so thick and you
will move through it with ease it will
not impede you though for now it may to
make you a little bit
sluggish recognize that one of the
primary focal points within this span of
time the 27th to the 5th will be what
you call the three days as we have
spoken to you before your 31st your
first and your second
for in this way these three dates are
your ritualistic symbolic ritualistic symbolic
representation
of your
remembrance the night
before all Hollows Eve the submergence
of
Atlantis November 1st the day
of and November 2nd the day
after these are your three his IAL IDE
is represented in this ritualistic form
you call all Hollow Halloween All Souls
and All Saints
St you all follow
along therefore since many of you
therefore since many of you
now have had many incarnations there and
since many of you now are replaying many
of the ideas that were played out there
yet choosing a different
outcome you will now find the
opportunity that as you pass through
this gate many of these ideas will be
brought to the forbear of your presence
and allow you now to reclaim all that
you have ever
been and express conviction towards all
you will ever be for now in your terms
is the night of dreams and therefore the
eve of the beginning of the
solidification of the force bity reality
which will gain much impetus in what you
call the springtime of your New Year
coming
I would like to ask you about a reur
dream that I have been having which is
one of getting up in the middle of the
night and feeling like something is
missing and that I am trying to find
something desperately all right and I I
can't get a handle on a
handle well what does it feel like when
you are looking for this thing you think
is missing um it feels like I'm missing
it by a fraction fraction of an inch and
um may I ask you question yes in your
imagination right now will you relax for
me for a
moment do not be so desperate all
right now will you exercise your
imagination just a bit play along with
me for a
moment allow yourself now to relax and
go in worded in a meditated state and
simply without
judgment
imagine how will you be when you find
this thing you are missing by fractions
of an what differences will occur how
will you be
different I don't know what my purpose
is in why you
don't that's very
simple it can come in two forms first of
all recognize
there never has
been and never will be another
individual like you you
follow you are
unique and even though you experience as
an overall Soul the idea you call
reincarnation you the you you are now
truly only does have one life to
live therefore recognize that you are a
manifestation a unique aspect in like in
this form as this idea of the infinite
of creation itself are
unique therefore recognize the basic
fundamental purpose of your life this
goes for every single one of you is to
fully be who you happen to be at this
point to fully be the idea you chose to
be to express and expand yourself
along the lines that represent what is
true for the being you are you have
created yourself
today now the second part of this idea
is also very simple did you understand
the first
part how does it allow you to
feel how how does understanding this
idea that the fundamental purpose in
your life life is to simply be who you
are how does that allow you to
feel it allows me to
feel amount of myself that I can all
right good then recognize the idea the second
good then recognize the idea the second
step is nothing more drastic and nothing
more complex than to express that idea
and express it not only for all to whom
you are are interacting with in service
but also for yourself the same
unconditional love for yourselves that
you express to all other individuals and
what this let us say pragmatically means
is well let me ask you another question
may are you doing in your life what
excites you the most no I'm not why
not I'm blocking what excites
nonsense what excites you right now
right now this very moment what is the
most exciting thing aside from doing
what you are doing this moment in this
interaction what is the most exciting
thing that you can imagine doing I like
all right
right
recognize therefore that if that truly
in your car is the most exciting thing
you can imagine
doing then all you need to do is begin to act
then all you need to do is begin to act
like one act like an individual would
act if that individual were ATT and in
this way recognize that if you know you
are doing the most exciting thing in
your life you can recognize that the
universe will completely and totally
support you and in this way that means you will
you and in this way that means you will
attract to yourself synchronistically
automatically all the events all the
situations all the people necessary to
allow you to function as the idea you
find most
ex without having to struggle without
having to strive
without having to sweat for it as you
say you follow me yes the idea is to
allow life to work which it does rather
than feel you have to make it work which
you cannot you cannot you
told
now in your
terminology what does it mean to be a
childel or recognize that in a very real
way you are always traveling always
always always always the very idea of
what you are as a physiological being by
definition makes you a conduit into
physical reality of the higher self that
you are so you are a channel for the
higher you so that it can express itself
in the realm you call physiological
reality you are already a channel being
a channel is not learning how to do
something you do not already
do you may redefine the idea of the way
you are doing it you may add specifics
but you are not learning anything new
does that make it easier to begin
with I understand all of that oh
but that person and I'm not sure how
that all right here we are thank you
very much the idea once again of going
and trusting and relying upon the tool
that is always in your life s if you
fall to your imagination
what does your imagination say what is
the picture let's play this game a
little bit further what is the picture
you have in your imagination of how you
would be if you were a channel can you
imagine yourself being a channel you
must be able don't tell me that you can
because if you knew you want to be a
channel that means you have to be able
to imagine that you can be I believe
that I would be a very relaxed and not
struggling for these things that I would
be able to simp sit to and do them
and and all right may I let you in on a
little secet you can do that right now do you
secet you can do that right now do you
believe that I do believe that oh really
all right you go
[Music] ahead I am quite
serious do you still believe
it I was all
right that is all right now first of all
once again allow me to remind you you
are channeling right now
remember all right your ability to say
yeah means you are
Ching because that yes comes from the
IDE of your higher
Consciousness it also comes from your
physiological Consciousness but the
overall idea originates from the
non-physical you the over that you
are oh there it is
again all right
now rely upon your imagination to
provide you with whatever technique if
you think you need one that you think
you need in order to get into the
relaxed State you think you need to be
in or will be in as a channel go into
this meditative relaxed state and
explore stretch your imagination out
open it out and allow what comes in to
come in do you
in do you
trust
that the idea of your channeling will
always allow you to perform service in
positive ways yes well then if you are
willing to allow yourself to simply be
open to the whole idea then you know
that whatever comes to you will be what
you need to allow you to serve in
positive ways you follow me therefore
there is no need to worry about oh well
do I need
protection you follow me all right now
when you are in that relaxed State you
are immediately always availably in
touch with what you call your guides and
your own higher state of
consciousness no matter whether you
interpreted at first as quote unquote
gibberish or not allow whatever to come
through come through
all right and in this way begin to explore
right and in this way begin to explore
you will sense it out you will feel it
out you will understand the difference
is you will begin to sense the
ideas you will begin to sense the
notations the connections to everything
the inter relationships of
all all you need to do is be in that
relaxed State and express your
willingness to commence with this idea
and ask for assistance you will get
it Beyond The Shadow without you will
get it but they will not do everything for
it but they will not do everything for
you you follow me all right now also
trust again with your synchronicity that
if this is truly something that excites
you the most you will always attract
yourself into the appropriate situations
always attract yourself to the
appropriate literature if necessary you
will always have somebody recommend
something to you that will be exactly
what you need to allow you to progress
in your growth as a
family B and do not forget that the ey
idea of your dream Consciousness in your
dream Consciousness you are always in
communication with all those you have
ever made all the agreements with
everything is proceeding at the proper
Pace always at the perfect Pace always
it is the pace that you are most
comfortable with so it is completely up
to you to determine that pace by
allowing yourself to be more relaxed
then you increase the pace because
you're saying you are more willing to
accept more and thus things will become more
more and thus things will become more
obvious
you is any of this assisting here yes
and and
all right you been you okay well it's
always exciting talking you but tonight
is astounding because what you say what
you said about Atlantis uh I just want
to share something first then I have
something to ask you uh last week I went
to a channeling with jubil you know you
know him Spirit juil we have what you would
him Spirit juil we have what you would
call a brief cognition but not what you
would call complete
definition well it where it was there
was um there was a picture called
Resurrection and uh uhhuh and I I've
loved the movie every time I watch it I
cry it in I just love it and it's
Loosely based on the Lea Morgan I story
and I've always felt the vicinity to
this film and I found out I was going to
meet her there and um I have past life
in Atlantis as many many many many many
yes yes I have to ask you about the
other ones I um of you think oh well
have I had a past life and at recognize
that ATL has existed for many thousands
of
years had many past lives in one of
those I taught children uh to learn with
Crystal he and as I found out uh the
other night before I met Alicia that she
also worked in Atlantis for children
with water with colored water right and
I thought that was very exciting that we
were both there and also I felt I had
this relationship with
her I wanted to ask you to when the 31st
the first and the second aside from
increasing my meditations during it is
there something else that I could do or
uh as through some incisive uh you can
beat a
drum okay the idea of the creation of
that vibration
alone like that in the pace that feels
appropriate to you will be reminiscent
of another idea another way of teaching
an Atlantis by aligning an individual
with the beat of a drum synchronizing
all the autonomic systems with that beat
of a drum and allowing the person to
absorb the information directly
intuitively with the beat of that drum
you will then by invoking the beat of
that drum once again recall many ideas
and see many flashes within your
imagination of those
parts just a low Dr okay something like
what you call your heart
beat okay thank you oh better
um I raed for a couple weeks really on
another planet please speak
planet please speak
up
oh what I what I was dealing with
um just this week was the week of the
Jewish New Year and I heard once again
um a story that is always troubled B
trouble yeah it was the story of The
Binding of Isaac and um how Abraham had
almost killed him he I want to have some
clarity with that story because I all
right go
right I get real Angry every time I hear
it I don't know why but I oh I feel like
it's never brought up the feelings of
what Isaac must have been going through
thinking his father was going to kill
him I see and even though nothing happen
you know he didn't get killed and he got
down that always bothered me and I don't
you know of all the stories I don't know
why that one strikes me all right now
recognize first of all the idea once
again that you call anger is your
opportunity to align with what you know
to be true for you and to express the
idea of your integrity it does not have
to be expressed in negative way anger is
for the purpose of aligning you with
what you know to be true for you when
you see something going on around you
that you know is not true for you but
this does not mean you have to judge the
thing you are seeing it simply allows
you the opportunity to know by seeing
the comparison of what you know not to
be true for you of what is true for you
so it has performed a service for you it
has gotten you in touch with the ideas
of Integrity of the polarity of the
positive and negative Expressions within
yourself and put you squarely in the
center of the recognition of those ideas
you following along to
thought not really I don't know the what
my
inte thank you we are getting you that I
said are you following along so far okay
yeah thank you in this way you have very
strong connections to those times in
your past and the idea specifically is
that you now know because you were there
and very conscious of the idea that you
were there in those times you are seeing
a representation in what you call your
biblical literature that in your terms
does not ring trueu the idea is being
expressed in an expression of
negativity and what you are recognizing
is that as it has been expressed many
many things many many things have been
quote unquote left out of the picture
those things that have been left out of
the picture are indicative of the way
your Society has structured itself to be
and placed upon mus literature you are
referring to a negative connotation
overall the
idea of the quote unquote Wrath of a
jealous God in this way the
idea of the
demand seemingly placed upon your
population by this God of the speak all
of these ideas of the scriptures the
rules and the
regulation rub you sorely for you
recognize that in those thought
you were very aware of what was going on
on many different levels and you
recognize that the idea of the
imposition of
limitation the incurment of Wrath and
displeasure of the infinite have nothing
to do with what much of your literature
now interprets as the going on of those
times are you following this more
closely yes in this way therefore for
this is your opportunity to clarify
within yourself the understanding that
you inqu have
that the idea of an infinite and
unconditionally loving Creator does not
be speak the ideas of the transgressions
in the terms you call Thou shalt
not these are
interpretations of your civilization
through the negative eye the negative
ego in this way as many of them feel it
serves in this way for the control of
the society the expression of what you
originally call the command ments are
not Commandments as such they are
recognitions of what you might call the
action reaction principles within the
universe they are indications of the
ideas of the self nurturing the
expansion of love and the recognition
that as you do so create in your reality
as an outward expression so do you
compound upon yourself that same
reality this is all was ever intended by
the expression of those ideas and they
have been transformed in very negative
ways in your society and this is simply
what you are getting angry about the
idea of what seems to be the Injustice
of an iron hand ring all without
consideration of the feelings of those
they are quote unquote ruling but the
infinite does not rule by
control the infinite quote unquote is in
commandment of the universe because the
infinite is the universe
and as the infinite expresses itself and
as that expression is recognized by
those who wish to be in synchronous
harmony with the infinite then they
recognize that is not so much the idea
of Commandments that are laid down but
let us say blueprints for how to be
synchronistically harmonious with the
idea of how the universe
works you
follow is this clearing up some of these
ideas it's clearing up some of the ideas
I'm am I am I understanding that what you're
am I am I understanding that what you're
saying is that uh this story didn't
happen um and it was interpreted by the
the society for its own purposes and it
is not so much that the idea of the
story did not happen but that was an
expression that leaves much out of all
the different interactions that took
place and therefore is only left as a
Remnant seemingly representative
seemingly representative of the life in
those times and in general it is not
representative of the understanding you
had in those times nor that a very vast
portion of your world even had in those
times but as a very as you would say
tunnel vision view of a particular
aspect that was being discorded by a
particular faction of your Society at
that time which was that um that of of
time which was that um that of of
negativity and
limitation um of controlling by by
um okay okay so you say that um that I
know from having been in that that
time um do you know what what what I don't
um do you know what what what I don't
have any sense of that um you were in a
sense let it say for now a
chronicler of prbe you saw much
you shared much you told of much and now
that you are seeing some of your
Works malign and made
malign and made
incomplete you are in your own eyes
justifiably
of this is not the way I wrote
it this is not the way it was this tells
nothing of the
interactions they have left much out you
are rebelling at the censorship that has
occurred over the several hundreds of
years that have passed since much of the
writings follow yeah fascinating
go i' love to
um how can I get into um a memory of
that of that whole experience of what
really happened there so that I that I
know what what it was that they're
leaving out
imagination is not a commodity in short
[Music]
supply you then will also attract
yourselves to the appropriate forms of
literature that will allow you to
reclaim some of that recognize there are
some forms of literature in your
society that do recall some ideas that
have for a very long period of time been
left out of what you call the more
official versions gopel yes
versions gopel yes
for in many ways you were a
MOS explore those and see what you come
up with all right all right thank you
very much much
last inner
earth instead of traveling lar across
the surface it seems like you just went
some and I did anyone else think
anything today
what time uh this morning
morning
okay go bump in the Night That Go Bump
within you what went bump within you it seemed
you what went bump within you it seemed
like somebody was under the bed and went
boom one went bump with you oh um
the first thing that comes out I heard
this saying a limitation of wall of
partition oh you supp it
dropped yeah it woke me
[Music] up you do not do things in a half hour
up you do not do things in a half hour
way
no how do you feel you well um
I haven't had anything this last time
that we compared to it it's um I'm at my
Peak you are at your Peak yeah well how
the
you clear H and clear all right allow
more and more and more of those
limitations to drop away you are making
connections and you are simply sensitive
to them to the energy you are
translating those energy Connections in
a physiological way which appear to be
the ideas of the bump but also
understand that many times some of those
bumps are also when you are just about
to leave your body and then make an
instantaneous
reconnection when you say leave the body
in what terms you mean what you call a
protection oh I
see very good thank
you I have had dream all my life that
have come through and it it bothers me
why because I don't know where I am in
reality I don't know you know you don't
know where you are in reality yeah I see
these things happen to me and today I
was in my office and I set my glasses
down and I looked and I saw and I went
oh great I've been here before and I've
seen you and down the hall he's going to
do that and that's all been there and I
know that I am a Healer I know that has
been my destiny and is what I'm doing
now but I want desperately to get in
touch with real healing because I don't
believe what I am doing is healing why
not CU inside it doesn't feel like it
feeling but it's is what I do what do
you do
do
mostly I mostly use the practices that I
learned in medical school
so prescribing medications all right
using things in what way do you now wish
to be a Healer I know just want to put
my hand on their hand and go you are
heal go for [Music] [Music]
it
now allow us to examine some definitions
may may we yes no maybe maybe examine
some definitions yes no maybe yes find
thank you do you recognize as a
you do you recognize as a
Healer that all individuals that you
heal actually heal themselves yes all
right so you are still functioning as a
symbol for them through which they can
exercise the belief system within
themselves that will allow them to
affect the healing that's what I tell
them all right you are then changing
into the type of being you wish to be
now if you feel frustrated with yourself
then perhaps it is simply that you do
not have the
trust and the faith necessary to believe
that you can be just as effective or in
your terms maybe more so in the way you
wish to express yourself as he as
opposed to the way you have expressed
yourself as a Healer do not discount the
way you have expressed yourself for it
has gotten you to where you are now and
it has performed the service and has
allowed many individuals to create a
healing aspect for themselves you follow
me yeah so first and foremost the first
step in being anything you choose to be
is to not invalidate anything you have
ever been all
right I believe I've been a Healer all
along of course you have of course you
have and I'm going to be a better one
you are going to be a different
one you will never be better for each
and every thing that you do has its own
reasons for existing and has no business
being compared to anything else
you follow me you are going to be a
different healer you may be more
expanded you may function on a more
synchronistic and let us say grander
broader level but that is not better we
understand what you mean colloquially
but recognize we are again examining and
exploring definitions because many of
these definitions in and of themselves
may be all that is preventing you from
actually acting as the being you choose
to be because you think you have to
become something better than you was
many times that is a task that many of
you feel unequal to because you are
creating it to be something une
equalizing to become better well let's
see becoming better oh my oh my there
must be a lot of work in becoming better
well there there is a lot of work in becoming
there there is a lot of work in becoming
better because you can't ever become
better so you will struggle with that
for quite some time I already
am I wouldn't have these dreams I
wouldn't I wouldn't know what I know
it's it it really spins my head around
all right all right all right
recognize that much of what you are
experiencing can not so much that it
will quote unquote go away but will feel
more harmonious to you as soon as you
catch up to it by doing what it is you
want to do you see many of the ideas you
are experiencing in appearing to be
quote unquote one step ahead of yourself
all the time knowing the future this way
is simply an example that you are just
slightly out of phase with yourself and
not allowing yourself to live in that
present moment spontaneously because you
are not yet willing to exercise the
faith to do what it is that truly moves
you as soon as you do that you will
catch up to this wave front you have
created in time for yourself and you
will spontaneously interact in the
moment and in this way not feel always
to be in a sense two steps behind what
has already happened but I'm you chose
to be here do not play victim with me I
will not let you get away with
it now first and foremost once again to
allow yourself the
cognition to allow yourself to not feel
trapped you must first take
responsibility for having chosen to
create the reality you are in I did yes
you did and you still do
now but the idea the idea you are now
living the idea you are now
being you are choosing them fully fully
full responsibility
fully Z
Z
instead of taking the
approach I am doing what I do because I
have no
choice Begin by choosing to recognize
that you do what you do because you
chose to whether it is negative or
positive the first step in giving you
the ability to choose more of the
lifestyle you actually desire is in
acknowledging that the lifestyle you now
have that you don't desire was also your
choice then making that connection puts
you squarely in the driver's seat
because if now you know you were fully
in control of choosing something that
you no longer prefer it means you have
the same degree of control in choosing
something you do prefer and physical
reality never has been is not now and
never will be an
excuse for not doing what you desire to
do it is not something that prevents you
from doing anything only the definitions
you give to it prevent you from doing
something physical reality is not a trap
it is not a jail if it is a jail you
hold the key so let yourself out let
yourself in let yourself enjoy the
choices that you made you chose to be
physical for a
reason remember that and remember that
you would not have have chosen physical
reality just to torture
yourself no I'm here to do something you
are here to enjoy you are here to share
you are here to be of service and being
of service is never a drudgery
medicine and being doctor andery me
garbage once again do not invalidated
otherwise you place yourself squarely
back in that world right when you hear
the phrase in your Bible judge not lest
ye be judged it does not mean you are
being judged from outside there is no
outside it does not mean that God is
judging you means that as you judge you
are placing judgment upon
yourself whatever you hate you
become therefore recognize that the way
you were and the things you did you did
for the reason of getting you to where
you are now so love what you did it was
not garbage when you did it it isn't
garbage now it's exactly the path you
needed to take to understand and the
difference you are
becoming otherwise you would not have
the same appreciation of what it is you
want to do if you did not do the thing
before that you had
done there would be no sense of growth
no sense of
change no sense of
expansion if you had not done before
what you had done and now allow yourself
to change into what you know you prefer
to do recognize there are many reasons
for the way you chose to do what you did
one strong one among them is the
recognition that as you have now
Associated yourself with what you call
the Orthodox medical world then the
changes that now occur within you may
rub off on some of the others and allow
them to also choose to change without
fear that will be of service will it not
yes I know it already have all right and
relax will not be so hard with your T
you are not trapped you never have
been you are doing exactly what you need
to be doing and the only little thing
you are missing so to speak although you
are not really missing
anything is that degree of willingness
to trust and believe that what you now
feel to be true for you is true for you
and if you are willing to exercise your
abilities along those lines you will be
supported by the universe because you
are being true to yourself as an aspect
of the universe mhm I already do yes I
don't care oh you do care I don't care I
put my hands on their head and I said
you are healed you have the power within
you I don't care if anyone judges me all
right I'm trying I'm you are not trying
you are doing okay I'm
breaking thank you for your willingness
may I remind you every individual makes
a
different and the more willing you are
to be a true reflection of the you you
know yourself to be the easier it is for
other individuals to do the same for
themselves because they see within you
an example of your trust and your
faith and to see it within you to see it
within any being means that they also
have to contain that ability otherwise
they couldn't see
thank you for your
love thanks I love you pleasant dreams to you
thanks I love you pleasant dreams to you
as well yes my
friend I have had a lower back pain for
the last four months and I know it has
some connection to do with I have been
blocked in any creative visualization
because of a fear a fear of
block a fear of that of creating that
which I do or would decide to desire
desire why would you fear to create what
you desire because everything I have
wanted I have created and I and
sometimes it's backfired on you so I no
no no no no
never never backf how can it backfire by
definition when you create everything
you want if you create everything you
want then how can what you get be
something that
backfires it didn't turn out the way I
thought it was going to so
what what does that got to do with
anything recognize that in our world a
long time ago when we began to go
through these changes ourselves to say
to someone well it didn't pronounce the
way I thought was reason for
congratulations because then it meant
you were trusting your intuition and
acting spontaneously and creating the
unexpected so that your life would
become ecstatic rather than creating a
boring predictable life through the idea
of analytical consequence
it's yes now as you have said you have
always created everything you have
wanted recognize that those situations
that you are referring to as the
backfire situations was exactly at that
time what you wanted based on what you
believed you could create and thus it
was a sparkling opportunity to recognize
what you believed in by seeing it in
full force in your reality thus giving
you the opportunity to recognize that
you do not prefer that manifestation you
do not prefer that belief that the
manifestation in your life shows you
have the belief and now that means now
that you can see it you can change it
into what you do prefer the idea of
seeing something like that in your life
is not a sentence pronounced upon you it
is an opportunity to recognize that you
have had that Bel within you and now it
shows you what you have had and now you
can change it if you don't prefer
it how do I get rid of the fear you not
get rid of anything there is nowhere to
get rid of anything
too what you do is make make friends
with it let it in you see the only
reason you have fear basically
fundamentally fear is a messenger it is
bringing you a message it is bringing
you another portion of your identity
another portion of you to examine and
integrate within you so that you can
expand as a being the only reason it
comes in a fearful way is because you
don't pay attention to the way it comes
when it comes subtly so when you ignore
that idea because you have been taught
to ignore the subtle ideas it gets
noisier and noisier and noisier and
noisier until you begin to pay attention
by the time you begin to pay attention
it is so noisy you want to run away from
it that is your Fe it simply knocks as
loudly as it needs to to get you to pay
attention to the portion of yourself
that you have ordered it to bring to
you it does not have to come fearfully
and as soon as you say all right all
right all right all right I know you
there I hear I hear I'm coming I'm
com as soon as you say all right I
recognize you have been very noisy
simply because I have not been paying
attention now I'm letting you
know that I am paying attention and I am
willing to pay attention to whatever it
is you have to bring me because I know
that whatever it is you bring to me is
something I do want to
see oh says the fear well then the next
time I won't have to be so scary to get
you to pay
attention I'll come a little more
quietly and if you are willing to pay
attention to that I'll come quieter
still and again and again and again
until you are
Overjoyed when I knock upon your
door you cannot wait for me to show up
your so ecstatic
because you know that the only things I
can possibly bring to you is more of
yourself and that Those portions of
yourself are the things that will allow
you to
integrate as a being they will allow you
in that way to know what it is you chose
to be in this physiological life you
follow along totally does this assist
you yes uh what do I do about my back
pain this is all connected I don't have it
this is all connected I don't have it
anymore the idea is that when you are
willing to relax a little bit about the
things you are discovering about
yourself then you will not hold yourself
so rigidly you will not be so
tense in that area it is primarily in
that area because it represents the fact
that you are now making let us say in
this particular go around in this
particular stage of your development you
are making final connections connections
begin at the base of the brain and work
their way
downward when you are about to make some
final connections then many times if you
are allowing yourself to judge and
invalidate the connections you are
making then any tension and pain that
you create will generally spring up
somewhere in the lower back in this way
once you relax this idea you will begin
to recognize that the final connection
will be made from one the positive Pole
to the negative pole and th a flly of
revelation will shoot up your spine you
refer to this in your society as the
calini energy once it hits the base of
your brain it will filter into your
brain altering the neuronic pathways of
your brain cranial structure and this
sense of the cellular structure in ways
at a rate that is comfortable for you to
realign the idea that you are and create
a completely new perspective and a new
reality you follow me yes I'm the pain
and the tension is only from the remnant
of Habitual ritual that you have bought
into in your life relax
and you will allow the energy to pass
through painlessly effortlessly there is
nothing you will ever discover about
yourself that cannot be used in a
positive way and integrated within the
total being that you are do not
fear you will always be able to handle
it always there would be no purpose in
you creating something you could not
handle there would be no purpose in the
universe giving you something you could
not handle the universe does not do
pointless and extraneous
things you follow me yes does this
assist you yes very much thank you thank
you my
friend you you
you you
m do all life for possess higher
self and some life forms are higher
and some life forms are higher
selves and some of them possessive some
of them create the scenario that they
are separated from
but of course that means that they were
created from the higher self and
therefore always have a connection back
to the higher self
yes uh I'd like to know some information
about the physical universe and the
Earth all
right was Earth
created uh was Earth created to support
the life system or did it come from
Earth both this is a simultaneous idea any
both this is a simultaneous idea any
idea that acts as a support system for
any level of Consciousness is both
created by the Consciousness and comes
from the Consciousness and is created
for that Consciousness everything
attracts itself to the vibratory level
in which it can exist by definition
these events occur in a sense
simultaneously the creation for and the
creation from occur simultaneously thank
simultaneously thank
you are
you uh first of all what life form are
higher self thank
you simply the idea that when you are
non-physical and existing as your over
soul and you are your higher self oh I
saw physical life that are higher sell I
thought that's what be said not exactly
no the idea of the non-physical you it
is still a life form that's true okay
the other thing that uh it just occurred
to me a while ago when you were talking
about pain and so on um yes pain and so
on yeah well I was a workshop this
weekend withar hey and he mentioned
something which I thought was very
important for all well maybe some people
are aware of it but I I wasn't not
totally and that has to do that
something he detected what you call it
metaphysical blackmail in that now most
of us are recognizing that we're
creating our own reality and when we
become sick we start feeling guilty
about it and all also not only that but
that when our friends become sick we say
oh you created your own reality get over
it and we lack compassion compassion and
so I just wanted to point out that you
know to become aware of that we should
not feel guilty about it and a lot of
times pain and failure is also just like
fear of a messenger
yay that's all thank you very much thank
you you um I was going down BR uh yeah
BR Street the other night last week I
forget what night
anyway I think I saw a uh a face craft
okay with me if I
didn't it really is the reason I think
it was okay is that um it had okay I
think I saw green light but I did see a
blue one and a red one and it was going
horizontally across a clear sky and it
was like a triangle but it was very it
was like in an angle so it kind of
looked triangular and it was
going wasn't there anymore you [Music]
[Music]
see no it didn't come into a cloud sorry
no clouds simply the angle obscured the
idea of the vision of your life and it
appeared to disappear okay it was one of
your own
CS all right thank you very much oh
thank you very much however you
remember that your
sensitivity towards being attracted to
the energy of that idea still works
towards opening doorways and creating
connections okay just been some
wonderful connections this week for me
those kinds of connections we were
talking about that are going to be
happening The Happening thank you
wonderful wonderful thank you
uh what is necessary for me to have a
satisfactory relationship woman
doesn't I see first of all you can
recognize that no relationship once
created ever
ends ever it may change its definition
it may change the parameters going on
within the relationship even if you
never physiologically see each other
ever again then that is the definition
of the
relationship now therefore first of all recognize
now therefore first of all recognize
that in your belief system maybe
embedded the idea that these things must
come to an end you resent this idea you
fight against it and create much of the
reasons for why it appears to end
painfully by attracting circumstances
that allow themselves to play out your
fears and your
beliefs nothing ends ever first of all
you follow me yeah all right now are you
allowing the relationships that you
attract in your life to be there for the
reasons they are there or to be there
for what you think they should be there
for well I think they should be there
why because that's what I think I want I
see why not let them be there for why
they are actually there well because
that think to be differ from what I
think I want how can it be what you want
is what you get in
life you see again the paradox
the idea as soon as you are willing to
face up to the idea that you attracted
this situation because it was at that
moment you created it what you wanted
then you give yourself the opportunity
to recognize all right this is what I
did want it is not what I prefer from this
want it is not what I prefer from this
point
forward the idea of in your terms owning
up to the creation of it to begin with
however as a recognition that at that
moment it was what you wanted will allow
you the ability to let it not make it
not force it let it allow it to
transform into something more
representative of what you now
prefer you follow me uh yes I I I I I
intellectually understand the idea that
I made it but I don't really experience
I'm not very connected with the
experience of making unpleasant things
happen if you say
so now can you not realize that even
when you create an attra the idea you
call an unpleasant circumstance yourself
that you still learn from oh yes then
why not begin to see the entire event as
a positive experience oh look what I
have learned Now by my how creative I
am following I seem to be learning the
same thing over and over
again that is only an illusion it is
only because you keep placing the same
definition in the symbols you
see all right here is the mechanism of
it one more time and of course this one
more time is in no way shape or form the
same time again nor the same thing it is
always new we use that term loosely one more
time allow us to remind you not tell you
something new but remind you whatever
level this already exists upon in
knowledge and your Consciousness to
remind you will you do me a favor
you will you do me a favor
sure oh thank you repeat after me no no
situation situation has has built built
in in
meaning all all
situations are
fundamentally are fundamentally neutral
neutral the meaning the meaning I give I
give to a neutral to a neutral situation
situation completely completely
determines determines the effect the
effect I experience I experience whether
it is positive whether it is positive or
negative or
negative now you understand that idea
all situations are fundamentally neutral
no
symbols symbolize
anything intrinsically
no symbol no situation has builtin
meanings you supply the meaning to an
empty symbolic shell when you fill the
Shell with your meaning that is the
effect you
experience so to say well I keep
experiencing the same thing over and
over and over and over and over again is
only because if you know you have
changed if you know you have made a
decision that you prefer something else
then all you need to do is truly act
like you believe you have changed and
act like you believe that your physical
reality must reflect that now recognize
that you still do live in a world of
time and therefore some changes may
still take a little time but the idea is
is that the change on the template level
has occurred instantaneously the second
you decide to make a
change the physiological symbols that
represent it may be a little slow in
changing but your opportunity and the
way to allow them to change most quickly
is the following way when you know you
have changed if you trust that that is a
fact for you that that is true for you
then when you see a symbol that you may
say is the same symbol as before do not
give it the same meaning if you are not
the same
person give it a new meaning this symbol
no longer means what it used do what
does it now mean now that you are a new
person now that you are a changed person
how would the person you now know
yourself to be regard this symbol don't
keep regarding the symbols in the way
you used to if you don't want them to
have the same old effect give them new
meanings give them new definitions know
beyond the shadow of a doubt that
whether it looks the same or not it
can't mean the same thing because you
are not the same
person then in the quickest possible way
will you allow those symbols to change
their shape and to transform into
something more physically representative
of the new meaning you have given it you
follow yes this is the mechanics this is
the physics of the entire
ID it is if you are willing to
understand it that simple you follow me
yes now are you willing to allow it to
be that simp
yeah the IDE is only that it is
necessary to
act like to act life you believe that
when you make a
change you have in fact changed you are
in fact different and therefore
everything in your reality has to be
representative of the difference you now
know yourself to be and cannot be by
definition the same old thing it must be
new it must
be therefore when you come with that
attitude that new
understanding you will then begin to
allow yourself to
see how the symbols in your life will
transform will change
to fit the new image the new
understanding the new idea you now know
yourself to be do you follow
me it does not take very much
time when you let it take the least
amount of time that it can in many cases
you will find
that as little as three of your days is
all that is necessary to allow any
situation to completely change in a way
more in line with what you now trust
yourself to be you follow me
yes has this assisted you
yes we thank you
very you you've made two statements
tonight I have made more than
that interested me oh all right thank
you two statements in your reality all
right thank you very much uh one that
tracked me was that uh the universe do
not do pointless things yeah number two
all situations are fundamentally neutral yes
situations are fundamentally neutral yes
uh would you comment on The Coincidence
of these two and how they interact with
theolog thank you very much the universe
in your terms is holographic do you
understand that term I do the idea is
that at any particular place in the
universe exists the potential of the
total Universe you follow me in this way
therefore recognize everything is
interconnected in a very very well
orchestrated Matrix and in such a manner
that meaning can be given to any one of
these particular points and the meaning
given to that point will give the life
to that particular point will Define
what it is that can exist in that
particular holographic point will Define
what phase of the interconnectedness is
perceived in that holographic point so
everything by definition must be
fundamentally neutral in order for every
point to contain the ability to manifest
any one portion of the entire universe
in
it you follow me I do um um it means
that the potential the infinite
potential of each point
is the purpose of the universe yes and
to realize what represents your
understanding of yourself is your
purpose to
realize the potential in any given
point which is you you follow me you do
thank you about a indeed it does thank
you very much
indeed will you manifest your
[Music] reality I just I just learning about
reality I just I just learning about
integrating the left brain and the right
brain and right now I was noticing that
I was listening with my left ear which
is uh music ear so if I'm listening to
my left ear which is uh music in vague
then I cannot uh register the words and
the information that I should be
receiving on my right here you can
receive it in whatever way you need to
but I have uh for my experence I have
register in my brain the information or
I cannot recall all the information that
I receive in my brain or
integrate again the idea to some degree
is to first of all recognize that you do
in fact register everything whether you
can recall it or not is another matter
but you do in fact register everything
on every level every level it is there
intuitively it is there intellectually
it is there musically it is there
mathematically it is there
linguistically it is there sensorially
it is there visually arly it is there in
every single level
now as we were just speaking of the Hol
graic Universe what you can recall will
simply depend upon where your reference
theme is
focused so who first of all know that
everything is in fact there will give
you the opportunity to Simply go into
whatever imaginary State you need to to
tune in to where it is that that
reference has been stored and be able to
in your terms retrieve
it rely once again upon the very finely
focused beam the needle of your
imagination it will always land squarely
in the area you need to have it land in
order to recall and live in the moment
and be with whatever idea it is you need
to be okay but also the information that
is received in the left bra and the
information that is received in the
right brain and if they don't integrate
together then you don't see the old
picture in the information we understand
what you are saying but also recognize
that if you are going to use chose what
may be called third density terminology
and continue to define the idea that
there is a separation between the left
and the right brain instead of thinking
of your brain as the homogeneous idea
that it is then you will continually
create a scenario in which you will
always feel that something is going into
one side and not the other when in fact
it is always going into both okay but if
I'm going to school right now and
learning this information and if I want
to help other people then I have to
understand how it function in in in all
the the tools that it represents so I
yes to some degree but recognize that
you are determining what the tools are
you will be using you are determining
what you think you need to learn you can
always change the definition of what it
is you think you need to learn and then
that will be the definition of how you
assist other people with what you learn
in that
way but I don't feel that I that I do
know so that's that's what I'm going to
other people that have search and I've
learned so they are giving me this
information so so so then I can sit down
and say oh I you don't have to tell me
anything I know it all you know what you
need to know this does not mean you
cannot be
assisted but that's what I mean so I'm
I'm asking a little more information on
on on
this that I that I feel what I have
learned and how I see it right now and
what I have what I have learned and um
just discussing with you to see if it if
it's coordinates and does
it no
you you went over my head
right in this way as we are saying we're
going to be discussing two different
points of view two different complete
realities yeah so I mean My Reality my
point of view to to be valid and for me
to able to be able to function it is
valid all right in this way therefore
let us say reflecting back to you your
own tool the tool you have chosen to
use in this way what you can get in
touch with with the idea of what you
call the lyic system of the brain the
Corpus colossum and what you call the
hippocampus allowing yourself in your
imagination to allow the energy in your
brain to be equally balanced in these
areas will possibly allow you an
opportunity to feel the ability to switch
to feel the ability to switch
hemispheres at will and allow yourself
to Avail yourself of whatever percentage
of either you feel you need to be in
touch with at any given moment to do the
things you wish to
do does this assist you how do I do this
in your
imagination understand something now pay
attention to this for this can assist
you very
strongly you are familiar with what you
call the neuronic halfways in your brain
yes remember this every single
thought every single thought Bashar yes
every single thought oh there must be
some exceptions Bashar no exception
every single thought that you
have physically yes physically changes the
physically yes physically changes the
neural Pathways in your brain into the
configuration that now physically
supports the new thought wow okay yeah
therefore using your imagination and
thinking whatever thoughts you wish to
will automatically arrange your brain in
whatever configuration it needs to be in
to give you the ability and the tool you
are requesting of
me so then I have to be in a relaxed
mind yes tension will only cause more
yes tension will only cause more
separation and an inability to perceive
the communication that is always going
on between what you call the left and
the right
hemisphere are you familiar with with
your CL is that
valid are you referring to systems that
synchronize the left and right
hemisphere yes it is always valid
everything is valid all tools are valid
if you feel strength in the
representation of that tool by all means
for you it is valid because it
represents your reality because you have
attracted yourself to that idea if you
are excited about it if you are not
excited about it then it is not valid
for you it is not a part of your reality
but if you are excited about it it is
very much valid for you and is
completely in line with what it is that
is the next thing you have to learn to
be a servant yeah thank you very much
thank you very
much you would you talk to us about the
fth dimension the sixth Dimension how
about if we leave that up to someone who
comes from [Music]
[Music]
oh okay another question of course I
heard over the weekend that the
Egyptians used S as a means of
constructing their pyramids is that some
of the ancient ones y not all of them
not the later ones and also what you
would call some East Indians and also
what you would call Tibetan utilized
much of the same idea much of the same
idea was utilized in Avantis as well
which is where basically the Egyptians
got their idea of it uhhuh while we're
talking about the Tibetans could you
explain how gong work in healing the
idea is that each and everything in
physical reality is the product of a
particular frequency vibration of the
Primal fundamental energy of all that is
you follow me yes the idea of a
tone can contain within it a formula and
equation that represents a fundamental
alignment with that fundamental
vibration a synchronous alignment in
experiencing a certain frequency or tone
it then washes over you washes through
you and allows if you are willing allows
the entire idea of the energy structure
that you are and therefore the physical
structure that you are to realign with
what that tone represents a fundamental
alignment with all that is so you in a
sense rebalance yourself reenter
yourself you follow me yes I do does
that assist
you sure thank you um
okay um long time ago when long time
well I went to to a um meeting with you
and you would asked me how I that one
particular moment um there was
a situation where I said that I got in
touch back with my
four-year-old and um you'd ask me how I
felt and I was saying I felt scared but
really what I felt when you asked me how
I was feeling and you emphasize that
word was that the umbilical cord for my
belly button was PA say a lot and felt
very um strong strong strong home
what is that the idea is close to what
you call the socer of intention in this
way within the solar plexus connection
but it is also an opening of a gate and
an extension to many ideas of your
future self many ideas of your past self
it is the forming of an energy umbilical
to many ideas that you may be now
Gathering into the present to allow
yourself to become okay okay I have um
two other questions number one uh yes
okay when you talk
about that okay we can
choose how we want our reality
to
and and that we can have control in that
sense what's the difference between that
kind of control and then the kind of
control that I've been learning to
relinquish or give up of of trying to
have things go A Very certain way oh
thank you very much
in this way recognize that what you
typically refer to in your society as
surrendering is actually taking
control control means letting yourself
flow with and in synchronous harmony
with the idea of the universal self the
universal infinite
choosing to flow synchronous de with
that idea is taking control
is knowing you are in control as we have
said there are two types of free will
the Free Will of the physiological
Consciousness the Free Will of the
higher Consciousness all that you call
the Free Will of the higher
Consciousness many times is relegated by
the physical Consciousness into the
terminology you call Faith or
predestination but this only occurs in
the most generalized of terms the actual
specifics of how the events the
generalized events that are determined
by the non-physical higher Consciousness
unfold how they unfold specifically is
determined by the physiological
personality the physiological desires
the physiological thoughts the
physiological beliefs that you create in
your physiological life thus in this way
the taking control once again is the
expression of your desire the expression
of your willingness the expression of
your conviction of what you know to be
true for you it is taking that stand of
conviction and taking the stand of
conviction in that way places you
squarely in the flow of the universal
energy that you are in touch with and
thus makes it seem as if once you have
taken control you don't have to do much
hearing does this help
you can you say that last sentence one
more time when you take
control then the Paradox is that it
becomes apparent that you actually don't
feel like you have to do this
stearing this is the Paradox of physical
reality when you know you are creating
your reality on are fully in control of
it because everything you experience is
what you
created then you open up to the
idea vulnerability is Infinite Strength
and not weakness and if you are willing
to be completely open which is what
vulnerability is then you know you are
completely connected to all that is
being completely connected to all that
is means you are always totally
completely reinforced you have Infinite
Strength and therefore you simply flow
flow along the universal lines of
momentum you are completely in control
by flowing along the lines of least
resistance th it does not feel like you
have to steer the only time it feels
like you have to do the steering is when
you fight your own ecstasy giving into
your own ecstasy surrendering quote
unquote to the universal flow of things
allows you to know that you are squarely
in control because then it is effortless
to create the reality you prefer because
you are drawing everything in parallel
lines and not going against the
flow going going on lately one is I'm
going going on lately one is I'm
starting to feel very flid yes and feel
the joy and feel that movement towards
it then there's another part of me
that's scared and excited at the same
time no and and a real one moment okay
and the real one
moment understand you are either
excited or you are anxious you cannot be
both at the same time because they are
both from the same energy excitement is
the positive Viewpoint of the energy
anxiety is the negative Viewpoint of the
same energy you cannot be excited and
anxious at the same time if you are
excited you are expressing a positive
faith in that in the flow if you are
anxious you are fighting your own
ecstasy I do it very quickly yes that is
what appears to create the illusion that
it happens at the same time but it is
not you are two completely different
individuals choose the one you
prefer and act like that so you can
maintain either the excitement or the
anxiety or you can continue to be the
overall idea of the two different
individuals back and forth back and
forth back and forth back and forth it
is up to you but you are still always
progressing at your own rate whatever
rate is comfortable for you the more you
are willing to enjoy the flip-flop idea
then the less anxious you will be about
it and the more you will tip the scale
in the direction of the excitement
rather than the anxiety oh good you
follow me yeah that's a any willingness
at all to
integrate any willingness at all to
integrate automatically by definition
tips the scale toward the positive side
of the
momentum yeah I do cuz yes cuz I get to
be sometimes I love being a tight ass
though it just a strange
feel all very very just like
picity Indulgence in that all right you
obviously are getting something out of
it
from it what you he and then when you
prefer to be something else be
it okay okay also you were in a dream
the night in a
few in a few of individuals as
well and um I I said I'm coming here the
this time I around for a while you said
oh good to see nice to see you
again that was the
Dre as we have said this night of your
time is called night of dreams and in
this way there are many gates and many
doors of opening that are taking place
and you are also recognizing as you may
perceive symbolically our energy that
what you are communicating within your
dream realities is also your own higher
selves as you use us to symbolize that
very often
once again the idea of
openness willingness unconditional love
and vulnerability is Infinite
Strength which will allow
you to be in
touch with the idea of what you have
called the
heavens and bring them into your heart
and fill yourselves with
ecstatic knowingness with
knowingness with
this firmly in mind firmly in heart and
firmly in
spirit may all with the accompaniment of
my little
friend take a break
insert tape two now
now
sharing you then you than
you the little sculpture that you did in
the first part hey is that a personality
from your it is a blending of many
things and it is an essential symbol of
the idea that you are now transforming
idea that you are now transforming
through the idea of the transformation
itself many different ideas that have
forly been cloaked in your secrecy now
coming to the Forefront of many of the
different doorways
aspects and actions that you are taking
in your life there are many
representational openings upon the
figurine as you would call it there is
one of the crown Cher one in between the
shoulder blades in this way that
represents the idea of the connection to
the higher self and the conviction and
commitment to allow that to channel
through you through what you would call
the chakra of channeling in between the
shoulder BL and face of the ne in this
way it also represents the idea of your
own scure selves which in many ways we
also symbolize energetically and in this
sense therefore there's a blending in
that sense it also represents a degree
of the idea of serious ener it also
represents a degree of ideas of all the
different kinds of loving connections
and the things that you are nurturing
within yourselves at this time and
bringing forth a new birth within
yourself therefore there is the idea you
call not only the serious connection but
also the pleadian connection also the
Arcturus Connection in this way it is an
overall symbol that represents many
Essences and many ideas that you are now
cing yourself within redefining the IDE
of the government that you wear and
allowing yourself more and more
expression of the ethereal in physical
terms and it is also simply in this way
an expression of the unconditional
loving bond that the Universe has for
you that's wonderful and the little
trailing out behind of the Rob does that
have a significant meaning in this way
it is the Gathering up of all that you
consider to be your past s now
collecting into the idea of that which
you cloak yourselves within it is in
this way merging and blending and leaves
as you travel As you move in your
momentum awake that allows you to know
where you have always been but brings it
up into the moment into the present as
something that you are availing yourself
of in the present that's wonderful thank
you is that
[Music] another or an
another or an
idea there seems to be some kind of well
you put a piece of clay over graped over
the heart in this way the idea again of
the unconditional loving expression but
in this way also the idea of that which
you are nurturing the new idea of
yourselves you are giving birth to as
your future selves it is also pointing
into the chakra of intention your solar
flexus hey I would like you to um help
me to understand fully a lot of images
and dream and some some separate things
that I know are connected and I just
feel that you could really I feel it's
important it feels like it's all really
important and um it has to do with the
energy of this person who's dying of age
that we talked about it also has to do
with a dream in which a character came
up to me an older man who in seemed like
a cowboy who introduced himself uh said
he was not aware that he
apologized um for not being aware that I
was a woman and an American all this
time and something about it was just all
the envelopes okay but anyway dream
character that seem to be a very
controlling character this is an aspect
of the culture of the same
individual oh okay all
right and then this this morning as I
was waking from the dream I had one of
those fast motion videotape things that
sometimes happened to me where I
suddenly just get these visual images on
top of each other and it was two people
but it seemed like both of their entire
lives but it was only so fast I could
only see them and one was the redheaded
woman and the other was another cowboy
boy all right now we will give you basic
fundamentals the specifics are up to you
okay the understanding is that there's a
very strong connection here in what you
call past life terms with certain
incidents and interactions and
relationships that went on that are now
what are being used to create the
determining factors of the situations
and the relationships now going on in
the present life the idea of the
callousness then the sensitivity now the
lack of blending of the male female then
the blending now but there is still the
idea of what is considered to be karmic
retribution involved in the idea or the
consciousness of that individual and the
relationships with you in this way this
is being played out and may play to the
idea of the term of the physiological
passage but does not necessarily have to
but in this way the soul will have
learned and have felt and have believed
that a balance has been performed and
this individual in this way may then
allow himself to be involved in the IDE
and a reincarnational way with the
transer
from this point forward okay can you
give me any more information on the
karmic retribution because I feel that
too but I I have no sense of really what
it is you have already described it and
defined it in very clear and concise
terms the idea of attitudes of calluses
towards the idea of the femininity
contained
within you follow me we will leave the
rest up to
you one one time am I was I the
redhaired woman okay thank you yes um
there are a few of us here involved in
plan for the
Future Okay youve mentioned in the past
something about a magnetic resonance
could you tell me what that means and
and how we use it oh F you what it
simply means is that in your world
because it is an electromagnetic
phenomena there are many points that
pulse with a certain beat a certain
frequency that represent the interchange
and exchange of different energy levels
throughout the entire world as it
balances itself as a unit that is simply
one of those points that has a high
degree of magnetic resonance frequencies
and it allows you to align when you are
in that frequency cellularly
electromagnetically align with many more
portions of your cell so that all is
moving in one linear momentum Direction
it gives impetus and momentum in that
way okay is there something that's been
put into the area or is it native are it
is native to the are oh we we start of
picked up that there was something
placed there by the people from the
spaceship many years
ago this is something that exists as an
energy idea but is not in your terms in
your dimension
physical okay you may be perceiving
across the dimensionality then in this
way there is in that sense something
attached to every single point upon your
planet that exhibit that kind of
phenomenon oh okay than thank
you I've been working with this idea of
integrating theas and various grounding
techniques I see are you having a good
time yeah
um specifically of during the point of
orgasm instead of concentrating on
physical bodies and stuff actually
concentrating on something totally
disassociated like cash
it's much harder it's much harder to to
produce the feelings but I was using it
as a technique for for grounding and
generating the feeling the intense
feeling necessary and I notic after I
did that it created a major shift right
a major shift it was like it grounded it
it was it was right took it from the CLE
into the physical plane yeah and it like
you know laar talks about going through
several chakras but it like took it all
the way down and um
and you know today some bizarre guy
needed this machine for me bizar yeah
yeah was bizarre and he needed this
machine to me just sitting around and he
said you know we talked about $5,000 for
this thing and I oh God where am I going
to throw this thing away and it was uh
that was like an immediate reaction I
wanted to know you know the chakra
integration there taking it all the way
down to that the Kundalini or whatever
the heck it is
[Music] there we I don't
there we I don't
[Music]
know is that more effective now we're
sticking all the way down to the is that
the first Shakra or whatever allowing
yourself to interconnect all levels and
in your terms drive that energy deep
within the Earth will plug you into a
source of your own infinite
electromagnetic power and allow you to function as a
power and allow you to function as a
completely totally supported extension
of the Earth yeah that's a total refocus
of that energy too because normally it's
sex means pictures of beautiful bodies
and stuff and now it's now it's a
totally different the energy can be
utilized in many different energy yeah
that that it lasts about 30 seconds or
33 seconds
[Music] and
and
33 left to but it left
that is the threshold 33 thank
you thank you I wanted to tell you that
in the past couple weeks since I've
heard you the first time the first week
I had a dream that um there was a man
who was um building topographical models
and he was uh dismantling one and I
asked him why he was doing that and he
said he wanted to build a topographical
model of the Bay of Bengal and I said
what do there and he said I swim with a
dolphin and I asked him if I could do
that too and he said look over there and
I looked over there and there was a
dolphin at the edge of the shore and I
went with a dolphin under the water very
fast wait a
minute and um I was completely unafraid
and very very excited and um anyway that
was a couple days after after hearing me
S the first time so um I wanted to tell
you that how synchronous you may discuss
it also with someone else who will be
here this evening of your time oh good
all right thank you the other thing I
wanted to uh tell you is that uh since
I've heard you last um first um I saw a
show on Channel 28 called the creation
of the universe and it's a research
that's um been going on uh with
physicists and scientists since Einstein
step on the unified field Theory Hi and
um scientists generally concur right now
that they know how assume there is a big
bang and that they know they know how up
to a couple of hundreds of billions of
seconds um right after the moment of
creation or the Big Bang How the
Universe reacted you know
electromagnetically and right okay
anyway um this one scientist from
Cambridge proposed that maybe the
beginning of creation is like is there
an edge to the Earth no it just keeps
going round and round yes so um my
question to you is um are they are these
scientists going to push until they find
the beginning of creation or is the Big
Bang thing just a kind of a wishful
thinking is kind of a they will find a
beginning within the time frame that
creates the idea of Beginnings okay but
beyond that there is existence which has
always existed that's the feeling I got from
existed that's the feeling I got from
from the show the idea you are referring
to as the quote unquote Big Bang is in a
sense one of the infinite events Within
in existence right thank you very much
thank you you okay
you since I saw you last inai I had
started that process called future s and
since that time has done a number of
individuals recently within the past
month or so did a small group of people
at the same time on the theme of Peace
which we worked with for about 20
minutes basically this is a sharing and
I welcome any input you have the vision
that I have on it now is to do this with
perhaps hundreds or even thousands of
people at the same time in a concert
context utilizing that process and
utilizing a video screen as feedback
reflective feedback for people to
witness their own evolution of their
state and verification of it and using
peace as a theme and making that
available to each individual that they
may retune to that frequency as a tool
when they need it that they may carry
the we inform you our input will be to
ask you to Simply keep us informed as to
how much fun you are
having we thank
you
may hello anyway
hello currently myself and other people
in this room are working with certain
purification techniques
techniques
that the purpose behind them is
to have a greater realization of who you
really are
hey would you speak
on what you the importance as you
perceive it or see it of specific
purification techniques to allow us
within ourselves to experience who we
are and to be of Greater service in the
times that we now living thank you in
this way recognize that there are what
you call techniques that may allow you
to tap into the generalized agreements
you have all made and thus put you in
touch with the very foundations of the
reality you have co-created with each
other and allow you therefore that much
more closer recognition of the pulse the
pace at which you beat in this way
however recognize that the idea of any
technique which you feel so inclined to
be attracted to is therefore
representative of the vibrational being
you are and therefore whatever you are
attracted to by definition will be the
technique that provides you with what
you need anytime you feel like changing
it then the feeling of changing it
itself is indicative of the technique
itself the ongoingness of the overall
technique which will always transform
into something else you follow me yes in
this way therefore the very simplest
thing we can say is that any technique
you feel is valid for you and you feel
puts you more closely in touch with the
idea of the all that is that you are is
the technique that is correct for you
and your own imagination and your own
life and the synchronicity in your life
will always lead you to exactly what you
need and in this way if you find that
you enjoy this if you are excited about
the idea of what you have led yourself
to then by all means recognize that your
participation and your involvement and
your expression of those techniques will
be what gets you to the next step to
allow you to then transform into what
will then attract to itself the very
next technique necessary if a technique
is then at that point even necessary the
overall idea however is that life itself
is the only process you actually need
and in this way in the willingness to
Simply live the willingness to be of
service in ways that move you that
represent you being the being that you
know you are that is the technique that
will always bring to you more and more
and more expanded opportunity to feel
that much more ecstatic about your
connections and your ability to express
those connections to all that is does
that the sister does one other question
M oh
you talk much about following one's
excitement what is your thought
on is the purpose of following your
excitement to lead you
towards more of a middle path to balance
the PA of opposit in a sense yes it is
the effortless way because of the
following definition what you call
definition what you call
excitement is your physical translation
of the energy that represents the path
you chose to be that is why you can
always trust it no matter what the
surface scenario appears like no matter
how different one scenario may be from
another scenario if the same level of
excitement is behind it it is the
excitement that is the arrow that is the
barometer to let you know this is a
continuation of the same path no matter
how it appears on the surface excitement
is being in line and in balance with the
path you chose to be and that is why it
is effortless to do what excites you and
doing what excites you will always find
you completely in a balanced way
supported by the universe because you
are squarely consciously on the level of
the path you chose to be on by following
what expect you it is the
vibration that calls you it is the
vibration that defines the path you
chose to be in this
life does that exist true thank you
thank you very much fale thank you
um I'd like to share something and I
like to ask a question all um I have I I
created I suppose you could say I bought
a car an old red convertible that was
very ensing 2 and 1 half years ago and
gradually I have become more and more
and more and more upset with this car
and the more upset I got the more the
car misbehaved I see etc
etc and I decided finally to sell the
car and yesterday with the same the same
attitude attaching the same negative
significance to that symbol continuing
to create that negativity went to the
DMV and of course we all know we have
all have our preconceived ideas as to
what the DMV is all about anyway um and
had a great deal of difficulty dealing
with the DMV and had also taken it to a
body shop and had been given nothing but
bad news about how unsafe it was but of
course I introduced the car as being
very unsafe and is it really safe to
drive and oh it's such a piece of junk
and of course the auto man said it's
really a piece of junk and it's going to
cost you 500 more dollars to fix it out
to sell it right so anyway as I was
driving yesterday afternoon after
hearing all of this home I just happen
to have playing in my car the tape from
last week which talks
about uh just what you were talking
about earlier tonight using the same
were seeing a symbol that one had
attached negativity to before and
without really realizing it um perhaps
attaching the same old negative
negativity to it okay but as I heard you
talking about it I heard you say if
you're truly transformed you should be
able either who should
I you can choose to create a new meaning
for that old symbol and
bo uh I decided that yes indeed I have
definitely been having wonderful
experiences of transformation and this
stor that has been in my side for two
and a half years of course I created a s
has actually been a
rose a Rand convertible
Rose so
today I actually someone else drove the
car down to Los Angeles but today I went
and talked with another mechanic with an
entirely different Viewpoint and even
admired the car when I walked in and
looked at it after 2 and a half years of
tremendous upset and expense I admired
the car and said all right now what
would you evaluate the problems to be
and he said well there are a number of
them here but really it is no major
operation to get this thing back on the
road not going to be expensive it's not
going to be lengthy and it's going to be
just beautiful and it's going to be
soill in no time at all and it is all
thanks to you no no it is all thanks to
you and if I wore a hat I take it off
it is really miraculous that within less
than 24 hours probably really in moment
of cognizing the of that take situation
I
mean now you have a very strong
example of the realization that the
present is not a result of the past
right right exactly what you are at any
given moment is what you experience in
your life no matter what you have
experienced before and also when you
said that the symbol was a a reflection
of me and I thought whoa I want this
piece of you know what to to be a
reflection of me hey I'm not you know
what I I'm not that negative thing that
I was calling it and all that you are
not a sword you are a Roose
right wow what a transformation secondly
the question um I'm I would appreciate some
question um I'm I would appreciate some
help in sorting something out I'm making
my awake
time my conscious reality I'm I'm
creating Transformations on a just a
very exciting um with exciting frequency
well you obviously don't need help with
that well well that but I am
wondering why when I
awake well first I've been U more aware
of my dreams recently upon awaking
because I've made a conscious effort to
be more aware of
them okay the thing that I don't
understand is that even though I'm
gaining more control and the sense of
preference over my awake times yes I
have a lot of nightmares and I've had a
lot of nightmares for a long time but
I'm becoming more aware of the specifics
yes and I I would like to so you are
working some things out in the
non-physical reality that you do not
prefer to experience in the physical
real would you prefer to have them in
the physical reality well at least I
could do something about them there I
feel so out of control
in you see and now I'm learning to how
to use how to use a preference how to
detach negativity from symbols yes and
look at them in a new unit of time yes
well now that you have done it in your
physical reality creative one why not do
it in the dream reality as well well
most individuals do it in the dream
reality first and then see it in the
physical reality the physical reality
and now you need to do it in the dream
reality you see dream reality to me has
a different kind of significance because
it's more like a nightmare reality and I
don't prefer that well do not let it be
a thorn any longer even right is it so
it is possible even though I'm a sleet
to consciously absolutely transform
abolutely so we recognize you always have the same
so we recognize you always have the same
degree of control and if it is something
you have now experienced tangibly as you
say in the physical reality then by all
means recognize that when you are in
your dream reality you are a thought
form in a world of thought forms and
what you think is instantly your reality
instantly is this something I'm creating
or are symbols from elsewhere like
higher consciousnesses or you are still
creating them no matter where they come
from because you have to create your
version of them in order to experience
them right ironically last night was all
about lost luggage which I think is
pretty humous actually considering
what's going on in my life you know not
I can't always I have not been able to
look at them that lightly until now
however I get the idea that now that
I've looked at a nightmare about lost
luggage not only of myself but of others
and I see the humor in that
meanings reality so maybe I'll be able
to do that in the future with other
dreams or
nightm [Music]
[Music]
um in the now well yes in the no but in
a SLE State upon a way but they are
becoming one and the same you are
dreaming right
now I'm still integrating yes still
working that is all right it is night of
dreams right dreams exactly
thank you very
much I understand that you might have
someone here from
Syria and I've been working with a
serious energy for several years and I
wondered if we could have something
to give us about the serious
energy as we work with it I and what he
might say about how it connects my
serious the idea first of
all of what you call all right all
right I will let him
bu one more [Music]
if you time in it way the symol that you
have just perceived the idea that you
call in your language the dog in this
way is the symbol in your Society of
that which performs service and this is
the idea of the representation of what
you call the serious energy that is
represented by by conscious time the
idea of service itself service within
the society you have created yourself to
be service within the idea of
recognizing yourself as an aspect of the
unconditional loving infinite of all
that is in this way the idea of serious
energy is that which represents Triad
which is represented by the idea of your
planet Earth the idea of the
civilization you call esani the idea of
the civilization you call the fous
civilization which is represented by the
time the IDE is that it is a three-fold
trary IDE you call a Triad each
representing a different portion of a
Consciousness a whole total overthrow
idea which can be represented as the
idea of your Earth filling in the idea
of the physiological the idea of eston
filling in the idea of the mental and
the idea of serious filling in the idea
of the spiritual connotations of the
idea of the overs soul that we represent
together as a trying re formation in
this way recognize the timing and the
synchronicity of the idea of the hearing
of the service of the symbol in this way
in your Society the dog for in this way
recognize that is why you have
intuitively called the idea you call
serious the star the dog star in this
way in this sense recognize it is a
symbol of service in your society and in
this way the idea of your willingness
your conviction your action your placing
of your own hands the placing of your
own physicality upon the world around
you upon the world before you that which
you have created to see in your sight
that which you have created to see
before you lay out on the table the
spread of the natural table before you
about what you have to draw from that
which sustains you in this way all upon
that table is what sustains you in your
life and in this way as you draw from
that idea and knowing that you are
nourished with every step you take every
step you take upon the Earth in this way
nourishes you yet again to perform more
and more service and increase the
accelerated idea of the transformational
agion which you have now co-created to
exist with everyone else upon your
planet in this way are we being of
assistance to you in this
manner the idea of the accepting of the
willingness of
having within yourself to of service in
your Society will only increase the
Bountiful riches that you experience
within yourself to be the idea of
serious energy is one of fluid motion
the idea of what you might call
spontaneous choreography the idea of
allowing yourself to know there are many
levels of communication taking place
between you and every other being within
your Society at all times on all levels
every level you can conceive yourself to
exist upon and in this way allowing
yourself more to be in touch as you are
connected to the Earth with all the
other levels knowing you are firmly
anchored firmly grounded and in this way
reaping of the benefit of the Earth's
vibration has it shoots up within you
and solidifies you so that you are a
beacon that receives and is sensiti to
all the other levels knowing that
because you draw your strength from the
Earth itself from the plan in which you
exist none of these other levels that
you are in touch with will ever
overwhelm you they will all manifest
within you in the way that is
appropriate to be manifested through you
in your service because as a beacon and
an extension of the planet Earth in
which you lived in this way you have
been chosen and are expressing the idea
of your choice to be of service in this
way and therefore you can simply know
trust and take it for granted that you
are connected to the infinet in this way
and anything that comes through you in
this manner that you deem to be what
excites you in the form of service as
you perform it will always be put forth
an unconditional love in a loving way
and have a great and powerful impact and
an effect upon your planet do you follow
along is this being of service to you it
is there anything else wish to explore
specifically within yourself yes for me
I've been doing it for four over four
years running that service from bringing
the Ser
hey how have you been performing the
idea of service in your planetary
fear do you perceive
perceive
doive how you perform the idea of
service in your planetary sphere I
bringing the Eng in and distributing on
the planet to different
areas matter
matter
meditation involving other individuals
or yourself with individuals is a
group recognize for the idea is that you
are forming stabilization points around
your planet in this way acting as the
idea of an energy Vortex acting as your
own energy Vortex that is an alignment
gate with all different levels of
consciousness in this way as you plant
yourself at various positions around
your planet you then allow there to be
the key of the energization of that
point in this way an alignment of those
forces and alignment of the
electromagnetic field in your world so
that therefore from that point forward
it is say if you are planting flowers in
the garden of your planet and every time
another individual will find themselves
coming upon that location in which you
have existed in which you have aligned
yourself in that they will come upon the
fragrance of that flower you have
started and see it in full bloom we
thank you for your service in this
way it's a great
jar can you talk more
slowly we can modulate the energy to
some degree
[Music] thank you may in
thank you may in
this the
thank
you yeah I'm getting to the point in my
dreams where I'm no longer afraid of
anything that that I'm confronted with
or that it's really a wonderful place to
be I I can't say that I've made that in
in my own physical life but in my dreams
that's true
um I don't how to explain it right
before I came here uh to California
about a month ago I was in bed with my
fiance and I just done a medication
trying to uh connect with a Consortium from the
to uh connect with a Consortium from the
PES my spirit guide from the
PES and
all right that you may proceed allow me
for the moment to interact with you in
this way for you will find that at this
time because of blending taking place
the energy level of the serious energy
devops in this way will not be something
that the physiological channel can
sustain for very long we will continue
with you um you are in this way as you
say negotiating recognition and contact
with creating energy continue right uh
an entity was actually in my dead with
me um
and I I talked to it I couldn't I
couldn't move my body okay at first
there was this is a very very typical
phenomena when you are half in and half
out of your body because the idea is
that you think you are still in it and
you try to move in the ordinary way and
you cannot move in the ordinary way
physically so you feel you cannot move
at all you feel rigidized it is only
because you are not moving in the astral
way uhhuh well I and it was on that
plane that you messy other entities uhuh
yeah I didn't feel threatened by this
other entity of course not it is very
loving exactly exactly um it was just
for experience to me how but there was a
part of me that was a little fearful and
so in my mind I was speaking to my
fiance and he actually woke up and
turned around and hugged me um this
entity was holding my hand and wanted to
get closer I so
I um so I guess I had a little fear of
it coming too close I didn't know if it
I don't know what that was I don't know
if I don't know can you explain
recognize the idea of what you call the
pleadian energy this is what we can give
you at this time for there are many
things still unfolding within your
reality and we cannot spoil all the
surprises but in this way the idea of
the alien energy is that they are in
very many ways quite literally in terms
of your overall Earth civilization quite
literally your brothers your sisters and
your cousins you are off of the same grouping
cousins you are off of the same grouping
and in this way you are reforming
connections to those who love you there
and to those who you love there yeah I
could feel that I it was just it was a
little strange it was a new experience
because this entity has come to me again
um but I asked if it was here to help me
in my soul Mission which I feel very
clear about and uh if it wasn't for it
to leave my bed and so it left my
bed it left your bed primarily because
you asked to leave because it sense your
uncomfortableness not that it cannot be
of assistance but the idea of course is
that it is up to you when I'm ready
right it was just okay all right thank
you thank you thank you for the blending
and thank you for the crystallization of
the vibration five and seven one
seven one
moment there is now an opportunity not
so much for the exact what you would
call continuation of the serious energy
but in a sense an offshoot through
another idea identity that now will
begin a rid of a time a little bit more
often in this way from this point
forward to interact with many of you in
this way this transference will
represent to some degree an ability for
the physiological channel to embody the
serious energy in a way that is Manifest
without the idea of the physical Channel
becoming as you say
taxed thus you will find that the idea
will come through a secondary conduit a
conduit that has been very used to
channeling the physiological ey the
energy of the serious connection for
many many years and thus in this way can
form a bit of what you would call a
buffer between the direct serious energy
and the idea of the physiological
Channel allowing the energy to come
through in a manifest way one
moment please sing your
please sing your
tongue and treat you sound to
sound to
you and
receive your Exo
Exo
we share with
you life we share with
life we share with
you brother brother sister sister
we share with you mother earth Mother
Earth we bring to you our love our joy
our Harmony our
sharing we rejoice in you
with what we for see your choices to be
now this time of your
time our time of our time so that we may
sing soon
together waterers of
life that flow within your ancient
dreams Waters of life that you
are are in our
are always as we share our x c x [Music] c
be
communicate as you say communicate to us
sing song with you
again we join Joy fully abound in and through
we join Joy fully abound in and through
the echo of your spirit your soul
envelops the waterers of Our Lives as we
intertwine in love with
you we we
sing your
soul we invite you to sing Our
Song we will sing together again this
again this
individual will from time to time
commence Communications with you and you
will find that this
individual will be most prominently of
theist since beginning this night of
your night the night of dreams for in
this way you will find that this
individual is what is termed in his
Society the
dreamers and in this way the
dreamers have been assisting you for
quite some time and in this way are
assisting in many of the ideas of your
dream realities communicating with you
sharing with you and also through the
idea of the bringing of new dreams into
your planetary spere specifically the
type of new dream you call physiological
birth this individual in time will
create an association with you more
strongly and more strongly
felt and as was pointed out to you
together you shall learn to sing each
other's songs in this way you will find that
songs in this way you will find that
this
individual and his physical counterparts
are with you always for it is
representative of the consciousness of
what you call one of your own Dolphins what
of the one you know to be the area you
call Y New
Zealand for therein as we have discussed
briefly lies the specific group you may
call them a club if you will but that is
a misnomer so to speak and they are
represented as the specific group of the
dreamers
contai that he able
to there was much blending and much of
that blending has to do with the ability
now to receive this
love we thank
[Music]
you um I just need to ask you um
oh when I was with the dolphin under the
water really
fast um what's happening what happened I
feel great the idea is that in your dream
great the idea is that in your dream
stat as we say in an astral form in an
outof body form you share many Endeavors
with many of the Dolphins and they with
you you swim together in the astral
seed always you are the two civilizations so
always you are the two civilizations so
to speak to use the term loosely upon
your planet you are the two Sensen
sees well Bashar you know I've I don't
really know anything about Atlantis and
I've never had a dream I've had water
dreams before but I've never had a dream
about ad doent i' I've FL in the water
and I've done all kinds of you know
anti-gravitational kind things but um as
far as swimming with the dolphins you
are now beginning to recognize those
that communicate with you whereas before
it was
aor is this going to um accelerate yeah
y
also it is an opportunity to bring that
dream into physiological Reality by
physically interacting with them and
entering their world in my dream in your
physical life
do [Music]
yes there will also
be in times to
come an understanding of another
grouping of
dolphins that is very active and may
become very much more interactive with
you in the area you call your
Japan sure hey I had an encounter with a
group of dolphins two weeks ago at Zumo
hey uh I swim really closely to them and
never came close to touch any of them no
I was a little with a friend that is all
right even though I know they really
love humans and they won't do anything
but I guess I was just overwhelmed in
sense and they left they came back they
played run for another half an hour and
they catch waves better than some of the
Surfers they have been at it for a while
[Music] long and they write the way gracefully
long and they write the way gracefully
and just when I said they going to hit
me and I'm gone
but together and there won't be
countries anymore oh there will not be
countries anymore in this way it is not
so much that all Races will completely
blend together you will still maintain
many of the distinctions right up to the
time where you no longer need to be
physical but it will be more Blended and
in terms of what you call politically it
will be completely Blended
again the idea is that you are forming
the foundations now for this and within
the cycle of the next 30 Years you will
begin to dissolve those borders
culminating in approximately 2 to 3
thousand of your years you will no
longer need to Incarnate upon your
planet anymore so what you're saying
you're going to survive the third world
war there will not be a third world
war you have already decided not to have
one appearances to the
contrary in fact the idea of much of
what is now as we have said coming to
the surface what appears to be what
appears to be an escalation of violence
in a sense is an escalation because you
now know it is safe and will not lead to
Annihilation you are getting it all out
in the open so to speak you are making
what was formerly hidden open what was
formerly covert overt so that each and
every member of your Society now has an
opportunity to decide for him or herself
is this what I really want in my
civilization or do I prefer to get
involved and change this idea that
Russian uh nuclear sub was another
example like Chernobyl to some degree
yes coming out of out of
hiding the idea that the attempt to
maintain secrecy now is what will pull
you down there
down there
we'll be in your turn a few moments
remaining for this interaction this
evening of your time
time
yes all right all right I'm just
wondering are are you the archetype for
this Yoda energy that came through in
that Star Wars uh not me
personally you got mean a still hooded
representation and your your quick wit
and all that uh that was that was
question number one uh more important to
me is this you are the
AR all of you all of
you wait One Moment One Moment One
Moment One let me fin um I'm trying to
figure something for myself here right
uh I read would you like Thum paper
and I'll use the all right I read a book
by
uiro called allies right and in it I
recognized some information pertaining
to
holographic projections and people doing
this in their homes with sensors and
their hands and all this that was the
same in information that came to me some
15 years ago in my head when the future
self idea came to me and now I'm able to
do certain things you know in TR honesty
in this the realm of this lifetime
accomplishing things with this future
self technique I do not have a conscious
connection with who I am that came back
to me to tell me all that that is all
right and I want to to know if that
information appearing the padian book
indicates that aspect of me there is
some of that in connection here okay is
the name sabot at
all yes but we also perceive that it has
much to do with what you would call
colloquially some very strong past
connections as well although there is a
flavor of the future Connection in it is
there any more you can give me in that second
exra this is the night of dreams you
will have what you need
you the male you have children and a
wife there are the eyes of children it
is not so much the idea Cally as you
understand it that you call a wife I
myself have not created physiological
children in this way in our society each
and every member is married to every
other member of the society there is not
the ritualistic idea of the wife but
that all females in this way are married
to all males and the vice versa [Music]
[Music]
create it on your
planet then you will be
there [Music]
everying a beautiful beautiful scene of
two dolphins standing
upright with um I don't know gold braids
in their mouths that lead to something
that looks like a chariot of some kind
where many many being on this Chariot I
I these are the
dreamers it is not a literal
interpretation but it is symbolic of
their energy and the connections that
they have to many other Civilizations
for do remember that the Dolphins have
been in communication telepathically
with many Civilizations for quite some
time all right anyway this this whole
scene seems to move it's I don't know
how to describe it anyway and it's a
beautiful turquoise and gold and it
seems to be underwater and it seems not
to be underwater we understand I'd like
to understand much of the serious energy
will be interpreted as aquatic to you
because in a sense they are energy
beings sixth level energy beings living
in an energy seed their Planet so to
speak is not a planet so much as it is a
sphere of energy it is represented to
you with the idea symbolically of a
planetary shape with white energy in
which they are embedded their
Consciousness is embedded but they also
know that their Consciousness is made of
the same energy so they are quite
homogenous with it and can in a sense be
anywhere and everywhere within it
towards the center is the increase of
the blue energy and towards the very
very very center is the black hole
doorway through which they communicate
and contact all levels of consciousness
and dimensionality as they explore all
that is the eye here is that since they exist
is the eye here is that since they exist
in the type of energy see you usually
equate that energy with the idea of the
Aquatic connection especially since they
have formed such a strong identification
with the dolphins upon your planet so it
is in the water and it is not at the
same time communication that has come from
time communication that has come from
them to your civilization in what you
call the past has usually rendered a
symbolic interpretation of them as an
amphibious [Music] [Music]
God sure
yeah would the I have had a vision all
right then you continue a long time that
um we would evolve on this planet to the
point where men and women would share
love with each other without
possessiveness without um
without um
expectations much as your civilization
knows uh and I see this accelerating
four density as we move into that what's
your prediction on I have no
prediction okay but I feel that is
happening yes faster and faster as we
release a lot of our need for negative
experience yes thank you thank
you that the Angelic or Kingdom will
have a a fixed play and bringing the new
phase of
civilization in very many ways but again
recognize that the big play they will
have in this way is in interacting with
your energy then they allow you to see
within yourselves the same Angelic
energy and to allow yourselves to know
therefore that if you are connected to
them you yourselves can create heaven on
Earth that's what I help us to bring
Heaven to Earth that would bring help to
change us from the human into the
Angelic being
okay after as we have said approximately
a couple of thousands of your years you
will no longer need to physically
incarnate upon your planet and you will
exist on what you call the Angelic level
Wonder but do recognize that some of the
representations of what you perceived to
be Angelic energy are actually
consciousnesses that in your terms have
never had any physiological experience
at all that's true in this way therefore
recognize that the level of angelic
experience that you will also as having
existed as physiological beings create
for yourselves will to some degree now
this is not in any way shape or form
meant as a comparison of better or worse
or any of that but simply recognize that
because of your particular ability to
have absorbed the experience of the
physicalized side of creation then the
Angelic beings you will be will be those
that in a sense will be quote unquote a
little bit more completed of an idea
since you will contain a particular
aspect of the universe that the or or
Angelic beings do not
contain thank you follow me thank you
thank you
very
much my what a pretty fall all
right I wanted to ask the significance
of um
significance okay you supply the meaning
okay um you speak often of blue and okay
um the electromagnetic energy vibration
of blue blue yeah um it comes to me a
lot and it come to me in my meditations
entities that I've been channeling uh
claim to be blue people uh blue entities
uh that the skin tone is blue this is to
some degree a lorean connection a what
lorean what is that it is what predates as a
what is that it is what predates as a
civilization what you call
[Music] Atlantis where there were in your terms
Atlantis where there were in your terms
blue skinned
individuals it represents a rising now
of your intuitiveness because you will
find that That civilization was almost
primarily instinctive and did not
operate analytically at all very
intuitive very in touch with nature and
so these formations and these
connections you are now making these
intuitive connections into the telepathy
and mentality of your civilization
accessing those levels put you back
squarely in touch with the existences
you had back then now that you can form
the idea of a connection you have gone
full cycle full circle coming within
physical reality in the Earth plane and
now creating the idea that accelerates
you out of physical reality in the Earth
plane so you bring the beginning quote
unquote and the ending together in the
same place and communicate with in a
sense your past
selves that just crazy
oh so exciting [Music]
[Music]
um two two past lives coming together I
mean I knew the the connection that they
spoke of when um when they had come
through the first time was that the
connection was made into Atlantis and
I Atlantis was the extension and
offshoot of Lura much the same way that
what you now call your president United
States of America was off of what you
call
England really need to know so that's
what the blue is and I I it is also
indicative of the telepathic Connection
in mentality to all in your
civilization I thought I saw also a um a
spaceship a couple um a nights ago it
was like um it was like a blue light that
like um it was like a blue light that
was up it was just um
I'm I'm real bad with directions whether
it was North or west of the of the North
Star and it was um it was blue and it
was like a ray of light shining down
from it and then probably West
West okay um the direction of
Loria it was
so I saw that I mean like I I I saw it
for a couple nights then the clouds and
stuff were there and I I wasn't able to
view it yes but I felt real strong
connections coming from from the light
yeah it was pointing the way to the
connection you are [Music]
making thank you thank you thank you
thank you wonderful
than you um I had a question concerning
porposes and um are they communicating
to us right now something about t about
a physiological ver yes that is as we
have said the idea is that they assist
you most often in your dreams and in the
realization of your dreams coming into
physical reality especially the
assistance with BS at this time which is
also an AR tourist connection and have
you I don't know if you've talked about
this already but um what exactly is it
has to do with underwater birs or you
are physiologically symbolizing some of
better connection in that way by
recognizing that some of the underwater
birthings may allow for different
advantag as you call it to be maintained
within the physical body of the child
that you give birth to and in this way
you will find that in times when you
have the idea of dolphin in the water
that you are giving birth within there
is some communication immediately
between the Dolphins and the child that
allows them to acclimate telepathically
to the environment much more quickly and
much more smoothly in this way however
recognize that all you need to do is
call in your imagination the idea of the
Zin energy when you are giving birth
anywhere and you will surround yourself
if you are willing and let them surround
you with the energy of the support that
the sea provides and the entire idea if
you also let the child be of assistance
in its own birth will be a supportive
one that will involve absolutely no pain
how do you how do you the
chance is that a communication simply
know that you are in communication with
that child and that this whole thing is
not on your
shoulders you do not have to bear the
brunt of the entire idea that is the
only thing that causes the
pain is there something about the
underwater birth besides the telepathic
communication with dolphins that enable
some sensitive
areas physically oh yes yes you see in
this way recognize that the child is
using less oxygen more of it is going
into the
brain you follow me yes I
do allows the child to maintain an
easier rate a slower pace of a
climatization it is in your terms simply
and most obviously less traumatic so
what is the outcome of of that in terms
of the way a child would develop a more
relaxed individual a more centered
individual and also an individual more
in touch and sensitive to other
Communications around them in the sea in
which they
exist now the idea of the underwater
birth is does not mean that every single
one of you should run out and have your
children underw and every person will feel when
underw and every person will feel when
they are so attracted and so inclined
when that is necessary for a while it is
not necessary for all and it may never
become completely necessary for anyone
but in this way it is one symbol to draw
yourself into more immediate and
intimate connection with the other
civilization upon your planet that is
willing to be a resistance in those
birthings and depart and impart some of
their ecstasy to the entire idea so as
we have said no matter what situation
you find yourself within call upon that
assistance and you will have that love
and the love will support the entire
event all right thank you sure
sure um I once worked with um some
people who were representing that they
worked with underwater birth but they
were one was a con man and two were were
not really doing it and um at the time I
really wanted to work with some people
and learn from them about underwater but
I love um reading about it I love have
given yourself an opportunity to
recognize when Integrity is being
applied to this idea and when it is not
for this recognition will also serve you
in what you call the
future for the idea of the maintenance
of Integrity is as you say of Paramount
importance when dealing with the dolphin
Consciousness at this time we will
extend to you once again our
appreciation in allowing us to
experience the unconditional love of
your Consciousness for you are a gift to
us and all that is in the willingness to
express the fastest of the
multi-dimensional crystal that you are
uniquely your own in this way we remind
you that this is night of dreams and
this goes for the entire idea of moving
into fourth B this is life of dreams
this is dreams that we share together
forever we thank you and extend our
unconditional love to you
all we will see you in your in many
different ways you will see us in many
different ways no matter what the
symbology the energy of all that is the
energy of the association the energies
of the Dolphins your own higher energies
your own guides your own assistants your
own energy is all accessible to you
through the doorways of your
dreams thank you for allowing us to love
you aond good night good night
[Music]
been go one [Music]