All right, out. How are you all this
evening of your time to create time to
engage? Allow us to begin this interaction, this
Allow us to begin this interaction, this
evening of your time with a reminder of
the idea of what you may refer to as
individual purpose. In this way, the idea we have
purpose. In this way, the idea we have
discussed it many times.
Fundamentally, foundationally, what you generally refer
foundationally, what you generally refer
to as purpose can be represented in a
few ways in your mentality, a few ways
from your point of view as a
physiological being.
Now you may find that from time to time
many of you have asked yourselves or
other individuals many times you have
asked us well what is my purpose in
life. Now recognize that within any given life
Now recognize that within any given life
that you live, you can create many
so-called purposes, many so-called
avenues, many so-called forms of
expressing the you that you are. And
each and every one of these different
forms, each and every one of these
different methods of expressing yourself, whether
methods of expressing yourself, whether
it be the idea you may call a
project, whether it be the idea you may
call a
service, all of these expressions of
yourself are the various political goals
and/or purposes you create in your life.
In this way they can be represented by a
specific series of
circumstances with an observable
beginning, middle and end as you say. It
can also simply be that the purpose can
be the methodology itself that you apply
the way you go about doing the things
that you do in
life. These can all be represented by
the word in your language that you call
purposes in life. But we recognize that
generally speaking when you ask the
question, well, what is my purpose in
life? You are usually referring to this
idea on a much more foundational level.
Now, I've shared with you many times
this idea of foundational purpose and it
is a very simple thing. Although you
will find that because of the society
you have created yourselves to be, many
of you will usually spend a great deal
of time searching for this purpose in
life, seeking it out, becoming perhaps
many times frustrated and tired and not
finding it, confused, disoriented, upset
and sad, despondent about not finding
this purpose in your life. Well, what is
the purpose? Why am I here?
First of all, first of
all, recognize and please do
remember everything is a choice. Yes, you chose
everything is a choice. Yes, you chose
to be where you are. You chose to be
born. So, first and foremost, allow
yourself to recognize that you made a
decision to be physical. You knew what
you were doing when you made that
decision. And whether you have conscious
recollection of it or not, you still do
know what you're doing. So at least
begin by relying upon the assurance and
the trust that you are doing whatever it
is you are doing for a reason. It is not
pointless. It is not aimless. It is not
so scattered as it may appear to be in
the illusion of the typical reality you
may have bought into.
Recognize that the idea therefore of
what you may refer to as the
foundational fundamental purpose of your
life is to simply be the person you have
designed yourself to be. It is no more
complex than that. The idea is as all of
you have had a saying for a very long
period of time in your society, well,
you only have one life to live.
Well, now reincarnation notwithstanding
this is true. You as the you you are now
only have one life to live. Even though
the soul that you are may experience
many lifetimes, each and every one of
those lifetimes is unique and a distinct
expression of the overall soul that you
are. Therefore, recognize that since you
have never been this you before, since
you will never be this you again, the
foundational reason for this life, the
fundamental purpose for this life is to
fully be the you you chose to be. That's
it. Period.
everything else, any way, any method,
any point of view, any methodology of
experiencing and expressing the idea
fully who you chose to be in this life
is up to you as the physiological
consciousness. The idea is that the
choice was made by the higher self and
that simply the fact that you are
present in this physical reality. That
is almost almost the entire extent of
what you usually refer to as
predestination. Just the fact that you
are here. There may be some generalized
here. There may be some generalized
themes, some thematic avenues that may
also be representative of the overall
predetermined reality decided upon by
you when you were the higher self in a
non-physical realm before you became
physically born. But they are only
generally represented in your life as
overall h the specifics of how you go
about living the life and the themes
that you find yourself exploring within
it are completely up to your
determination as a physiological being.
If you experience these ideas of life
positively, negatively, quickly,
negatively, quickly,
slowly, in this way, with friends, in
this way alone, as you may say, any way
you choose to experience is your
choosing, is yours. But the idea simply
is that whatever you decide to do, do it
fully. That's the foundational purpose
of this life. Now, of course, to the
higher self, there is no judgment imposed in
self, there is no judgment imposed in
all essence upon what it is you do
decide to do. And even if you choose to
experience the idea of
lacklusterness, boredom and mediocrity,
as you may call these ideas in your
life, then to the higher self, well, at
least you are doing boredom and the
mediocrity in a full way.
The idea simply and foundationally is to
recognize that since you are a unique
expression and a unique facet of the
multi-dimensional crystal of all that is
just be fully aware of that fact and
living to your full potential is the
actual fundamental fulfillment of the
purpose of your life. That means it's
completely wide open. You have complete
and utter freedom of choice as to what
you wish to experience in this
life. You follow me?
Now the
idea we have discussed also many
times of the expansion of your individuality.
of the expansion of your individuality.
expansion even beyond physical reality
in more and more and more of yourself in
what you may locally refer to as higher
and higher and higher plains of
vibratory existence may still for quite
some time involve the seeming point of
view that you are familiar with now as
the identity you know yourself to be.
Even as you expand and become more and
more and more blended with all the other
remnants, all the other portions, all
the other fragments of yourself, you the
you are now will still tend to see that
blending taking place from the point of
view you are used to thinking of
yourself as. Now, paradoxically, this is
true for every single point of view you
are in terms of every single life you
live. Each and every light as it expands
will tend to think of the blending and
the integration and the expansion as
occurring from its point of view. So no
fragment loses its individuality while
paradoxically it becomes blended into
more and more and more of the whole. You
follow me? This is the holographic
nature of creation. Each and every
point, each and every light, each and
every being, each and every
consciousness within creation contains
the whole. And therefore there is no
reason for each and every point to have
to lose its individuality to blend. But
a gaining full expression of its
individuality is what will allow the
blending between all individuality to
take place while at the same time
retaining the essence the uniqueness of
each particular point of view. Because
every single point of view is equal to
every other single point and will never
be wiped out or erased in the overall
acceleration of the blending and
integration of yourself as a higher and
higher and more integrated more expanded
consciousness and follow along. Uh-huh.
Now, we have also discussed from time to
time the idea. Well, all right. Now, I
recognize to some degree. Oh, I have a
purpose just to be in my life. But, oh,
but what is the purpose of all of this
to begin with? What is the purpose of
all that is? What is the purpose of the
infinite? What is the purpose of God if
you wish to call it that? All right.
Now, we have approached this from one
particular point of view. add this
evening of your time and this
interaction. We will also approach it
from another point of view. The point of
view we have already generally taken is
the fall await and this is simply one
way to look at it is not the right way.
It's not the wrong way. This is simply
one way. Purpose that idea you call purpose
way. Purpose that idea you call purpose
is one of the infinite creators
creation. So the infinite creator is not
subject to purpose. Purpose is subject
to infinite creation. What this
basically colloally means is that that
which existed before purpose was created
doesn't need a purpose to keep existing.
It exists because it does. Period. Now,
if that is something that you feel at
this time you maybe cannot wrap your
mind around, that is all right. It is
one point of view from a particular
dimensional frame of reference. However,
we can find that there is a way to state
the same idea from a reference point
that may allow you a little more let it
say meet in the matter. Now it may still
seem to be in a sense just as
paradoxical but at least you will allow
yourself perhaps to recognize the
selfsupporting aspect of this next
particular definition. For the
self-supporting aspect is really what
the fundamental idea of the infinite
creation actually is all about. It is
that which creates itself to be in this
way. Therefore, it can be said that all
right what is the purpose of creation?
What is the purpose of the infinite?
What is the purpose of God to begin
with? Why? Why? Why? Why? Why? Why? All
right. Another way of stating it
therefore is just as simple. The purpose
of the infinite creator is to
create you. Each and every one of you
and all of the beings, all of the
individualized consciousnesses within
creation are all of the purposes that
the infinite has created. And that was
its purpose and still is to continue the
creation of all purpose within creation
itself. You all follow along. Okay.
Now, once again, but from a slightly
different point of view, because you are
never the same you you were a moment
ago, neither are we. We will remind you
before the interactions this evening of
your time begins to take it to heart and
from the point of view real
eyes that in this understanding of your
own expansion of self in the exploration
of all that you desire to be many of you
again simply because of the habits in
your society this is not a right this is
not a wrong this is not meant in any way
shape or form and morally but simply
because of what you have created your
society to be. Many of you still think
in separated ways. And even when you are
forming connections to things, you still
think of them in terms of connections of
separate things rather than one
homogeneous all that is event one and
the same idea. I have reminded you many
times that everything, every
individualized thing is the same one
thing manifesting in all different
aspects and points of view that it can.
Everything and everyone is the same one
and every one thing. The idea to
remember perhaps if you wish to you're
not have to but if you wish to is that
it is not so much in your pathway of
expression and understanding all the
different expressions of consciousness
that you are. It is not as we have said
that consciousness is actually in the
body. Consciousness does not exactly
except in the illusion of physical
reality reside in the body. The body
resides in consciousness.
understand that difference and it will
have a very profound difference in the
way you experience your physiological
life because then you will recognize
that everything everything that you
experience is within the same ocean of
consciousness and therefore you all are
a part of the same one thing and
therefore everything you see is very
isol
Oh, thank you very much. Sherry,
a dear friend of mine has just left the
physical place and he has shown up several times
place and he has shown up several times
in dreams, right? And last night, we're
sure of voice, but I started to come out
of sleep three different times and
another friend and this friend Jimmy
said not yes. And that happened three
times. And the fourth time they said,
"Now it's complete and now you can be
awake." Then I awoke. And I'd like I
would like to know more of what that's
about. You are utilizing them. They are
acting as reflections to you to lure you
into higher states of being. They were
simply giving you time to adjust and
acclimate to the i.e. of the out of body
experience you are having. So that this
can be something that can occur more and
more often in a conscious state. You
simply had not yet absorbed all the
energy vibrations you needed to absorb
to allow you to feel that a completion
of the communication between you had
occurred to allow certain ideas to
settle within the different levels of
your consciousness to take hold. Take
firm hold in the way you truly do want
them to and they were simply regulating
the timing for you because from their
point of view they have a little bit
better overview of how that sort of
timing and integration is regulated if
you follow me. Yes. In this way,
recognize at this time that it is more
and more probable that many more of you
will be creating conscious remembrance
of the out of body experiences and the
expansions of consciousness that you
have. Even though you all do it almost
all the time when you are asleep anyway,
whether you remember or not, but is now
your opportunity to blend the dream
reality and the physical reality as
simply different aspects of the same
reality. Then you can begin to live your
dreams and merge very smoothly, very
easily between the physical and dream
reality back and forth, back and forth
with no discernable borders. They were
simply allowing you to get a taste of
that idea. And the amount of time they
were allowing you to take is what serves
you best in terms of your own timing.
Thank you. Oh, for sure.
Yes. Do you in your society experience
consciousness between physical lives uh
in that period of transition or is it as
it seems to be for most of us uh an
unconscious process? Do you mean that
while we are in our physical lives do we
have a memory of when we were not?
Because everyone experiences
consciousness when they are actually in
between the physical lines. Whether you
know it not in your body now is another
idea. Yeah. Well, then do you guys know
it now in your body? Yes. And when and
where we wish to or need to. Okay. Okay.
Is that very much different from what
we're experiencing here? Is it a matter
of choice and awakening and timing and
what have you or it's always a matter of
choice? It is also particularly in your
society a matter of making the
determination to do so because you are
finding that in order for many of you to
do so smoothly, you must unteach
yourself many of the things you have
bought into as a child.
For example, the idea that you cannot
exist outside your physical body.
For example, the idea that to leave your
body is to physically die
period and not be able to come back. You
have a very deeply ingrained fear of
death in your society. That in and of
itself is the major what we may loosely
call barrier to the ease of remembering
that we go in and out all the time.
It is that fear only the
fear but you have as a society many
fears getting in touch with that there
are many methodologies that are
available to you on your planet very
clear very concise among them paramount
though we rarely recommend will be those
that are part and parcel of the
individual you call
Monroe these will be very assisted in
allowing individuals to get in touch of
all the ideas of their fears, their
beliefs and get into the relaxed state
necessary to be able to project
consciously, easily,
smoothly. In thank you in line with that
is these techniques that are called in
our world here soul travel and all that
is that uh the same type of thing or is
it the creation of our own mind?
It is the change of focus and the
perspective of your
consciousness from being projected into
the material world into the non-material
world into the less physical
world. Mind what you call mentality is
utterly and completely only a product of
the physical material
world. Okay?
It is created out of the electromagnetic
field of the physical universe. When
consciousness intersects with that
field, it creates what you call
mind. But your consciousness exists
apart from mentality. Mentality is
created by consciousness. Consciousness
is not created by mentality.
The illusion of consciousness in a sense is
illusion of consciousness in a sense is
represented. Consciousness is
represented by the illusion of mentality
in physical reality. But mentality is
not what gives birth to
consciousness. It is only the
representative in physical
reality. You follow me? Thank you.
Therefore, you can recognize that it is
very simple to detach so to speak from
the point of view of physical
materiality and move your focus around.
That is actually what you are doing. Now
there are many levels that are
semi-material so to speak the astral
plane and so forth that still make it
seem as if you function within a type of
body when you are out floating around
doing whatever you are doing when you
are having this out of body experience
but that is still in a sense a type of
creation to some degree of a remnant
mentality. Consciousness itself when it
moves around does not really move
around. It is that the universe you
perceive more accurately actually moves
around you.
Awareness it is just awareness.
Point of view is all it is. It is all
everything is we mean that literally physically.
is we mean that literally physically.
Yes.
Question. Last week when we were talking
with uh our dolphin friends, the
dreamers, one of the questions that was
asked was whether the uh dolphins were
hurt at marine land when somebody rode
them as no hurt, but sometimes it was an
emotional pain of captivity. Thanks.
Based on that, I got very excited and
came up with a concept of creating an
open sea uh marine land in which we'll
just build it on the surface of the
ocean outside the uh surf line and
invite the developers to come in and
share
for starting on a bunch of designs,
integrated some of the projects. Um what
do you what do you think of that? How do
you like that? Well, I'm very excited.
So
much do we get a chance to talk to
dreamers tonight? Not this evening as
far. Okay. Well um I want to propose
this particular sequence of events in
which we uh um get some sharing as to uh
what uh he thinks of this idea what the
developing culture thinks. Oh they will
be very excited as well of course
because they are very willing to
interact with you in any way shape or
form. You are willing to co-create such
an interaction. Anything that will in
your terms make it easier for that to
occur will be very exciting to them.
Wonderful. Well, do you feel that we can
then start to set up some uh actual
sharing where we can physically meet at
a location in Sher Practically? Oh yes.
As you have said your maloo area will be
very conducive to this. And we can we
set up a specific time and location.
Oh, early morning will also or just
before in a few hours just before what
you call dusk late afternoon. And when
can I physically when will you be
willing to channel dreamer again so that
I can talk with them and share that? Oh,
recognize I in that way do not channel
dreamer. Dreamer is channeled by the physical
Dreamer is channeled by the physical
channel and it is simply conducive of
the time. There is much gathering this
night of your time in different ways
other than the specific interactions
with dreamer that is necessary. Although
of course as always every single night
you interact with the dreamers. Of
course. Of course because they are and
you are sharing the same dreams now. You
are beginning to interact in that way.
I'm very excited that ancient can go
forward in this particular project. Then
go and interact with them physically.
Okay, I'll do that and we'll do an
interview next week for us to further
me.
Well, I'll be here. All
right. But in this way, recognize you do
not really need to communicate with the
dreamer to allow yourself to simply go
and interact with the dreamers that are
off your own shoreline. No, I know that.
But to articulate specific agreements to
a sequence of events that That needs to
be done. Yeah. But this will be done by
your actual physiological interactions
with the zoomers you have access to.
Good. You will start to recognize the
patterns. You will simply recognize them
by observing their actions.
And you will know that I do. Good. Oh,
thank you very much.
What can I do to make my work
environment more to be more successful
in my work right now? More enjoyable.
more enjoyable. Does that mean that what
you are doing is not what excites you
the most? It does not excite me the
most. Why are you doing it? Because
right at this point it seems to be the
thing that that gives me the freedom to do
that that gives me the freedom to do
some of the other things I want to do.
Oh, I see. So you are a
conditional connection in that way
rather than an unconditional connection.
I guess so. All right. What is it that
truly excites you the most? And do you
realize in what you have just said that
you are saying that the thing that truly
excites you the most cannot support you?
Well, one thing that excites you the
most is the artwork that I've just done,
but I need some money to to start
producing it. Oh, takes a while to
produce. Uh the man is going the factory
is going to produce it. Okay. But who
says in this way that the money has to
come from
you? Who says that you cannot attract an
individual or a situation that will
either bring you the money necessary or
an individual who will simply become
involved with you to such a level that
they will in this way out of their own
excitement of involvement provide what
is necessary.
Why only focus upon that one way or then
nothing can be done if you do not see it
happen exactly the way you think it
should before something can happen. It
is not that it cannot happen that way.
But why insist on that particular path
when there may be many many ways that
the ability to get it done could happen
in your life. I'm looking at as many
ways as I can. I I think I have it is
not so much that you have to look for
them. The idea is that when you are
acting in any given moment upon what
excites you the most at that moment, you
will automatically attract yourself
co-incidentally into the situation that
will allow you to be able to continue in
the overall idea that excites you the
most. What this basically means is that
all right you have the overall idea that
excites you the most. But let us say as
we have used the analogy many times that
you are simply walking down your street
and you are on your way to where you
think you should be going relative to
what you think you should be doing to
connect you into the ide but at that
moment an offer comes up or a situation
comes up that at that moment is actually
more exciting than what you are
immediately doing. Take it. It is the
excitement behind it. No matter whether
it appears on the surface or not to be
connected to what you ultimately want to
do. It is the excitement behind that
situation that lets you know it is
connected. That's what excitement is
for. When you follow it, you will
coincidentally find yourself walking
through a scenario and a situation
interacting with exactly who you need to
interact with to lead you to where you
thought you were going to begin with.
I I guess my problem with doing that is
that
there goes that old hearing again. density deafness.
I assume there was a word in there, but
it wiped out.
I didn't hear it.
Now, what was it you said?
Um, as I brought up these various
approaches and started working on these
various approaches, I keep
I keep hearing from people that if you
do that, your idea is going to be stolen
or this is going to be stolen and you
can't and you choose to believe them, of
course, over your own feelings.
Well, then what do you expect to have
happen in your life with all of that
quote unquote
confusion? It is an opportunity to
co-fuse with more of yourself, but in a
positive way. does not have to be
negative
confusion. You can use them as
barometers. You can use them as
reflections to allow yourself to guide
yourself, not to allow them to insist
that it must be done such and such a
way. If that way truly conflicts with
what you know to be true for
you, why buy into it?
It is an opportunity to simply allow
them to allow you to recognize what is
true for you within you by seeing what
it is they are saying and making that
comparison not a judgmental one not an
invalidating one but that comparison
between where they stand and where you
stand that simply allows you to know
that you are always on your own perfect
path.
So if you truly understand that those
particular situations that they are
defining is not something that you need,
they will not
occur. If you follow what excites you,
you will only because you know that
following what excites you creates a
positive reality for you. You will only
attract yourself to individuals and
attract individuals to you who will not
steal the idea from you because that
won't serve the definition of the
reality you know you are. Anything that
does not fit the vibrational reality you
truly 100% trust yourself to be cannot
happen in your life. It is simple
physics. It can't be in your reality if it's not
It can't be in your reality if it's not
of the same
vibration. You follow this?
So be the vibration you know yourself to
be in 100% trust and then the only
situations that can occur in your life
will be those reflective of the reality
you truly are living.
That's great. Oh, yes. All right. Sounds
great. Oh, yes. Which are easier said
than done all.
Every morning I wake up exactly that
way. By 4:00 I feel. I see. Then why not
take a nap?
You're only recognizing your natural
connected cycle. As we have said,
approximately around the idea to 4 p.m.
is when you actually
naturally make connections in the sleep
state, in the dream state. Whereas the 2
to 4 a.m. is when you are actually more
naturally active energy wise, although
your society forces you into the
opposite role.
If you find yourself ebbing, as you say,
on your energy about that time, then
make your
connection, realign
yourself and
continue on your way. Do not think that
it is an indication that you have been
beaten. Oh, I woke up so positive this
morning. Now I am failing miserably. I
cannot seem to
maintain this energy level. Even if you
think you have to try to maintain that
energy level, that gets very tiring. It
is a natural automatic maintenance. It's
not something you have to try to
do. Go with your
love. That is the automatic maintenance
of your energy level. Do not insist. No,
no, no. I am tired. I have to stay
awake. No, no, no. I am awake. I have to
go to sleep. Then you are fighting your
own natural pattern and that of course
is very
tiring. You follow it. Is this a
let yourself walk into the situation
that will act now upon whatever
opportunities are available for you to
act upon that do excite you to the same
degree. That's all you have to do. Push
those buttons. Everything else that
follows is automatic. But you have to
push those buttons.
They are very clean.
People show you. Hi. Um, hi.
I just like to share a couple of things.
All right.
Especially uh with what the lady just
was speaking about in attracting money.
All right. In attracting abundance.
Thank you. Opportunity.
Um the last few years I've been
experiencing or I've chosen to not
attract as much money as
as I now am attracting. Basically, the
last month or so, I've just
totally allowed
myself to experience that. and
expanded the idea of yourself. And so
your physical reality has to expand to
match the idea you now are. Yes. Right.
And I've been practicing the situations
that have been working in perfect
synchronicity as you what a coincidence.
Um so that's just my sharing on that. My
thank you. Very loving sharing. Very
loving reflection. Continue. One other
thing. Um, you spoke about anger. You
gave a very interesting definition of
anger. And
a client came to see me about 3 or 4
days ago and
before I gave her a session, I do body
work. She talked uh much about the anger
that she was experiencing with a
particular individual. And I saw this
developing into just more and more
expression of anger which was fine. That
was her expression. Hi. And I remembered
what you said about anger and it gave me
the opportunity to express myself and I
asked her if she knew what anger was.
Okay. And I gave her the definition that
is now my truth of what anger is which
is that it's an instant alignment with
who you are. Hey
And as soon as she had been experiencing
some intense pelvic pain when she came
in and that was one of the reasons why
she'd come to see me and as soon as I
told her what my truth about anger was,
the pain vanished instantly. She allowed
herself to see that the anger was no was
no longer necessary to create that pain.
Validation of the alignment,
right? Thank you very much for the very active
Thank you very much for the very active
reflection of understanding that shows
graphically as you say that all
pain spiritual, mental, emotional and
physical is only the result of the
invalidation and therefore the
separation of a portion of yourself from
the rest of all that you are.
You remove your own
support. That is what causes
pain. Realignment with all that will only be
Realignment with all that will only be
true in that way without invalidating
any portion of yourself will not create
a conduit that experiences
time. For then there is infinite
willingness. And where there is infinite
willingness, there is infinite action
and infinite ecstasy.
Thank you.
Sorry. I'm talking about in terms of
bringing these things into
reality. Um, and I and I believe these
things if I don't put them into my own
mind, they will not exist in my own
consciousness. But I understand that these things
But I understand that these things
exist. I and it's because of, you know,
I see them every day. I see them exist
in other people. Then they must be
within you. You cannot see. You cannot
perceive what you do not contain.
Well, it's like I understand that
there's a hepatitis B virus, but I don't
ever perceive it coming to me. When I
say you contain it, this does not mean
that you have to manifest the
potential. But if you can see it, you do
contain the potential. You do contain
the idea of the ability to relate to
that reality to be that reality. Now
perhaps if that simply does not
represent the focus of your life, then
it does not have to be
realized or manifested. But you still
can earn the vibration. It is still
potentially within the holographic view.
What if I don't want it there for me? It
does not have to manifest in your
physiological world. But I can be aware
of it still. Of course. Again, the
library analogy can be of assistance.
You can go into your library. You can
sit down and you can read every single
book on the shelf. The positive ones,
the negative ones, the joyful ones, the
scary ones. You can scare yourself.
Silly. It does not matter how many of
those books you read in the library. The
one you make the conscious determination
to check out of the library is the one
that becomes your physical manifested
reality. Read all the books you want
while you're in the library. Just
because you're aware of the stories
doesn't mean that those stories have to
represent your autobiography.
So if I if I don't believe these things
will ever exist in my consciousness
personally. They exist in your
consciousness. They do not have to be
manifested in the expression of your
physical life. The idea is to simply
recognize that because it does exist in
your physical consciousness. Then it
gives you an opportunity to be of
service to perhaps an individual who may
be manifesting that in their physical
reality. Because if you had no way of
cognizing what it was, you couldn't be
of service to them at all. Yeah. That's
what I I tell them to visualize
themselves as the perfect pure being
that they are. Okay, that is one way.
Then this will not exist within their
reality. Okay. But recognize many
individuals will believe that it does
need to exist. And how do I help them
visualize themselves as pure and free of
their allow them to be in touch first of
all with the idea that they have created
it. They have chosen it. Now this does
not mean analytically consciously that
they sat down and said all right I am
choosing to have
hepatitis. What it means generally is
that they choose things many times out
of reactive fear. The idea that if they
fear a certain idea can happen in their
lives, then there is a manifestation
that will be
more than capable of manifesting in
their life to represent the idea that
they fear in whatever represents it in
the way that will allow them to see what
they need to see to face their fear. So
first and foremost allow them to
understand they chose it. Whether they
created out of fear or conscious choice
does not really matter much. But the
idea is that if they know they chose it,
then they can allow themselves to
understand the idea of how does it serve
them. All right, you have this idea.
What have you learned from it? Look at
it from a positive point of view. What
has it taught you positively? Once you
allow yourself to understand the reason
for why it is there and the lesson, the
reflection that you can glean from it,
then once you are willing to accept the
message easily, you will no longer need
the messenger to deliver the message in
that form and the messenger can
transform into something
else. Okay? If you understand that you
can glean positive meaning out of it. If
you only think it will lead to more
negative meaning, then the messenger
will usually only transform in a
negative way. I have a problem with you
have a what? Well, I have a situation
understanding the reality of it, but yet
I'm trying to keep it out of my own
personal physical. You do not have to
keep it out of your own physical
reality. Simply recognize that if you
simply know that the idea has no meaning
for you, that you are willing to
acknowledge any message that any portion
of yourself wishes to deliver to the
conscious, analytical, physical you, and
you are willing to accept that message
in the easiest possible manner without
having to have the messenger force it
upon you because you may be too stubborn
to pay attention, which is what many
diseases are about. that then you will
simply trust that you will receive the
message in the easiest possible manner
and won't ever have to get to the point
of forcing yourself to face it in that
way. So it's not a matter of having to
keep it away. It is a matter of
acknowledging that you will accept and
acknowledge anything that comes your way
because it is there for a reason. That
attitude is what paradoxically will only
allow positive manifestation to occur in
your life. Thank you. Well, thank you
very much for
Thank you. Um, last week I was
considering coming and I, if I put would
say it, um, went out and my girlfriend
went out
and, um, I was afraid to deal with what
it is that I came to talk to you about
tonight. All right. That was you then.
This is you now. A totally different
you. So, you now were not afraid of
coming. Well, I didn't want to stop me. That was
Well, I didn't want to stop me. That was
you then. Okay. So, what it was last
week, my friend was talking about um a
connection that we have. Um when we're
together, I tend to it tends to bring
out a lot more of my psychic ability.
All right. Okay. That's something that I
I enjoy and I can deal with and I
accept. Um Oh, you can deal with All
right. Well, I like it. Yeah. All right.
Thank you. Fine. But part of it, there
was something that happened. I had an
experience that is really holding me
back now. And I find that I'm resisting
a lot because I'm afraid of this
experience that I created. Why?
Because I feel Do you remember that
there is nothing nothing that you could
possibly discover about yourself and
every experience you discover something
in will be something about yourself.
There is nothing you could possibly
discover about yourself that is
intrinsically negative.
It will only add to the overall you that
you are and therefore by definition make
you more integrated and therefore by
definition less fearful.
Okay. I I don't totally accept that yet.
No, that's all right. I understand it
and it makes sense and I feel that
because of So, let me tell you what
happened. Oh, what? Um, my friend was
channeling, and this is something that,
you know, we've talked about having her
do in my presence for quite a while. As
she was channeling, I was getting I I
was becoming fearful that something was
going to come, something negative was
going to get involved with this. And so,
and get me is what? All right. Now, one
moment. Back up a little bit again.
As you describe this
scenario, listen to and design your
terminology in a positive way because
then you will be assisting yourself as
you go
along. There is no energy that is
intrinsically fearful. No symbol and no situation has
fearful. No symbol and no situation has
any builtin meanings. Nothing means
anything. No symbols have intrinsic
meaning. There is
energy. You chose to interpret it in a
negative way. And so your reaction was a
fearful one. The energy was not a
fearful energy. You follow me? Yes, I do. Put
energy. You follow me? Yes, I do. Put
yourself squarely in the driver's seat.
When you illuminate these situations,
listen to what you are saying. What you
are saying completely reinforces what
you think you are
experiencing. Oh, better fearful energy.
If there truly was a fearful energy,
then no wonder you are afraid. But there
is no such thing as an intrinsically
fearful energy. There is simply energy.
You chose to interpret it in a negative
way and that created the reaction of
fear within
you. So do not bind yourself to the
situation in a negative way by creating
a terminology which will not let you
experience it any other way. Right? You
are only reinforcing what you say you
don't prefer. Right? Define your terms
clearly. [Music]
[Music]
Um what was I don't know how to say this
now. Yes you do. Um perhaps you are not
in the practice or the habit constructed
them in a positive way. But the idea you
will find and if you find yourself now
at a loss for word so to speak. It may
simply be because when you begin to
allow yourself to define the situation
clearly, you may find there is no longer
a problem to consider. Because all it
usually takes is a clear definition to
allow yourself to continue on and
recognize that what situation you
experienced was something you can grow
from. And it really carries no more
weight than you gave it in that frame of
mind you used to be within. with a new
frame of mind. What appeared to be so
real and so scary to you then now takes
on the proportions of a shadow and you
cannot even find it anymore.
Now, do you wish to continue with your
definition? Yeah, I'm going to try. I'm going to
Yeah, I'm going to try. I'm going to
Yes, I'm going to continue. Thank you.
All right, she loads quickly.
Okay. after my friend channelneled. Yay.
Um there was an energy that I was
feeling in the car. Um we were in the
car when when she was channeling and how
appropriate. Yeah.
And the energy what what
I interpreted as happening was the
energy was go came through me and a I
don't know what it was. It was an energy
went through me. Okay. was
um it was like for a split second at
that time what I felt
time what I felt
was when I'm not supposed to say fear.
Oh, you are not supposed or supposed to
do anything to say whatever you Okay.
And what I what I what I felt was that
it was we are not saying you do not feel
fear, right? We are simply saying there
is no intrinsically fearful energy.
Well, what I Yes. and and what was what
went through it was something very
familiar and something very frightening
to me. All right. And um what ever since
I was I can remember of being taken over
by something that somebody was going to
take me over and this is what I felt was
going to happen and it's and after that
it's like I felt that I was in a process
of growing and building and maybe
getting to
um to to move on and and grow and then
having that experience I felt myself
want to back off and not go any further
because of what It's a It's I don't know
what's going to happen and that is
really what I'm Oh. All right. That's
all right. Now, first of all, give
yourselves a pat on the back. Okay. All
Okay. All
right. Now, do you know
why you deserve a pat on the back?
I'm not sure. All right. I'll tell you.
You deserve the pat on the back because
you gave yourself a perfectly flawless
example that you're not going to move
any faster than you deem to be
comfortable. The idea that you were able
to quote unquote back away from it
should let you know, not in a judgmental
way of should, but simply is an
indication of the fact that you are
completely and utterly in control
because you have the ability to back
away. And therefore nothing by
definition really can force itself upon
you that you do not choose to
participate with in that illusionary
scenario.
Do you have a a suggestion as to
um a way of of moving forward and
getting and going past it of dealing
with this? May I ask you a question?
Yes. Did you hear anything about what I
just said? Yes. All right. Will you
repeat it to me? No. All right. I need
to listen to your tape. No, you don't.
I'll say it again if you wish.
All right. Yes. Oh, thank you. Are you
having a good time?
Sort of. All right.
When you encounter in a situation
something that allows you to choose to
back away from
it, the ability to back away from it
lets you know that you are in control
and you will never go faster than you
are comfortable going. You have your own
governor on the situation.
You will never proceed faster than you
are able to assimilate the ideas. That
in and of itself lets you know you are
in control. And knowing that lets you
know that you can proceed as quickly or
as slowly as you want, as you are
comfortable in doing. So the way to go
faster is to recognize that you are in
complete control and you will only ever
go as fast as is comfortable. And should
you come up upon that self-created wall
again and feel the fear, you will back
off and you will be just
fine. That is the way to know you can go
faster. By always knowing that should
you ever encounter that self-created
wall of fear, you will always be able to
back off and be just fine. That will
give you more confidence to go faster
and not back off as often.
Now, does that make some sense? Yes.
Thank you very much. Now
I will ask you to read it not in words
but in actions in your life.
All right. All right. Is up to you.
Thank you. Oh, thank you very much.
You that you. Thank you. Okay. Um, I
went with this woman, Jane Elman, who uh
I'm meeting last night of what's called
the summit organization. Okay. She told
me something about and I hadn't heard
about it prior to her telling me and I
thought I'd investigate as they do many
things. Okay. So, I'll be fine. Well,
that's the
thing. They they're perfectly nice
people. Basically young professional
people who are professional people
um they get together for um classes to
um for seminars and networking and um I
guess social reasons or whatever.
and you can only get in via a member.
So, I went with this woman and I liked
it. Um, but I really didn't have any
specific feeling as to whether I wanted
to become a member or not. But the way
it works is that they have kind of a
hard cell at the end where they sit down
with you and um just talk about why
you'd be interested in joining it and so
on and so forth. And I decided at the
time that it wouldn't be a bad idea if I
just put a deposit down. So I did and
they gave me a packet of information and
I got home and I started feeling really
bad about it. I
mean looking at it from a um I don't
know just a um not a practical but a
factual standpoint the worst that could
happen is that I pay them a certain
amount of money and I and I um undergo a
class and if I don't want to continue
with it I don't. That's the worst really
that could happen. But my reaction, my
emotional reaction was very I I began to
feel very upset. Not that these are bad
people or anything, not that anybody's
intent is really bad, but I felt it was
to me without judging myself, my
reaction, the degree to which I was
upset seemed too much, too extreme of a
situation. And I even woke up in the
middle of the morning very upset about
this. And other than the fact that maybe
I don't really want to spend the money
at this time and I feel like I was
pushed even though I made the choice to
join, I can't think of any reason why I
would be so upset about it. And I just
want to know if you could enlighten me
or I don't know. I'm finished now.
Recognize therefore in this
way that of course as with anything any
upset of course is being upset with
yourself and so in a sense that is a
self judgment otherwise you will not
experience the upset.
simply you oh let's put it very
you oh let's put it very
colloqually you are a being of high
energy you know well you met your match
didn't you and the idea in this way is that you
you and the idea in this way is that you
now have ingrained within you the belief
that you came up short
in what way in seeing an expression of
energy equal to your own. You felt that
you backed out of your integrity and
complied where you did not wish to and
therefore feel as if you made yourself
unequal by them presenting the idea in
their manner as a contest of
will. You were impressed with that level
of definition, that level of energy. And
in this way, because you made the
decision, you made not because you
actually made the decision, but because
of the way you allowed yourself to buy
into their definition of your having
made that decision, you feel you
succumbed in a battle of
wills, in a matching of energies. You
now consider yourself to be less, then
to be more powerful. That has really
nothing to do with the overall basic
scenario, but that is what we perceive
within you. So you are simply angry and
upset with yourself for letting your own
self down, so to speak,
and not simply maintaining your
integrity along the same lines without
succumbing to the idea of what you may
refer to as their particular approach or
game.
Um, I agree with that. I what came to
mind and you didn't actually mention it
is that perhaps they represent me
um or my attracting them right
represents um
me say on a more expanded level like me
maybe not being comfortable like I'm on
on a conscious level I really want my
exterior world to expand and to feel
what to match what I feel is my interior
world. And maybe they represent on the
outside an
a symbol of my expansion. Represent a
symbol of the expansion in a way that
you do not prefer to
show the idea of what you pick up on as
the quote unquote forceful need of
someone to comply.
Now again like anything it is a tool and
valid if you wish to use it and in this
case you are using it. You are using it
to get in touch with your own
understandings of your own
integrity and to realize that you can
stand firm without being what you see in
your mind then to be obstinate.
Standing firm means
obstacles. That is what you are
exploring now with them.
now with them.
And so you are availing yourself of
their services in that way.
Fair trade.
All right.
Do what you will. Thank you.
Thank you. One moment. One moment.
Uh you before you were talking um go
before you were talking. Do not deprive
these wonderful people of your gift of
sharing from which they can all see
reflections of themselves and grow and
expand. Okay, that's loud enough. No.
Nope. Really? Okay. Stand up.
Really? Okay. Stand up.
[Music]
No shy people allowed. Okay. Um, hey.
Okay. Um, a few weeks ago I had an
experience and you were sharing about um
how to create um how pain a painful
situation may come into your life and
you can transform it once you learn the
lesson from the
from it. Well, I had sprained my ankle
and uh I was looking at okay, what did I
uh I was looking at okay, what did I
need to learn from this experience? And
you know, they were telling me it was
going to take a week, two weeks before
my ankle was going to heal and that was
totally unacceptable to me. And
um I did some exploring and I got to see
that what I needed to understand was the
word balance kept coming into my life.
So I kept Okay. because I was off
balance and so therefore I had recraed
ankle and once I learned that um by
Monday I went to a healing service and I
was healed and I was walking around and
I still have and my ankle spine. Very
good. So I believe this and I'm real
excited about this process. Oh goodness.
I want to thank you for it.
[Music] um getting into the balance situation.
um getting into the balance situation.
I'm still exploring
[Music] um the areas of my life that are out of
um the areas of my life that are out of
balance and um an enjoyable endeavor.
Yes, it is. I'm I'm real excited about
my process right now. Thank you. This
transformation is really incredible. Um
I had
I'll let that [Music]
If it were incredible, you would not
have experienced this. It is obviously
very credible.
Okay. Yes. Wonderful.
[Music] Um my I do not mean to make you walk on
Um my I do not mean to make you walk on
a trail. Simply speak freely.
Um the process that I'm going through
has um tended to make the process that you
um tended to make the process that you
are the process that I am. Thank you.
Okay. And
um I have to say this. I'm in a group on
um on Thursday and a
woman shared that she was experiencing
that she found out that she created well
she didn't say she created diabetes in
her life but she had shared that her
father had it and it was almost a
release because she had feared it all
her life getting it and so I shared well
obviously you created it and I was
looked at by the rest of the members of
the group as being totally heartless and
here this woman is really upset and into
are paid. We are not done.
And there is a method of delivery
[Music] that can allow them to understand what
that can allow them to understand what
you are saying without the feeling that
they are being attacked. Because do not
forget they are already deeply within
the belief of victimhood. And therefore,
anything anyone says that is not very
specifically directed with a lot of
unconditional love will be interpreted
as yet another reinforcement of their
victimhood and therefore you will be
considered an attacker. You hold
heartless cruel person.
Yeah. I said I was feeling a lot of love
and I didn't know how to express what I
was feeling and still stating the fact
that she created this which is what I
believe. Oh. Oh,
you strong strong creative person. I love
strong strong creative person. I love
you very much for creating this
manifestation in your life for it will
be something you will learn a beautiful
thing beautiful discoveries about
yourself within. I support you. I will
assist you in any way, shape or form to
allow that idea to transform into
something else if you do not prefer the
manifestation it is in. But I salute you
and I congratulate you for the courage
and the strength to have that
manifestation in your life. For it means
you are ready to face much about
yourself. I congratulate you. How about
that?
Then at least if they say what do you
mean they will generally
be off their guard and will be
interested in what further you have to
share rather than immediately invoking a
defensive position. All you need to do is get into
position. All you need to do is get into
love within yourself and truly express
that love. You will be motivated to say
what you need to say. Let it move
you. You know that when you experience
an individual speaking from the heart,
you say it was a moving
experience. Let it move you as well. And
then what you need to say will very
easily come out. And they will also be
moved for they will sense the clarity
and the love within you in what you are
saying. They will know that what you are
saying is not being said in a
invalidating judgmental way. They will
be open. You will have allowed them to
share their vulnerability with you and
that is what will allow them to become
strong because complete vulnerability is
infinite strength.
share your vulnerability with them but
not in a victimhood way.
I don't understand not in a victimhood
way. I don't want to grow up as a victim
and I in turn don't want to support
their victimization. That is why if you
share the idea through love, you can
allow them to begin to understand that
their concept of vulnerability does not
have to mean weakness.
or victimization that your concept of
vulnerability is the willingness to be
open to support them in what they are
doing completely, utterly, totally. You
believe in them even if they do not
believe in
themselves. This will come through in
whatever you say. Let me point out
something if I may. All right? Sure.
If many of you and many of you may have
already realized this many times. If you
will only listen to the wording that we
activate from the physiological channel.
Many times you will hear the wording in
and of itself may sound if that's all
you're listening to very harsh, very
direct. But we also send you the energy
of our unconditional love. And this is
what lets you know what we actually mean
regardless of the
wording. You follow me? Yeah. You feel
the idea. And so in that sense, you
well, all right. to be contemporary in
your language. You let us get away with
saying many things you would not accept
from people around you because you don't
believe that they are coming with your
best interest.
Whereas you feel from us that we love
you unconditionally. And therefore
anything we say you know we are simply
sharing that love with you and you
accept it on another level other than
just what you think you hear us
saying. You follow me? Yeah I follow
you. And what
I I
think what I what I've gotten clear to
me is that that's where my life has
gotten out of balance is that before I
was so totally coming from the feeling
and so sympathetic and um we understand
reinforcing their victimhood that now
I'm going to the point of trying to get
stronger and disencourage victimhood
when I see it and the love is getting
lost and it's not coming through. That
is simply because perhaps you believe
that compassion has to be erased from
your repertoire in order to achieve that
repertoire in order to achieve that
balance on the other side. But that is
not the case. Compassion is the
blending of the directness and the
emotionality. Compassion is the
blending. Reason is the blending.
Reason is the blending.
You
follow and trust that because you
created cocreated that particular
situation that you put yourself exactly
in the situation you needed to be in to
allow yourself to begin to get
experience in doing just that in forming
the blending you need to get the message
across. Do not be so hard on yourself.
No, I'm not. I I'm I'm much lighter on
myself than I used to. All right. you
haven't lost the love in any way, shape,
or form. I know it's there. And what
what I get frustrated is with is the
fact that
um what my intention and what what gets
reflected out there is not coming in my
heart. You will learn to align. You will
learn to align. Simply remember that it
is not so much that the love is there.
The love is
here. Always here. not I know it's there
somewhere it's here simply always trust
that it is and know therefore that in
whatever way shape or form you do happen
to say something at any given time that
is the way you need to say it at that
time you know you are doing your best so
don't be so hard on yourself
please all right if you are going to let
them see your love then Begin by loving
yourself as you are.
I do. Is that not coming across either?
I'm feeling that so much more now. I All
right. But simply trust that you can use
the self love to allow them to feel that
you know everyone and everything is also
the same as you and therefore they can
feel the same love from you in that way.
But again the idea that No matter how it
comes out, if you know you are doing
your best and if you know you are coming
from love, then why buy into their
reaction? Their reaction is their
choice. If you know that what you are
sharing is within your integrity, then
anything you may be feeling from them as
a discordant vibration is not your
doing. It is their
doing. You follow me?
You cannot be responsible for them. You
are only responsible to them to be
completely who you are at any given
moment. See, I guess I I got confused
then with victimization. I feel like if
I don't take responsibility for
everything I do and say, then for
everything you do and say. Yes. But
taking responsibility for everything you
do and say doesn't mean blaming yourself
for what you do and say. It means
knowing you have the freedom of choice
to recognize that what you do and say
may at times be representative of the
way you prefer to be and at times it may
not be representative of prefer to be.
But so what when those times occur where
it is not representative of what you
prefer to be. Use them to allow you
therefore to get more in touch with what
it is you do prefer to be. Use it as a
positive lesson. Don't get down on
yourself for having done it. It has
shown you now what you don't want to be
and that allows you to be more of what
you do want to be. Yay. Yay.
Yeah. I mean that's exactly what what
I've been doing with with this is by
saying okay this was a really powerful
lesson and I didn't get depressed and I
didn't get upset about the experience. I
just said I want to learn what it is
so that I can balance the energy. You
are learning. Yeah, you are.
Thank you very much. Well, thank you for
you. Thank you. Um, I want to ask a
question with concern for a friend of
mine. Concern again. All right. Caring.
All right. Thanks. Um, anyway, he has
been um, uh, astrally projective for
probably 12 or 15 years, and it just has
always been very natural for him, but
He's very he's he's uh he doesn't have
any kind of a support system or anybody
who really knows anything about any um
thing to do with that around him or
anything spiritual. He has you. Yes. And
I'm rather removed. But anyway, he if I
may just continue, he what he does is
that he leaves his body, but he never
leaves his body far enough to where he
gets he he always feels that he has to
be able to see his body because he is
afraid because of the fundamental things
and he and so I thought that maybe that
there was was some way that I could the
literature we have already mentioned by
Monroe will be of great
assistance for it charts like a map the
entire experience through many different
levels. Realize there are many beings on
that level that are more than willing to
assist your friend. All he has to do is
ask. He doesn't know that. Help him.
He doesn't know that. Help him.
Then the next time he is out, all he has
to do is say,
"Help. A little bit of assistance,
please. If you don't mind very much, I
would very much enjoy that. Not help out
of panic, but simply
assistance. He will get it.
All right. Okay. Allow him to learn the
literature also of
Monroe. It will be of great assistance
and then he will not feel so alone.
There are many, many, many, many like
your friend.
[Music] You see the idea in this way is that if
You see the idea in this way is that if
he does not allow himself to go beyond
that particular point and he's not
allowing himself to avail himself of the
level that can actually be of most
assistance to him in getting over that
fear. He knows he knows that but he just
he being that he doesn't know anything
beyond what he is experiencing that
comes naturally to him just in that
realm. He's just he's not willing to
take the chance to go beyond because he
really does believe in, you know, all
the fearful students and things that are
out there that may just say, "Okay,
well, thanks. You left, so I'll walk
in." All right. All
right. Give him the suggestion of a
courage and let him know once again all
he has to do is ask for
assistance. Not in a panicked
way, in a determined way. in a knowing
way. Perhaps what might also be of some
assistance is to
before allow themselves to leave the
body so to speak to have a predetermined
destination in mind.
Something clear and concise, something
familiar, someone
familiar more than some thing or place,
someone such as
yourself that feels like a
friend, then he can wean himself by
making quick
trips to and
fro. Body's still okay. All right, one
more time. to and
from. Still okay. All right, let's try
someone else. All right, let's see. What
about this person? To and
from. Pretty good. All right, I guess
I'm getting the hang of this now. The
idea is in all
actuality that they may find it that any
any any disturbance of the body at all will
any disturbance of the body at all will
immediately snap them back into it. No
matter what the source,
you follow. Uhhuh.
If you wish to think of it this way, it
is an automatic safety mechanism built
in. Any disturbance of something that is
not the vibration of the idea will not
allow him to remain out of the body.
But our suggestion is to focus on
someone that he
knows. Recognize he is a thought form in
a world of thought forms. And as soon as
he has the thought of seeing that, all
he has to do is think of that person. He
will be there. All he has to do is think
of being back and he will
be. It's that
easy. And it can be that quick.
Stick his ass will toe in the water and
pull it out as quickly as he wishes.
Oh, thank you very much. Rashad.
Yes, back here. You know, it's very
difficult to get your attention as first
time attendee. There's someone back here
who is eager to get a question in or I
think gave up because of the
competition. Could she ask a question
and if it isn't taking unfair advantage,
could I ask one after that? Absolutely.
do recognize first of all that
everything occurs in perfect timing.
Proceed. Um my question was uh that some material
Um my question was uh that some material
has come to me lately about um it sounds
more excuse me but what uh about being
what happens to beings that are
atomically disintegrated and that it's
much harder on them because the body is
totally disintegrated and I wondered if
this is true. There can be some
relevance to this idea within certain
belief systems. There can be energies
that may bridge what you call the
physical non-physical barriers in this way and
non-physical barriers in this way and
cause some sense of
disruption. But in this way also is
there some specific reason why you are
overly concerned about the idea of
atomic disintegration?
Yes, because of something that was said
to me about my energies and my my
inability to to um my energies can get
extremely very difficult much difficulty
bringing them back together and uh
someone told me un unasked by me that I
had been at one
time things
that I've been atomic that I was
atomically blown up and that my that my
energy field had was scattered and
that's very difficult for me to bring it
back together. And in what era were you
atomically blown up? I'll tell you, I
was so blown away. I didn't
even I don't know.
All right. One moment.
May I ask you a few questions myself?
Yes. Do you believe you are here for a
reason? I mean on earth. On earth. Okay.
Yes. Can you say that is something? No,
I just No, I I think that anybody who's
here has to believe they're here for a
reason. All right. They don't have to.
Yeah, I know. All right. Do you believe
you are here for a reason of your own
choosing? All right.
All right.
Do you or can you therefore recognize
that even if this idea of the atomic
disintegration were so that therefore by
having chosen to be in the physical life
you are in now is representative of your
ability to reintegrate yourself that is
perhaps one of the ideas you are
learning. Yes. And therefore having a
tough time all
the only reason you are having a tough
time per se is because you have been
taught to treat the time you are having
as tough to think of it as a negative
experience. The second you can begin to begin to
The second you can begin to begin to
realize the ideas in your life, the
situations in your life, the occurrences
in your life as therefore a positive
reason, you will allow yourself to
accelerate into the
integration and therefore not experience
the reality as tough. It is only the
definition you have been taught that
creates what you are perceiving to be
toughness. Only the definition. That is
it. Only the definition.
I do. I don't know how to change it. Oh,
it is very simple. Oh, good. Very
simple. Now, first of all, recognize
this idea. Do you understand that what
you call your imagination reality and
your physical reality are both real?
Yes. All right. Then you can very simply
recognize that if you have the ability
to conceive of something you prefer to
be, you are already of that vibration.
And all you have to do is begin to act
as if it is true for you to allow your
physical reality to reflect that in your
life. It is only because you continue to
assume what you have been taught that
well if I have imagined it now what do I
have to do to become this idea of what
long involve process is necessary in
order to achieve this thing out here.
That is what makes it tough. That's not
it. is that I have consistent ev
consistent
evidenceh evidence. Evidence evidence
what you are calling evidence is only
what the physical reality reflects that
you believe to be
true. Do not forget your belief of what
you believe to be true is what creates
the physical evidence, not the other way
around. Belief creates physical reality
which then may
reinforce the original belief and that
is what you think of as evidence. Well
yes well look this is happening
therefore it obviously is tough but it
is only happening in a tough way because
you believe it has to be tough. The
evidence is only a result of the fact
that you contain a belief it has to be
tough. Now recognize therefore that the
Now recognize therefore that the
evidence you are seeing is not
representative of the idea that you are
stuck in that belief. It is
representative only of the idea that you
have the belief because you are seeing
that reflection in your life. that
so-called evidence that is there to let
you know you have the belief that things
are tough and then it puts you squarely
in touch with the fact that you have
that belief. Now that you know you have
that belief, if you don't prefer that
belief, all you have to do is redefine
that belief. And then the only other
thing that is necessary is to act like
you have redefined that belief and not
act as if you haven't. Then your
physical reality will give you evidence
that your belief has
changed. Your physical reality is only
the shadow of the idea you believe you
are. When you change the idea that you
are and start acting like you truly
believe you have changed, your physical
reality being the shadow of your soul
has no choice but to give you new
evidence. Is any of this making concern?
Oh, very much. It is only simple
physics. It is only simple mechanics.
And I can remind you of a very important
foundational idea that in many ways
contradicts many of the beliefs you have
in your society, but nonetheless can
work if you let
it. It is that
simple. Are you sure it's not any more
complex than that? Yes, I'm
sure. I'm sure it can be made more
complex than that. But I am equally sure
that it can be that simple if you will
allow it to be. That is all it takes.
Willingness to believe it is that
simple. Then the physical reality in a
very short period of time will begin to
change and transform into the type of
reinforcing feedback
evidence that then reinforces the new
belief you have now made a conscious
choice to become.
Now the idea of what you refer to as the
atomic disintegration is representational of a
disintegration is representational of a
system, a planetary system that no
longer exists physically as you know it.
It is what you call
Maldc. It
occupied what you now refer to as the
asteroid belt in your solar system.
You following? Yes. Yes.
Many many
many individuals are reincarnated from that
individuals are reincarnated from that
selfdestructed
civilization upon your earth and are
beginning to explore the idea of
reintegration, rebalance because this is
rebalance because this is
now this light this time.
Now the
transformational age life what that
means is that since you have chosen to
be here it is at least as far as our
perspective is concerned a foregone
conclusion that you will
balance because you are of a mind to
want to.
So you will the only thing you need to
assist you is allowing it to be easy,
allowing it to be simple and recognizing
that anything you experience in physical
reality is completely and utterly and
only can be the product of what you
believe to be true which is the same
thing as saying what you fear might be
true because then it becomes the
overriding emotion the overriding
belief. So choose what you prefer to believe in
So choose what you prefer to believe in
and then live as if you truly believe it
and you will see your life change in
what we call an expatic explosion of
synchronistic coincidence. There are no
accidents. Follow me. Yes. Does this assist you?
Follow me. Yes. Does this assist you?
Yes, it does. Thank you, brave soul.
Thank you. Male. Yes. Uh interesting
what you said about the timing. Uh very
perceptive of you by the way. and you as
well where we cocreate this event
together. Uh when you were making your
opening remarks about uh purpose,
self-created purpose and individual
purpose and intention as having dominion
over the events in your life. Uh this
reminded me of the saying God is simple,
man is complex. And what I mean by that
and how this brings me to the question
is
that I find for myself and for many
other people that the spiritual
questions right now are not so much the
ones of deeper knowing or understanding,
the simplicity of the greater simplicity,
simplicity of the greater simplicity,
but the intricate complexities of making
those realizations work in material
circumstances. Okay. And that I'll use
myself as an illustration. Oh, please
do. Now, I was never one who had to do
much to fight through the limiting
belief systems of this culture. I was
empowered as a child. I was taught
exactly the kinds of things as a child
that are now considered higher
consciousness. I don't think I've ever
lived with any discernable fears. And
yet, while it's very clear to me what I
feel are the things for me to do in my
life, I continue to see a large gap between
I continue to see a large gap between
the inner reality and the inner knowing,
between the knowing that I'm the author
of that outer reality. I continue to see
these apparently frustrating
circumstances. Right? The usual answer
given to this kind of thing is the
scapegoat answer, the catchall answer.
Well, somewhere in your subconscious,
meaning you can't know about it. you're
doing something to get in the way of it,
which just seems to be what has been
done throughout history with religion.
Wherever we didn't have knowledge, we it
was God or the devil. Now we are in a
psychological age. So it's just
subconscious and to me that just becomes
another dogmatic belief system. So I am
continually perplexed but never defeated
and never cynical or skeptical about why
it is that the relentless clarity about
where I want to go and where I see
myself going that vision tends to push
its attainment further away. So I
continue the receding horizon and the
present reality is is contradictory. All
right. Very good. Beautifully said.
Now first of all from our point of view
in allowing allowing allowing allowing
not making not forcing anything to work
but allowing the reality you desire to work
allowing the reality you desire to work
is to recognize that it is first and
foremost an allowance and not a making.
Have we got that? Yes. All right. In
this way,
therefore, the first step, shall we
say, always has been and still is to let
whatever it is that does happen in your
life. Whatever seems to be the apparent
reality, as you have
said, to be what needs to be there at
least for that moment.
If it is there, regardless of why it is
there, it still is there for a reason
and can still be considered no matter on
what level it comes from to be there for
a reason that will benefit your
acceleration towards the state you wish
to exist within. So, first and foremost,
allow yourself to not necessarily see the
yourself to not necessarily see the
things in your life that perhaps you
don't prefer to be something that appears to
prefer to be something that appears to
be standing in your way. Let what is
there, even if you don't prefer it, be
there for a reason, for the reason of
getting you to what you do prefer. First
of all, if you attempt to get rid of
anything in your life, you will very
quickly find that there is nowhere to
get rid of anything
to because there is no outside. You are
the complete universe of your
experience. Attempting to push something
away that you do not prefer is an
invalidation of that immediate present
reality. And the only place you can push
it up against is the immediate wall of
the universe you have created. The
harder you try to push it away, the more
energy you actually give it to spring
back because it has nowhere to go. And
so it may generate what appears to be
the repetitive cycle of negativity in
that way and appears to keep you from
what it is you truly feel like you want
to be. Now, is any of this making sense
so far? Oh, yes. But let me if I may
clarify one. Are you saying that perhaps
formal practices such as meditation,
affirmation, visualizations can be
overdone to where you are not increasing
the thing that you're focusing on, the
reality you seek to create, but that you
are somehow implicitly
uh uh expressing too much resistance to
your present reality. Yes. And that if
you lightened up on some of your your
personal then you will be enlightened.
That is all enlightenment really is
lightening up allowing the balance to
exist in a natural way a natural pace a
natural timing.
In this way, you may find that the
individuals that in your terminology,
which I will now use, overdue the
meditation idea, are very similar to
individuals that are overly concerned
with their health and thus bring on
disease. The idea of expressing an
overconern with health is actually a
strong belief that disease can get you
and thus that's what manifests. So in
the same way the belief that you really
really need an overage of that
meditative state is in and of itself
perhaps a reflection of the belief that
if you truly need that much then perhaps
this idea this life this reality you
don't prefer really is more
powerful more powerful than anything you
do prefer if you have to really meditate
that hard on it and that is what gets
reinforced Your actions many times can
reinforce the true belief which is not
subconscious is right on the surface
because your actions are very apparent
in a general sense that if you have to
really work at it that hard you are
saying implicitly that what you don't
prefer is more likely is more probable
to be the reality you experience than
what it is you do
prefer. Okay, I think there may have
been some breakdown in communication or
may have given a wrong idea amongst most
of the people I know who do one or many
of all these kinds of things that I do
or have done. I'm probably seen as being
a little on the sloppy side and and not
and not fevered enough. I tend to go at
it a little bit loosely, but
consistently Let's take another I don't
think that's my tendency. Let's take
another tap. Yeah.
What is it in life that excites you the
most that you do want to
do that you believe you are not doing
now? One thing only can I get whatever
excites you the most.
I want uh a creative career specifically
as an actor. I want I want travel. I
want quality relationships, finances. I
want to be able to contribute to the
healing of the planet and uh staving off
some of the brutalities we visit upon
our fellows. All right. And basically
and some there's some health
considerations as well. Any
clarification or change in those areas?
All of them would be very All right.
Now, do you actually consider each and
every one of these things you have
talked about to be distinctly separate
things or can you begin to understand
them as one thing? Oh, I'm sure I
fundamentally it's all connected.
Connected still implies separation.
Well, let's say there's unity and
diversity. There is there is identity
with distinctive individuality within
the identity. There is. But how reliant
is any one of these things on the
creation of any one other of these
things? Are you saying that one will
give rise simultaneous to the other?
Yes. Yes. And the idea therefore is that
perhaps there may be within you the idea
of believing that so many things so many
differentiated things have to happen all
at once that perhaps it may seem like
too much to ask for. Oh, I've never
limited what I thought I was entitled.
Then can you recognize this idea?
The universe does not do extraneous and
pointless things and
always flawlessly
flawlessly
flawlessly supplies you with what you
truly believe you need at any given
moment.
You see, here's the place where I'm on
the horns of the dilemma that feels,
seems, is has revealed itself to be true
to me. It is my fundamental take on the
way things all work. And yet, I continue
to see this nagging static, this uh
apparent contradiction and other
circumstance, which has a nasty way of
seeming very real even though I know
some sort of real. Everything is real.
Everything is real.
In this way, however, simply yes or no,
do you recognize that the universe
always supplies you with what you truly
believe you
need? Yes or no?
My most complete answer, yes or yes and
no. Yes or no?
one idea or another idea. In my inner
knowing, the answer is yes. In my outer
experience, the evidence tests that
inner knowing by appearing to run
counter. Here we go with the evidence.
You see what I'm saying? Yes. But drop
the evidence. I am asking you the
question as a whole being. Answer it as
a whole being. Remembering that if you
do choose to say yes and no, that that
is a distinct and separate reality from
either yes or
no. The reality of yes and no may be the
reality you are creating. Bashar may
have permitted this answer. Of course, a
man of wisdom, it was either Neils Gore
or Berner Heisenberg said, "The opposite
of a lesser truth is an error. the
opposite of a greater truth is often
equally true. So that when we're getting
to the nub or the paradox, the turning
point of life and and this question of
the total rightness and total perfect
response of creation in all
circumstances versus the contradictory
stew that human beings in this level are
working with. This is one of those
fundamental paradoxes where both sides
of the question seem to be true. Yes.
Now maybe there's a false seeming or
maybe there's a way in which mutually
exclusive apparent opposites are really
both simultaneously true. Oh, they are.
Oh, they are. The truth is composed of
all truths. There is no one background
reality against which to measure any
other reality for its level of
validity. But the idea in this way
perhaps therefore I will restate as
follows. answer in the way you would
answer in the way you would
prefer to be true. Oh, that's easy. And
the answer is
yes. Now, whether it seems at this
moment or not to be any different, trust
that by having answered that way, it is
now different. You are now different. You
different. You are now different. You
are now not the you you were moments
ago. You are now the you that truly
knows you prefer the answer to be yes.
And therefore that is now your reality.
Hallelujah. All you have to
do, all that is necessary now, the very
simple idea of truly recognizing the
following in a conscious way. That now
that you have made the choice to prefer
that the answer be yes, that you act
like you believe
it. That's just me. That's the way I've
always been. Then all that is left is
trust. 100% trust.
100% trust.
Yeah, I think there there may be about
95, but I'm working on 100. I appreciate
the answer. All right. Now, do
understand that you are of course always
a 100% trust in whatever idea you are
experiencing. That is
That is
all why it is simply the necessary idea
to understand the definition you prefer
and then put the 100% of trust into that
definition. Mhm.
I ask something very brief. Of course.
Could you at some point uh now or later
you like explain why it is that there is
this characteristic
uh exaggerated inflection pattern where
some words are given unusual emphasis or
elongation like actuality or things like
in our communication. Yeah. Yes. The
idea is that we are not speaking your
language. We are in a sense identifying
with the vibrational pattern of the
consciousness of the physiological
channel and the appropriate
translations are being
activated. They are being activated in a
way that represents the energy
intention. And therefore the way you may
be perceiving the vocalization is that
you perceive not only the word but the
underlining of the intention on many
different levels. What may
sound like the patterns of inflections
and the variations in pitch are
representative in many ways of different
levels of communication going on that
you may not be consciously aware of
between us.
There are
modulations of energy that are reaching
you in many fundamental ways. Let us say
outside of the threshold of your
mentality. You follow me? Yes. So you're
saying these vocal modulations are
intentions derived from that level of
intention that's using the memory banks
and motor faculties of the channel and
they are representative of many levels
upon which this conversation is taking
place. Some of which you may be
consciously aware of and some of which
you may not be. But the most interesting
idea was that those physical vocal
modulations are producing perhaps unseen
or uh unwell unknown consciously changes
on a vibrational psychic or opening
doorways but
only those you choose to open
yourselves. Nothing is being forced into you.
Nothing is being forced into you.
Interesting. At this time we will thank
you for your
sharing and all
all
sharing you. Thank you. I would like to
share um very recently I've been going speak
um very recently I've been going speak
up very recently and I was just saying
that you were speaking too loud. Okay.
Very recently, I've been experiencing a
deep sense of connectedness, a feeling
of being very complete, almost at will.
And then paradoxically today, I've
experienced a complete sense of being
disconnected, spaciness. I
set something down and I can't find it.
I I'm busy doing 12 things. Yes. Do not
forget that the idea of your expansion
into more of yourself can still at this
time this is still the transformational
time you bring with it that
disorientation that you are still
disconnecting disorienting from many
different preconceived notions and
reorienting and reconnecting into
others. You can still go through those
particular limbo states, though they
will become more accelerated and you
will begin to recognize that this
disoriented dreamlike state is actually what your
dreamlike state is actually what your
natural state is as you are simply
getting used to it. My natural state, I
felt like I couldn't connect with that
sense of trust where my neutral or my
automatic was functioning in the way
that I was comfortable with. I couldn't
rely on my I call it automatic. It's
that state where I don't think about
things. I function very in a flow. And
being so disconnected, I was
constantly feeling that I couldn't rely
on that sense of inner trust that was
always there for me. All right. And now
what do you think?
Well, I feel that that trust if I just
allow it in the course of everything, the
it in the course of everything, the
puzzle will all fall together. But right
now, I May I remind you of something?
Sure. Had this happened to you some time
ago, it would have induced a state of
panic rather than mere puzzlement.
Oh, that's probably very true. So allow
yourself to recognize it as an
opportunity to see how quote unquote far
you have come.
Oh, may I ask you one more question? You
do not have to ask if you can ask.
Otherwise, you have already asked the
question. You do for sure. [Music] [Music]
[Laughter]
It's a hard act to follow. But
then usually no one responds to me that
I do not have to ask if I can ask.
Therefore, we will still
maintain that interaction.
Your ability to make yourself right is
phenomenal.
I love it.
This is my
[Music]
nickel. I' I've recently been mentally
playing with the idea of integrity. And
it's occurred to me that even though now
I have a deep sense for that feeling of
integrity in my
previous experiences where I now in
retrospect sense that I was not
functioning from integrity at that time
I did not know that and if somebody were
to ask me if I were functioning from my
integrity I would have responded that I
was. Then you learn at that time. Isn't
that the truth? Isn't that the case for
all beings at all times that they always
feel that what they're doing is the
right thing? Oh, one moment. You have
many times know this is so a conscious
awareness that you are going against the
grain of your integrity.
But there's if you are very honest with
yourself. Doesn't that come with awareness though?
Doesn't that come with awareness though?
That sense of integrity has to grow as
you grow. And even though you always
have choice and you can still because
anything is possible for you reach a
state of integration and still choose to
do something that you then know is in
opposition to the state of integration
you have already reached. You can still
make that conscious
choice at any stage of your integration.
You can still make the conscious choice
to go against the grain of the
integration you are already aware of.
You follow me?
Yeah. Why do people do that for sure?
Ask them.
Many times. It may be because they still wish
times. It may be because they still wish
to test themselves because they maybe
believe they need testing.
Many times it may be because once again they
times it may be because once again they
choose to create or recreate the idea
that they are not as
self-empowered as they chose to believe
they were at one time. There may be many
different reasons for this idea. But it
is still a possible thing to
do. You always have choice. Always. Now
the idea we are colloally speaking of is
simply that at any given moment if you
truly believe you are functioning within
your integrity truly believe that and
believe that you are being as honest
with yourself as you possibly can
recognize yourself to be then in that
sense in the overall sense you are
functioning within integrity even if
from a later point of view you learn.
Yeah, that's kind of what I'm alluding
to. But that is all right. That is how
you learn. That is how you grow. The
idea now for you is to still recognize,
however, that no matter what degree of
integrity you recognize within yourself,
you still know that you have a choice to
express an opposite grain to that
integrity, don't you? Yeah. It's almost
like you tough it through that there's
this I know. I know. But that's what I
feel. came back in in a reflective way.
Those instances where I was going
against my grain, even though it was
uncomfortable, it's like I was beating
my head against the wall, but there was
a strong determination to tuck it
through no matter what. And yet, I felt
like I was coming from integrity in that
I was doing what I was
motivated to do. Now, you are simply
coming from a different definition of
integrity. And now that you have allowed
those experiences at that time to be a
part of the integrity you are now, then
the expanded view you have become makes
it seem as if you were struggling then.
The expanded view you will become may
carry with it a belief that you are
struggling now later on.
And so and so on and so on and so
thank you very much. You
You
l are you familiar with an entity named
Isis? Well, to some degree. Uh, is Alex still
Well, to some degree. Uh, is Alex still
here? No, he left. Oh, Alex left. Um,
apparently no comment.
[Music] No comment. He's aware of it already.
No comment. He's aware of it already.
Uh, no comment about the earthquake. No.
Well, I mean, you can about ISIS or or
whatever. Oh, not be sorry. There is nothing to be
Oh, not be sorry. There is nothing to be
sorry for. Oh, you you don't want to
talk about it.
Let me put it this way. We are now going
to give to you a gift of unconditional
love. We will allow you to begin and end
the conversation that you have begun. Thank
conversation that you have begun. Thank
you, Rashelle. Go ahead.
Oh, it was just that he mentioned that
two separate people had told him about a
prediction by ISIS. about an earthquake
and I said well if you're going to
perceive it you'll perceive it or if you
believe in it you'll perceive it and if
you don't you won't but why don't you
ask Bashad and he said you would and I
heard him say Bash in the first section
first part of the session and but there
are so many people trying wanting to
talk to you and I thought well since I'm
right here maybe he can support me but
apparently he's left
so I was wondering If you had any
reception of the prediction. Yes. And
but since this is now your story, you
will continue, not I.
This is the opportunity you have asked
for. That's why I said no comment unless
you're willing to go through with this.
You continue. Now your senses are in
focus. Your senses are in force. Your
understanding of your point of view, of
your relationship to this idea now can
be what you can share with the group.
Well, my first reaction was there have
been lots of predictions of earthquake
and this is just one more right and but
he
seemed apparently this person ISIS and I
don't think I ever heard of her uh I
mean obviously I've heard of ISIS but
not of the
entities channeling Sue the person in
Texas uh is very well known and has a lot of
uh is very well known and has a lot of
credibility
and I thought Um, this is interesting. I
I would do recognize that any prediction
that has ever been made has had a lot of
credibility at the time it was made.
Right. Yes, I know what you say about
predictions and I And what is it that
you now understand about predictions?
Please share. Well, at the time that the
prediction is made, the prediction is
based on the energies that are available
at that particular time. But as soon as
you start actually just the prediction
itself can change the energies. Yes. And
because because people become aware of it and
because people become aware of it and
they can they they have they create the
energies that make things happen.
Therefore, you can change them. Right.
And so I don't, you know, I'm not
worried about earthquakes particularly,
but since this was one of those big
ones, I thought
Not just not just any old person saying,
"Oh, there's going to be an earthquake."
We know there's going to be an
earthquake sometime or another. Always
earthquakes. If we create that reality, if we create
If we create that reality, if we create
that reality, oh, there well the earth
shifts and it shakes a little bit but
doesn't any damage.
There are many types of quake, right?
That's right. many types of shiftings,
many types of transformations.
So perhaps that prediction was really
based on the transformation that we're
all going through that you said was sort
of going to come to a culmination at the
end of October, beginning of November.
Could that be related to that? Could be. Let's discuss
Let's discuss
it closer to November.
This This is what the 27
wonderful number, isn't it?
It's a wonderful Every number is
wonderful. Oh, yeah.
seven opportunity to thank you and
allowing us to have so much fun with
you. Thank you so much for letting me
have so much fun.
We will at this time allow each and
every one of you to explore the idea of
this particular type of energy on your
own for now. Thank you.
We will discuss it later. Okay.
All right. I love your voice. You are
not hearing my voice.
Well, thank you.
What am I hearing? You are hearing the
channel's voice modulated by the
identification with our energy. Okay. I
love it.
You sure? All right. you um bash I uh
yay I think I well my dog
is has had this arthritic attack in the
last few days
and before that at one point
I had a fear
that and the fear was now that my
husband was away on location what would
I do if my dog Mof got sick? Well, then
then now he's sick. I see. Pain.
So, I recognize And so now what would
you do?
Well, it's nothing like creating your
reality. Yes. I really I'm seeing it.
It's interesting. And I So, and
therefore the dog being the symbol of
service is being of service to you. He
is. And now then what I did was I
went to heal him, Bashar. I did healing
on him and I did some
visualizations, but it didn't work.
Well, he's still in pain.
And you?
Well, I don't want him to keep going
through pain just to be of service to me
anymore on this. Then how about the pain
you go through?
H okay. Do you want to keep going
through pain? No, I do not.
I want to let go of that. Okay. All
right. What can you do to do
that? Can you become supple and flexible
rather than rigid and stiff or critic?
Yes, I can do that.
How would it feel to be supple and
flexible? It would feel calming.
It would feel calming.
I would not be worried and nervous. All
right. Very good. Then if you are
willing to now be supple and flexible,
calm and not nervous, then you can
radiate the necessary energy that then
the dog can reflect back to you.
All right.
Thank you, Michelle. Move on your
intuition. Move on your excitement.
Thank you. Thank you. We also at this time as
time as
always will avail our energies to you in
the conscious and in what you call
colloially the dream state to allow
yourself to align with your
representation. your
your
representation, your version of our
energy. Let yourself create that
reflection. Let yourself be that spontaneous
spontaneous
reflection. Then you will have infinite
suppleness and infinite
flexibility and no longer need to create
around you reflections and symbols of
rigidity.
You follow me?
Thank you very much. Thank you.
You Thank you. Uh I've been listening to
your tapes. I haven't been around for a
couple of weeks, but uh recently. Oh,
butterfly. Hey. Hello. Thank you.
Hello, Strawberry. Hi, baby.
uh on this
transformation that you're talking about
how the when you immed when you get a
new idea the frequency starts aligning
and it's in a 3day since we've agreed to
time this 3-day
uh area we go through is the general
representative amount of time necessary
for transformations to begin to manifest
into physical reality. Right? once you
have created them in the non-physical
template. Okay. Now, what I've observed, I've been
Okay. Now, what I've observed, I've been
talking to some other people about it.
It seems like there's a situation that
perhaps you can shed more light into the
survey. It seems like those three days
like all right, as as of for instance,
two days ago, I put I I found out how
something served me and it just it it
was incredible. [Music]
And right away I put the frequency of
what I what I did prefer and it was like
the goosebumps and goose pimples and all
that came in. Now I remember I was going
through this three-day thing and it
seemed like this three days on the
second day and I wonder if I'm going to
live to make it to the third. It's
almost like this isn't what I'm g what I
had but just to give you instance like
saying art I'm free of judgment and the
next three days everything you look at
you can't stand you hate this guy's dumb
this one's stupid he's I mean it's just
real and it's in that same realm I'm
using an example there but it's like the
volatilness of those I'm going to say 3
days or whatever
is there any light that can perhaps
temper that just well to where you Don't
kill everybody ghost you or a little
Yeah. When you activate that energy in a
knowing way, you accelerate
everything everything as a
unity. Therefore, any ideas of those
particular types of reactions still left
within you may also be
magnified. Allow yourself to simply
treat them as opportunities.
once again to perhaps simply see how you
may or may not still be clinging to
those ideas and then change them as you
find them in the moment in the
now. Act instead of react
even as rapidly as they come. I mean
they come in click click I got you. If
you are attempting as you have to
request little time instead of more time
for these transformations to take place,
then all of the things that you know you
may still have to look at are going to
accelerate accordingly.
Put it at whatever pace is comfortable
for you. You are the dial. I knew you
had some frequencies. This is all You
are a
multi-dimensional creator. This is an
opportunity to begin perhaps to
consciously understand what that really
means.
Thank you for your willingness to
explore as you have every decision of
integration in any way, shape or form
that it is manifested allows the entire
civilization that much more opportunity
for further integration.
Everyone makes a difference. Everyone.
Everyone. Everyone.
Thank you. Okay. Just on like one more
facet of that like when you when you do
get into this frequent this I mean this
volatile almost like an explosion. Yes.
Um like another manifestation seems to
come up of of levitude like you don't
want to be you just you just want to
stay in bed all day, put the pillow over
your head. Um turn some of that can be
simple denial.
of the denial of your own power.
That's interesting. Not wanting to deal
with what you are now discovering in
that sense.
Yes. But you are making the connections
as you need to. Excellent. You are
flowing. Now again with particular regard to the
Now again with particular regard to the
idea of specific
manifestation in your life, there are as
we have already discussed some ideas,
some techniques. Of course, every single
individual will create their own
technique from their own imagination and
alter whatever techniques are perhaps
functional for the mass consciousness in
their own way making it their own
technique anyway. But according to many
of the requests that we have had this
evening of your time with the idea of
monetary this career that object this
and so forth. There is once again the
consciousness entity that we have
referred to many times as Lazarus who
has provided to your
civilization a very strong and powerful
tool for the very specific
manifestations of the things you desire
in life. It will of
course it will of course involve a
complete and total honesty of
communication with yourself as you will
find out if you listen to those
techniques on what you call your tapes.
But they will work. They will work.
Avail yourself of them specifically in
that way for any specific idea of desire
of manifestation and you will be using a
very powerful tool of acceleration and
precise manifestation.
Bashar um Carrie and I obtained the
Lazarus tape on the causal plane and we
found that after a while we experienced
resistance to doing it. All right. Now
would you would you say that the way to
best utilize working on the causal plane
in that way is to all right let's say
you take a particular aspect of your
life a particular visualization your
your business life is to do it a number
of times and then drop
it is it best to let's say do it three
times really so but the idea in terms of
doing it for one particular thing, you
can simply find that you can do it once
for one particular idea, for one
particular thing. If you do not, as you
are instructed on the tape, if you do
not see what appears to be a sign, a
signal, or a manifestation within that
3-day period, then go back and
re-examine the honesty of the
communication you had with yourself in
answering the preliminary questions that
put you in the state necessary in that
way. It'll work. If you allow those
things to align. Now from time to time
you may come up with the ideal once
again of that contrariness that exists
in the habit of your society. The same
idea that you might generally refer to
not so much as writer's block but
writer's avoidance. The idea that all right here
avoidance. The idea that all right here
I am. I have a great idea. I'm ready
willing. Sit down. Ready to write. Oh
well I just thought of three million
other things.
because you don't really want to get
into that thing because of all your
preconceived notions about the way you
think it might
be. So simply allow yourself to know. Go
through the exercise as Lazarus has
outlined it. Gladly you will get in
touch with yourself in whatever way,
shape or form is necessary and you will
see the manifestation of synchronicity
in your life
increase. Come with varying degrees of
honesty within you in terms of whether
or not you are truly willing to listen
to the
answer or avoid listening to the answer.
You follow me? It is a preparatory step
in the particular exercise that we are
discussing. There are several questions
that are posed for you to ask of
yourself and depending upon the degree
of clarity of communication and honesty
with yourself in letting yourself
receive the true answer, the answer you
know to be true for you will determine
the effectiveness of the technique later
on. And it simply is therefore that if you
And it simply is therefore that if you
find this technique does not work as you
have created the idea of it working then
all that is necessary is to go back and
re-examine the original tool.
My sort of missing link is expectancy.
You don't like everything's cool and you
go through your belief systems and all
of that and you
but then you you know honestly you don't
100% expect it to manifest in your life.
Then it won't
you see the thing of it is is that with
something you truly know you own, you
don't think twice about it. You really
know you own it. You don't worry about
owning it. It's yours. You don't even
think about it. That's
expectancy. That's really taking it for
granted. That's that's yours. Plain and
simple. [Music]
[Music]
Period. You only worry about the thing
you don't know.
The thing you believe you don't know.
Your belief isn't being set in your Oh,
yes. And there are once again very
powerful techniques within that tape for
getting in touch with the belief system
as well.
It is all there. It is a nice neat
human. Okay. So let's say you want to how do
Okay. So let's say you want to how do
you if you recognize you don't have the
100% expectancy and you want to have it.
Well, first of all, again, get honest
with yourself and ask yourself, do I
really want this thing? really really
really Yeah. Let's say you really want it, but
Yeah. Let's say you really want it, but
you haven't utilized the technique
before, so you don't 100% expected to
work. That's what I'm talking about. We
will simply suggest that if it is truly
something that drives you, you won't
care how many times you do it. It will
be an overwhelming desire. And the
overwhelming desire in and of itself
will become expectancy.
this secrets of manifesting what you
want. Yeah,
I I have found in in doing that
technique that you do get those gifts on
the first chest and even though I didn't
totally expect it either, I believed in
the gift of expectancy and it worked,
you know.
and delegates to the desire and all
that. It's very powerful.
Bashar, a key point that he I want to
share with everyone that he talks about
is that you always do get exactly what
you are what you want, not what you're
asking for, what you want, including the
frustration of almost having it or
something like that. This is where the
honesty comes in. But many times as was
pointed out a scenario can be manifested
that will represent that what you
actually honestly wanted was as you have
said the frustration of almost having
the technique I found no matter how
roughly one uses it always works. It
always works. It is up to you to get in
touch with why you want what you want,
where the beliefs come from that give to
you the understanding of what it is you
want. I found it to be more profound in
looking at why you don't want it because
obviously your reality that's an
approach too.
Fine you
all according to your belief structure
all of it. Your entire physical reality
is only a reflection of what you believe
it can be.
Sharing. All right. You
Yeah. I had um this
Sunday something happened to me between
2 to 4 in the morning. I I Very typical.
I couldn't go to sleep, so I decided I
was going to watch TV. But
um now I
heard something it was so
valid I mean vivid that
um I don't know whether it was my dream
or I really heard it on TV that there
was a earthquake in New Zealand that
could have created um a title wave going
through Hawaii but they cancelled the
title wave um warning. Mhm. And um I
because of that I wanted to make sure I
heard if it was for real stuff cuz that
was to me that was really exciting you
know strange news. So I waited for the
news for if there was some kind of news
like that and there was no news like
that. So I thought well maybe it's me I
I mean it was my dream. So if it is my
dream now um that the earthquake said
well it says in my dream that uh there
was an 8.2
earthquake and in New
Zealand and um that almost created a
title going through Hawaii. Could you uh
give me some about that if it was my
dream? Again understand it is both your
dream and dreams are real, right? And
the idea of tapping into a potential
energy, an idea that has a very great
degree of energy behind it, energy
potentiality behind it, does not make it
any less real whether it manifests in
your physical reality or not. Now, the
idea has a great deal of validity at
this time. Right. In your physical
reality. Yes.
Okay. The idea
also has a great degree of actuality in
what you might call an alternate earth,
a parallel
earth, maybe even more than in
yours. It also represents energy shifts.
Again, not necessarily seismically
represented, but simply energy shifts of the waves of
but simply energy shifts of the waves of
connections that are made in the New
Zealand area as they are related to the
Hawaii energy.
This has to do to some degree with
manifestations in your dream reality and
it is a connection also to the dreamers
themselves. Right. That's the first
thing that came in my mind was it could
have been uh it had something to do with
the dreamers. Yes. But I wasn't I wasn't
clear whether it was there are very
strong electromagnetic shifts taking
place in that area and the dreamers are
very sensitive to them. You may be
identifying with them and picking up on
the shifts in that way.
There is a potential for it to be
seismically realized but again it does
not have to be. The idea can be looked
at this way. Let us say in your old
style of thinking you recognize the
potential for connection to take place
around your world through seismic
events. Now you are recognizing these
potential seismic events quote unquote
before they happen and you are following
them up and transforming them before
they have an opportunity to come into
the physical manifestation in that
way. You are hunting them down and
changing them before they happen. You
are now sensitive to where they can
occur and you are allowing connections
to take place so they do not have to
occur in that way. You are simply
sensitive to the areas of great
potential release and therefore as
energy eaters you are attracted to those
areas because that is the highest source
of sustenance. Oh wow.
That is where the highest changes the
quickest changes can take place in those
areas of great potentiality.
For now, the idea can be transformed
into the understanding of what you call
the rter magnitude as a direct
correlation to the potential
transformation that can occur in that
area. Now there is another way to think
of seismic release as
well. Even should it come to pass of the
idea of seismic release, you can all
engineer the release in a very specific
way. Let us say you are considering the
idea as is nominally thought of at let
us say the idea for a quick release
7.5 magnitude why not a prolonged release of
magnitude why not a prolonged release of
five
instead rather than the quick
75 that can occur as
well. You follow me?
There will be more on this because this
is a very strong area of potential
transformation. The realization
consciously of this energy and your
ability to tap into it and use it,
channeling it through yourselves as
valves. For that is what you are. You
are a
valve through a doorway through too many
different levels of
existence. All the energy of the earth
is yours.
Bashar, could you elaborate a little bit
on how you do that? Meditation or what's
the we will soon. Okay. Thank you. There
are other energies that will come in to
assist in this transformation. Some of
them being connected into the
association. This will be soon. Thank
you. Caps involved in these
transformations to some degree.
When Betty asked about the 8.2
earthquake and the tidal wave, I also
knew that I got that information I
thought from the newspaper as I was
waking up and I thought, "Oh, here was
not in New Zealand was an island close
by." Nothing but there was no damage or
anything. Yeah, there was no damage. We
can't hear you guys back here.
Speak of physicalized manifestation
without damage.
And in this way again as you have begun
to understand this is one of the ways
you have begun to transform this you are
relocating the energies in areas where
it will do no harm.
Right? You are allowing release valves
to occur where the energy will do no
catastrophic effect through us. Right.
Yes, you are creating the shift. Right.
Yet El Salvador was quite damaged.
You will find that in that particular
area as was before there is still much
to be faced by that particular miniature
mass consciousness about their own
deservability and about their ability to
reconnect to nature. As of this time,
they still believe very strongly that
they have gone so far away from nature
that the only way to reconnect to it is
to absolutely level every symbol that
represents their climb away from
it. They can relearn this idea. You can
be of assistance to them in this way.
They do not have to experience it that
way. But right now that particular
culture simply has the strong belief
that they must absolutely exercise
themselves of the physiological
manifestations of the physiological
symbols of that which they consider to
be detrimental to their relationship to
nature, the artificial society they have
created, so to speak. Yet it's also
brought a lot of connection. Oh yes,
always. Well, of of course and and
bringing the world and
um towards them instead of it being so
separated as different parties that will
fight each other. So yes, as we have
said, there will still be some
physiological release of these energies
simply not anywhere near as many nor as
widespread.
Can you give us a date when you
No, I'm not I'm not talking the book.
I'm talking about a date when we can uh
acquire more knowledge for this
releasing technique. Oh, I see.
So, we can be present.
It will carry on through the
transformation for some time of the
approaching dates. Even though we will not be
dates. Even though we will not be
interacting specifically
on some of these dates, it will
begin just prior through and slightly
beyond what you call your approaching
31st, 1st and 2nd. Right?
So in your terms, it will begin within
our next session. Right? For again the
idea of the first
Surrounded by the 31st and the second is
again the commemoration of a very strong
seismic gate. Again, the commemoration
of
Appalantis, the night before All Hollows
Eve, the release of the spirits in that
way, and then the all souls and all
saints day as you call it
colloquially, the day of and the day
after the
destruction. This is a very powerful
gate for you all at this time. And that
is why many of these transformations are
occurring in this way. And that is why
many are picking up the senses of the
shifting of energy in seismological
symbols because they are very connected
to the Atlantean times and remember that
time very
strongly and can only think of a similar
shift in a similar manner. But it does
not have to be that way.
There will be about a few moments
remaining for this interaction this
evening of your time. Richard
um would you speak of this thing which
is so evident at at third density which
is the negative ego and how it is sort
of the anti-thesis the self-destructive
part of of uh human nature. All right.
Now the idea again is that it's not
generally destructive
unless you choose to believe and give
over to the negative ego the control of
your higher self. For the negative ego
is the product of the higher self and
not the master of it. You know, I'm
wondering because there's there's
feelings of hatred back and forth for
that negative ego. Lazar speaks of it.
There's a there's an intent to destroy.
There's an intense uh resentment in a
sense mostly it is a culmination and a
focus of a portion of yourself that
believes that to give over to the
totality of yourself will cause that
particular portion's
annihilation. So it resists.
Oh in other words it's too much power
for that function. Okay in a sense and
it only interprets it as self
annihilation. It does not see by
definition a blending to be that which
can also support its existence. It only
sees a blending of the totality of
yourself as that which will cease its
existence because it does not think in
integrative terms. So is it a machine?
Are you suggesting in a sense? In a
sense, it is a reactive
machine. In a sense,
it is the portion of yourself that has
been created to always
demand absolute
control. And if it doesn't get it, what
a tantrum.
It is
nurturing, loving in an unconditional
way that can teach the negative ego that
it is all right to let it become
blended with the overall aspects of
consciousness and that it will not be
annihilated but only enriched.
Not that you will experience the
manifestation, the continued
manifestation of the negativity, but
that the energy and that particular
portion of your consciousness will be
allowed to coexist equally with every
other portion. It simply has been taught
that it cannot function as an equal but
only as a
superior and therefore it rebels at any
attempt at equality.
I was wondering here if it's it is an
aspect of oneself. It's it's almost like
the the the drive or the taste to could
it be packaged in that way to say it's
it's the urge to experience uh
segregation. It's a taste. It has a it
has its own taste. Yes. Own it own
preference. To some degree it can be
represented as the creational force that
leans toward the experience of
separation. Yikes. when it is given full
reign then separation is accelerated.
Okay. On a larger scale uh the negative
ego is it a situation of a drama where
uh we we is this in other words I I have
difficulty conceiving it as an idea
where it was something that just
accidentally went arise sort of thing.
Oh no no no no. It is a part of the
definition of what you are exploring the
entire manifestation of limitation. And
the game is to regain one's power. There
seems to be part of me that knows that
that is part of the part of the
scenario. The game is to get one's power
back. That's sort of the way the story
goes in a sense to know that one has
never actually lost it. Yes. Okay. And
then um if if the body dies what happens then
um if if the body dies what happens then
to that condition of the negative ego
man you know behaving in such a way it
generally does not go with you. Ego
itself in general positive and negative.
Although there can be
aspects in the non-physical realm that
may at first seem like the negative ego
it is not exactly the same thing. Ego to
begin with is simply the function of
keeping you focused into the physical
reality you have chosen to be focused
in. Okay. So it has specific programs.
Yes. Everybody's would have a different
type thing. Yes. And negative ego can
simply be the polarity idea to allow you
to know that you are always in a state
of choice. Always have the opportunity
to be in a state of balance between the
two. Physical reality by definition is
the exploration of polarity.
And in a couple words, what would you
say uh you know the best the best no the
best way but an effective way of of
uh ceasing that that drama so to speak.
Let yourself recognize as has been
pointed out in some of the literature of
your society that anything that you have
experienced in your life as drama by
definition is for the purpose of
building
character. So now you know you are a
strong character because you have
explored been willing to explore both
the positive and the negative side. Let
it be
accepted. Let yourself know that you can
let the negative ego know that it has
done a good job for you.
Like angle is all right. It has built
your muscles in that way. It has allowed
you to explore and experience the
physical reality polarities in a very
dramatic way. Do remember transformation
is generally not the product of
mediocrity.
So the idea of a very intensely focused
drama in one direction will usually
reciprocate when you make a change in
the other direction just as strongly.
Beautiful. Thanks a lot. Ask this
timing. Can I just I need to share something
Can I just I need to share something
with you.
stand and share.
Okay. Um it's on polarity. Oh, right.
Okay. And it's on an experience that
I've had in my universe understanding
the function of polarity. Hey, and I
hope by sharing this hope hope. Yeah. I
desire by sharing this. All right. to
help uh several other people in this
room to integrate
the same experience that I've been able
to integrate and that my dear friend
here has been able to integrate. Speak
up. Can you hear me? Yes. Now we can.
Okay. Um, I like several others in this
room were involved in an organization
that keeps coming up and up and up in
our questions that we were all very
heavily involved with emotionally,
analytically, financially, financially,
financially, financially,
you name it. We had a lot of energy
wrapped up in it. And it was for some
period of time in our universes and in
my universe, I'll speak for myself right
now, a very positive experience. still
can be right and then there came a point
where this positive experience switched
into an apparently very negative
experience. All right. Okay. Now um for
myself for a long long time I have been
looking at the polarities of situations.
That is what the tool was for, right?
And in this particular situation, I was
able to glean that understanding
quite some time ago and as a result of
it to not be stuck with a lot of the
upset that a lot of my friends were
stuck with. don't write by not
recognizing that there was the positive
side of that experience and therefore
must lead to also the experience of the
negative side until we handle that that
ability. And for me, it blew out every
iota, every little bit of upset and
question and pointing fingers at and
blaming all types of people and myself
for that situation turning into what it
was. Yay. Then I was over at a friend's
house, this wonderful lady right here,
and we were discussing this idea of
polarities, and she was running this
whole trip on me.
Right. And yeah, and here we go again
about all the strength right now that
was existing or right then that was
existing in her universe in regards to
the negative experience of that idea.
And it was just kind of boring, boing,
boing, boring, boring, boring. And I was
looking at this. I was going, "Yeah."
And I'm hearing this, you know, from
lots and lots of my friends because it's
still a very strong part of his
universe. All right. Right. And so I
just mentioned to Faith, guess who was
that um what we had discussed and the
things that I had learned on the
polarities of an idea. And she said,
"Well, what did what did they do or what
did I do to create the situation?" And I
said absolutely nothing. What you did
was just create the situation and
therefore that put it into motion. But
by creating the positive side of the
situation, then automatically the
negative side gets created too. And
you're going to experience that whole
thing as a circle. And she just went
flat. Everything went totally flat. Am I
correct? In her universe. and she has
been muttering and
uh sputtering and and agonizing over
this situation for years ever since in
her universe it went to a negative
point. And I was I was wanting to and I
want to share this with all of my
friends that have been involved in the
same type of situation to help
understand that there are there does not
have to be any negative significances.
There does not have to be a cancellation
of the positiveness of a side of an idea
just because because in this physical
universe we have decided that we are
going to also experience the negative
side of an idea. We don't have to let it
cancel each other out. Yes. The
cognition that everything contains
positive and negative energy. The
willingness to have that balanced
cognition is what will paradoxically
allow you only to experience positive
manifestation. Right? Cognition of positive and
Right? Cognition of positive and
negative energy does not mean you have
to have negative manifestation.
Right? Once you spot them and then you
can you don't have to if I if I am
understanding you correctly from before
you don't have to res then resist that
negative side coming in because you
understand it. Spotting it is what puts
you by definition slightly on the
positive side. Right? The recognition
that both positive and negative energy
exist and can coexist puts you on the
positive side because that recognition
is an integrative point of view. Right.
One more thing. I told her something
that now I'm not I'm not sure that was
correct. I She said, "Well, Victoria,
why why did why did what did I do to
Right. What did I do to pull this in? or
what did they do to create this
situation? And I said to her because I I
thought I remembered you saying it to me
and then I questioned it and I may have
been creating it myself at that moment
moment that the fact of us as beings
when we create an idea and we create it
from the viewpoint of wanting to create
a positive
experience by putting
that definition on the experience that
we want it to be positive. positive
instead of
neutral. Does is that part of what
creates? The idea is in recognizing that
every symbol in every situation is
neutral and that you will have you have
the expectancy of positive manifestation
when you allow yourself to recognize
both the positive and the negative which
forms the neutrality to begin with. Oh,
so you can't just go well everything's
neutral and therefore I don't have to
experience the polarities. You still
make choices. You do not have to
experience them in a manifesting way
physically, right? But experience them
as cognition. Yes. Right. Awareness is
what you are talking about and awareness
is necessary to make choice. Right? Now
the idea also do not forget is that the
overall tool you are referring to not
that other individuals have not been
able to avail of themselves of it for
their own reasons is a very Orion
tool and it was created specifically for
the reincarnated Orion so that they
could get in touch with the
balance your cognitions the cognitions
that you are recognizing now each and
every one of you in that way having
attached attached herself to that
particular tomb are what now
allows light in Orion
and light on Earth. What is the Orion
tool? Right.
Right.
specifically, though there are many. The
entire methodology you refer to as
Scientology was created by Orions for
Orions to understand the polarities of
the Earth system and the polarities of
their home systems.
Oh, and that is why we have the negative
as well as the positive to experience.
Yes. That must be part of the blending
to understand polarity and form a
blending an opportunity Bashar to explore
an opportunity Bashar to explore
experientially the judgmental viewpoint
and see good and see where it leads.
Yes. Right. And so now that we've
integrated that experience through many
lifetimes. Yes. Right. the final
culmination so that now we can trans
transform the judgmental viewpoint into
the loving view. Yes. Thank you very much
loving view. Yes. Thank you very much
the title Orion light.
Thank you. Thank you. At this timing,
therefore, allow us to share with you in
light and in love the blending of all
factions, all
components as simply different
manifestations, diverse expressions of
the same one whole idea, the same one
whole event, the same one whole
reality. And
Allow together us to
become the
association that will play itself out
physically in your world through the
actions you are willing to be the
realities you are willing to
live. We thank you for your sharing our
unconditional love to you all. Pleasant
dream lives and life dreams. All is one
in that way. We bid you a fond and
unconditionally loving good night. Thank
you.
How did it go?
[Music] Thank you very much, Darl.
Thank you very much, Darl.
[Music]
Those of you who would like the tape of
tonight, we already got the first one
made for about uh 12 people. So, we can
have we got a high-speed tape duplicator
that can make them real fast. 4 and a
half minutes for free tape. Uh Steve, my
wife Lynn, right over here, and we can
she'll give you a number like the
supermarket
and you can have it tonight. Anyway,
thank you all for coming. will be here
next Wednesday. And if anybody sees a a
good auditorium, something like that,
please let us know.
Unless you like feeling like a sardine.