Oh, I don't say how are you all this
evening of your time as you create time
to exist.
In this way, we begin the idea of this
interaction this evening of your time by
the sharing of the remembrance that all
the ideas and concepts and points of
view and perspectives that we have
discussed with you in what you call the
past and up to this point. Many of you
will find that as you go on about the
idea of your so-called searching into
the idea of your growth, searching into
the idea of your acceleration into
spirituality so to speak, you may find
yourself coming across many of these
concepts again and again from different
sources as you call them. The idea
simply is a reflection unto you that you
are gathering together as a mass
consciousness. And so the idea of all
consciousness that is communicating to
you at this time can function in the
idea of a mass reflection. Hearing in
this way on your part what seems to be
similar information yet coming from many
different sources, many different facets
of the multi-dimensional crystal of all
that is. In this way you will find that
the information will from time to time
seem to be in your terms different from
different sources in this way. that
simply recognize that the information is
simply altered in whatever form it needs
to be to allow the individuals that are
present according to the ideas, the
beliefs and the structures that they
perceive to be their reality to also
understand the principles. For each and
every one of you have many different
points of view. And if you wish to
understand the same idea, it is in that
way easier as it is said for you to
understand it by hearing it in your own
terms. So you will find that much of the
information comes through many different
individuals in this way at different
times in different places with different
modalities different terminology so that
each and every individual that finds
themselves attracted to such information
will understand it on their own terms so
that there can be the primary
subconscious understanding that will
allow there to be the blending of the
society as you are seeking to do. Are
you all following along so far? Yes. In
this way, therefore, simply recognize
that many of the ideas you will be
discovering will allow you to come face
to face with what you have for so long
believed to be reality within your
society and allow you to examine an
opportunity to decide for yourself, to
choose for yourselves what will now be
the reality you deem you will be living
in this transformational age from third
to fourth density, as you have called
it, old to new age awareness. As you for
more and more recognition within your
consciousness of what it is that defines
for you the reality you wish to
experience upon your planet, allow
yourselves to recognize that because of
the type of society you have created
yourselves to be, many of you will be
coming from the point of view and from
the perspective of having created many
habitual ways of looking at things. And
these habits to you may be in your terms
so ingrained that you may not even
realize that you are hearing the new
information through old ears. In this
way, simply recognize that the ideas
that we are discussing, sharing with you
that we are allowed to reflect to you by
your willingness to interact with us in
this way are in this way to many of you
seemingly philosophical concepts that on
the surface sound nice. Well, that's
nice, you say. But how do you apply it?
How is it real? How do you allow it to
mechanize and manifest itself into the
real reality? Talking about it is nice.
Imagining it is nice. But what is the
real reality? Recognize the ideas we are
discussing in this way. As we have
shared with you many times, is that from
our point of view? Imagination and what
you refer to as philosophy are to us
solid reality. And we are in the
definition and description of the
so-called philosophy actually giving you
the real mechanism. It is simply that
you do not believe that the real
mechanism to manifest something into
your physical reality can be as simple
as the way it sounds. But it
is the idea simply is for you to
recognize that what we are discussing
are discussing in this way are
reflections of your
imagination which you are beginning to
recognize is just as real as physical
reality. And in fact your physical
reality is created from your
imagination. Even though you think it is
so much more real than imagination, it
is simply one fragment, one aspect, one
perspective and point of view of your
imagination that you have decided to
believe in with all your heart and all
your soul. And so it seems so much very
much more solid than what you normally
consider to be your imaginary reality.
But it is no different. What you are
learning now is that it is no different.
And that as soon as you allow yourself
to begin to blend, dream reality,
imagination reality, and physical
reality are simply different aspects of
the same one reality, you will then find
yourself dissolving and removing the
barriers, the separations, the judgments
between those different ideas. You will
not create them to be different levels.
And you will literally live your dreams.
Living within your imagination all the
time. Always dreaming. Always being
perfectly wide awake and aware at the
same time. Are you all following along?
Yes. Sharing. Sure. Yes. How are you?
Perfect. How are you? I'm perfect. Thank
you, Strawberry. Yeah.
Darlene, I gave a seminar this weekend
and you got to you got your tape played
at one of my seminars for the first time
and uh Darlene who was there sends
thanks for the experience that she had
via you. We will extend our appreciation
to any individual not because it is us
they are interacting with but because
they are willing to interact with all
the portions of themselves. I'm sure
she'll enjoy that. Thank you for
sharing. Thank you. Last week when you
were um channeling our mutual friend,
had you actually physically visited the
person a long time in an earlier
incarnation? No. And this in his earlier
incarnation? Yes. In mine? No. So you
actually uh materialized physically in a
time earlier time. Very good. Thank you.
Good. When the spirit leaves the body
and looks back at it, does this not
demonstrate that we uh are not the body?
Uh not that we are identity from it. Not
so much exactly for recognize that there
are in your terms the creation of
different levels even within
non-physical reality and so you give
yourself the opportunity to still think
of yourself as being separated even on
that level. Okay. So we're actually
taking a viewpoint of a viewpoint. Yes.
Very good. Yeah. Okay. Very nice. Thank
you. What is the light the light norm
the white light normally reported to be
seen when people die? In this way, it is
the recognition of the connection to all
of all that is. Okay. The blending of
all or at least the level that they need
to recognize as all. Understood. Thank
you, Rash. Yes. Friend of mine has a uh
her father has multiple scerosis and uh
he has been in and out various clinics,
hospitals, what have you. And uh I'm
wondering if there is something that you
could part with that we that I could
maybe help her in some way with her
father. This will take interaction with
the friend for it is in your terms quite
a personal arrangement between them and
in this way will require the
understanding of what that individual is
learning from the experience in order to
interact with them.
Simply share with your friend the idea
that every situation is chosen and every
situation is an opportunity to learn and
be of service.
All right. Okay. Uh the other thing is
that you mentioned a wolf um the animal
wolf. What does it symbol out? There are
many different specifics but in general
you can recognize it is one form of
parallel manifestation of your own
humanity as you will find that it is
representative of some of your
instinctual sides yet it still forms the
idea that you do called family groups.
So what will be mostly representative of
the idea of your familial security yet
with the embodiment of the instinct that
allows you to know your place in nature.
Okay. Thank you. Thanks. Uh our
conversation last week opened up a path
of much deeper understanding. Thank you
for opening your own doors. And uh yeah,
I didn't realize it at the time, but um
as soon as it was over, it started
happening and I want to thank you very
much for that co-creation. Well, thank
you. And I do now uh I am now actually
quite happy about being a freelancer.
Thank you. Uh in fact, I have an
interesting EC douch share ecstatic
explosion of coincidence.
The weekend I I started to think about
what it meant to be a freelancer at
various levels and I started carrying it
over into my personal situation, my job.
Nice. And so I thought well uh for the
first time I considered seriously the
idea of perhaps becoming a consultant
rather than being associated with a a
company. exploring your levels of
deservability. All right. And but that
had never occurred to me before. That is
because you were never the you you were
now. That's correct. Anyway, Monday
morning, the first phone call I got was
from a a friend from out of state. Yes.
And we were chatting and after a while,
she said, "I'm going to ask you a silly
question." Sure. And I said, "Why?" She
was a little shy about it because she
knows me quite well the way I was. Yes.
And she said, "How would you um would
you be interested in consulting on a
particular project?" I see. And I said,
"What an
excision." Uh but but I thought it was
wonderful the way this happened. All
right. But recognize you are always
making in that way decisions.
Automatically you have made decisions in
this way. It does not have to be brought
down to the idea of needing to make a
difficult decision. simply act upon what
you know to be true for you and what you
call synchronicity and coincidence in
your life will always continue because
that is how life works when you let it
and it's exciting yes right I have a
couple of other questions with respect
to to the uh interaction with naman is
it neon ne a m-
an o n m o non uh I was a little
confused because he is in third he was
in third density V still is transitional
force just like you. Okay. Now you
appeared before him and it didn't your
energy didn't interfere the way it would
understand that even within the society
being third density as it was even
within the idea of all of what you call
the suppression within the systems the
idea of interaction with other
civilizations was still normal to them.
Uhhuh. So it was different than it would
be with us. Yes. Okay. The other
question about that was I thought that
you had not developed teleportation of
of bodies. Did you get go there with
your spaceship? Of course. But did you
appear on his planet with your
spaceship? Yes. Uhhuh. Okay. Okay.
That's first there was a mental
projection. Okay. He thought he was
going crazy.
Okay. And then you landed with your
spaceship because it was normal there
and he knew he was going crazy.
space. Yes. He knew that the type of
crazy he was going was all right.
So on that planet then it was it's it's
quite common for them to see uh alien
spaceships. Oh yes. In this way not so
much alien as he would call it but
simply their own interystem ships. In
this way simply what he was describing
is that he had never seen the like of
our civilization. Okay. Thank you very
much. Thank you Sharon. Nice. Dennis
Watts is my name. I have an idea I would
like to express to you and I want you to
tell me if it is going to work or not
going to work. Now what I have maybe
what I have on my drawing board I
believe is the essence of uh that uh an
idea for implosion engine the engines
used for driving spaceships or UFOs as
we call them implosion define. Now what
implosion is to me is a system of spiral
curves using a medium of either water or
air. And what I'm looking at is to
contract through the system of spiral
curves and create what I call a circular
I call it a um implosion
manifold. And what I'm doing is using
this water to spin and gain the energy
from a suction force. And I would like
to know by circulating this air or
water, can I in essence create enough
force to drive uh a vacuum to drive for
the purpose of directing a spaceship and
and what I call control space flight or
control flight? Is that possible? Do you
understand what I'm talking about? It is
not impossible. But in this way we find
that there may be ramifications and
steps that you are including that may
still in your terms be mechanically
cumbersome. Mechanically cumbersome. Now what I'm
Mechanically cumbersome. Now what I'm
looking at is that the spiral curves in
essence will will concentrate this
atheric energy or I like to call it
maybe diamagnetic energy. All right.
Very good. Now what I'm looking at is
this concentration of diamagnetic
energy. Does it create levitation? Yes.
Good. Now the other it will mostly
create the idea if you project it in the
proper manner of an isolation field that
will allow you to create what you are
terming to be levitation. Okay. Now I'm
looking at vacuums to be able to give me
my uh directional control. Is that
possible? To some extent although again
it will not so much be what you would
refer to as direct vacuum but simply
modulations within the electromagnetic
field. Okay. Now what I would like to
know as a result of this concentrated
diamagnetic field or is it possible to
create cold current that I can make a
cool light from? Oh yes. Okay. You will
find in actual fact that it will be a
natural byproduct. Good. I just want to
know is there a way to uh insulate this
energy um from after it's being
concentrated. I don't want to be emerged
in it and continuously. a good
idea. Recognize that simply the building
of a conductive shell round and about
will divert the energy into a form that
will maintain a field outside the crowd.
What is that material can be form of
what you call magnesium?
Magnesium as very good. In this way
there will be multi-layers which will
involve magnesium copper alloys. Right.
I understand in my mind would I use
copper purely for the purpose of the
spiral uh contractive
curves copper you can experiment with that at
copper you can experiment with that at
first and determine the ratios of purity
that you
desire ratios of purity is that
important it can be depends upon the
effect that you will be satisfied with
now one more important question from the
uh books that I've read over the years
and these sightings that other people
have had, it appears that most of these
forces are created in an anticlockwise
direction. Is that important or can I go in a
Is that important or can I go in a
clockwise direction? Does it make a
difference as to the direction of the
implosion force? Yes. Which direction is
important? Anticlockwise or for you in
what you call your northern hemisphere?
Yes. Yes. It is what? Anticlockwise. A
Yes. It is what? Anticlockwise. A
okay now I have just another group of
questions dealing with universe
organization southern hemisphere clockwise
southern hemisphere clockwise
southern hemisphere clockwise are you
saying that it has to work if I'm
working in northern hemisphere of the
planet I have to go counterclockwise and
I and if I'm working in the below the
equator I have to switch it around and
go in the other direction for it to work
y are you saying that this thing is
uh bound to the earth's magnetic field
to an extent. It is using it. It's using
it. Yeah. It's channeling the earth's
magnetic field into the die
polar field. You are suggesting that
makes the design very complicated. No,
it simplifies it.
Altering this way, you will find that
all you are doing is altering a field
that already exists into a preferred
format. Yes, I I I'd agree with you 100%
on that. At least of the way I
understand it. All right. Now, our
suggestion is to simply when you find
that you are excited and drawn and
attracted to some information, act upon
it and see what you get. Oh, I'm in the
process of believe me. Thank you very
much. Now, one more question.
It come to my attention over the years
as far as information is concerned about
uh how the universe is organized and I'm
interested to know organized. I want to
know if what I have is either true or
false or there will be no true or false.
The truth is composed of all truths.
Your reality is your own. We understand
what you mean. Proceed. Okay. I would
like to know for instance it came to my
attention that this planet as we call it
earth is in the creation records called
the planet Uranchia number 606 in the
system of Satania. It has had many
titles. Does the name Uranchia to some
degree 606 mean anything to you? To some
degree. Now, but it is a vibration in
your terms that no longer exists in
exactly that format. Although there are
some ideas, variables and equations that
you may draw some conclusions from by
associating all the ideas your planet
has ever been. Okay. You are familiar
with our holy entity you call Jesus,
right? We understand. Okay. Now it come
to my attention that he was the uh
creator of the lo local universe of
Neoddon. Does that mean anything to you?
Not so much. For in what you term to be
a hierarchy from the hierarchy point of
view there is no hierarchy. And so in
this way you will find that what you're
referring to as isolated events or
connections to specific creations in
your terms let us say to put it
colloquially is a little bit muddled on
that level for you are the creator of
your own universe as well. Okay. So this
information then that I'm looking at
studying may not be what it claims to
be. Yes it is. But the idea that you are
missing is that every
terminology is only befitting the
reality in which the terminology is
created. Okay? And it does not
necessarily apply to another reality.
Okay? So that means it may be true for
me but not for 5 million other people on
the other side of the planet. Correct?
Okay. Thank you very much. Hello. I am
Nina. I want to ask you, do you know
Jesus the Christ? We are familiar with
the energy. Do you feel love for that
energy? That is in this way one of the
definitions of that energy. Thus in this
way our unconditional love and the
unconditional love of that energy are
blended. Are you from the astral regions
of the universe or would we are in your
terms fourth density extending to fifth
and sixth. In this way, we will have
connection to our astral realms, but
also have a fourth density physiological
manifestation that will assist in our
interaction with you. Uh, where do you
live in civilization? You would call
Esasani, which translates into your
language as place of living light.
Is this a a planet? In a sense, it is
not in the same vibrational matrix as
yours. Um, are you in the garden of
waiting? Are you going to be it again as
human? being on earth. I have only had
one life as you understand it upon earth
and that is within the physical channel
you see sitting before you.
So you were in the in what's his name?
Daryl, you you were Daryl before in a
sense. In a sense, when you left your
body, when after your mortal body died,
uh could you give us your experience?
What happened to you? Much the same as
you. Within this way, you will find that
our energy consciousness allowed us to
relate to a new level of existence
wherein we found ourselves attracted and
in a sense embodied again in another way
so that we could course back through
what you perceive to be time and
communicate with you to be of service in
your transformation and to assist you.
Dear Vasha, I am also a teacher.
Everyone is. Yes. And I want to ask you
um do you do you know about the solar
universes and how many they there are
infinite infinite solar universes. Are
you sure? In this way you will find that
the idea in your term can be expressed
with a finite number in your third
density reality. But the idea of third
density reality also has an infinite
number of parallels to it.
Yeah, I understand. Therefore, in that
sense, it is infinite even though each
and everyone may be able to be perceived
as a finite. Do you have friends in your
dimension who you love very much, who
are very close to you? All of them are.
Uh-huh. Understand that in our
civilization, there is no
differentiation in terms of worth or
importance. All are loved
unconditionally. In the exact meaning of
that term, unconditionally.
So in your spare there's no more
jealousy and Oh no thank you.
There is no need for that tool in our
civilization. Do you uh are you connected with the
Do you uh are you connected with the
teachings of teachers like Buddha or
Jesus to some degree? To some degree. Um
which uh which step of initiation are
you going through? This in this way will
be the idea of fourth transitional
fifth. Uh are you in the garden of waiting so
Uh are you in the garden of waiting so
to speak uh getting ready for another
incarnation on planet earth? No. Which
uh we are not in this way at this time
of your cycle anymore at all? At all. So
you will not take any more physical
bodies on any planets.
I will be fifth density non-physical.
Non-physical. Is this called etherical
or astral?
More etheric. More etherical. You mean
totally ethereical like for example
beings from Venus like Ashtar? More
along that line. Uhhuh. That's very
interesting. So tell me about tell me
tell me about your UFO. How does it look
in the inside from the inside? In this
way you will find that the particular
craft that I am want to be using more
often than not will be in your terms
triangular preided equilateral.
Therefore, you will find that the
interior will be hexagonal for the three
points will be isolated for machinery.
The central portion being relegated to
what you would call control. That sounds
great. Uh c could you uh be visible to
our eyes? Oh yes. When and where our
opportunity in this way will simply find
that there are many beings that are
interacting with your civilization at
this time and we will not be physically
the first to interact with you. For we
are assisting the others that will be
the first. In your terms of time
counting, our opportunity to interact
with you will occur somewhere generally
within the next 10 to 13 of your years.
Uhhuh. So you are not directly connected
with the intergalactic
uh plan of evacuating planet Earth.
There is no evacuation necessary. Well,
but in case the [\h__\h] will hit the fence.
Understand that if I may share with you
our viewpoint of what you are defining
they are. Yes, please recognize that
what you are ascribing to is one point
of view that stems from some connections
that still are within the realms of
third density judgment. The idea that
you think you need saving. The idea from
our point of view is you do not need
saving. The idea is that what you are
believing to be a connection that will
be formed with what you are calling
intergalactic associations will be simply the
associations will be simply the
recognition of what reality you desire
upon your planet. The choosing of that
reality, the acting as if that reality
is real for you, the creation of the
vibration on your part of that reality.
Therefore, identifying with the
intergalactic association. Therefore, by
analogy, lifting yourselves beyond the
idea of needing to experience [\h__\h]
So, uh but do you do you um do you
believe or do you realize that one day
we are going to step into levitation
beings with our one moment, one moment?
One moment. One
moment. Understand once again from our
point of view certain individuals may
experience a liberal version of that but
not all have to. The idea from our point
of view is to assist you in
recognizing that you are the controllers
of this world that you are on. And
therefore the idea is that to create the
type of reality you desire now with your
convictions will
alleviate the point of view that you
need to be saved. And in this way you
will rechan much of what you have
predicted for yourselves to be negative
aspects of transformation in destructive
terms into positive transformations so
that you will simply elevate not so much
within the idea of beams into crap but
the idea of the entire planetary energy
into fourth density light bodies that do
not need saving.
Okay. Since you said we are all
teachers, do you recognize that there
are higher teachings and teachings which
are meant for different kinds of
development. One moment. The idea of
that recognition again will be that what
you have stated to us is a
contradiction. Different teachings. Yes,
I know what you mean when you say
higher. But once again recognize that
the idea of hierarchies is a third
density point of view. From within the
hierarchy there is but oneness. And the
recognition that there are different
teachings for different points of view
and different levels simply makes the
teachings different. Not higher in the
sense of better. Higher only in the
sense that it represents a different
vibration. But no better simply
different. Okay. You said you were uh in a sense uh
Okay. You said you were uh in a sense uh
living with Daryl's or in Daryl's last
life. So you said you only had one
incarnation on planet Earth. Did I
understand? As what you are perceiving
to be Daryl. Uhhuh. So you you say you
only had one incarnation on planet
Earth? Yes. Yes. Yes. All of my other
lives have been on other civilizations,
particularly my own. Could you name some
of them, please? At this point only
Espani will apply.
So it's like two incarnations you had.
So far many incarnations within my own
society. Within your own society which
is rare. Esasoni. Esasoni. Where is
that? Approximately in your terms. 500
light years distant but in this way not
visible to you. It is not within your
vibratory plane. What do I have to do in
order to come and visit you there where
you are now? Go to sleep. Uhhuh. or
leave your body. Uhhuh. Do you think
that um when I wouldn't eat food for
like uh let's say 3 days and just drink
drink water, I would have uh
possibilities to go to even other
places. It is possible. It will be up to
your own personal vibration and what
agreements you have made with the rest
of your society as to how you will use
that experience to serve them. Can you
see any spirits around me? There are
always interactions going on with
everyone. to us. Our perspective of all
of you is that you are linked and
connected with infinite intelligence in
many different ways. Do you know any of
them? Do you know any of the spirits
around me? One
moment. To our perception at this time,
although I will once again caution you
that to us labels are an arbitrary
thing. You follow me? kind of
labels create separation
rather than integration. Therefore, what
we will now label for you
briefly according to what we are allowed
to label for you
briefly will only be arbitrary names. In
this way, even though you may have
connection and association to them, to
us labels are arbitrary definitions. I
understand. All right. Um in this way
our perception at this time is that
there will be to some degree what you
are calling sixth density Vujian
connection some serious connection and
some of what is called the idea of
identification with the energy of the
crown chakra shasta in this way what you
would call St. Germaine.
Oh
hello I want to ask you um may I ask you
a question? Oh yes. May we allow the
interaction of others at this time? Oh
yes. Thank you guys. I just want to
thank you uh for my experience last uh
week. It's uh the past week has been
extremely full and rich and I understand
everything that occurred in the last 10
months. And I understand it as a as a
coincidence. Yes. Coincidence, not
accidental. The
entire Yes. Yes. synchronicity. Yeah. um
and all that terror and uh confusion and
everything. It's just God in one week. I
can't believe it's just lovely. Thank
you for forming a connection to the rest
of all that is and also to everyone
here. I mean filled with all of you.
Um the other thing I would like to say
is that my skin is also becoming more
subtly luminous unless of course it's
just my imagination.
In addition, I would like to um I came
across an idea the other day where
someone described the uh transcendence
of
familiarity in which um the idea of
labeling things as you were just talking
about becomes almost well if you get the
idea in other words the end product of
it is is that there's really no way to
know what anything is if you don't label
it in this way. You get what I mean?
Knowing is simply knowing. You do not
need a label to know what you know.
Right? Labeling is for your outer aware
physiological ego consciousness to be
able to make sense of what you know in
physical terms in certain conditions.
But recognize you can still function in
the life in many ways by simply knowing
what you need to know. In other words,
if you wish an analogy, the idea let us
say if you were a completely instinctual
surgeon. You could simply walk into an
operating room, not have a label for any
tool, and simply know which one to pick
up to do the operation, right? You would
simply know. Gotcha. Because the
vibration is what you would be feeling.
Mhm. Um this is connected with the idea of um
Um this is connected with the idea of um
actually I want to skip on to something
else. Oh, right. Uh the other thing is
was that there is a person in my life
who um in a dream state has uh I felt
the quality of this person's love which
uh and this person has told me that um I
represent to them what it's like to love
someone and and things like that that's
been reflected to me by the person and
but this person but uh I I have a
strange response to this person and if
there's any judgment in it I want it
gone but do not judge your judgment.
Well, okay. Allow it to be integrated so
that it can transform into preference
and love.
Yeah. Right now, I'm not preferring this
and I find it a little a little strange.
What do you prefer?
Um, this person I find this it's very
judgmental, but I'm going to say it
anyway. All right. This person is I find
very fawning and it's almost as if I am
the most woripped more important person
and I just hate Then what does this give
you an opportunity to do? Um I have let
this person know that I find that very
unequal. All right. I don't know how
real it is to that person yet. That does
not matter. As long as you are willing
to reflect to them the light and love of
the understanding that they are equal to
you then you are functioning in your
responsibility to them. You cannot be
responsible for them. That's true. You
can only be responsible to them by being
responsible for who you are. Okay? Being
yourself. The part that I have a little
trouble with is my own reaction to it.
It's almost cruel. Um then in this way,
simply recognize again if you truly wish
to serve them, there is no need for that
idea. for simply being who you are. If
you are willing to fully be that
vibration, you will not experience them
in a negative way. You will love them
for what they are and radiate your love
to them so they have an opportunity to
see within you a reflection they can, if
they so desire, change themselves to
share with you. Thank you very much.
Well, thank you. For sure. Sure. You
Yes. Um I would like some reflection
from you on how I can assist my father.
whom I love very much. In what way?
To I would like to be able to share with
him his the
understanding of his own
immortality because he doesn't really
believe that. So well he will find out
soon enough. That's true. I know.
It would be so wonderful to be able to
somehow have you simply shared the ideas
you believe. Yes, I have to some extent.
That is all you can do. It is up to that
individual to choose for themselves.
That is all there is to it. Be who you
are. That is what gives them the best
opportunity to decide whether they want
to share that idea with you or not. Your
willingness to continue the conviction
in your beliefs is what will instill
within them an understanding of your
persistence without forcing on them your
ideas. Thank you. You
Thank you. You
um uh before you said like not to judge
people and I was Oh, you can if you wish
simply that if you do judge people, you
are automatically judging yourself and
thereby limiting yourself in the same
way that you limit them by judging them.
Well, I was wondering. I'm having
trouble not judging people. How How
could you do that? Help me. Simply
recognize that the idea is this. You can
prefer what you want to prefer without
invalidating everything you don't
prefer. For in this way recognize if you know
For in this way recognize if you know
that you prefer a certain vibration, a
certain idea, a certain reality, your
ability to be that reality, to
experience that reality is directly
proportional to your willingness to
grant equality to all realities within
creation. For then you are supporting
all the different ways that the creator
can manifest itself including the way
you have chosen to manifest. By
supporting everything, you are
automatically supported in what you want
to be. By invalidating even one portion
of the way something expresses itself
within creation, you are automatically
removing your connection to all that is
and removing support from yourself in
what you want to be. Does that assist
you? Yes. Thank you. Thank you.
I have a feeling that life is about
healing yourself. Life is about living.
Okay. Not healing yourself unless you
create the idea that you are diseased to
begin with. No, that's not what I'm
saying. All right. I just want to state
this before I ask the questions and I
also feel it's about loving and sharing
and helping other people. So I was
wondering why there is so much iousness
and pain because as a
civilization you decided to explore one
of the aspects of creation that can be
explored and this particular aspect is
called limitation. You are and have
become the masters of limitation. Y now
you are at the end of the cycle of
limitation. You are now discovering,
reawakening, remembering that you are
integrated as a part of all that is.
That is why you are now exploring many
of the ideas you are now exploring.
Simply what you will find is that
because you have been doing
limitation for many of tens of
thousands, hundreds of thousands of your
years as you count time, as you created
time in which to experience limitation,
you have created another notion out of
limitation, habit.
It is only the belief that a habit is
something difficult to change that
creates for you the continuation of any
particular aspect of pain and or
suffering that you find to be within
your life. All pain all pain mental,
emotional, spiritual and physical. All
pain is the result of separating a
portion of yourself from the rest of all
that is that you are. All pain is
separation and judgment. all of it.
Therefore, when you simply recognize the
concept within yourself that you no
longer need pain to show you the
understandings, the experiences you have
chosen to experience in this life, but
that you can create a positive
manifestation, a positive situation in
which to live the same idea, in which to
discover the same purpose. Then you can
allow pain to transform itself into
another modality, another frame of
reference that will allow you to know
that pain is only a tool. It is your
choice to experience it or not. And that
if you are willing to love yourself and
all that is as unconditionally as all
that is loves you, you will then know
that you deserve happiness. It is your
birthright. Pain is your choice.
Recognize against it is simply a matter
of not being quite so hard upon
yourselves. For you did not have to do
anything to deserve to exist. Existence
was granted to you automatically by all
that is. Therefore, treat yourself with
the same love and the same respect that
all that is treated you in creating you.
Thank you.
Yes. Since January, anybody that's tried
to launch a rocket into space with a
satellite or anything like that, they're
all blown up. Is that just a
manifestation of the mass consciousness
of this civilization or is there an
interaction with some other
civilization? It is mostly your
recognition because you are now
beginning to identify with the vibration
of some other civilizations that you
have been creating much in the way of
judgment within your technology in this
way. And you are giving yourself an
opportunity to recognize it is now about
forming the idea of a union upon your
planet and not forming the idea of
competition and spying upon each other and keeping
and spying upon each other and keeping
everything covert. So you are forming an
energy action to allow yourselves to
tell yourself with many different forms
and many different symbolic ways that
you may be pushing yourselves a little
too hard. In this way you may be racing
towards destruction so you will not
allow it. You are putting the stops upon
yourself. Why it is our perception at
this time that you are accelerating in a
manner and to a degree that will mean
that you do not need to be saved.
Elevate yourselves. recognize every individual,
yourselves. recognize every individual,
every single individual makes a
difference in the whole.
There are now upon your planet more than
enough individuals to have created what
you call a kickover momentum. It will
continue. That is our perception at this time. You
That is our perception at this time. You
can change it. You always have the
opportunity to change it.
It is simply our perception that we do
not think you will. That however is
simply our opinion. Ours.
We prefer it that way. Well, thank you.
Does June 14th hold anything? It
obviously holds something for you.
[Music] Otherwise, I assume you would not be
Otherwise, I assume you would not be
asking me. What is the connection you
are making?
several people that I know about
something significant happened happening
on June 4th. One in particular, this
lady uh has actually dreamt her death or
occur the 14th and she she feels very
ready for it. All right. Then she can
manifest it in whatever way she wishes
to, either physiologically or simply
energy-wise, allowing herself to know
that she will be in a sense dead and
then reborn as a new understanding of
herself within the new acceleration.
There are many types of death. They are
all transformational. Well, I'm not
necessarily interested in that specific
lady. I just wanted
to relate something that has been given
to me. All right. terms of a 14. Again,
understand anything you find occurring
in your life, including what information
appears in your life, obviously you are
attracting for your own reasons.
Otherwise, you would hear something
else. Therefore, act instinctively upon
it and you also can partake of whatever
energy is being co-created for whatever
your imagination wishes to make use of.
Simply all we are saying to be
colloquial in your language is that you
happen to be inviting yourself to
someone's particular
party. Go or don't is up to you. But
allow yourself to simply know that you
may now, many of you may now begin to
recognize within each other the timings
that you are all co-creating for
yourselves so as to function as a
holographic reflection for each other
about your own timings. Well, I thought
that's what was so significant in as
much as these people don't know each
other. They don't even know that I'm
here or know you or anything like that.
It's just that perhaps not consciously
but obviously on whatever level they
need to they know. Thank you.
Um I have a question about um in my
dreams I occasionally visit an inner
family and I was wondering if this is
you all have in a sense spiritual
psychic families as well as
physiological ones.
Um, I've decided
to myself become the idea of teaching
people about blending the dream world.
Oh, thank you very much for choosing to
make a difference in that way. And
um one of the things that
um I received some information from an
entity that I'm beginning to I'm just
learning how to channel right now. You
have always channeled. You are simply
putting a specific notation upon it now.
Okay. And um all of you have always
channeled. You channel yourselves into
physical reality.
Um, one of the devices I was asking this
entity whether one of the devices that
I've been imagining has any association
with the the dreams or any connection to
that define.
Well, I have I have on in the last
couple weeks been describing devices
that I've received from Yes. an
individual from your planet. Yes. He's
fine. The one that I'm seeing, it's very hard
The one that I'm seeing, it's very hard
to describe. It's like a long
um I don't know, it's like a long curve
and then it has like a French curve that
connects the two
um projections that bend to come back to
that French curve. I just call it a
French curve device.
And and then it also has like a strand
that connects the top and the bottom of the
connects the top and the bottom of the
French curve and with beads on it or
crystals on it. It's not real clear to
me. I haven't you are interpreting to
some degree into something that you can
understand. It is not that you will
create identically the device as it can exist
identically the device as it can exist
within our civilization. But your own
version can suffice. In this way, our
understanding of what you are defining
is an electromagnetic oric
modulation antenna, so to speak, but not
really antenna as you understand it.
And this does have some relationship to
the dream work that I'm doing. Yes.
Okay. My understanding of it is that it does
My understanding of it is that it does
help in blending the three worlds. Yes,
the triad. Yes. And um I was to shed
some light on that. In this way, simply
all we will ask you to continue to do is
trust your imagination and act upon it
knowing that the symbols that you
receive are correct for you or someone
else would have received them.
Act upon them in trust. They will
manifest what they need to manifest in
your reality to allow you to be the idea
you are willing to be. Again, the
universe is not
pointless. Therefore, all that you can
receive will in your terms function
within the reality you are defining
yourself to be. You cannot receive
anything else other than that which does
fit into the reality you define yourself
to be.
Okay, you follow me? Yes, I do. I have
one other question.
Um I'm curious about in the Chinese
symbol of
um balance. I've forgotten the name of
the symbol, but it's like it looks like
two fishes.
The yin and yang symbol. Well, in that
symbol and in various other sort of
connections, the feminine is connected
with negative side in a sense. This does not
negative side in a sense. This does not
mean in your terms negative quote
unquote bad. It means negative
receptive. Okay. I was just wondering
how we created it being associated with
the negative bad because in this way you
have created once again separation
within yourself which means separation
within the polarities of the male female
energies within each and every one of
you. The idea is that when you create a
society that functions upon rigidized
structures and judgment in that way, you
will find that the individuals that will
be created to function within such a
society will create themselves in your
terms to be very vibrationally rigid as
well. Thus more aggressive and less
receptive. Okay? Thus, the idea is that
in order to quote unquote survive within
the structure of society you have
created, it is quote unquote bad to be
weak, bad to be receptive. That is what
you have created yourselves to be. That
is where it comes from. Now you are
beginning to integrate and recognize
this strength is what comes from
vulnerability. For vulnerability is as we have said
For vulnerability is as we have said
being open to all that is. Being open to
all that is is being connected to all
that is. Being connected to all that is
is being as strong as all that is.
Vulnerability is ultimate strength. That
is what you are running. And that is why
you are all now male and female blending
the male female energy within each and
every one of you. Because you have
created it to be a polarity in physical
reality. You are now binding it in a
sense back together in light and love.
You are marrying the portions within
yourselves to be one.
Also, I have one other or two other real
quick questions. One, um, I received
information from my dream world that the
physical life that we experience is the
least conscious of the three dream
worlds in a sense. Okay. And then the
the last question I have about
specifically about a dream. I had a
dream in which I it didn't feel like
this planet, but I'm not certain about
that. I was in an enclosure in which
several young people were being taught.
I was one of the young people. An
enclosure of stone. An enclosure of
stone. Yes. And there was no roof on
this enclosure. And I was fantasizing about
enclosure. And I was fantasizing about
dancing and not paying attention to what
seemed to be
geometry or geology or physics or some
combination of those elements. And the
teacher got really annoyed with me for
not paying attention and not paying
taking notes. And uh so she confronted
me about that and and I think I
confronted her back or and I'm not quite
certain what I said but I
basically was not intimidated by you
know her confrontation. All right. And
then she broke us up into like a a you
know we had a break. Nice. And there was
another, you know, outdoor enclosed
classroom that was like caddy corner to
hours that had a corridor between and we
all went over to the other one except
for myself and a few kids who did some I
did some dance acrobatic dance type
stuff. And then a man came through
who the instant I saw him, I knew that
he would like somehow be involved in
either enslaving us or something.
So I left out a back door and the
teacher although she knew she was going
to get in trouble let all of us out
those who were aware that we were in
trouble and those that were left she you
know could not save. I was wondering if
you could tell me where this dream comes
from. All we can share with you at this
time is that you are forming a double
vision connection in a parallel time track.
connection in a parallel time track.
Do not take either of them literally for
now, although there is some literalness
to the event you are describing. But
simply in this way, understand that the
energy is a parallel
creation in not only what you have
termed athism,
but also to some degree some of what is
termed the Orion energy as an offshoot
and to some degree was played out even
yet again in what you call Mayan
civilizations. Thus forming once again for yourself
Thus forming once again for yourself
with that particular aspect another
triad foundation.
Okay. Can I explore more of this in my
dream world? Of course. Always.
One more. You. Thank you.
Um, okay. I have to go slow with this
one because this is I feel uncomfortable
about expressing this. If you say so.
You are among threatened. Thank you.
always, no matter where you are. By the
way,
um, now this kind of circumstance has
happened. I've created it many different
times. All right. In many different
ways. Oh, you must enjoy it. Maybe so.
And also that I'm learning through it.
All right. That is enjoyable. Yeah. And
this what I feel proud of is that this
is the first time I'm expressing it. Why
do you do? Okay. Um
now, okay. When I first got interested
in coming here to listen to you, um I
was coming with great
enthusiasm and feeling quite equal.
Nice. And then what I started feeling in
And then what I started feeling in
myself was fear because I started to
feel myself become a groupy. Oh, right.
Of yours. And started to feel that this
is ridiculous. I don't want to
uh support something inside myself where
I feel like I'm going to give my power
up to you. Neither do we. Right. And
also because I think in some past
lifetimes I've had some experiences
of being in a sort of like a Jim Jones
type of thing and working out through
it. Um. All right. Okay.
You are doing splendidly so far. Thank
you. Thank you. Please continue.
Recognize, if I may remind you, anything
any of you ever have to say is a gift to
everyone else.
So, we thank you for what you are
willing to share. Please continue. Okay.
Okay. Then I stopped coming for a while
because I
felt I felt like I didn't quite know
what to do with I really enjoy coming
here. I really enjoy the people. I
really enjoy listening to you and with
you. Thank
you. And I also
felt stressed with with the idea
of I don't know enjoying you too much or
or I just didn't want to
um I just don't want to become a groupy.
I really then you are not recognize the
idea simply is that what we to use your
terminology would wish for you is that
you are willing to recognize you do not
need us that you are willing to act upon
what you know to be true for you. do
what you will. And if you are willing to
simply interact with us, that it be not
because you need to be with us, not that
we can supply you with anything that you
do not already have access to, but
simply because you are willing to be
equal to us and simply give us the gift
of your presence in sharing.
Right? Which is why I've started to come
back because I'm interested in being
here as as equal to Thank you. to you,
to everyone else.
Um, what thank you. What I feel still
strange with though
is is okay. Moving off of that whole
scenario now I feel a little strange
just interacting with people in this new
approach feeling where
is because I think I relate spatially to
people and to myself
in in how I am. Um,
you do recognize that you are
discovering exactly right now how to
relate by sharing your convictions and
statements the vibrational reality you
now know yourself to be. You are now
functioning quote unquote as an equal
teacher and a learner by sharing the
vibrations of your reality. That is how
you relate. You are doing splendid
learning. Thank you. Thank you. What I feel
Thank you. Thank you. What I feel
strange with though
is is being is saying something that I'm
scared of. Is saying my fears because
of. Is saying my fears because
But then you are making your fears your
friends and letting them serve you so
that they do not have to scare you. All right.
All right.
Um Okay, then if I put this
stuff aside
within you.
But I'm wanting to move it through. It
will. Okay. But it can only move through
when you take it within you, not cast it
aside. That is why we suggest that if
you allow your fears to be your friends,
you will then be able to receive the
message they are there to deliver to
you. simply that they deliver messages
in ways that force you to pay attention
is all that you call
fear because maybe you are simply being
a little bit stubborn in your habits and
not willing to hear the message in a
softer tone. So many of you will create
fears in order to pay attention to the
messages. Simply recognize that that is
all it is there for. Once you accept the
message, it will transform into
something else. You no longer need to
experience it as negative fear.
Okay. Okay. Then in in relating to
people as an equal. Yes. Okay. Okay.
Then this goes back to also my family
structure. Oh, which I've moved from and
I shared with you last Monday about
about reexperiencing my four-year-old
within me. Yes. Okay.
Um Okay. In my family structure, I was
the youngest child and
um well, always having to find myself
than the others in my family because
they were very intimidating. They wanted
me to be responsible to them in being
the little girl. All right. Always the
little girl. So I would
um pay difference to them. All right.
You obviously I will assume at any rate
understand now of course that that was a
perfect opportunity for you to come to
terms with your own inner strength.
trans private. The idea that in placing
yourself in a situation where you were
considered to be so much less, it
allowed you in your terms to gather
together the strength to recognize your
equality. Okay. Yeah. To create equality
for yourself so that once you did so it
would be unmovable, unshakable.
All right. But then very creative. Thank
you. But then still uh Okay. I've I've
moved through some of it. Sometimes I
still relate to pe to other people
according to my family's pecking order.
You do understand, however, this when
you relate to people in the way you
quote unquote used to and when you
relate to people in another way, you are
two different
people. You that relates to everyone
equally is not the person that relates
to others unequally. You are not the
same person. Therefore, in your
sentence, you are contradicting the idea
that one person can be responsible for
both actions.
Who you want to be act accordingly. That
will be the reality you experience. When
you experience quote unquote different
realities, it is because you are
defining yourself in one moment to be
one person and in another person.
Okay. Then then okay then what comes
next is the feeling of
just so to speak being blank when I
relate to people. All right trying out
the um newness. Yes. It is simply a
recognition that every situation is
fundamentally neutral. Every situation you are the one
neutral. Every situation you are the one
that gives situations meaning. Did you
all hear that?
Every situation is fundamentally
neutral. No situation has builtin
meaning. You give it meaning according
to your outlook, your attitude. Positive
attitude, positive effect, positive
result to a neutral situation. Negative
attitude, negative effect will you
attract to you.
Okay. Okay. Then with that part of me
that's that's just willing to go and try
things a new
um that feels a little scary. All right,
that feels awkward. You will get used to
it.
Okay. All right. Recognize you have in
your terms gotten used to many things in
your life. This will be no exception.
And the sooner you are willing to
recognize that everything you used to be
not used to, you have gotten used to and
apply that idea to the new situation,
you will get used to it that much more
quickly. Okay. Great. In other words,
trust. All right. All right. Thank you. Then
All right. All right. Thank you. Then
the second part is Well, that was all
the That was
all I had a dream yesterday morning. It
was I dreamt about
um seeing photographers's work on
dolphins. Nice. And being on a ship,
right? And I was seeing the photographs
um as if as if he could had created a
photo journal. And he had taken pictures
of dolphins in all
um directions. Do not forget that you
are the photographer.
Oh, okay. But there was one shark among
them, but it was it was a dolphin, but
it had teeth. All right.
So it looked like a shark and that was
just a little odd looking because that
was from the photograph that was taken
from underneath them. Simply recognize
that once again the dolphin
consciousness which is connected also to
the serious consciousness when they
interact with you in your dream
realities which they are more than
willing to do because they love you so
dearly is more than willing to reflect
to you some of those portions within
yourself that you yourself fear. So you
were seeing your own teeth.
All right. And then the rest of the
photos were were so clear. I mean, all
the photos were so clear and colorful.
Yes. That when I woke up, I thought,
"Wait a minute, that was a dream." And
it was it was real
and it was a dream. Same thing.
Um, but I don't think about dolphins
really when I'm awake. Obviously you did
then for you were directly in communication
for you were directly in communication
with their consciousness. Yeah, that was
that is simply the level you allow
yourself to be comfortable with it. You
can become just as comfortable in your
waking state so to speak. Then how do I
hear them in my waking state? The same
way you hear them in your dreams. You
feel them. You know them. Do not forget
the idea of telepathy is that to love
them is to know them. Telepathy is
emotionally activated, not mentally
activated. That is why individuals you
consider to be in love often seem to
know each other's thoughts.
We don't really talk to each other. We
just either I either It is a form of
talking. Okay. Because I either see them
or I play with them. Nice. It is all
communication. Perhaps more on their
terms than yours, but you can also get
used to it. It is very enjoyable.
Very ecstatic. Do not fight your own
ecstasy.
Yeah, that was what I was realizing the
other day.
Thank you. Thank you very much. [Music]
I've got a question. Oh, what? I've
wanted to find the bill for a long time
and um I was
wondering um what was it like in my last
lifetime? In my last life. What do you
imagine it was like?
Wow. Have you had in what you call your
Have you had in what you call your
earlier childhood what seemed to be
memories of a place you have never been?
Sort of. Where?
Well, out in the country. Daddy, what do
you smell? What do you feel? What do you
hear out in the country? Bird. Yay. Yes.
Do you have a feeling as to where you
were? Do you
Do you
think that you were in what you call the
country you are in now or another
country? How does it feel to you? What are you
How does it feel to you? What are you
wearing in that life?
dress. What color?
White with yellow flowers. All right.
Did you think it was beautiful? Yes.
Who gave it to you?
Do not think about it. Trust your first
impression. Who gave it to
you? What did she look
like? Can you see her? See her right now
in your imagination. See your mother
then in that light giving you that
dress. Yes. What did she look like?
Simply describe her as you see
her. And in your terms, it was, let us
say, rare that the day was so sunny.
Did you find that occurred quite often
for [Music]
[Music]
you? Did your mother ever talk about
things that were going on in the world
that disturbed
you? Never.
Did you find that your mother talked
with your father about such things?
No, I never I never.
Use your imagination right now. You are
out in that field. All
right. Do you know where your house is?
Yes. In your imagination, walk towards
it. Do not go in, but recognize that
your mother and your father, is he
there? Are having a conversation? They
do not expect you to be
overhearing. But
listen, what are they talking about?
What words do you recognize? What words
do you not
recognize? Let them come into your
imagination. They do not have to follow
a particular order. What words pop into
your mind?
What is it?
That that my cat ran.
Your cat ran?
Is that what you heard? Yes.
What else did they
say? The was very nice.
What else besides about the cat? Do not
think you are thinking. Do not think.
Simply listen. The conversation is going
on. You do not have to create it. Simply
listen. Do not think about
it. Now just simply imagine that your
mother and father are talking in that
light. What is a word your mother said
often? Do not think. Say it
Do not think. Say it
now. The first thing that comes into
your mind. Say it now. Dear.
Dear. All right. What about your father?
What did he say quite
often? You are thinking. Do not
think. Feel. Feel. Feel what he said.
Feel what he said.
What do you
feel? Say anything that comes into your
mind at all.
All right. Very good. Very good. See him
looking at the newspaper.
All right. Can you see him looking at
the newspaper in your imagination? Yes.
What expression is on his face? Think
again. Look at his eyes. Look at his
eyes. Now, I want you to do something a
little bit different.
You remain looking at him. You remain as
that little girl thinking that he is
enjoying his
paper. Now in your imagination, I want
you to do a little pretend.
I want you to pretend that while you are
the little girl looking at your father,
looking at his paper, I want you to for
a moment also be your mother looking at
him.
Does he look different when he looks at
the paper if you are your mother looking
at him? Yes. What changes within his
eyes?
Do not be afraid to say what you
see. You cannot get any of this wrong. His
eyes like he was looking at it. No.
All right. Do you mean he is very
intently looking at it? Yes.
Thank you. One
moment. What I can share with you about
your last life at this
time will be
this. Anything you experienced
then of what you consider to
be the
love, the happiness of the
family, the joy that you experience in
and around your
home are all available to you again in
this life and do not have to be disrupted
life and do not have to be disrupted
again.
You will not be cast in this
way from things that you
enjoy. Nothing
will come between
you and the idea of what you enjoy about
your family
life. For there will be in our
perception not
again another such war to break you
apart.
You were in what is called
Europe. What you are remembering is one
of the last times you remember that in
your terms was happy for you. From that
point forward, you found that your family
forward, you found that your family
became progressively more worried about
the state of affairs in the
world until such point as it disrupted
the life that you
had. At this
time, simply recognize that the time
frame would be just prior to what you
call World War II.
But in this
way, be joyful, for the flowers are
yours again, and they will always bloom from
again, and they will always bloom from
this point
forward. And the family has expanded to
include the entire
world. And now
everywhere shall be your home.
We thank
you. You may all take a short break.
All right, we will say shouting for
sure. For sure. Okay.
For sure. Okay.
Since you have many seeds for growth and
very juicy and big spaces, I've decided
to call you watermelon. Right. [Music] Okay.
Okay.
Couple of goodies. All right. Are you
able um via this particular method of
channeling to telepathically pick up
images? If I were to form some images
without verbalizing them, would you be
able to pick? It can occur and from time
to time in a sense does occur. Although
the idea of drawing specific attention
to it is what shuts it off. Excellent.
But in this way, it created to be a more
analytical process rather than the
emotional process of what would be a
naturally ongoing communication.
This is why you will find again it is
not impossible but simply that many of
your scientists in exploring the idea of
telepathy and ESV in their laboratories
create their interaction in what you
call a sterile environment. They are
actually stopping the process they want
to observe. put in way the idea of that
sort of telepathic communication more
often than not once again not that it
cannot occur under the circumstances you
are defining but more often than not
will be a spontaneous product of an
emotional interaction. Thus you will
find that many times as we perceive our
interactions with you we do receive the
i of translations of imagery in your way
from the vibration you happen to be
simply in this way we take it as part
and parcel of the interaction as it is
ongoing. Nice. Nice.
What have you learned about this?
But in this way,
the strength that you have used to
create separation is now being applied
more and more to the creation of
integration upon our planet. Thus, there
will be an
opportunity to share
Let us say a different form of this
communication to some degree altogether
commencing in for us in this way what
you turn out to
be the October month of this year
very good and what have you learned
about yourself
in this way that I am connected and able
to perceive that much more of the
manifestation of all that is through you
that you are allowing us to share that
we are expanding within our civilization
to other levels of consciousness in many
more roots than we had expected in this
way. For we will find that in
interacting with you, you give us a
reflection of the idea of that many more
ways, many more perspectives, many more
angles that there can be created within
all that is through your willingness to
explore to the depths you have been
willing to explore limitation. This
gives us the understanding that our
connections to all that is are in your
terms much more varied than we may also
realize. Very nice. Thank you for you. [Music]
The one that said one, two, three.
Thank you.
Um I've been exploring the idea of
um reincarnating in groups
as opposed to reincarnating as uh
individuals coming in and the it's not
as opposed it is concurrent. and coming
here together in agreement. And I have a
question. Is is this group we're here
with in some sort of agreement in that
sense? Obviously, since you are all here now,
Obviously, since you are all here now,
it is not that you have all shared every
life, but that there have been general
times, general ideas, general aspects
going on, similar occurrences in
different civilizations that you have
partaken of. More likely than not, the
last let us say time in which it is most
likely that you all were at least
relatively close in physical time aspect
was in what we perceive to be ais.
For in this way you will find that it
was within Atalas that much of the
separation you are experiencing was
created. And thus you each went your own
ways forming minor groups here and there
partaking of different situations until
you now find yourselves once again in an
almost historic parallel of Atlantis
what you call the United States of
America. Does that answer your question? Yes.
Does that answer your question? Yes.
Thank you. And I have a
second two of them. No way.
[Music] um in the sense of exploring um all of
um in the sense of exploring um all of
our possibilities and our dreams and our
imagination um I sometimes come through a process of
um I sometimes come through a process of
looking you're aware of Buddhist
teachings about the ego to some degree
um a sense
of there's a real joy in in the
expansion of belief But I've also found
in the past that sometimes in those
expansions um one's ego or my ego um has
come back and kind of owned those
changes and expansions
um and I worry about that. Understand
that it is not in your terms the ego
that does so but the judgment the
negative ego. There is positive and
negative ego.
Recognize that the idea you are
attempting to assimilate is negative
ego, not positive ego. Positive ego has
just as much right to assume authorship
of all that you do in many ways, for it
is a part of you as you have created it
to be. The primary function of physical
ego is simply to keep you focused in the
physical reality you have chosen to be
focused within. Plain and simple, that
is all it does. When you judge however
you may create the aspect you call
negative ego which is assigning to the
ego the creation that in your terms
actually comes from the higher self. Now
the ego does create a version of the
idea so that you can experience it in
physical reality. It must create a model
a reflection in physical reality that
you can relate to with what you call the
senses. In this way, in that sense, and
in that portion of the creation, it does
claim authorship, but not to the total
whole in that way. And when you place
your ego in charge of running at all,
that is when you create an ego that is
in your terms unstable and likely to go
into negativity for you are giving it
far more than the definition of its
existence and it cannot handle the job.
So in a sense, it is a kind of
designer of our energy in a sense not
control but taking that energy and
putting it into some form some direction
without judgment but a design it is
responsible for what you perceive in the
physical reality in physical terms of
what you experience in the physical
reality it creates the physiological
symbols for the
experience so you have something to
relate You follow me? Yes, I do. Does that
You follow me? Yes, I do. Does that
answer? Yes. Thank you very much. Number
three. Did you want to go up on the ship? Yes.
Did you want to go up on the ship? Yes.
Brian didn't go up on the ship. You had
the ship and he wants to know if we can
go up on the ship tonight.
Me, too. Me, too.
The idea once again will simply be
allowing you to get used to the idea
that your imagination is real. We will
take then a imaginary reality journey
briefly in a bit. One
One
moment. Allow me to remind each and
every one of you that the idea of
anything that anyone is here to share
can be reflected to you as a portion of
yourself. So in this way understand that
if you are present in this interaction,
anything anyone says can be applied to
you. So pay attention
one moment.
Okay. I my family is so separated that
it doesn't so they are together in
separately. Yes. And I'm the only one
that knows each of them or has met them.
One reason is being adopted and another
reason is
um that even the people I was adopted
with like stopped talking to their
family like they cut off all their
relations. All right.
So since I So what family did that allow
you to create?
Um, well, like I it allowed me to create
a family of
three sort of orphans together. Oh,
right. But that didn't feel good. Why
not?
Because everyone just wanted to hide and
be cut off from other people they had
known.
when I began
to I'm the only one that Are you playing
mother again this time? Oh god.
[Music] Well, you were so very good at it
Well, you were so very good at it
before. Perhaps that is why you elected
yourself again. [Music]
I was not going to be the one to say [Music]
[Music]
Now therefore draw unto yourself the
collection of all that you have ever
been and function within the strength of
the idea of the nurturing that you are
providing. But in this way recognize it
is not up to you to live their lives for
them. And in this way it is also
available to you to recognize that you
do not have to rely upon them to give
you a sense of
stability. You are stable or you are
not. Um I
Um I
just well I have a twin brother too and
I'm just who I wasn't raised with and I
met and it just brings up why we met. I
mean why all these people um coming
together to leave so quickly you know to
I mean I met again you are simply
exemplifying a pattern that has occurred
in many of your
lifetimes the idea of collecting
together so that you can then gather the
strength that is necessary to go on and
be about your independent businesses.
So we recognize this is an opportunity
for you to understand one thing.
No matter where or when anyone is, you
are as connected as you feel.
Yeah.
So it is your opportunity to
recognize that
everyone is your family. Everyone. and
that you make associations as you desire
to to any of them, anywhere,
anytime. This is your opportunity to
recognize that you do not have to play
mother pen and have all of your chicks
right around you.
Now the paradox is that as soon as you
allow yourself that stability and feel
the connection that is there, more
likely than not, you will find that they
then have been given by you the
opportunity to attract themselves back
to the central core.
So to let them see if they want to be
separate. If you are a reflection, yeah,
in their ability to come and go of
someone that is fractionated,
then all you are reflecting to them are
splinters of yourself, the splintering
of the group. What makes you think they
can see within you any opportunity for
the gathering together and stability?
Unless you choose already to know that
you are connected and are
whole, then you can reflect the idea to
them. So on on a daily level though, I mean I
So on on a daily level though, I mean I
I I sometimes think I should just let
them all be. I mean not write or call
because to you can do so as you feel,
but recognize you do not have to do so
in order to go them to your point of
view. You simply call them because you
love them, because you want to interact
with them, however you feel like
interacting, however they feel like
interacting. Do not call them because
you expect a certain type of interaction
is necessary. Then you will be
interacting with who they are, not who
you want them to be.
Follow me. Um, you know, who they are
and where they've chosen to go. Yes.
That is who they are. That is who they
are. If you place expectation upon who you
If you place expectation upon who you
think they should be, then you are not
interacting with them at all. So, it is
no surprise that they are not around
you. Well, I feel really that they don't want
Well, I feel really that they don't want
to be. You are missing the point.
They Yeah. are who they are.
If you allow them to be who they are,
then the they you will allow them to be
may feel free enough to interact with
you because you do not expect them to be
someone else other than who they
else other than who they
are. You owe me. Yes, I do.
You are not allowing them to interact
with you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Um, hi. Thank you for being here. Hi.
This is my uh
and so I've never asked anything before
and I What does one have to do with the
other? I don't know. Thank you. Uh I
would like to share the fact that I've
gained so much from listening the last
two weeks u to the other people and in
their sharing to me how much it's meant
because my life has changed. You have
changed it. Thank you. I have changed my
life. Do not forget that no matter how many
Do not forget that no matter how many
individuals you listen to, the choice is
up to you to accept what beliefs you
will into your reality. So you make the
change. Yes, they are of service to you.
Yes, you can thank them. It is still up
to you. Well, okay. It it has happened.
And the question I have to ask is um
I've been dreaming and I had never
really been aware of my dreams before I
started coming here. And there was a
specific two dreams and one they're
intriguing to me. One is I woke up and I
wasn't in this body. I was in another
body for it was it was a female body and
it was getting up getting ready for work
and then it became aware of me and I
became aware of it and I left and the
other and then the next day I got up and
um I was in my body and I went through
my whole day. I did everything that I
did that day but in like three or four
seconds and um I got back to sleep and I
was back in my body and I went woke up
and did it. But I was extremely
exhausted from living two days that
in you did not have to be but because
you assume that to spend that much time
without rest means you have to be
exhausted. You created the idea of
exhaustion. It did not have to exhaust
you. Okay. So I'll know that next time
you
Um, and so I was uh telling this to a
friend and she wanted me to ask the
question is it is it possible to be in
two bodies at one time controlling two
bodies or was this just I was somewhere
else for a moment. In a sense both and
one and the same for recognize the idea
is that you as an oversoul have many
counterparts which is other what you
would call bodies living at the same
time.
other bodies that you recognize as other
people but are a part of the same soul
as you am I do their problems that or
confrontations that they would deal with
in their life are they am I aware you
can be is up to you and the purpose that it
be is up to you and the purpose that it
serves to know of such
things about your question in more ways
I knew
uh what's the best sleeping pattern for
me? What would be good to be awake? The
best is what you feel like. The idea of
the general pattern that we perceive in
your society is that more often than not
you will have a high degree of
activation energy at what you call 3:00
a.m. and a low period at 300 p. them.
This is why many of your cultures have
what you call siestas. They recognize
the more natural cycle and many of you
have created a type of society that
forces you to be awake when you know you
want to sleep and to sleep when you know
you want to be awake. The idea has come
down to even creating the idea that when
you awaken in the early morning hours
between 2 to 4, you think something is
wrong with you. I have a disease called
insomnia. What is wrong with me? Nothing
is wrong with you. You have made all the
connections you need to make, which is
all sleep is all about anyway, aligning
with all the different levels of
yourself. Once you have made the
alignment in a satisfactory manner, you
will then project yourself back into the
physical reality so that all the energy
you have now created, you can do
something with it. It is a natural
pattern. Sleep when you are tired. When
you are not, don't. It is that simple.
No matter what time it
is and no matter for how long or how
short the sleep is, that is all the
connecting that is necessary. You will
find that as you accelerate into fourth
density reality, you may in your terms sleep
reality, you may in your terms sleep
less because you will always be allowing
your life to be a dream.
So the connections will always be
consciously present and you will not
have to become unconscious in order to
make the connections which is the only
way you now feel you can handle it
in. Does that answer your question?
Does that answer your question?
You what do you know of the the being
that had the body of Elron Hover? No
comment. All we will say at this time is
that there was service in the idea of
allowing individuals with Orion
connections to find themselves in the
way they wish to. That is all we can
say. What is he doing now? No comment. I
have another question.
Um, I've had a cold since I heard the
tape uh of you and I wondered if there
was any connection or if you could tell
me anything on simply that the idea may
be that when you create an integration
of many portions of yourself, when you
allow a vibration to open up ideas
within you, you may find that the bits
of resistance, the bits of judgment that
may be remaining within you will allow
you to experience a slight degree of
discomfort as you acclimate to the new
level of the
vibration. I got
that. Many of these ideas will affect
most strongly what you call the solar
plexus, the heart chakra, and the area
around your sinuses. For these areas are
sensitive to specific types of energy
that are connected to what you call the
electromagnetic field of your planet,
which is also undergoing major shifts.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
My little girl has been just ecstatic
lately. She's been glowing. And I asked
you what
about I asked her has has she been
communicating with someone because in
the last day it's been especially
matching and she said yes and I said
well who and she said Bashar.
So, and I don't say that name around too
much. I think that so so I just wanted
to let you know
our energy as I have said is available
to all who wish to tap into it. Okay. We
thank you for your willingness to
remember the agreement you have made
with your child and to allow yourself to
be the person she made the agreement
with. more more
[Music]
after last week um with Naaman
I and that chart that I told you about
that I had channelneled I uh was in very
intensive communication with the triads
over a period of a couple
And I do want to say that I do fully
understand what the change is and I
understand the chart and it's very nice
and um it's wonderful.
Full of wonder. Yes, it's um now also
um I was wondering well I particularly
have one name I am curious about and the
name is Dear God. I'm wondering if you
have collection.
All we will find at this time will be an
association to the idea of once again
some of the foundation of the triad
being again in Orion energy.
Let us say this
the vibration is representative of a
state of being of a state of existence
of in a sense a life.
Thank you. That was connected. I am not
true. There is simply a matter of
translating what the being was then to
your terminology. Now one
moment. This is not a direct
translation.
Somewhere as we perceive the terminology
in your
language between the
vibration of a technician, a priest, a
proctor, a
teacher, an
acolyte. There simply is no terminology
in your language for the vibration of
what the being played in that.
Okay. Will that do? Yes, that helps a
lot. Thank you. And uh one more thing is
ever since that I I started here, I've
been going four or five weeks. Every
time I come here and sometimes in
between times, I feel like someone is
trying to ch channel through me just
like you do through Dale. And I was
wondering if I could get some help on
that. What are you going to do with it?
How in your imagination do you wish to
allow the energy to combine with your
own?
Um as you close. What would be in your
imagination the most comfortable
facilitation? All right. See the
triangle in your mind. All right. Okay.
See red, green, blue on the triangle.
Okay. All right.
Spin the triangle until it blurs into
white light. At that moment, feel the energy
light. At that moment, feel the energy
build. Feel the blue white energy. Feel
your electromagnetic or
field. Infuse it with an association of
this solar system. Infuse it with a
little gold. And then know that you have now
gold. And then know that you have now
allowed yourself to create a template
for the door and the conduit to be
freely open in whatever way is
comfortable for you. That gets you to
the door that unlocks it. All you need
to do is push it is
open. All right.
Utilize that as a symbolic reflection of
some of the vibrations you have
associated to yourself. Let your
imagination alter it as you feel so
inclined. All right,
All right,
I will. Thank you. That's
I hear Ben once again coming at
you concerns with some other uh ideas
that I have been working with over the
years. Um, I've been experimenting a lot
with what is called radionics or
psychotronics. I've been using it from
the standpoint of learning and
stop. This is what we can share with you
at this time.
Research if you have not
already ideas of individuals that you recognize
ideas of individuals that you recognize
in your terminology to
be a Einstein B. Nicola
Tesla
see the town brown
brown
poly. These combined will give you the
foundation you seek in terms of the
understanding of vibrational
resonance and how to utilize vibrational
resonance in terms of what you wish to
apply it for.
Particularly pay attention to the fact
that the vibrational resonance of your
planet is approximately 7 and 1/2 cycles
per
second. Pay particular attention to the
fact that this is achieved by taking
what you
call speed of light and dividing it
by the circumference of your planet.
This will result in the cycles per
second of the frequency of the planet.
That is what we can share with you at
this time. Thank you.
Um I want to ask you a question about
the phenomenon of uh people accepting
Jesus into their as their savior. Um
these people seem to be happy and
forgiving and loving but they don't
really want to learn anything outside
that realm.
The idea that we will share with you at
this time is simply this.
The consciousness that you are referring
to as Jesus, the Christ consciousness in
this way was not seeking followers. Mhm.
But was reflecting
equals the idea that was shared with you
is not to follow but act like the
individual that you call Jesus.
Yeah. They seem to have let this entity
and given up their own determinism.
There is simply in this way a
misconception in your society because of
what you have created the society to be
that surrendering is giving up control.
Surrendering is taking
control, taking responsibility for what
you are creating in your reality and
letting it flow in the way that is
representative of you
forming a parallel connection to the way
all that is creates.
What do you what's the best way to
surrender? There is no best. Well, is
there do you surrender to something or
do you The idea again of surrendering is
what we had discussed as
vulnerability. Being open to all that is
to become congruent with the vibration
by knowing that all that is created you
to be what you are. So act like it. That
is surrendering and at the same time
taking control and being Christ's life.
Can I Okay, that's fine. Uh, I just want
to ask you about two human emotions that
I would like your comments on. Uh, one
is guilt and one is depression.
Guilt is not hate but the true opposite
of love, guilt.
For in this way you will find that love
is complete and
unconditional worthiness and
deservability. Guilt is the lack of that
idea. How does one undo it practically
though? One feels guilty towards
children or something like that. What
simply recognize that you are forming
judgments within yourself about yourself
upon yourself and that in this way you
can recognize that all it takes is
simply aligning yourself with the
vibration you call your own integrity
and acting in that
manner. Depression is meditation. Again
judged the idea that when you know you
cannot find the answers outside
yourself, you go to where you know they
are within. You judge this meditation
because your society tells you that to
do so is
antisocial. So you think you are doing
something wrong or that because you are
going within to find the answers there
is something wrong with you. Recognize
each and every time you emerge from your
so-called depression, you are quite a
new person. Literally
that's magnificent. Thank you very much.
You Thank you. I just have a question in
regards to the experience my boyfriend
and I had a few weeks ago that one
morning or afternoon he asked me what
what were you dreaming last night and I
said well I have quite an incredible
dream and I quite what incredible
credible dream
very incredible dream
and I didn't get into the specifics of
it because I was very curious as to why
he asked me the question and very
excited about him sharing something with
Maybe that's why
maybe that's why what you have the dream
you was in it was there then you were
sharing and it allowed you to form the
connection that you desired
on some level whatever it takes you for
this is interesting because in a series
of days I had dreams of him or shared
dreams with him my dream stay well once
the connection is formed why
Very good. Very nice. Yes. Well, what he
said to me as far as my question as to
what it was of why he asked me, he was
we went silent and he said because he
saw me standing in the hallway into the
bedroom just staring at him for a few
minutes. And I thought I thought this
was very interesting because I said I'm
not known to sleepwalk. He says, "No."
Then I looked to my left and you were
sleeping next to me, but you stood there
in the hallway staring at me. He allowed
himself to become sensitive to the
vibration of the astral realm and saw
your projection.
That's pretty cool.
I I just didn't expect to hear that. Um,
well then it came as a pleasant
surprise. Yes, it did very much. Thank
you. for sure. Thank you guys. Um I was
here last week for the first time. I'm
really nervous talking in front of
everybody but nervous is simply being
excited but you are judging it. Okay.
Someone had mentioned about cancer last
week and my father's having kidney
cancer a kidney removed Friday and
um you I didn't grasp what what you were
saying and I would like you to repeat it
because in this case the idea is simply
that it is a recognition that where the
majority of judgment is taking place
within that individual is within what
they consider to be their filtering
systems In other words, judgment itself
is under their microscope. The idea that
the strongest action or reaction that
they have to their reality is to
immediately filter what they do not
approve of. You follow?
of. You follow?
No, cuz all this is very very new to me.
So just go ahead and recognize this as a
foundational understanding.
Your reality, what you call your
physical reality, is the product of what
you believe it is. What you perceive is
what you
believe. You follow me so far? Yes.
Therefore, recognize that what you
believe is what allows you to perceive
what you do. You only allow yourself to
perceive what you feel you are
comfortable in perceiving. and shut out,
filter out like the kidneys all of what
you consider to be
impurities, something worthless,
something less. But putting a judgment
upon your reality for a very long period
of time in that way can cause the
filtration system to become broken down
or clogged in this way because it is
functioning under a strain because you
are not allowing what you have created
in your reality to be what you need in
your reality. It is the lack of
willingness to recognize that what
occurs in your reality is what you need
to look at. If you judge that what
happens in your life has no business
being there, you are
invalidating the fact that you created
it to show yourself something. You are
not accepting the lesson from the
situation. You are saying, "Oh no, this
has nothing to do with me.
I
disavow my connection to that
creation. Snap goes the filter.
You follow me? Yes. Thank you.
Now project with your love into
all bodies of that being astralic,
mental, causal, physical. your golden
light of love, your blue white
electromagnetic energy so that there
will be an electromagnetic balance in
that individual. Send it to the individual on
individual. Send it to the individual on
whatever level you think the individual
will accept it so that the individual
can allow it to filter down at a
comfortable rate.
All right.
Thank you.
And in this way, your point of view is
to recognize that any situation that any
individual creates in life, those
situations are created from their
strength, not from weakness. Therefore,
no need to
reinforce a belief that you think this
person is
helpless. That will only allow them to
choose to weaken themselves further.
See them as having made the choice from
strength so that you at least will send
them a beacon that will let them know
that they are in control of their
reality and can choose whatever they
wish. All right.
Thank you for your willingness to
interact with that individual on that
level. for that in allowing yourself to
have reflections of that nature shown to
you and in your willingness to recognize
that that
individual is willing to create that
scenario for themselves to learn
whatever lesson they wish to learn. That
is a reflection of
boldness. In this way, recognize that
there is also no need to be nervous.
Boldness can serve you as long as it is
not the boldness that forces itself upon
another individual without your
integrity. But boldness in being who you
are will always be of service to other
individuals. All right. Thank you.
It's our um my younger sister, his name
is Lesie Hoff, is an alcoholic and um I
think partly due in reaction to the
transitioning of my brother, my mother
and my father and um my sister and my
other brother, we don't know where she
is and we haven't heard from her for
about a year and the last place we know
she was is in North Dakota. Can you tell
me if she's all right or where she is?
Our perception at this time is that
there is an opportunity for this
individual to come into terms with
aspects of her past lives and bring them
into the future that are connected with
what you call the culture of American
Indian. In this way, there may be the
opportunity in that direction for the
individual to form associations with
that particular situation you call
alcoholism with the Indians in the area
and allow them to show her a path to
allow it to be in your terms integrated
within herself so that she will not have
to take responsibility and thrust it
upon the tool you call alcohol and
putting all the responsibility in that
way. There is an opportunity for that
individual to have come to terms with
this at this point. You may fully send
her your light and love in this way and
allow yourself in your dream realities
to know that you are in contact.
Therefore, take your self-empowerment,
give her her self-empowerment back to
know that in the communications and the
dialogues that you can have in your
dream reality. There is an opportunity
for you to suggest to her that she
steered herself in the direction that
will form connections to the idea of the
American Indian culture that she is a
part of in that way and has formed
association too, so that she can regain
her own self-empowerment in physical
reality as well as non-physical reality.
That's interesting because we heard she
was on an Indian reservation.
She is in your terms in good hands.
There's another question I want to ask.
One moment. One moment. One minute. Um I
saw the movie Broken Rainbow on last
Saturday and it has to do with
relocation. Yes. Yes. Yes. Um
am I being speeded up here? Is she um or
is this group going to be relocated in
July? That's not going to happen. I'm so
shocked that at this time all we can say
is this is a primary opportunity for you
to recognize it is not a matter of
asking is this going to happen but will
you create it to be so take action now.
Not accusing anyone for the situation. Not
accusing anyone for the situation. Not
blaming anyone for the situation.
allowing you to be who you are and
allowing you to remind the Indians to be
who they are. Well, I wrote a letter and
I didn't accuse anyone. All right, then
you have made a difference. Understand
one other
idea. Whether it happens or not, you can
still allow there to be a positive
effect from any situation.
Now the degree to which you are willing
to become involved in that way will also
determine the idea of how willing you
are to actually allow that to be a part
of your reality.
So follow your feelings. Okay. Thank you
very much.
Could you um read other people's minds?
Not exactly. It is more the idea again that
exactly. It is more the idea again that
your feelings are a vibration we can
relate to from time to time. We can in a
sense share some of your thoughts if it
serves a purpose as the interaction is
progressing. But in this way, simply
recognize we are non-invasive and the
idea of what we know and what we do not
know is directly related to what we can
and cannot share with you about a
process you might be in the middle of.
In other
words, we will know what we need to know
to share with you when we need to know
it. If we do not know it, it is because
to know it and to share it with you
would be to interfere with your life and
what you have created it to be.
Therefore, the idea of reading your mind
will in a sense happen from time to
time, but it will usually need to be a
spontaneous idea without in your terms
calling attention to it. Because when
you call attention to it, you are in a
sense closing up all the available
information that we may have had access
to because then you are saying let's see
if they can get
[Music] this. The idea of being open in an
this. The idea of being open in an
ongoing interaction is what allows you
to be open enough for us to perceive in
a sense what is on your mind.
Yes. Yes. I have two questions. One, I
have a high interest in lasers. I mean,
I actually like them. Although I know
you're Is that supposed to be something
that is not called? No. No. I'd like to
know if you could enlighten me as to why
I have enlightening you about lasers.
No, no, no. Maybe just give me some
information as to why I have such a high
liking relation since I because they are
an analogy for the energy crystals of
Atlantis which you also were connected
to.
Will that do? Yeah.
All right. Another quick question is
there's a process that I've come across
lately where you take hydrogen hydrogen
peroxide into your body and it helps to
cleanse it. Um
by putting uh oxygen yeah oxygen into it
add anything to that I mean could you
tell me anything about that if it's an
okay thing to do on on one's body and is
it really is it real beneficial
let us say it is not unduly
[Music] harmful idea will be found that you will
harmful idea will be found that you will
derive some extraction of energy from
this process that is beneficial in your
terms if kept to a minimum. Now the
idea is that you can also simply take
what you call purified water and allow
your blue white electromagnetic energy
field to crystallize that
and drink it or immerse yourself in it.
That is what will in a sense oxygenate
your entire system.
Okay. Thank you. for sure. No more than
10 minutes is necessary for the
energizing of the water from you.
All right. Yeah. Thank you. How do you
do that?
In a sense, by projecting your energy
into it in whatever way seems comfortable for
it in whatever way seems comfortable for
you. All right?
If you just take it in your body, then
you you in other words, become what you
are, a living laser.
Project a blue white energy beam into
the water for 10 minutes. What are you
drinking? I see it. Okay. Or before you
immerse yourself within it.
The same thing with food. Yes.
But in this way, once again, recognize
it is not for the purpose of thinking
that you need to do it because you need
protection. simply that you are forming an
simply that you are forming an
alignment, an identification and
allowing all to be one vibration.
All right. Thank you. For sure. Sure.
For sure. Hi, this is Millie. I love
you. I love you. I have someone very
special with me tonight and that's my
mother in his life and I was wondering
if um has read Shannon Mlan's book, as
have I, and I was wondering if you might
be able to just shed some uh information
on our some of our past relationships.
You like this game, don't you? [Music] [Music]
[Laughter]
Then no wonder you have created so much
of it.
Do you want me simply to proceed or are
you willing to share your own intuitions
first? The choice is up to you.
In this case, either is fine. In this
case, I would like you to speak. All
right.
There seems to be a propensity for the
idea of sharing familial ties in what
you would call farm
situations. In this way, it was the
identification to the soil to the earth
to the animals that you shared and you
have shared it both as sister mother and
sister sister mother child mother.
There are also propensities to the
terminology of what you refer to as
Elizabethan times. This way you find that again as
times. This way you find that again as
both females and
friends you experienced and enjoyed the
courts and the [Music] courting
courting
also. Though this was not necessarily
shared at the same time by both of you,
let us say taking turns, there has been
from time to time some fascination with
what you call the medical
arts, primarily in the heart area.
It seems there
are very directly a few times that
formed a strength of bonding between you
wherein you enjoyed the idea of creating
what you call mister and found that one
or other of you would involve yourselves
in that mist to a point where you would
need the other to extract
you from the trouble you have caused.
Some of these incidents were quite in
your terms deadly, serious,
and under the full
moon. Many times have you
shared what you would call witches
rights.
And once very strongly did the sea
connect you both. Many times as females,
many times as
males. Than
seashells and foreign
ports from this in a way may still fill
your nostrils. Memories.
This is what we can share at this time.
Wonderful. Thank you. One moment. One
another thing, another topic. Now that I
have your attention,
um last week I had um the completion of
a major transition within
transition within
me. And then also during the week I had
a visual
appearance of someone who I felt a presence of for
of someone who I felt a presence of for
a long
time. And
um it was in a way very comical because
the visual persons appeared to be trying
to take a form that I could relate to or
something because it was like a a
montage of images very very fast upon
each other. an extreme acceleration
ranging from everything from Benjamin
Franklin to the Statue of Liberty. All
right. And following the appearance of that
And following the appearance of that
person, that being, which was very vivid
and almost to the point of creating a
little bit of fear in me, which I just
said, "Oh, don't be silly." Uh then
there was this uh perhaps many of you
would find that fear would be your
friend more often if you were to be
silly a little more often. Continue.
Continue.
No. Allow me. Okay. At this time, simply
allow us to extend to you our perception
of the idea that the transformation has
spurred within you. One of the
foundational symbols you have created
for yourself. In other lives, in forming
a connection from an old republic to a
new republic and expressing the spirit
you call liberty.
In that way, therefore,
1,776 will play a part with
you. You are not unfamiliar with musket.
Now, we would add only one more thing.
None of what we have shared with
you in any way, shape, and form is
insisted upon by us that you
believe. It is up to you to form your
own identifications, nor your own realities,
identifications, nor your own realities,
which is what you do
anyway. We are not here to link your
lives, nor delineate for you what your
lives have been.
But we will share the energies we
perceive in the way we understand your
symbols to reflect them.
But it is all all of
the choose what you will.
Things you tell me are great great
benefit and I'm able to utilize them uh
in a way that I feel really really helps
me in my progression and transformation.
But we thank you for allowing us to
reflect to you what you are willing to
create for yourself.
I'm in the process of raising money on
it for a business transaction. And about
a month ago, it looked as if
I the process was going along comparable
to zipping along in a car on a super
highway and I had money coming in from
two different sources. Nice and all of a
sudden nothing happened. Then it was as
if being on a highway, I'm now stuck in
the mud up to my hubcat. No, no, no.
Okay. So, once again, before you
continue, allow me to remind you that it
is only judgment that makes you think
any acceleration has stopped. It may
have changed direction. It may even have
changed its form. But the only reason
nothing quote unquote is happening is
because you make the assumption that
when the change occurred, it did not
represent the continuence of the
acceleration in an unexpected way. Well,
I can assume that. But in mechanical
terms, there is no difference between
the mechanical terms and what you
assume. Again, you do not have to have
the same tool to create the continuence
of the acceleration.
into money
or anything else you think is necessary
for the continuence of that idea. It is
continuing in the way it needs to. You
simply don't think it is continuing
because you're not willing to allow the
symbols it is continuing in to be just
as valid as the symbols that it was
using. No, I'm willing to and I can
appreciate that. As far as I personally
am concerned, my relation that is all
there is to it. my relationship to this
project. I can appreciate that there's
continuing acceleration for me learning
but that doesn't ensure that the project
you do not need insurance that the
project will survive in physiological
terms and there are other people who
depend on it. You are missing the point
a you are taking responsibility for
other people
in this way again recognize everyone
that is interacting with you on that
project whatever happens that is what
you have all
co-attracted if you allow what happens
to be what you decided can co-attract
you will all get out of it what you
really need to get out of it rather
rather than what you think you should
get out of it. Allowing that reality to
pervade your imagination is
paradoxically what will usually allow
you to get out of it what you always
thought you were going to.
When you relax about the way something
is going on and do not make it a demand
that it has to happen in the way you
think it should, then paradoxically it
will most likely happen the way you
thought it should. because you are not
insisting that it has to. Okay, I
understand that.
But what I there's a difference
between the lessons or learning or
growth or acceleration that I and the
other people who are co-creating it will
derive on a emotional spiritual basis.
That's one thing that I understand.
That's fine. At the same time, there is
the physiological reality about whether
the business gets funded or not. No, no,
no. You are making the difference. There
is no difference. That is the whole
point. You are saying physical is
different from what I will gain in a
philosophical way. You are saying that
the emotional experience is not the same
as the physiological experience. And
that is what creates the dichotomy.
It is the same. Let it be the same. Then
the physical reflection that will be
equal to the emotional experience will
be there. You are making the separation.
You are not allowing physical symbols
and emotional symbols to be the same
event. Not allowing them to communicate
because you see them as separate.
Fulfillment is fulfillment on all
levels. Fulfillment on one level is
fulfillment on all the others. if you
let it be.
Well, I understand conceptually what
you're saying and I operate with it. But
in this particular case, my experience
is that they are
I can experience positive things going
on as a result of all of this. Your
concept and the experience are the same
thing. You are simply saying and making
the conscious choice that the way it is
manifesting physically is not the way
you think it should in order to reflect
what you say you conceptually
understand. That's true. It doesn't have
to. The point is trust that it is and
you will see how it
is. Other words, you are judging a book
by its cover.
So judge trust judgment. Trust what?
Trust that the way it is happening is
the way it needs to happen to manifest.
What appears to be a lag is not a lag.
What is it? The way it needs to
manifest. It is the correct timing
pacing so that everyone will benefit in
the way they need to. You stretch it out
into something that does not seem to be
fulfilling because you are judging it.
Judgment creates more time.
Okay. My concern is that I'm somehow
sabotaging the dream. Stop being
concerned about it. You are judging
yourself. And again, you are accepting
far more responsibility for everyone
else's reality than you have a right
to. Okay. Do can you do you have a
perception of the specific transaction
I'm referring to if you had specific
perceptions about William's alternate
lives only in a
general in this way again we find that
our reflection to you will be of best
service again to not create more
dichotomy and separation and labeling.
We are reflecting to you the energy that
is necessary to actually function as the
mechanism of what you say you desire.
But you are analyzing yourself to death.
Well, I wondered if you had a perception
of of the inclination of the energy as
it existed.
What is it?
I was trying to phrase it. I know that
you The idea once again is this. The
idea of connecting telepathically is an
emotional idea. And you will find a that
if you are not excited about something,
if it is not a part of your reality, you
usually will not connect to it. Right? B
the idea of having ready access to the
information but not being willing to
share it in the easiest possible manner
will also cut the cord of communication.
Right? Therefore, what is it?
Your project. Oh, the project funding uh
the medical device. All right. Are you
enjoying it? Yes. Does the idea excite
you? Yes. Then simply recognize that if
the idea itself excites you, the way in
which the idea manifests won't
matter. Just be the idea. Know beyond a
shadow of a doubt that that is the only
idea you are being.
Do not assume that if you see something
you judge to be an unexpected direction,
do not assume it is not part of being
the idea. Assume that it is a part of
being that idea since you trust fully
beyond a shadow of a doubt that that is
the only idea you are
being. Then you allow your life to show
you how what you previously judged to be
not a part of the idea actually is.
Well, what do you know? What an
unexpected direction that was, but we
wound up exactly where we thought we
were. Never would have guessed we would
have gotten there that way. That's the
point. That is surrendering in control.
Suspense is killing.
Once again, if you find yourself in need of
again, if you find yourself in need of
patience, that is the only thing that
creates impatience. You do not need
patience if you are enjoying being the
idea you are being every single now
moment. You do not need patience.
Patience assumes that what is coming
along is better than what you are now.
That is what keeps it away.
And that is why you get impatient. Live
impatient. Live
now. That's how
Well, I understand.
Again, again, again, if you say it makes
sense, let it make sense on all levels.
Take it for granted that you do in fact
understand it on all the levels you need
to, whether you think you do or not.
Trust is all there is. No, I understand.
It just doesn't feel good.
So what do I you know so it's like I'm
contradicting yourself. Well I I can
appreciate that but nevertheless that's
my experience but that is also your
choice. So but I'm interested
in stand
up break stand up standing turn
around. Repeat after me.
I I am am the idea the idea that I am
that I am sit
down with a little more conviction.
I
am I am the idea that I
am. I am the idea that I am. I am.
That is all there is to it. If you need
an exercise, use
that. I have the idea that I am. That is
all there is to it.
Yeah. Yes. How does one get out of
judgment? Just practice.
Then you answer. [Music] [Music]
Next question.
Excellent question. Don't. Yes. Well,
I'm waiting on you to answer. I just
asked you to. What does that have to do
with you answering it? Come on. Come on.
You spoke up. You were bold. You thought
it was a good question. Therefore, I
assume that you are relating to it.
Therefore, you must have a good answer.
Well, I thought it was a good question
as well, but I can't answer it.
Well, I tend to Are you going to answer
it or not? Yeah, I get in harmony with
it and uh in harmony with your judgment.
Is that what you're saying? If if is
that what you are saying? Yes. How does
one get into harmony with one's
judgment? Would you please illuminate
us? Thank you. If if I have judged
something, okay, I see the judgment.
Yes. Okay. And I let it flow through in
what way? In other words, I look at it
in appreciation because it's there.
Teach me something. And if I am that
keen on it, I tend to at that point look
at it and let it flow through and I just
practice that and eventually I don't
judge. All right.
Will that suffice or would you like
something different?
I'm a bit confused of judgment. You see,
there should be two words in the English
language. You see, I can judge whether
I'm going to go home on the venture or
on the There is two words, judgment and
preference. Preference is simply recognizing the
Preference is simply recognizing the
vibration of the reality you happen to
be. That does not mean you have to
invalidate everything else you don't
choose. Preference is simply choice.
Choice is not
judgment. Okay, I see the difference
that. But I just find myself being
sucked into judgment. Somebody does
something and I just go. That is because
you are more willing to react than act
like who you know you are. Well, what am
I supposed to say to them? What are you
supposed to say? Well,
okay. Um, if you know that the idea, the
vibration that you happen to be only
contains the idea of love, peace, and
harmony, why would someone else's
reality be able to go you into anything
else but okay, I understand that. Well,
um, and I believe it. I appreciate it.
But nevertheless, my but but but one
moment. What has gone before has nothing
to do with what is happening now. The
present is not a result of the past.
Therefore, anything you desire to be now
be it. It doesn't matter what you used
to do because the you are now is not the
same you.
Does that assist you? Thank you. And
thank you. One more. If uh if you truly allow
you. One more. If uh if you truly allow
every situation to be neutral, there's
no way you can judge it. All right. Very
good. Yes.
Very good. There's just no emotion.
Correct. Judgement. Correct. It just
seems to me that it takes practice and
that is what happen because you define
habit as something that is difficult to
change. Therefore, you create the need
for practice in order to change
it. Well, that is my way. That is
and lovely it is and learning from it
you are.
Thank you.
I have a question. One moment. Is it
possible that
not completely in their former states
but to some degree? Minute amounts. The
majority of the energy is that it is
rising within
you because you are blending all that
you have ever been in this
transformational life. The end of the
cycle of separation and the beginning of
your integration.
You does fate enter into the scheme of
Thank you.
It is simply that what you recognize as
fate and or destiny or
predestination plays a very small
general part in your life. Small in a
specific way, large in a general way. In
other words, there is free will of your
physical personality. That which you
consider yourself to be here physically.
There is free will of your higher self.
The free will of your higher self is
usually viewed by your physical
personality as fate. Now the idea is
this however the free will of your
higher self usually only expresses
itself in physical reality in very
generalized terms very generalized
concepts. In other words the higher self
wishes to explore with this physical
life a general series of
themes. How you experience those general
themes is completely up to the free will
of your physiological personality. So
the idea again once again by analogy the
higher self says that the physical
personality will walk down that hallway
in life. That hallway right there it
cannot divert. That is fate. However,
how you walk down that hallway is up to
you. You can run, you can crawl, you can
go quickly, slowly backwards, upside
down, in the light, in the dark, hating,
loving. It is up to you.
That is free will on two levels.
But go down that hallway, you will.
Yes. To to extend that question a bit.
Uh when we are born, yes. Uh do we make
do we make a deal uh or or do we have
Yes. You choose we choose.
How do we agree to that? Simply by being
the vibration of a certain idea, you
form connections with other individuals
that are willing to participate in a
similar vibration with you. That is the
agreement. So you attract your parents,
your brothers, your sisters, your
relatives, all of that. You are all
gathered together to enact a scenario of
a similar vibration. Each knowing that
every person will be a reflection for
every other person within it according
to how the other person wishes to
explore and discover aspects of
themselves in that given interaction.
Everyone is a mirror for everyone else.
Yes. Um I have another question about a
dream. Um this is a dream in which a
real short dream man came to me and he
asked me for help dreaming in his dream
world. Hey and I was wondering if you
could um shed any light on that
functioning as spirit guide spirit.
You mean I there are levels of let us
say again instruction in the astral realms
again instruction in the astral realms
and you can recognize that you have
again jobs to do there just as you do
here and that you can assist other
beings that consider themselves to be on
different levels to understand what they
are doing to blend with the rest of
their personalities.
So I'm actually in my dream world
tutoring tutoring in the United States.
I had another question about my friend
on
um I was visiting him this week
and my visualizations of him are not
real clear. That is all right. And so I
was drawn
to since I was feeling sort of blind,
what I wanted to do was touch him. And
so in touching him
and I formed a a more clear picture of
him and his eyes were very much like my
brothers. They seem to be like my
brother Paul's
eyes. And I was wondering if there's any
connection simply that you will
recognize within our form the eyes
always first. In this way you will find
that it is quite truly the idea you have
called it the doorway to the soul. And
in this way you will find our eyes will
be quite enlarged by your perceptions.
They will appear to be large black
pools. So in this way you are forming a
So in this way you are forming a
connection and understanding that the
area that you need to be aware of you
are very clearly aware of and that area
can allow you to function within
communication to other individuals as
well. I lie
equal to equal. Okay. So it has nothing
to do with my my physical brother in
this lifetime. Oh yes, there are
connections, but simply you are
utilizing what you have been taught in
terms of how to form a connection to
allow you more conscious recognition of
what connections you
have. He does share some of the same
energy. Oh, you're laugh forming connections
Oh, you're laugh forming connections
that I'm I'm using communication with
other individuals. Communication with
portions of yourself.
Okay. See, you may require a few more
dream interactions to get the whole
picture, but you will see.
There will be in your terms a few
moments remaining for this interaction
this evening of your time. All
All
right, then. All of you relax.
relax.
Recognize within your imagination that
you are all gathered out of your
conscious choice to
form one identity at the same time
strengthening the individual identities
that you all are together. In forming a
unity, you will strengthen the
individuality. That is the paradox of
life. And that is how you have brought
yourselves together. In this way, unity
will be formed by the infinite diversity
within all that is. So, you have
gathered yourselves together as infinite
diversity to now form the unity of one
imagination projection. Surround
yourselves in your imagination with an
energy bubble of blue transparent
crystallin energy. It surrounds every
single one of you and it will become
your ship. Allow yourselves to begin to feel
ship. Allow yourselves to begin to feel
the connection and the linking with your
physiological, your emotional, your
spiritual, your mental selves in this
way. and recognize now that you have
created with this crystallin bubble an
isolation field that allows you to
unlock and detach yourselves from the
particular universe that you have lived
in for so long and take it for granted
to be the only universe within
existence. Allow yourselves to recognize
that while you still may perceive the
idea of your natural surroundings and
the house around them bound to allow
everything outside of the bubble to
begin to dissolve into a gray white
foglike substance of primal energy. the
energy out of which all physical reality
is created. You are floating in a limbo
state, floating protected and warm
within the crystallin energy bubble in
your own spacecraft.
Now recognize simply that while you form
the transformation, the transitional
state of disassociating from one
frequency into another frequency, you
will begin this way in a sense
projecting yourselves aboard what we
call the mother craft, which in your
terms is a cylinder approximately 7,000
of your feet in length and 1/10th
diameter. You may refer to the vibration
of its name as the solar wind. In this
way, allow yourselves to simply
recognize that you will simply
materialize as you perceive the idea in
whatever shape or form is comfortable
for your imagination in any portion of
this craft. The idea will be that there
may be taking on within the fog, within
the homogeneous mass of energy, the idea
of form that may become slightly more
substantial as you appear in whatever
formation, whatever level, whatever deck
of the idea you feel so inclined to
project within. Allow yourselves now the
recognition that the idea of the energy
with which you have allowed yourself to
perceive around the energy crystal will
begin to materialize in a way that will
allow you to dissolve the energy crystal
in a form that will now allow you to
know that you are taking it for granted
that no matter what you perceive in
whatever way you perceive it you are
aboard that craft at this time you may
form projections that are more familiar
to you. You may project the idea of your
experience into familiar patterns so
that you can become comfortable with the
experience. But recognize that you are
part and parcel energy projections of
consciousness aboard the craft at this
time. Allow yourselves the opportunity
to experience the dissolving of the
energy bubble and the crystallization of
any aspect of consciousness that greets
you within the craft. In this way, allow
yourselves to feel free to explore where
you will. Allow yourself to perceive
anything you will. simply take it for
granted that what you are perceiving is
exactly what you have attracted yourself
to perceive and the identifications with
the consciousness upon our craft that
you need to form identifications with.
Allow yourself now the freedom in what
you call one minute period of your time
to freely explore within your
imagination the reality you are creating
for yourself.
deeply of the atmosphere within the
manifestation of your own energy and
recognize that while you are all
individuals, you are also connected and
know the whereabouts of any other
individual that has come with you to
this graph. Explore freely through the
decks in any materialized manifestation
that you so desire to perceive. For you
are now in a sense quite immaterial and
can penetrate any soul and surface.
[Music]
Recognize the consciousness and the
energy which is allowing all the
consciousness aboard the craft to be in
touch with all aspects of all the
different multi-dimensional multiaceted
universes that the craft plies itself
through in this way
transdimensionally. Allow yourself to
feel the core of the vibration of the
energy of light that powers the craft.
For the craft is powered by the very
fabric and essence of the universe
itself.
Recognize in this way as you form
identifications with our consciousness
within the homogeneous mass of our
consciousness as we greet you within our
dimension of imagination that you are
existing coexisting co-creating and
co-sharing with us the idea of your
dimension of imagination as well. Allow
yourselves to reform the energy bubble
around and bow to and gather together as
a crystal in consciousness. Recognizing
that it is not a matter of not wanting
to leave, but recognizing that the idea
now as you form the identification of
the removal of your consciousness from
the craft. And as you look upon the idea
you call your planet Earth in its
emerald green loving crystal
consciousness that you have before you
and below you in space the idea of a
crystallization of your loving
consciousness, your connection to nature
and a home that is worthy of
you. In this way reidentify with the
idea of the vibration of the solidity of
the reality you have formed. Recognize
this. You are in your terms forever
different, forever changed, forever new,
and never the same individual that you
have ever been. You carry within you now
the co-blended reality of the idea of
the experience of other realms of
dimension and imagination. Allow
yourselves to partake within the reality
within your imagination. For energy is
always available to you in whatever way,
shape, and form you wish to co-create
it. You may now allow the solidity of
your familiar surroundings to become
manifest within your consciousness,
recognizing at the same time that there
is no less, there is no worse, that this
is only another manifestation of the
idea of the unconditional love and
beauty out of which all creation is
manifested through you. Allow your own
to become just as crystallin as you have
experienced any reality within your
consciousness to be. Dissolve the energy
bubble and reconnect yourself in this
way in love and light with three deep
breaths to your physical
reality. We would therefore remind you
at this
time that your reality, however you
choose to perceive it, is your
creation. That you are as
unlocked and locked as you wish to be.
that unlocking and locking are
unlocking and locking are
both.
Knowingness, trust is all that is
trust is all that is
necessary for the transformation of your
reality into anything you desire it to
be. In
essence, the
symbols that you require to be that
reality are
always always there for you. Whatever is
always there for you. Whatever is
occurring in your
life is your creation and your loving
reflection of your
recognition of the all that is that you
are.
Remember that with the deep breaths you
have taken, what you have breathed
taken, what you have breathed
in is the very
fabric of love that you are made from
and what you have breathed out is the
reality that is also what you
are. Extend at this
time once again our
appreciation in your willingness to
co-create with us. An interaction of
consciousness that for us is always a
gift and allows us to view that much
more of all that is that there is to
explore. We thank you for the creation
of your dream
realities. We are with you the sharing
that continues forever.
You exist
now. You always
will. Existence always
Existence always
exists. You are
eternal. Remember
that. We send you our unconditional
love. We bid you a fond and loving
greeting.
Thank you. Thank you.
[Applause]
Thank you all for being here today.