How are you all thinking your time is a
great time doing this? Amen. Allow us to
begin this interaction this evening of
your time with the furthering of the
idea of the taking the responsibility
upon yourselves for the actions in your
life for the creation of your reality
and the idea of the communication once
again that will be created to go between
yourselves and any other individual that
you may encounter now in your lives in
this time of transformation that also
attract themselves to this type of
information and your ability and your
willingness to share this information
with them in a clear and concise manner
so that there will be as little as
possible of what you would call negative
confusion in the communication of the
ideas you now are allowing yourself to
utilize and understand in your life. In
this way, this communication and the
clarity thereof is of in your terms
parallel importance at this time so that
the transformation and the blending that
are to take place can be of the
smoothest possible continuation, the
smoothest possible creation and
coordination as you call it. Therefore,
allow us to illuminate the ideas at this
time, that when you find yourselves in
the position of sharing this
information, of course, not that anyone
you are sharing this information with
have to believe what you are saying, but
simply that they may be willing to ask
you to share the idea so that they may
understand for their own, as you say,
perusal in this way, to make up their
own mind and come to their own
conclusions about what they wish to do
with this information. Share this
information and allow yourself to know
that as you do so. Be
very clear,
very methodical, very
methodical, very
precise in the
definitions in the modality in which you
deliver this information. So that there
is time for consideration on the part of
the individual listening. And so that
you in sharing will create also the time
that you require for consideration of
what it is you are saying. For you will
recognize that each and every time you
share this information, you will hear
something new in it as well.
You follow me? Yes. In this way, you
will begin to recognize yourselves as
the multi-dimensional creators. We have
shared this idea with you many times.
You will now begin to speak like such in
this way in your sharing and recognize
the multi-dimensionality in everything
that you say and the opportunity to
recognize all the different points of
view that go into making up any
communication you have with any
individual or group in your society.
Thus always will you create yourself the
opportunity in your life for you to see
the reflections of all the different
reflections of all the different
perspectives and points of view that you
can in delivering and sharing any
communication outward. Do not forget
that a teaching is also always a
learning and a learning is also always a
teaching.
Therefore, allow yourselves to be
cognizant in the moment that there is no
rush in the transferring of this
information, of this
communication that to deliver the
information in a very
relaxed and joyful manner without any
need for the other
individual to believe what you are
saying at all. but simply that you are
sharing, outlining, illuminating for
their understanding, for their
clarification, and that you will be on
your way, and they will be on their
way. Creating this interaction to be a
relaxed time will allow all information that
time will allow all information that
needs to be absorbed to be
absorbed at a rate that is comfortable
for all involved.
And at a rate that will allow what that
individual does decide to absorb within
themselves to
grow in a nurtured way in a way that
will expand very rapidly the ability expand
expand very rapidly the ability expand
the ability of the rest of your
civilization to understand what it will
what it chooses to understand of the
same information. Each and every
individual willing to
understand the ideas that are going on
in the transformation now in their own
terms on their own level allow the
entire civilization that remains to
understand it more easily. For each
added number makes a geometric
difference in the ability of the total
civilization to absorb what appears to
be a new idea but really isn't.
also be cognizant of what it is the
content of which that you are sharing
that you are
saying and take
it all the way through to its
foundations. Do not leave them hanging
with half an idea so to speak. For as
you have say now I will be colloquial in
your language for a moment. A little
information is a very dangerous
thing whereas a lot will allow more
clarification of understanding. An
analogy is as follows.
You will now begin to understand that
one of the primary
fields of discussion in this new age
will be the phrase that has occurred as
we have shared with you many times so
often. Well, there really is no such
thing as good or evil, right or wrong.
Now, you will understand that this is a
statement, but it is not an explanatory
statement. It is simply a statement. And
many individuals may feel within
themselves upon hearing that statement
that they understand what it means. But
in sharing that statement with someone
who has no cognizance of what the whole
idea is all about and has really no
inclination to understand it by
feeling. They are then likely to
misinterpret in their own frame of
reference the idea as it is being shared
and come to much consternation because
of what they think the phrase means.
Thus in this way it will only as you
would say cloud the communication to
leave the statement without the
explanation of the statement because the
individuals who may feel they understand
it intrinsically may not believe it
necessary to explain it any further to
anyone else because they themselves do
not need a further
explanation. But be cognizant that when
you share to share on the terms of the
individual you are sharing with, not
just on your own terms, for that does
not serve. Allow yourself to
serve. Allow yourself to
identify to identify with the individual
you are sharing this information with
and allow yourself to understand how the
information can be put to best serve
those you are sharing it with.
Acques, explore the terminology, broaden
the horizon, expand the scope of the
terminology, invite the other individual
to share their understanding and supply
you with the terminology necessary to
make the idea clear to them in their own
terms.
The idea to further the analogy of the
right, wrong, good and
evil. Is that an
individual who may hear that only as you
would say halfway? You may say all you
are saying there is no right, there is
no wrong. That means anything goes. I
can do anything I want no matter what.
Is that what you are saying? Is that
what you really believe?
Now recognize of course that the
individual who said the phrase generally
speaking does not believe that but in
saying the statement halfway without the
foundation they may create that
confusion in the other individual.
Therefore recognize that a more
precise definition when it is shared with you
definition when it is shared with you
that there is no good and evil, right
and wrong, it is not that they do not
exist. Obviously those concepts exist.
But what is meant is that right and
wrong, good and evil are simply value
judgments and do not necessarily
represent the actual situation occurring
in terms of what it is as an expression
of positive or negative energy.
Allowing yourselves to understand
situations as expressions of positive or
negative energy will allow you the
precision to lay down the foundation to
explain what is meant when you say there
is no good and evil but only positive
and negative expression. For you can
even when you think of it yourselves
recognize that many things you may
consider good others can consider evil.
Many things you may consider wrong
others can consider right. Thus you
recognize that the ability to go back
and forth in this iie and have these two
perspectives of any given situation
should let you know right then and there
that what you are using as terminology
is only a value judgment and has nothing
to do with the definition of the
mechanics of the situation.
Therefore, a positive expression and a
negative expression will be a more
precise definition of the actual
mechanics of the situation as
follows. Positive situation, positive
expression is always that which is
integrated which allows a wholeness, a
unification, an addition to be formed.
And once again, very simply put in what
you would call practical terms,
according to what you need to hear as an
individual, it simply means that you are
as powerful as you need to be in and of
yourself to have anything you want
without having to hurt anyone else or
yourself to get it.
The idea of negative expression is that
which is segregated, separative,
limiting and in this way functions out
of domination, forcefulness and
therefore is a belief in powerlessness.
For the idea is that an individual who
needs to force themselves on any other
individual or group obviously does not
believe in the power of the idea they
are pushing. And thus it is an
expression of powerlessness and a saying
that you need a parasitic relationship
and rely upon another individual's
energy other than your own in order to
achieve what you wish to achieve.
Thus, you can recognize that
while individuals in your society may
label certain situations good, evil,
right, and wrong, there may be many
situations that are expressing positive
energy which many individuals may term
evil or negative in the sense that they
mean wrong. Whereas there are many many
negative situations that many
individuals may say that's good that is
right that that should happen even
though it is a negative
expression. Therefore recognize more
precision and more
clarity in explaining the
foundation of what the terms good and
evil, right and wrong have sprung from
will allow an individual to know that
when you say well there really is no
right and wrong it does not mean
anything else. It means that you still
have the opportunity and option to
function within
integrity powerful or without it
powerless. It is still that there
are negative situations. There still are
individuals who do not express
integrity. Some individuals may judge in a value
Some individuals may judge in a value
sense this to be good or right at
certain times, but it will never change
the idea that it is a negative
expression and thus brings its own
consequence, its own effect because it
is its own cause and the cause and the
effect are same event, one single idea.
Are you all following along this idea?
Yes. We share this idea at this time with you
We share this idea at this time with you
now because this is also the
representation of a shift and a change
taking place. And your opportunity to
recognize more and more physiological
interaction with more and more
individuals, more discussion of these
ideas will be as you say popping up in
your society. Now that you are expanding
and coming into contact with more and
more individuals who are at least
beginning to be aware of many of the
things that your society is
rediscovering about
itself. Thus, we simply suggest you that
you go forth in these interactions in
your lives clear and
concise, not
forcing, but simply clear and concise
about what it is you mean when you say
something. When you share
something, it is always of course up to
the other individual to supply their own
meaning, which they always will no
matter what you
do. But if you know you are clear and
concise and giving them the benefit of
the maximum amount of your
understanding, then you will have at
least painted the clearest picture of
yourself and your understanding that you
can. And thus you have completed your
responsibility to them. From that point
they are responsible for
themselves. You all follow along
for this and your willingness to share.
We will at this time thank you for all
the expansion that you create makes a
difference in our ability to interact
with you on many different levels and
share more and more. Thank you. Sure.
No, it's it's really amazing as usual
very many times. Your introduction is
reflects exactly something that's
happened to me and I just want to share
this. Yesterday I stayed home from work
and in the past whenever I had people
come with religious pamphlets or
Jehovah's Witnesses and so on come to
the door I would just tell them I'm not
interesting, close the door and thank
you goodbye. And I had two Jehovah
witnesses come
yesterday to the door and um very nice
people. And so I started talking to them
and I listened to what they said and I
started sharing my ideas that I learned
from you uh about uh judgments and
making choices and good and evil. And I
found it very exciting and it it's
exactly what you're talking about in the
introduction. So I thought I'd like to
share that with you.
Bashar Duke
as the uh civilization goes through
cycles of great enlightenment then it'll
go into a dark age and and cycle back
and forth. Is that like every time it
goes to a peak another graduating class
of the of the culture goes on and then
it goes down for another dive so to
speak is that's my picture of that is as
it has been not is as it is.
This is the transformational age and
represents what you would call an upward
spiral now that shall not cease
until you decide that you no longer need
this realm of reality. Is it is it what
what makes a difference now? new
management or something. In a sense, you
have formed a new coalition, a new
alliance with the rest of yourself.
And thus, you are now a full management
cooperation. That's different. Thank you. Well, this
That's different. Thank you. Well, this
let me ask you, let me go one step
beyond uh to higher dimensions. A lot of
things are pre-programmed and
predestined and preset. some some things
are done that on on a cultural basis to
to open up and blossom in certain
timings. Um, is this something you would
would you call this pre-programmed or
would you call this spontaneous new uh
uh a diversion from the old way? Would
you would you call from one level it is
both? Yeah. Okay.
And in your sense of timelines, it is
let us say at least in terms of an
opportunity pre-programmed. The
opportunity is pre-programmed. What you
do with it is still up to you. Okay.
Great. Thank you. Thank you. You venue.
Thank you. Uh Bashar, I just wanted to
say that I really enjoyed your opening
statement. I always do, but I enjoyed
not only the substance of it tonight,
but the form of it. I just really enjoy
your articulateness
uh just above and beyond. Not above and
beyond, but in addition to the substance
of it, it's just a lot of fun for me.
So, thank you for that. Thank you for
allowing us to reflect your enjoyment of
the idea, as you call precision. Yes.
Hey, I have another All right. Um I have
been experiencing some I'll call it
oddity of uh feeling in my body. Uh my
digestion is different, sluggish, going
through a an unusual phase and my
friends are experiencing some dis ease
and uh I I perceive that as some kind of
energy change or flux occurring. I can
you there is much once again thickening
of the energy field. Uhhuh. It is now
becoming as you would say palpable.
You are moving through the last
vestigages of the idea we can call
punny. A thickening of the energy field syrup.
A thickening of the energy field syrup.
Yes, it's been very much that way. I I
see the end of it right now because I'm
starting on a project and I can see
myself catapulting out of the the limbo
state is beginning to plug back in.
Momentum is being recognized again in
subtle waves. Would you explain the
limbo state? The idea I have discussed
that you have all generally been
disassociating yourselves completely
from the reality you used to be floating
in a nebulous state where you are
observing all the opportunities that are
available to you and now just beginning
to recconnect into a new reality.
Watching everything of the old reality
coming apart and watching things of the
new reality plugging in. Explain how
this is different. The limbo state is
different from the thickening. The limbo
state is more vacuous. The thickening
represents the replplugging in and the
identification of the new
energy. The thickening of the reality,
the solidification.
Okay. So, we're coming to an end of this
of the thickening. Back into a limbo
state. Not back into a limbo state. The
end of the thickening will signal you
getting used to the new energy. Not that
it is changing. It is that you are
changing and getting used to existing in
that more dense atmosphere.
Okay. I'm still confused. All right. We
weren't in limbo. You were in old
reality. As you unplug from old reality,
you put yourself in limbo state.
Everything is falling apart. Nothing
seems to be connecting. Everything is
swirling around me coming apart at the
seams. I am in the middle of this
vacuum. Everything seems beyond my
reach. What is happening? What is going
on? As you now begin to
As you now begin to
reconnect, things may thicken up because
you are now absorbing and accepting more
and more of the energy of the new self.
And at first, until you get used to it,
it will seem that you are breathing
thicker air because you have been used
for a while in the normal state to
existing within a vacuum. It seems as
you acclimate to the new atmosphere, it
will seem to spin out. But it is not
that it is spinning out. It is that you
are getting used to breathing the
thickened energy.
This represents the momentum towards the
idea of what we have termed your new
year and the acceleration of the
momentum towards many events that will
perpetuate more strongly and accelerate
more strongly the fourth density
reality. There are now going to be and
are beginning to be now more and more
physical opportunities for you to see in
your physical reality that represent the
way you are desiring your world to be.
And the more willing you are to become
active and participate and support and
create them physically, then the more
accelerated this energy will become, the
more acclimated you will become and the
more natural it will seem. What it will
leave you with is a sense of
invigoration, vitality that will never
leave you.
Will will this uh cycle repeat? um not
exactly repeat but similar cycles of to
some degree it will continue for some
time but each will now for those that
are willing to perceive it as such be a
cycle that will represent a stepping up
a stepping up a stepping
up and will not appear to be a repeat
the same the same the same so the
affirmation to the thickening then is uh
beginning and we're it is more
acceptance of more of your energy and hence the
of more of your energy and hence the
idea perceived in your third density
state so to speak a thickening. You are
bringing more of yourself into the
present space-time illusion. Thus the
atmosphere gets thick. Yeah, it is thick
with your potentials.
Manifest them, form them, shape them,
breathe them in, breathe the reality
out.
Does that assist you very much so? Thank
you very much. Thank you. Male venue.
It's nice to see you again to hear you
again. And I also enjoy your clarity and
conciseness and you speak with such
intensity that it kind of wakes me up
with each word and it's great. It
energizes for you. Uh I have a visitor
here with me. She's here for the first
time and I think she's a bit
overwhelmed. Um she's 84 and her
eyesight is failing her and I was
wondering if you could have some feeling
of what she can do to improve it. uh
she's a bit desperate about it and how
can I play a role in helping her? Thank
you. You can always impart the healing
energy of unconditional love and sharing
and recognize that the individual can
know themselves as an energy being, a
complete homogeneous energy being. Now
there are reasons for everything that is
created in your physiological life. And
in this case, as is many of the cases,
the idea of the stoppage or the
limitation of what you would call your
physical sight is now that it represents
a time when you are turning your sight
inward and exploring other dimensions of
reality. Allow us to ask a question.
Sure. Is the sight of your imagination still
Is the sight of your imagination still
sharp?
I don't think she like but I think it
is. She's very much aware.
In the
imagination your vision is always
crystal clear.
Allow yourself to begin to
remember to
remember for this is nothing new and you
have done this many times
before to
remember that your physical
reality is created from your
imagination. And if you are now willing
to remember that your physical reality
and your dream
reality, your dimension of imagination
are all one in the same
reality, then your physical reality can
become as clearly defined and as
crystallinly sharp as your imagination.
When you are willing to know that your
physical reality and imagination are one
and the same
thing. Do you understand?
Less and less separation there is
between that which you have for so long
called imagination and what you call
physical reality. For long in your society has
reality. For long in your society has
imagination been considered unreal.
when it is the prime reality out of
which you create all the illusions that
you experience. Allow the physical reality
experience. Allow the physical reality
to simply be another projection of the
imagination and it will gain in clarity
the same degree of clarity you know you
have with your inward vision.
Allow the vision that you have to be
what serves you as it is and
paradoxically you will relax your hold
upon it sufficiently to allow it to go
back to its balanced
state. Anything that is
imbalanced is only there because you are
holding it out of balance. You do not
have to make anything rebalance. You can
let go of the hold and allow it to
realign and
reclarify to come back
into focus.
Trust your energy. Trust your
imagination. and trust that you deserve
to exist in as natural a state as you
were created to begin
with. Identify with the infinite with a
capital I.
It is an opportunity also for you to
become a broader expanse and not so
limited in
focus. For the diffusion many times of
the physical site is what allows you to
broaden your vision on other
realms. You are
seeing other aspects of the path you are
walking more clearly now or will begin
to do take to heart the communications
and the visions you have in your dream
realities as well.
Relax and share the energy that is your
birthright to dip deeply into. Partake
of the pool of all that
is. Drink deep. We thank you. Is there
anything specific
that we can do to help or any symbol any
physical symbol that comes to your
imagination can be of assistance. Use
the one that feels right to you. One can
be the idea if you are willing as a
healer, recognizing of course that all
individuals feel
themselves to
place upon the eyes when
closed. the
hand. After
dipping into energized
water, waste with what you call
waste with what you call
punitis and spread the
aroma. Touch the
eyes when clothed and
partake and impart your unconditional
love along with
deep many many deep relaxing breaths to
oxygenate the system and allow for
cellular realignment and restructuring. One moment. Oh, also
Oh, also
as you
feel also you may find that as a tool,
as a
toy, a pattern of what you would call
116th diameter
holes, approximately 10 lines high,
approximately 10 lines wide, staggered,
not in a row but offset one row to the
next. Peering through will create the idea of
Peering through will create the idea of
utilizing the opposition muscles
physically in the eyes that are not
being used that are being held out of
focus and allow there to be the
exercising of those muscles to realign
so that the other muscles can come into
play and bring the eye back to the
equalization of all the musculature that
holds it in shape or out of shape.
for recognize that it is being held out
of shape.
Do you mean create a grid and place it
in front of her eyes? Yes. For exercise,
for you will find that looking through
such a grid with those center lines
placed one whole 16th of an inch in
diameter. Base 16th of an inch. Whole
16th of an inch. Base 16th of an inch in
both directions. offset will when looked
through give the eye the you call clear
vision physically. It allows the muscle to
physically. It allows the muscle to
realign in such a way that the ones
holding the eye out of shape are now
letting go and allowing the other ones
to pull it back into the other shape
necessary to form a
realignment. It functions as another
type of lens in a sense.
It can be used as a symbol, as a tool,
as a toy to get the
idea. And it will also allow you to know
that as you peer through that
grid, you can use it as a symbol to know
you are looking into other doors, other
probable realities, other physical
extensions of yourself and allow
yourself to also create a different
pattern of electrical activity in the
brain that goes along with it
to structure
electromagnetically, electrochemically, and give you a New
electrochemically, and give you a New
attitude. A new attitude will change the
physical being that you
are. All the while, breathe deep and
oxygenate yourself poweredly in a relaxed
yourself poweredly in a relaxed
way. We thank you. Thank you. Okay. What
do you mean by energized water? The idea
of your own oric field, the blue white
energy and the golden white simply in
your imagination projecting your hands
over the water and seeing the beams of
energy or the field of energy. Immerse
the water, seeing the water become in
its own way crystallized, crystallin,
energized. Approximately what you would
call five to 10 of your minutes of this
medication over the water will energize
it sufficiently. Ideally, as you say,
purified water is used.
Thank you. I wanted to ask you a
question about my ear and my right ear
in the station to the
ears and what can I do for that to clear
it up so my hearing can be clear? Have
you already attempted what you would
call your typical belief systems within
your own physical
reality and availed yourself of what you
would call your own medical
practitioner? Yes.
And um basically just to allow myself to
hear your medical
practice. You want
chiropractor and you're doing a lot of
balancing and healing,
but I feel that there's one moment.
Have crystals been utilized yet?
Some can be. If your practitioner has a
favorite, what you might call quartz,
also what you might call amethyst or
fluorite can be utilized, placed in
proximity, moved
around the area, and particularly
touched point first to the area
approximately along this line.
back and forth and then around and out
back and forth then around and out.
Okay. Also some degree of tolerable heat in
Also some degree of tolerable heat in
that area to allow the circulation to
flow. Add some on the surface
skin of what you would
call allows and
allows and
also an herbal substance that you
call the
arco. You follow me? Yes, but I never
heard of that. You can ask for it. It
will be understood. Pow the article.
Thank you. I'm the one. One
moment. What would also assist
you metallically will be certain types of
metallically will be certain types of
what are referred to as clays placed in
warm water and immersed in bathed
in to balance your electrolytic system.
All right. Okay. Thank you. I have one
more. All right. I was just curious if
we could get in touch with relationship
that um relationship bit
pardon continue. Um I was involved in a
relationship with a man for a year and a
half and all of a sudden about a month
ago he said that he doesn't want to ever
talk to me and he's not interested in
your relationship anymore and I felt
very close to this person and I was
wondering if he could give me some
insight if there's any past um yes there
is some past ideas. about what are you
learning from the present situation
that I seem to be opening up to a lot of
my own interest. It's just like what you
explained in the beginning about
everything falling apart and then coming
back together. Yes. But I feel strongly
that there's there's some past life that
that I don't know about that's going on.
That is all right. You can understand
everything you need to understand by
simply examining the situation in the
present for that is where you are. You
follow me? Yes.
Now one more.
Do you think there may be an opportunity
for you to recognize that there may be
some ideas that you are now reflecting
to that
individual that they may fear to see
within themselves. Yes. Exactly.
That's why they didn't want to take the
relationship because they didn't want to
hear it. In this way, can you recognize
that in this you are being of service to
the individual by reflecting these
things? Yes.
Then can you allow yourself to recognize
that in that way whether you see each
other physiologically ever again or not
the relationship still goes on for that
is one of the primary definitions of the
relationship to allow that individual to
see these ideas being reflected to them
so that they can come to terms with them
within themselves at whatever rate they
are willing to.
unconditional love. The same
unconditional love can still be sent
knowing that this individual is learning
what they need to learn and knowing that
that part of the relationship is still
being served in the way it was designed
to be served by both of you in
co-creating it. It is serving its
purpose. Allow it to serve its purpose
as it is not what you think it should
be. You follow. Then while that purpose
is being served, you
also will feel fulfilled and attract
into your situation whatever is
necessary to allow you to know that you
are still supported within any
relationship or situation that you
create. You will have what you need. He
will have what he needs.
Sometimes I feel a deep sadness and a
loss and emptiness. Why? When I think of
the closeness that we experienced and I
feel sad. One moment. Listen to
yourself. You are using past tense.
Closeness we
experienced. This means you are giving a
particular definition to closeness. Is
not what you are sharing with this
individual allowing him to understand
and learn right now. Close. Is it not
intimate? Is it not intimacy itself that
you would do this for him? that he would
allow this sharing to go on to learn
what he needs to learn to allow you to
be that reflection. Is that not
intimacy? Yes, it is. Yes, it is.
It is only your definitions of closeness
that allow you to feel as if you have
lost something. Change the definitions and
something. Change the definitions and
recognize that once you form a
relationship, it goes on forever and you
are always just as close. in different
ways but always just as close. Okay,
thank you that a lot. You are doing
different things within the closeness
that allow the purpose of the
relationship, the reasons for why you
formed it to be
served. Allow it to be
served. Then you can see a smoothing out in your
Then you can see a smoothing out in your
life one way or another. Whether it is
through that individual or not does not
matter. But there will be ultimately a
smoothing forward.
Allow any
relationship to be what it is, not what
you think it should
be. For many times what you think it
should be has no bearing on the actual
service being
rendered. And many times it allows you
to think that a service is not being
rendered and that you have not agreed to
create it exactly as it is being created
which you
have. You follow me. So I created it to
be how it is right now. You cocreated
it. It cannot be otherwise.
Now get in touch with the idea that you
are being very intimate in new ways and
you will recognize with more clarity why
you have cocreated it that way. Because
if you truly wish that
individual to be as full an individual
as they can be, then you will want them
to see certain things that are coming
from you now. so that you can also be as
full an individual as you wish to be
without the
idea of being what another thinks you
should be and vice
versa. Would you not want an individual
in a relationship with you to relate to
you rather than what they think you
should be?
Then give them the same gift. All
All
right. a lot clearer. Thank you. Thank
you for creating the clarity within the
reflection we have shared with you. It
is your doing. We thank you for your
willingness to open those doors and
expand the relationship that you are
with all beings in the universe.
Thank you for show.
Yes, I understand that Monday through
the physical channel uh you did some
clay actual clay sculpting with
I'm sure you enjoyed it. Nice. How does
it feel to to sculpt the remote for the
channel? Invigorating. Really sounds
exciting. And it opens an add what you
would call a new dimension through which
some of the levels that we are
communicating with you on can gain a
physical representation that do not exist now.
uh to have clay available for the future
next week of your time. Thank you. Sherry,
Sherry,
I have two questions. Um one concerns
dreams. I was wondering if we still
learn from dreams whether we remembered
them or not. Of course, consciously. So
we we still grow from the experience
always. Um, my other question is that right
Um, my other question is that right
before I came here, I fell asleep and I
had a dream and but in the dream all I
can remember was an incredible
recognition of some kind of
connection and and then I woke I woke up
and I have no absolutely no memory but I
felt as if it was something that
was I don't know it looked like a very
deep realization. You will begin to see
that realization in your physical life with
realization in your physical life with
more expressions of synchronicity, more
coincidences occurring in your physical
reality. Many times understand that
these realizations, these connections
that you make do not have to come into
what you would call analytical
understanding. They will manifest as
realizations in your physical reality.
And then you will understand what the
connection is you made because you will
see it in your life physically more and
more of what you need. exactly when you
need it will appear in your life
automatically. That is one of the
connections. It is becoming more of the
idea of synchronicity. It is recognizing
that everything is the same one
thing manifesting in multi-dimensional
simultaneous aspects.
You follow me? Yes, I do. Uh will the
dream state and the waking state begin
to blend into one state?
Yes, you are living a dream right
now. Right
now, spacetime is your illusion, is your
dream, is your creation to understand
yourselves in that particular
manner. As you allow yourself to
remember that dream reality, imagination
reality and physical reality are all one
reality. Then you will remove, dissolve,
absorb the barriers that you have
created between them and you will be
able to experience more of the dreamlike
quality in your physical reality and
things will become most magical. Bishar
is the uh negative ego a contrived
ballast system for perceiving these
these levels. Is that its function? It
is a part of the artificial personality
construct that allows you to express and
experience polarity within the space-time illusion.
polarity within the space-time illusion.
So it is essential for experiencing that
for the polarity. It is essential for
experiencing negative effect. But now
you no longer need to.
Ego itself will remain as long as you
are focused in physical reality because
that is what its job is to keep you
focused into the reality you have
created yourself to exist within. But
even that will loosen up a bit. Yeah. As
one I was doing that the other day I
couldn't I couldn't remove my
frustration on a certain area. So I
started pulling it in and pulling it in
digesting it. Yay. And it um it seemed
to be the only thing that really got rid
of it. That is because you cannot get
rid of anything. There is nowhere to get
rid of anything to Well, it it made it
so it was not it was not uh you
transformed it by accepting it by
exploring it by letting it be something
that would serve you in a positive way
that would allow you to discover more of
yourself rather than rejecting it as
something that had nothing to do with
your life.
You accepted it, acknowledged it, loved
it, used it, transformed it, and
accelerated and expanded the being that
you are by adding it to yourself rather
than rejecting it. Attempting to get rid
of anything only diminishes you because
all that you are attempting to get rid
of are aspects of you and they are all
there for a purpose and all there for a
reason. And the moment you acknowledge
and accept them as you have, you will
then add to the being that you are in
your sense of your expansion, your sense
of your awareness of how much more of
you there is to explore and enjoy.
Thank you.
One moment for the uh I got a lot of
things but the one focus right now the
big bang where there was this initial
explosion and consciousness dispersing
out in very all directions.
Um there's been other big bangs, haven't
there for other other systems? Is there
a continuous like eternity or infinity
or whatever the word is that would
be initiating these sparks? Something
beyond our own our
own, you know, is there another whess or
whatness out there that would that would
in a sense? But again
understand any level to which you care
to take it, you can always ask the same
question. Well, is there something more?
Yeah, it is infinite with a capital I
infinite. That is the otherness, the
whess. It is the infinite.
I guess what I was asking on a deeper
level uh was is it bridgeable? Can you
bridge over to it and and experience
that? Is I guess what I'm saying? Or it
can one step keep stepping up in a
sense. Yes. But once again, by
definition infinity always carries with
it the ability to know there is always
something more.
M you know it's a kind of a a clever
system of sending these things these
runners out in all directions and
they're all going to work on different
things and create then there'll be a
whole gallery of stuff to see as do not
forget that some of the runners is the
concept direction
itself. You follow me? No. Some of the
so-called runners that are being sent
out in all directions is the very idea
that there is a direction something in
direction itself are some of the
runners. Yeah, I was thinking in terms
of particles. Okay. Thank you. Yes.
Um, part of that
thickening, something that's been
happening with me, uh, is a thickening
of the mucus in my throat and sinuses,
just buckets of it. Yes. And especially
sinus sensitivity to electromagnetic
changes upon your planet at this time
are primarily because of the high degree
of the substance you call magnetite in
your sinuses, which is very sensitive to
electromagnetic changes in your
planetary sphere of influence. Okay.
Also, as much
release, too. Nice. And I've actually
been choking um and staying up all night
doing this. I I took an hour and my
concern is that that suppresses the
release. Is that true?
Not really.
Good. But in this way, you can also
recognize that once again, the deep
breathing and the pure oxygenation and
the increase in the intake of purified
water into your system will also be in
the system.
Oxygenate your system and in your
imagination allow yourself to know that
you are creating within your oric field
the type of atmosphere that you can
breathe easily and
clearly. Create the atmosphere you wish
to breathe.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm having trouble. That's
good. Thank you very much. Thank you.
Hello. I wrote something for you I want
to share with you. Oh,
I cuddle with poor Bashard.
You who have been my friend even when I
was not. You who have gently guided me
to see the light that I am. You who have
been so kind when I judged so harshly.
You, sweet soul, are cherished beyond
the power of my words to express.
We thank you for your reflection and we
thank you also for speaking of yourself
in the same way. And we would remind you
that it is very easy for us to look upon
you all this way because whether you
choose to do so or not, we believe in
you. Thank you. Bishar,
Bishar,
um, we've been over this before, but I
still have a little difficulty. That is
all right. It is very enjoyable to
examine the creations of your
difficulties. Okay.
Now I I have this distinction between
form which I categorize all thoughts,
all spaces, all concepts and I have a
spaces, all concepts and I have a
difficulty cuz I I believe I understand
you to say that a person is their
uh creations. I there is no need to beat
yourself up with terminology.
It is quite easy to understand on
whatever level you need to. Okay. Now,
we understand you enjoy the terminology
game and we will play along. Okay.
Well, let's let's try this. Okay. I look
at it there's a there's a contradictory
which at some levels everything all
truths are contradictory. All right. And
uh the way I see it okay I can see your
point of view that that
um a person creates something they are
that thing. I can also see a not so much
spatial distance but a certain kind of
um quality distance between the creator
and the creation and the distance itself
is also a part of the creation and
therefore also a part of the creator. So
I see this just to come to terms with
this I is that yes a person is the
creation they are the perception of the
creation and neither is true both are
true right
all truths are real and true yes okay
that that steps it up a little bit
very enjoyable game
um talking Now again after this one um a
couple of the things that he was talking
about I'd like to share another aspect
on on he was saying something about his
frustration and trying to deal with that
and you were saying the answer was to
integrate and to love that part of it
last week I um spoke to you about a
situation that was going on with myself
and you gave me some similar um advice
in the area and I went home this week
and tried to tried.
Yeah. To apply it. All right. And then
once as I was trying to apply it, I
began to
more and more understand what it is that
you're communicating to me and to try
and relax with it. And then I began to
relax. Okay. Right. And I began to see
that the situation that I spoke to you
about was a reoccurring situation and
one that anytime it appeared in my
space, I would get very very tense and
upset about and try to stop that from
happening. And what I realized was that
I had two methods of handling that. One
was to
um one was to avoid the situation to try
to make it not occur. I see. Right. To
probably hold it down and then when it
came back try again and again and again
and again and again and again.
The other was to invalidate myself for
having the situation. Oh that has always
been much fun.
Lots and lots of fun. Couldn't stop it
any harder. And and then I was lying on
the beach last week and I was looking at
the situation and I was going through
all this mental activity on it and I
realized that one of the basic things
that I was doing was I was resisting
very heavily this situation at all. Yes.
And that by the very act of resisting
it, you gave it more energy, right? And
more power. Yes. The harder I would
resist it, the more I would get it, of
course. And the more I would run away
from it, the more I would get it has
nowhere to go. You are its entire
universe. So I'm like carrying him
around a leash.
And interesting cuz I decided that in my
universe and totally in my universe that
one thing was one of the very few things
that I could not
experience for myself that I felt I
could not experience. I can I felt that
I could experience a lot of things but
not that one. All right. So I decided
to let it go and to let it permeate me.
Thanks and see what occurred. I couldn't
speak more than anything expected. It
was it was um it was interesting that it
was definitely a force and I let it flow
through me and just was there with it.
Yes. And then it began to peel apart and
to to blow apart and to the un and to be
replaced by an understanding
of what was creating the situation which
was as you said what um what value that
that situation by flowing through it
could give to me and I came out of that
after freing out and avoiding it so
strongly with the most wonderful gift of
realization within that situation. Yes.
Two things. One was that I was indeed
beyond a shadow of a doubt both creating
the positive and the negative aspects of
the situation continuously. I was giving it
situation continuously. I was giving it
its meaning. Yes. And I was creating its
intensely negative meaning. Absolutely.
Right. And I was also creating that I
couldn't have that. And I was creating
that way to get out of it. And all these
things that were going on, I I realized
without a shadow of a doubt that I was
creating them moment by moment. The next
thing was that the resistance of ideas
and situations is what gives them the power
situations is what gives them the power
and the energy and that I am also
creating that. Yes, that is it. That is
the only place they get their power
from. Andrew, is there anything more
that you can say on resistance as an
idea? Well, simply that once again to
expound upon what you have said,
recognize you are your own universe.
There is no outside
Therefore, you can't push anything
outside of your universe and when you
try to in that you do try. The idea
simply is that it comes up colloquially
speaking against the membrane against
the wall that
represents the edge of your universe.
And because you are pushing it up
against the wall, it has nowhere to go,
nothing to do but compress, compress,
compress, compress. And you know that
when you compress something, it has more
potential energy to spring back that
much harder. Right? So that is all
you're doing is giving it the potential
energy to come bouncing back 100fold
instead of letting it in, letting it
through you and transforming it when it
first makes itself known. Right? And
then it can move and change into
something else. Then it is a dance.
Right. Right. Yes. Do you know how
excited I am right now?
I got it. Thank you very much for your
crystallizations. Sh. Sh.
Guys,
do you know what's in the um runes of
the pyramids that haven't been opened up
yet? Some
would you tell us what it is and what in
fact it's going to have? Don't you want
to find out?
Yes. Now,
then go and find
out. Become involved.
become involved. This is more than a subtle
involved. This is more than a subtle
clue.
You know, it's interesting because there
was about a month ago there was a big
deal about they're about to open the
tomb and this new passageway that was so
carefully sealed up. so carefully sealed
up, but they detected it with I guess
some sort of resonance equipment or
something that there's another space
back there and then it just like no news
after that. It was a big thing on the
news. Go and find out. And then it was
just sort of make your inquiries where
you will
where you think is available to make
such inquiries. See what answers you
get. Are you saying that to me
personally? I am saying it to whoever is
interested. All right. Thank you. Can
you give her a ride?
[Laughter] She can take herself much farther than
She can take herself much farther than
she thinks.
Oh. Oh, I should go not in the physical.
You can do that.
You can also go out of body. You can
also do the physical thing of opening up
the idea with other individuals. say
whatever happened to you
know what's going on with that I would
like to
know talk to your
media let them talk to you equalize this
idea use it as an opportunity to
equalize and empower yourself to know
you have the ability to communicate with
these individuals and they are not so
very far away
after all it's all on the same planet
Very close at hand. And as you open
those chambers within
yourself, then will all information be
revealed to
you. The chambers that are being opened
are within you first and
foremost. When you are willing to take
the responsibility for what is within,
then any symbol in your physical reality
will also become
clarified. Now you have tunnneled a
small hole into that chamber and you
have taken a
peek. Find the door and go in. It is
there. Communicate. Communicate.
Communicate. Get it out in the open. Do
not let it become a
secret. Do not bury it in the sands of
your unconscious. Once
again, this is an
activity, physical activity. This is one
of the opportunities we have been
speaking of. Go and find out.
bring it out into the light for all to
see. If you are truly excited about
discovering what is there, then
recognize that as soon as you are
willing to take part in the overall
discovery as a single event that
includes you, the sooner it can come to
light. And it is one of the things that
the discovery of that chamber actually
symbolizes. Your willingness to
participate in opening and revealing
what was formerly buried.
You follow. Great. Yes. Thank you very
much. You let me know what you find.
Okay. More and more this is your world.
More and more you have the opportunity
to truly act like a citizen of the
entire planet.
get involved.
There are no
barriers unless you choose to continue
to reinforce them.
All right. Okay. Thank you, Bashar. You
um on the way back from Las Vegas, uh
Steve and I were driving in the car and
just as we were leaving Vegas about I
don't know maybe 50 miles out, I Okay, I
didn't see a spaceship. Okay, that's
okay. Um,
I
believe however I feel
I do feel though a
um Oh, I was very happy to describe
feeling a very marked change of
frequency about 50 mi out and it was
almost it was just you know
Okay. The energy vortex, the magnetic
vortex in the area, the edge of it, so
to speak. Yeah. It was almost as if I
almost felt that I could explode, but I,
you know, I wasn't going to do that.
Didn't feel that I had to. It was just a
very high intensity. Um,
that is what it was. Yeah. Passing
through a membrane.
Yeah. Okay. Bashan, what is that out
there? I've noticed it, too. It's very
uh, of course, part of it's called the
devil's the devil's playground and death
valley and all that. is once again the
ideas in a different form that we have
been discussing about energy gates,
energy doorways. There is a very highly
magnetic one in that area. It it's very
draining in in some areas. It's very
depends upon what you bring in with you.
Bashar following uh yeah like uh hope
hope is despair. Despair is raining.
Yeah. Yeah. strips that off.
Thank you.
The shark you um I have this is my first
time here first of all and I'm very
excited about all of this. It's
something that I'm really into. I have
created a lot of blocks and a lot of
problems in my physical body. Oh, you
have created so many rich opportunities
then. Not blocks, not problems. Thank
you. Um yes, that's true. I I'm rather
confused about this. I I heard
everything that you said and I do feel
like my life has fallen apart and it's
starting just a little bit now to come
back together again. Nice. You are in
sync with everyone else. Good. Um I just
don't I don't know. Are you doing in
life what excites you the most? I'm not
doing anything. Does that excite you the
most? No. What does excite you the most?
This kind of stuff. All right. In what
way does it excite you?
Um, I become alive and I I have more
energy. How would you wish to
participate and be of service with
regard to this
idea? How would it excite you to be
involved with this idea? As you say, how
could you express it that would be most
exciting to
you? What can you do with it?
I'd like to somehow be able to share it
with with anybody who's What do you
think you are doing right now?
But I feel real confused about that is
all right. Confusion is only fusion with
more of yourself. Co-fusion it is part
of the limbo state is one of the
symptoms of change. It is not
intrinsically negative unless you think
it is.
You follow me? Yes, I confusion is
becoming more aware of more of your tent
so that you have more to draw upon.
Do you draw? No.
All right. All right. Close enough.
You draw pictures with words.
Yes. Does that excite you?
Yes, it does. A lot.
Yes. When I do it successfully, I don't
feel like
Are you a writer? No. You're not? I just
write poems for myself. I'm not. That
means you're not a writer.
I told you I'd be giving up too much.
Oh, you are not as new as you think.
You are creating the understanding and
the comprehensions rather rapidly. I
find now are you a writer or not? I'm a
now are you a writer or not? I'm a
writer. Yes, you are. Do you enjoy being
a writer? Yes, I do. Then act like
one. write because you enjoy it. And
know beyond a shadow of a doubt that if
you truly are a writer and that is
really what excites you in life, then
you will be automatically supported in
the writing and you will attract
whatever situations you need to
coincidentally synchronistically that
you need to to allow yourself to
continue to be the writer that you are.
In whatever way you need to be supported
in your reality, you will be and you
will coincidentally attract all the
situations you need. Anytime you are
willing to do what it is that excites
you the most, you are allowing yourself
to consciously recognize that you are in
synchronous harmony with the path that
represents who and what you chose to be.
That's what excitement is for. It is the
barometer. It is the arrow that lets you
know that following your excitement does
represent the path you chose to be.
That's what excitement is. That's why no
matter what the situation looks like on
the surface, if it has the excitement
behind it, no matter how different it is
from any other situation you did, that
had the same degree of excitement, it is
the excitement that is there to let you
know that this is a part of the same
overall path. No matter what it looks
like, no matter how different it appears
on the surface, that is what an
excitement is for. You follow me? Yes.
How am I stopping myself? By not
believing in yourself. By not trusting
that to do what it is that does excite
you can support you.
by simply thinking it is more difficult
than that, that it isn't that
easy. As a writer, you may be familiar
with many of the phrases your society
has concocted that allow you to believe
it is not that simple. Easier said than
done. That will never work. Grow up.
That's
childish. Anything worth having is worth
struggling for. No pain, no gain.
So you think, well, if I'm really a
writer, I have to pay my
dues. I have to really suffer before I
can write something worth anything that
anyone would want to read, that anyone
would enjoy, that would have any meat in
it. You follow me? Yes. Now all of these
You follow me? Yes. Now all of these
things may simply be unconsciously
within you because of the society you
have been born into and grown up within.
But recognize writing is an expression of
recognize writing is an expression of
your own creatorhood and comes
effortlessly without struggle without
strife. Now if you are excited about all
these ideas we are sharing then write
about them.
share in the way that you share as a
writer and what you give effortlessly
will come back to you effortlessly a
thousandfold guaranteed by the universe.
It's in your
contract absolutely 100%
guaranteed no loopholes.
I'm probably more of a teacher than I am
a writer. You are always a teacher and a
learner. And writing is one way to teach
and one way to learn. You are a sharer,
which is the blending of a teacher and a
learner. You follow me? All beings are
sharers. Teach in whatever way is
enjoyable for you. You will always be
supported. Do what excites you the most
and watch your life become an ecstatic
explosion of coincidence. It will not be
very long before you will share with me
all of the coincidence coming back into
your life. You will find that this will
occur very
rapidly. Very rapidly. Why?
Why?
Because you actually are beginning to
believe you really have that much power.
The idea previously in your society to
know you are that powerful that is what
has been scary because you think oh well
that much power that's a big
responsibility. What if I screw
up? I don't want that much power. No,
no, no, no, no, no, no. Take some of
this power away from me. Take the
responsibility. No, no, no, no, no.
But understand getting in touch with the
understand getting in touch with the
fact that you are that powerful means
you are totally yes totally in control
of everything in your life and therefore
you can choose what you prefer and if
you simply know that you have no need to
express the idea of your power lacking
in integrity then you never will. So why
worry about it? Right on. Yeah.
We follow along. You are completely in
control even when you create a scenario
in which it seems you are out of
control. So knowing that you are in
control of the seemingly out of control
illusion will put you squarely back in
control and allow you to choose what you
prefer. If you do not prefer the
illusion you have created then create
what you prefer consciously do it. Just
do it. Act upon what you prefer knowing
that you will always function within
your integrity.
All right. Yeah. Trust, trust, trust.
Faith is the mechanism. It is all you
need. Trust. Again, we understand what
your society has been taught.
But when you allow yourself complete and
total trust that the universe always
supports you, when you do what it is
that represents what is truest for you,
then you can understand very simply that
by definition when you are what you know
you are. The universe will completely
reflect everything that belongs to
you because you are willing to truly be
what you are. And thus all you will get
in your life is all the things that
support the you you are willing to be
that is what you get anyway all the
time. You are always supported 100%. Do
not think that we are saying you have to
begin to do something you have never
done before. You do not have to learn
one new thing except that it is your
point of view that will determine the
type of support you get from the
universe because the universe always
supports what you believe to be true for
yourself. You always get what you believe you will
You always get what you believe you will
get. You follow it? Yeah. So all you
need to do is get in touch with the idea
that now you know that everything you
are getting is something that will
support you in a positive way. And no
matter how it appears, if you know that
to be true, you will not supply the same
old meanings to what may appear to be
appear to be the same symbols. Four, no
symbol has built-in meaning. You supply
the meaning. The symbols may appear the
same, but if you give them a different
meaning, they will have a different
effect. All right.
All right.
Well, why don't you march and you may
all take a short break.
The idea of creating a reality in which
you do not believe you are creating your
reality and thus must ask the question,
how do I choose the reality I prefer?
Because along with the idea of fighting
your ecstasy comes
forgetfulness. You block out the reality
by fighting your ecstasy that you are
creating your reality because all your
energy goes into the idea that you are
not in control of your reality and
therefore have to fight it to get it to
be where you wish to
be. So if you are willing to know that
you can simply do what excites you the
most and that will put you squarely in
touch with the fact that you are
creating your reality because then your
physical reality will be a complete and
obvious reflection through synchronicity
and coincidence that you are creating
your reality. Then you will see it in no
uncertain terms in a very clairvoyant
and obvious way. All you need to do is
do what excites you the
most. What do you prefer?
I have trouble. I'm not quite sure if
I'm ready to look at it. All right,
that's up to you. Now, may I ask you a
question? Yes.
Yes, you are making sure that you will
say yes by allowing someone else to say
it. So that if you cannot bring yourself to
So that if you cannot bring yourself to
say it, at least someone will. Very
creative reflection.
But in your estimation that you are not
ready yet, what do you think you could
possibly find that would be something you would
find that would be something you would
not be ready to
handle? Go ahead. Use your imagination.
I didn't quite get there. When you say I
am not ready to handle it yet, I am not
ready yet to understand this or explore
a certain idea. What is it in your
imagination you think you could find
that would be something you couldn't
handle? You must have an idea or a
reason for saying I'm not ready yet.
What is it you imagine you will find
that will let you think you're not
ready? Would be would actually be
changing what I'm doing in life.
Yes. You're not ready to change it.
Apparently, I think not. All right. But
now that you are in touch with that, do
you prefer to change it? Yes. Then
apparently you
[Laughter] are. It is that simple. If you are
are. It is that simple. If you are
willing to let it
be allow what you prefer to be what you
are capable of
handling. It is that simple. One more
time. Allow what you
Allow what you
prefer. Allow what you prefer to be what
you are capable of handling. Why
handling. Why
not? Otherwise, it never would have
occurred to
you. You can only have an occurrence of
what is something that is within your
ability. The universe does not do
extraneous and pointless things.
So you do not conceive of things you
cannot handle.
Thank you. Thank you. For sure.
For sure. I understand that it's
appropriate for me to get out of that
wedding. Appropriate. Does that mean you
are excited about it? Yes. Ah, very
appropriate then. However, I
However, one of those fancy cologne
wheel. Yeah, but you know, I I don't
know how to begin. I know so much. Oh,
you have already begun. What do you mean
you don't know how to begin? You have
already begun. Well, can you can you
help me further? I mean, as far as I
know so little. I can help you help
yourself. Okay. Would you Will that do?
That would do very well. Oh, thank you
very much. Thank you. All right. Now
what do you
imagine will be the expressive form that
this will take? How do you see it
manifesting in your imagination? Well,
it will be like this. Describe it for me
how you see it
manifesting. Go on. Get into it.
I I don't know. Oh, come
now. Well, I I imagine that Yes. that as
I sit with paper and pen in hand that
information will come. Do you see
yourself writing this information out in
your visualization? Yes, I do.
First and foremost, please don't tell me
you don't know.
Because you obviously do. I am not
asking you for anything more than that
visualization at this moment. Follow me.
Fine. Fine.
Now see yourself
writing this information whatever it may
be right now it does not matter. All
right. Uhhuh. Can you see yourself doing
it? Yes. Does it feel like it can be
real for you? Yes. Are you sure? Yes, I
am. Oh, thank you very much once again.
Then allow me to remind you once again
that if you can imagine yourself doing
it, you are doing it. You are the person
who does it. Not the person who will do
it. You are the person who does it. If
you can imagine and feel what it would
be like, paradoxically, you are actually
the person who knows what it is like. In
that moment, you are imagining what it
would be like. You are the vibrational
frequency of the person that knows what
it is like.
Get a hold of that. All right. All
right. Bring it into the present. Don't
keep it in the future. Well, it will be
like this. If you can conceive of it,
you are that person right now. Okay. All
you need to really do in an overall
sense is begin to act like you are that
person. Do the things that person would
do if you truly were that person. Put
the paper in front of you. Put the pen
in your hand. Sit
there and play. Feel around. Open up.
Experiment. Use your imagination. Let
anything come out. Let it be gibberish.
Who cares? Okay. Let it be squiggles.
Let it be lines. Let it be geometric.
Let it be free form. Let it be circles.
Let it be squares. Let it be triangles.
Let it be a grocery
list. At this point, what it is does not
matter. What matters is that you do the motion
What matters is that you do the motion
that you get used to allowing yourself
to be in that state and feel what it is
like to be that person. You follow me?
Yes. This is your technique. This is
your exercise. Simply do it bit by bit. As
exercise. Simply do it bit by bit. As
you begin to relax into it and begin to
go into the daydream that you
are, things will flow a bit here, a bit
there. It may, even though each letter,
each word may be in your terms
intelligible. The whole sentence may not
make sense. Uhhuh. It may not work into
a paragraph yet. Or it may. And allow me
to remind you of one very important
factor right now. Wait a second. But I'm
getting there.
Do not fall off the edge
of let whatever
comes be all right for now. Even if you
think you consciously wrote
it. Understand this. This is very
important. Let it be all right for you
to be conscious of what you are writing.
Okay, let it for now be all right to
feel well. I'm just doing this. This is
my own expression. Let that be all
right. You follow me? For you at first
will find that it may be subtle and you
will wonder, well, is this me? I cannot
tell. That is all right. That is
precisely what is needed. For in order
to allow, paradoxically enough, linkage
with what you would call another
consciousness to occur, you must first
be completely willing to allow it to
fully be
you. You follow me? Because then that
says, you know, you are always in
control and nothing is going to take you
over against your will. Thank you. You
follow me? Yes. Then bit by bit as you
express confidence that you are equal to
the communication, equal to the
consciousness you are communicating
with, then you will blend as equals and allow
then you will blend as equals and allow
you to form a simolacum, a model
in your reality of the other
consciousness. And you will simply go
into your daydream and allow whatever
comes out to come out. And it will be.
And here's the second important point.
It will be wherever it needs to be.
Trust, no matter how it sounds, is
serving a purpose. No matter who the
other individuals are that are receiving
the information you are giving, if you
know that you are being of service and
you simply trust that you are doing it
in love and light and integrity,
whatever it is that comes out will be
what is needed to be heard.
Even at at first it is as you say
sketchy all thing you will progress. All
right. All right. So the primary
prerequisite is that you do not try too
hard that you enjoy enjoy enjoy for it
will not serve your
purpose that you do not be allowed by
the other consciousness to enjoy and to
function as
yourself. You follow? Yes, then it will
be a
co-creator simply you will acquire more
and more confidence and more and more
trust and then what comes out will not
just be the idea oh well what does this
other consciousness have to communicate
what will come out will be the
representation of the trust that you are
co-creating in the blending for
recognize what you are experiencing
right now is not so much the idea
distinctly of just my consciousness And
it is not precisely the consciousness of
the physical channel. It is a third
identity that is at once neither of us
and both of us. And it represents the
idea of the trust we have within each
other. You follow me? Yes, I do. Does
this assist you? Yes, it does very much
so.
Also simply put
out though it may appear in unobtrusive
ways which is the more likely way it
will appear since this is totally up to
you but put out that you are willing to
accept whatever
assistance others are willing to give
physical and
non-physical you follow. Are you
speaking in terms of a spirit? Yes.
Fine. Simply put it out that you are
willing to accept the assistance on
whatever level it needs to be there upon
whether it is apparent or not is not
important. Okay, it will be there
in exactly the way it needs to be to let
you know you are in full control. Once
again, it may come in the form of simply
being in connection with your quote
unquote higher self. And it may come in
the form of simply finding exactly the
right material you need at exactly the
right time or talking to exactly the
right person, the right place, the right
time to get the answers you need or
walking up and seeing something that
sparks an idea within you and allowing
yourself to act upon that intuition, act
upon that excitement and go with the
flow. It can be any of these. It can be
all of these. It can be more of these.
Enjoy. Thank you for Thank you very much for
Thank you for Thank you very much for
your willingness to function as a
doorway and a gate to more of all that
is
for sure.
Yes. Um I understand that these weekly
group channelings may be discontinued
this month as such. Uh some of them may
be can you at this time share more
specifics on that? The idea first and
foremost is that it is time for less
talk and more do. Yes. Can you indicate
uh what the frequency will be? Uh when
this frequency will change it will be
more spontaneous. For now the idea of
what you are calling this particular
interaction this night of your time will
continue for some time. The major change
at this time comes in the format you
would recognize as what you call Monday
Tuesday. Okay. But there will be changes of
Okay. But there will be changes of
content. There will be changes also in
the expression of your willingness to
do and be equal by doing. Yeah. I have
something else to share also. Oh, what
do you recall that we chatted about the
fact that I found that my metal watch
was uh disrupting the energy flows of my
body? Well, I got a plastic one and I like it
Well, I got a plastic one and I like it
a lot. It doesn't disrupt the flows like
the other one did. And I'm enjoying it
very much. It's got the standard
features, you know, like time, day,
date, micro wave, field, or space and
time travel, the usual
thing. Did you get it wholesale?
[Laughter] You got a black hole. Thank you.
Is there something else you wish to
explore? Not really. I just wanted to uh
say that
uh crack a joke and have some fun. Oh,
thank you for cracking a joke. the light
shine. Hey,
Hey,
um I would like to explore further how I
can create more wellness in my life and
get rid of some of the blocks that are
under. You go right ahead.
You go right ahead.
How can I create more wellness in my
back? How can I stop eating sugar so
much? All right. All right. Are you doing what
All right. All right. Are you doing what
excites you the most in life?
Big hesitation. I went over that.
Understand that many times the idea of
what you call the increase of the intake
of the substance you call sugar in your
life many of your lives is a
representation that you know you are
sped up but because you are in a sense
not doing exactly what you want to do.
You are giving yourself a symbolic
intake of the idea physically in order
to speed yourself up to match that
vibrational level. You do not have to do
it with a physical substance. The idea
is that you can energize yourself by
simply doing what it is that excites you
the most and it will sustain you as it
needs to and you will no longer need or
have the urge. The idea of the
physiological representation of that
accelerated momentum.
It will also aid and assist in your
wellness since you will be functioning
from a balanced point of view and you
will not be out of whack with yourself.
Thank you.
You follow me? Yes, absolutely.
Flex ability. Flex
ability. Not so rigid. Not so strain.
Not too
tense. Flex ability. Enjoy.
ability. Enjoy.
Will this do?
Yes, I have. But I had another question
too. Proceed. I wanted to know how I can
help a friend of mine who has very bad
tension headaches and prevents him from
moving in his life in any direction. Is
there something I can do to help him
with that?
You can explore the idea of what he
fears in the movement.
Does he fear loss of
control? Afraid to make a move?
He is afraid to make a move. He's very
dependent on his
mother. There may be an opportunity for
this individual to allow themselves to sit
individual to allow themselves to sit
down in a meditative state, a relaxed
state, and become that which they
believe they are dependent upon and have
a dialogue with it. and say all of the
things to that portion of
themselves that they wish to say to the
physiological being for it is actually
to themselves that they wish to say
it. Then perhaps once that type of
communication has been established
within the self, the type of
communication necessary in the outward
world between the different beings may
be initiated and movement may be
started. You follow me? Yes, I do. In
any event, there is always an
opportunity to take any reflection of
any other being you see in your physical
reality and recognize it as an aspect of
your own consciousness and have a
conversation with it in whatever matter
you desire
to. There at
least knock down dragouts will not cause
any disruption of the family.
Yes. You follow me? Yes.
Then he can get it all out of the system
and begin a more open communication
within the self. That will allow for
more open communication externally as a
reflection of the open communication
within the self to that particular
fragment or aspect of his own
consciousness represented by the idea
and the symbol you call mother.
Yes. Thank you.
Does this
individual like citrus?
I don't know.
The biting into of what you would call
the fruit orange, the fruit lemon, the
fruit lime. A single bite and the
savoring thereof may also assist in some
of the alleviation of what you call the
pain. We will let you figure out
why. For that is a part of your process.
For sure. For sure. One moment.
Have you figured it out yet?
Biting into the citrus. Yeah.
After biting a lemon, you're not going
to feel anything. Close.
Very sour. Close. The lips.
Come on. You are so close.
Focus. Well, yes. But why? [Laughter]
[Laughter]
Is it because of the acid and the acid
quality of the This all has to do with
it. The bitterness of the relationship.
Thank you. Taking a bite out of it.
Savoring it.
Biting into it. Getting your teeth into
it. Becoming involved. Not being afraid
to take a bite out of it.
And this is part of my process
to understand the symbology.
Thank you very much. Bashan, I have a
question. I asked you before about
transportation. If we can just go from
one place to another by the thought in
our mind and you said that we do it but
we have series of what we call movement
is to just eliminate the process. How
can I do that?
recognize that if you have a reason to
do it, you will do it first of all.
Secondly, once again, for now with that
particular aspect, we will allow you to
rely on your own
imagination. For the idea right now is
not something that is not that it can't
be done in your society, but basically
you will find it is not going to be an
overall acceptable way of getting around
in your society yet. But it is for me
and I would like to know. But how will
you getting around that way be of
service to the society you are in? Well,
I have a feeling that it will be of
service. All right. How get in touch
with how it is and then you will give
yourself a clearer path as to how to
create that idea.
Um, can you assist me in getting in
touch? Only if you take the first step.
Now I'll give you a clue or a hint as
you call it. All
right? In what society, in your
planetary civilization, in what culture
would such an opportunity, would such an
exhibition would such an ability not
seem as out of place? here.
here.
In what culture in your
civilization would the ability to go
from place to place instantaneously not
be so far-fetched? I
don't culture. All right. You have
Tibet, you have India, you have American
Indian culture. Which one appeals to you
the most?
American Indian. I have a feeling that I
I'm getting in touch with my Indian. All
right. Very good. Then that is your
clue. Go and talk to those and surround
yourself with those who will not think
it's so strange that you can do this
thing. Then you will create for yourself
and surround yourself with an atmosphere
in which it is more conducive.
more conductive in which you increase your
conductive in which you increase your
conductivity.
I don't know what my connections are
with you. Well, you'll find out, won't
you? Go and
Go and
talk. Are you afraid of
something? You seem hesitant rather than
excited about this idea.
It does seem like something's in the
way. I was thinking about the question.
There is no something in the way. You
are in the way.
Now, are you sure you're really excited
about doing this? Yes.
Then why the hesitancy?
Maybe it's just not your kind. Well,
maybe. Maybe.
But are you willing to find out if it is
or not? Sure.
Then why not avail yourself of sharing
information with individuals that may be
likely to support you in your cause?
Okay. Then go and talk to
them or attract them to you.
But immerse yourself in whatever aspect
of your culture will let what you want
to do be all
right. Because what you are asking to do
still goes against the grain of the
belief systems of many of the cultures
upon your planet including the one you
are living in right now. What are some
uh what is the near culture that I can
um attract to me? The American Indian
culture is very close to you. Do you not
live on what you call the American
continent? Recognize that the idea of
the culture we are speaking in that you
live in and the American Indian culture
are not remote geographically.
Does anything come to mind of what kind
of What about you?
Um, a name doesn't come to mind.
I don't believe you.
A name did come to mind, but you threw
it away.
Right now, she's showing something.
Thank you.
One will lead to another.
Where in what you'd call your
geographical United States do you
imagine that you would meet the most
receptivity to this idea in terms of
dealing with the American Indians in
that area? Where do you see yourself going if
area? Where do you see yourself going if
you have to go somewhere and talk to
them?
a place that um isn't inhabited by
buildings. Give me in your terminology a
Give me in your terminology a
geographical location.
It's fuzzy. I don't know where is fuzzy.
What state is fuzzy? All
All
right. Will you do me a favor? Will you
envision before
you a blank field of white sand or beige
if you wish?
Are you doing that? Yes. All right.
Now, are you in any way, shape, or form
familiar, or have you ever seen at all
what you call a map of your United
States? Yes. Can you now envision that
map upon the sand in front of you?
Yes. You do not have to have all the
outlines of all
the general configuration will do.
Now, northwest. Ah, northwest.
I know it's direction, but I don't know.
Do you see an area of a different color?
Yes. What color is it? It's darker here.
What color is the rest of the map?
Oh, that was the location. Yes. What
color is the idea of the rest of the
map?
Does it have a different color from the
background or is it the same? Is the
location the only difference in color?
It's part of the same color. The
location is just darker. What is the
color? Um, black. All
right. Northwest.
Can you picture that area in your
imagination right now? Yes. How does it
appear to you? A lot of trees. Um
the earth. All right. As you are
picturing this, breathe it in. Smell it.
Taste it. Feel it. Touch it. Hear it.
Walk through the woods as you are
describing them. Now describe them.
The animals and the trees and the sounds
of birds. Yes. Is it enjoyable? Yes.
How's the temperature? Very peaceful.
Um, cool and invigorating. Cool and
invigorating. Fresh air.
Fresh air.
Yes. Is there any ocean spray or are you
inland? Um, just inland. All right.
How long will it take you to get to the
ocean if you had to walk?
Um, hours, days, minutes?
It's not far. About a half hour. All
right. Allow yourself to focus on this
entire feeling in general, this entire
area in general.
Now envision yourself right now in the
middle of that forest once again. All
right.
Pick a spot within
eyeshot that is on top of a low
rock that has nothing on it. All right.
How far away is that rock?
All right.
Now look around where you are standing. standing.
Now imagine
yourself looking back from the
rock where you were standing a moment
ago.
Notice all the changes, the shift in
perspective. All right. Now, go back to
the original location and look at the
rock again. Back, forward, forward, back,
again. Back, forward, forward, back,
back, forward, forward, and back.
Increase this
range if you wish. Change the local if
you wish. But for the exercise, being in
a place that gives you empowerment
connected to the
earth and doing it always as a line of
sight idea for now. Only go where you
can see you can get to and vice
versa. Do this exercise when you are in
a relaxed state. And this will begin to
loosen up some of the preconceived
notions within you about mobility and
motion and space-time reality illusions.
Right? And then I can travel short
distances and then longer. Yes. And also
if you find the opportunity occurring in
your life, take the opportunity to go
physically to these locations.
Okay. speak with the individuals you
attract that may be of the idea of
American Indian heritage as you say that
may be willing to discuss some of this
idea with you.
All right. Okay.
Um where where were the Sony Indians in
the United States?
More in what you would call south or
Midwest. I don't know why that came to mind
I don't know why that came to mind
because that seems to be kind of that
does not mean that all of them are in
that location.
Okay. All right. And it may also be
closer to a name of an
individual than a trial.
All right.
That has assisted me a lot. Thank you
very much and of course as always enjoy.
Okay. Thank you.
There's a show in Idaho.
I was just thinking [Music]
[Music]
Monday night you helped me understanding
a couple of sightings I had earlier in
September and last night I observed
something else and I wondered if I could
share it with you and help me. You can
share it at this time. We will not
guarantee interpretation. Okay. It was
like a um giant crystal sky with a lot
of light and there was a central light
shining out of the middle of it with
rays coming down towards the earth and
um it stayed in that state for quite a
while and then all of a sudden it turned
it. This is hard to describe. All right.
You are doing just fine. Um it took the
shape of a pyramid and um
[Music] Can you see it? Can I project it to you?
Can you see it? Can I project it to you?
I have the image I require. It's hard
for me to put it in words. It was
largely a feeling too but very bright
and it seemed to signify. Let us say
simply for now, treat it as a doorway.
Treat it as a
prism through which you can refocus your
point of
view symbolically for now. All
right? There can be more
later. Simply take it as you
feel the general
feeling to be that is created within you
rather than the labeling of such at this
time. This goes for all of you. And once
again for
now to simplify
matters, my rule of
thumb, if it is not in your terms
obviously, very obviously a spacecraft,
then it isn't one. Even if it
is for there's no need to strain and
wonder when it needs to be obvious as to
what it
is label wise as you say then it will be
obvious until then go off the feeling
it wasn't I didn't have the feeling it
was a spacecraft I thought it was more a
projection of my own in a sense yes
though there is other consciousness
involved I felt that too. Um, and I am
not saying that you did. I am simply
giving the general rule of thumb. Once
again, I'm not sure I got the total
message. I have a feeling that kind of
Oh, you got the total message. It will
play itself out in whatever way your
conscious mind needs to see at whatever
rate you need to experience it.
These things come in
gestalts and they play out at whatever
rate it is necessary for them to play
out over the course of the time span you
are living. But all the information in the
living. But all the information in the
incident is there. It will unfold and
unreal as it needs
to follow. That's interesting you should
say that because it did seem to change
and unfold as
I had. unfolding
um that reminded me of a time when I was
living in New York and I had an
apartment that was very high up
overlooking the Hudson River and every
now and every time I sat down on my sofa
and I looked out this picture window uh
there was um predictably I would look
out in a distance where I wouldn't see
any buildings or anything. It was just
sky. And out a distance of about 75 ft
or so, there were these beams of light
in a uh like particles of light going
out in in a tubular fashion. Um and and
everywhere that I I I focus my attention
that particular beam would go straight
out. The only thing I can think of it
was a lot of fun. It was very calm and
you know, nothing no particular emotion
attached to it. Um, and I often wondered
what it was. It was just a very simple
light thing. I I guess I was just What
was it actually? I don't
know. Just beams of light or energy
really or particles of light or energy.
what it looks like. beams of
potentiality, beams of
intention, the cognition in a laserlike
fashion of your probable
paths, the pointing, the
indicators, your
direction, your
directions in life in the sense of you
doing the directing.
Your search light, your spotlight, your
projected beam, third eye energy, chakra
of intention energy, solar plexus, third
eye.
Why didn't you say so?
Three deep breaths. That's the thing. Okay. [Music]
at your own pace. One more time.
Those who wish
to with whatever hand you are
comfortable and your index
[Music]
finger point straight
up and repeat with
conviction. My intentions
My intentions are clear.
point straight out in front of you. The life
The life
I live I live is just It is just as
clear as clear in every way. in every
way. point up.
My thoughts My thoughts are clear are
clear on this matter on this matter.
Un conditional conditional
conditional love
will will support me support me
I I am am an aspect of an aspect of the
infinite the
infinite point straight ahead.
All All that is before me that is before
me is that is that which is behind me
which which is behind me is that is that
which is below me which is below me is
that is that which is above me which is
above me is that is that which is within
me which is within
Three more breaths.
hands folded over your heart.
I am I am an expression an expression of
infinity of infinity.
Thank you. Thank you.
More and more
synchronicity, more and more
synchronization, more and more harmony will
harmony will
abound in your
lives, in your
thoughts, in your dreams.
Sharing Bashar you Bashar review we're
doing again the
uh tools of manifestation first of all a
couple words I want to clean up
manifestation get out your question is
um manifestation primarily a
condensation process would you would you
use that term a process of concentration
not concentration mentally but
condensation materially so to speak
taking it from the essence that is and
putting it squeezing it down and giving
it archetypal form. In other words, to
some degree. Yes. Okay. In the
manifestation process, these are all
only mechanical analogies and not
necessarily directly representative of
the way it is. Yes. But only sufficing
as a representation of okay
manifestation say in this this dimension
guys. Uh the tools that I know of at
this time are desire
which can be
modified by
um one's beliefs. Dice. In other words,
I could desire to have a car right away,
but I have a belief that I have to go
through a certain process. Okay. And
then there would be the element of
expectancy and imagination.
if I don't work on the imaging of it
which is a which is a compacting and and
this is something I'm I'm missing a
little data there uh in the process of
imagining it guys where is that message
going how is that
transformation process occurring from
imagination when you have the idea or
what you call the experience of using
your imagination
You are cognizant. You are being
cognizant of the template itself. The
non-physical template itself. Yes, you
are reading the blueprint. Okay.
Therefore, you are focused on that
level. Okay. Then who is picking up that
message? How is that going from that
level? And then the you on that level is
picking up the message. and then to to
receive it down here. What's the process
involved then of the U here is
communicating with the U there which
then recommunicates with the U here and
either delivers or you know in other
words let's say I want a car and it will
either give that but it would be based
on beliefs and expectancy and certain
faith structures and things like that
right guys
anything anything else you can add to it
is it I mean is it extremely simple
process if if those are just the tools.
Yes. It's just a question of quality. It is
It's just a question of quality. It is
also hinged upon whether you actually
need that or not. Yeah.
For you may find it that it is an
opportunity sometimes when you focus on
a particular object, the manifestation
of particular object in that way that
the focusing on it will let you know
that there really actually is something
else you're more excited about.
uh me
I understand that literally but example
wise ask for what you really want guys
sometimes in other words you may find
well all right I put the whole idea into
the focusing of this particular object
let us say the car that you mentioned
and then you say well I see no
manifestation of this idea and as you
begin to examine perhaps why there is no
manifestation of this idea as you
expected to see it then you come into
understanding that in the examination of
this whole process, there's actually
something else you stumble across that
actually has more meaning for you than
the car, but you use the car to get you
in touch with what it is that has more
meaning for you. Oh, in other words, you
would get maybe mobility in other ways.
Yes, maybe. Okay. Uh maybe the car was
only a symbol and not necessarily
something you actually literally wanted
gets you to where you're going. Thanks.
Interesting. What is the difference in
your definition between an attitude and
a belief? That's that's one of the
tools. An attitude is your physiological
expression of a belief.
Okay. So if I believe that so and so
type people were bad, if that was a
belief, the attitude would be you would
have a bad attitude when I'm around
them.
Okay. Thank you very much.
uh in terms of our time, it seems it's
been quite a long time since we heard
from  And I was wondering since since
And I was wondering since since
this is such a a a an intense time of
transformation, I mean, it always has
been, but it's getting more intense. Uh
what are they doing in serious these
days? I know. I know. But it comes for us. All
I know. I know. But it comes for us. All
right. next week of your time and with
him a friend.
Thank you. I have nothing to do with it.
It's still nice. Thank you, Ash. Yes.
I've begun working with crystals only
recently and I'm I'm interested to know
if you can can guide me or help me
decide what kind of crystals I should be
specifically working with at this time.
What do you think? What do you feel?
Something in me is attracted to a black
obsidian sphere. Go for it. Oh, not yet.
It is that simple. What once again you
are most excited about, what you vibrate
to is your signal. Your imagination
always provides you with exactly the
tool you need. That's what it's what you
are most attracted to. That is what is a
representation of what will work the
best for you at that particular moment
as a tool. But recognize the power is
within you, not within the tool. Yes.
However, it will be an accurate
reflection of what aspect of your power
you are now in the mood to examine. I
see. Now, one
moment. Did you happen to recognize that
particular tool? The obsidian? Yes. The
obsidian sphere.
Uh, Orion symbology. The dark crystal
move. Ah, yes.
All right. It's too obvious.
Say no more for now. Okay. We do not
mean to be
mysterious, but there are things you
will discover. They are not
necessarily as deeply connected as some
other individuals, but there is an
aspect that is there to serve you in
this idea, in this connection. Allow
yourself to create or attract yourself
to such an object and see what it brings
up within you. We will speak of this
again. Thank you for Oh, thank you very much.
Thank you for Oh, thank you very much.
You sure? Yay.
I'm having a problem trying to You're
having a why? I'm trying to figure
something out. All right. When you say
that we're going that we went into
agreement with someone in another
lifetime or Yes.
It's not a conscious agreement.
Rarely unless you can use what is
happening in the physical reality
between you as an overall symbolic
generalized reference for what that
agreement was. then it is conscious. In
other words, no matter how you are
exploring it, whether positively or
negatively, ask yourself, what is it
that is being explored here? Then you
will have a conscious recognition in
general terms of what the agreement
was and follow me? Yes.
Does that help you somewhat? Do you wish
to explore this further? Yes. Go ahead.
Well, it's a it's an agreement that you
both made. Yes. But to to be of service
to each other, to reflect to each other
what you need to see. A different lesson
from the same.
Yes. Okay. That's all for now. Are you
having a good time?
Yeah. Yeah.
I'm thinking about All right. Well,
enjoy thinking about it. I'll do
something about it. Oh, you are doing
something. Yeah. Whatever you do, enjoy.
It is all for the purpose of knowing
more of you and more of all that
is. Have a good time. You sure? Is there
a mother crap very close by? Is that
perceived?
Let us say it is not so much the actual
physiological configuration that has
shifted but more the intention and the
focus of the energy with the thickening.
Okay. Thank you.
Let us
say there is more concentration of focus
and thus it feels closer. I see. By the
By the
way, in case any of
you are exploring the idea
of wishing to become conscious of out of
body experiences, allow yourself to utilize
experiences, allow yourself to utilize
similar technique to what we just did.
When you lie down, when you are about to
go to
sleep, while on your back, no matter
what other position you get into later,
while on your back, raise your hand and
your index
finger and give
yourself a specific destination to go
to. Then ask for whatever assistance is
Then ask for whatever assistance is
necessary knowing that you are also
going to do your part and that it will
not be done for you. But ask for the
assistance. But
have now this is not something you have
to do but in this case as a suggestion
have a specific intention. Have a
specific local a specific
idea and ask for assistance in
and ask for assistance in
remembering when you wake up. Now
whether you have a specific recollection
of the exact idea you thought you would
have, I will tell you this.
99.9% of the time you will find that
what you do recall as a so-called dream
will be much more intense and lucid.
If you give yourself a specific
direction before you go to sleep,
you will begin then to concentrate your
focus.
Do this every night and you will begin
to feel the
acceleration. More and more of your
dream reality will then begin to leak
into your physical world. One
moment. Do this for the week and we will
speak of it next week at a time in terms
of your experiences.
At this time, allow us once again to
extend to you our appreciation of the
experience of your consciousness and the
sharing that you have allowed yourselves
to be through the unconditional love
that has co-created this interaction,
this event, this reality that we share.
We thank you for allowing us to
experience the gift that you
are. Pleasant dreams.
A fond and energetic good night to you
all.