wa I how are you all the singular time
as you create time to
exist no before we begin the idea of sharing
no before we begin the idea of sharing
allow me
briefly to remind each and every one of
you one more time if you're not too
bored by the
idea of knowing that this is the time of
conviction the time of willingness the
time of committing to being who and what
you know yourselves to be the time as
you have all co-created it for each and
every one of you to
express your own idea of who and what
you are your own expression of
are your own expression of
willingness to allow yourself to know
that the purpose the basic foundational
purpose for which you chose to be
physical is to be completely who and
what you are because each and every one
of you is your own facet of all that is
now we have discussed this idea with you
many times recognize that now that we view
times recognize that now that we view
that your civilization has
begun to live within the idea of the
transformation now that you have allowed
your vibration to shift into an idea that
vibration to shift into an idea that
reflects and represents an awareness of
more of
yourself then there is
now a sense of more more
equality between what you have previously held
between what you have previously held
yourselves to be and what you are now
viewing or creating your self image to
be in the
present therefore you have given us and
many other consciousnesses that are
communicating with your civilization the
opportunity to be able to begin to
interact with you and your civilization
more frequently more openly more
naturally and in this way to not come to
you so to speak as only teachers but as
Learners as sharers as teachers Learners
combined for you are also teachers and
Learners and sharers and in this way you
can begin by this conviction by this
willingness to create very
consciously instead of un or
subconsciously the type of
reality that you desire upon your planet
without struggle without
strike without needing to strive to
achieve to become but simply by
allowing not making not forcing but
allowing your eles to fully be the
expression of the particular unique and
creative facet of all that is that each
and every one of you
individually and collectively represent
are you all following this
idea Shing yes V you hi uh I have a couple
Shing yes V you hi uh I have a couple
different things I want to discuss first
of all on my way over here tonight the
the lights on my car have almost gone
out and I'm wondering what on on another
level this really means uh as far as my
life goes and uh you know just now first
of all understand that everything in
your reality yes is an extension of your
Consciousness and can form a symbolic
representation of an idea that you are
willing to explore about yourself but
recognize in this way since since it is
an extension of your Consciousness then
your imagination should be able to
supply you readily with the idea you are
exploring simply extend yourself into
the idea of the symbol you have created
and see what it brings to you if you
cease to judge and invalidate what comes
to your imagination first without
needing to analyze it but simply feel it
and act upon it then you can know that
you are always giving yourself accurate
information to represent the ideas that
you are symbolizing and reflecting to
yourself in your physical reality now
what for you was the first idea that
came to your mind without judging
what just that I've been LAX about
taking my car to the garage oh it can be
as simple as that but in this way the
idea of being LAX about anything that
you have created then reflects the idea
that you are exploring laxness within
yourself now in this way it also may be
that you could in a positive note simply
know that you no longer need to I'll say
depend upon artificial ill um ination to
allow yourself to know that you can move
easily through what you previously
considered to be abject darkness and now
you can know that your senses can extend
themselves in ways that will always
allow you to know exactly where you are
standing exactly where you are stepping
exactly where you are walking without
the idea of
outside illumination needing to provide
something to support you that all
illumination comes from within and even
in the environment of absolute Darkness
as you would call it there is still the
ability for you to know to sense exactly
where you are at any given moment of
time as you create time to exist it can
also be a symbol of that idea what do
you think which one do you
prefer well I prefer that I get home in
one piece tonight so I prefer that my
senses will take me there without any
problem all right very good now this is
simply to illustr straight that a symbol
is what you make of it recognize that
many times you will create a symbol to
reflect something which is already in
your mind but that does not mean you
cannot allow yourself to change the
meaning of the symbol even as you
recognize it for you are an unlimited
Creator and can allow any reflection to
transform into positive effect the
moment you conceive of
it follow me
um not too all right simply
stated when you give yourself a
symbol there is no need first of all to
separate the idea of the symbol from you
and wonder wonder
wonder simply go into the center of your
being and know that you can sense what
the symbol May mean as you have already
created it conversion
allow yourself to know that even as you
perceive that a symbol
exists you can then recognize that like
any other symbol in your life it is a
reflection simply of the
opportunity to create at any moment
whatever type of reality you wish thus
you can use the symbol for whatever you
desire to use it for and your desire the
direction and indication of the type of
method that you are willing to apply to
the symbol will change the symbol into
one that reflects the positive attitude
you have decided to
create thus any symbol that you give
yourself is always going to contain the
polarity you can either use it for the
negative idea within yourself and that
will be true or for the positive idea in
yourself and that will be true because
you have ultimate choice and all choices
positive and negative are equal
therefore in whatever way you decide to
filter the symbol through you will be
the way in which it serves you so make
your choice how do you wish to look at
the symbol as you have already said in a
positive way then simply know that you
can trust the higher conscious you that
allowed you to create that idea and the
the physiological conscious you that
perceived the physiological symbol you
can trust that they are working in
tandem to give you symbols and
Messengers and messages that always
serve you and do not interrupt you
because you cannot be
interrupted also it may I've been
feeling lately that I that I'm searching
so and I'm I'm looking so for answers
and the seem the more I search and more
I come here and the more I find out the
the more confused I get about everything
all right now on one level that is very
good and very creative because the idea
you call confusion to us is not negative
it is cusion fusion with the idea of
more possibilities you are unlocking and
disorienting yourself from the reality
you have for so long allowed to be your
habitual ritual and now you are confused
because you are unlock talking and
disorienting yourself this means you are
opening up the possibility to reorient
onto something that represents more of
what you are do not let depression and
confusion be negative confusion in this
way is simply the recognition of more of
yourself and depression is simply a
meditation where you go to the center of
yourself to find the answers that you
know do not exist outside because there
is no outside and as long as you
continue to search outside you will all
always allow yourself to feel that you
are stumbling in the
dark you follow
me therefore if the lights on the
outside have gone out turn on the one
within okay
that um as we were talking last week and
you again said now about our purposes
which I had stated last week um I I'm
doing a performance and I need to have
some help with it and I brought some
cards tonight and I would just like to
put them out if that's all right with
everyone and if anyone's interested in
in participating in a a performance
which has to do with spiritual
involvement I would appreciate your help
very good for being bold enough to have
the conviction to know that you can rely
on the sources of information and
interaction that are available to you
upon your own Planet within your own
civilization very good thank you for
sharing thank
yes female oh
me yes I have a several things one of
them is last Wednesday uh I made some
attempt at at sharing what I made some
attempts I knew you would say that did
you not
share well everything you do is a
sharing I know I know all right all
right what I was willing to do and um
I felt that do you remember that yes
okay I felt that that your U your
responses were quite unsatisfactory oh
thank you what responses would you rather have
you what responses would you rather have
created for yourself yes well no that's
what I'm getting at I'll tell you in a
minute um I realized my reaction and I
thought that's an interesting reaction
why and then what I noticed what I what
I from the reaction I had I became aware
that the purpose of The Interchange was
totally different than the topic of The
Interchange nice I was Wonder do you
know are you aware of that keep going
well I'd like you to know I'd like to
know what your perception was in other
words I I created to to perceive your
answers to be
unsatisfactory because of something I
needed understand that what we are doing
here is reflecting something to you in
the moment of The Interchange is the
most accurate reflection now when you
continue to change you are going to
always then understand that you're going
to be creating new answers but when you
go searching for the U you used to be
then answers that were given to that you
are not going to be satisfactory to the
new you you are willing to be uh yeah I
don't think I don't I don't think that
was it actually the the way I perceived
it is I became a little angry because I
felt your your responses were very very
general and what I expected was some
some very specific inputs and what
difference does it make what you expect
oh I know I realized that and then when
I felt myself getting angry I thought
that's an alignment you yes so what am I
aligning to well and what I realized was
um that I had begun to to make a go out
of you thank you no thank you I don't
like it either thank you and so I I
created a situation for myself in which
I had to change my perspective yes and
it didn't change my feelings about being
here which I always think is exciting
all right but it did it it did change my
perspective about it oh thank you and so
I was wondering if if you at the time
were're aware of it or not only in the
sense that we know that one whatever it
is we are reflecting to you we trust
will always wind up being of service to
you in whatever way you care to use it
not that the specifics have to be known
to me okay but I thank you for that
anyway we will thank you for being
willing to co-create that idea I thought
it was quite interesting because I never
had such a a very immediate realization
of what was going on for me thank you
for doing that so anyway uh the other
thing that I'd like some clarification
about is you we are in the transformational
is you we are in the transformational
life going from third to Fourth now
going into fourth is that a 100%
certainty going to into Force density is
it a 100% certainty for you yes for me
then that is all you need to know plan
that is all you need to know well you
understand that you are your own
Universe I do understand that which
means you are also your own planet Earth
which means that if you are 100 %
certain that that is where you are going
then you will see and live within the
planet Earth that exists on that level
and live with all of the individuals
that also already exist on that level
okay therefore you will be surrounded by
a
population you are already there
yourself and all those other individuals
will then when they choose to understand
that they simply have to be 100% the
idea that they want to be when they
arrive in the idea of themselves as
fourth density then they will also see
the you that already exists in fourth
density oh okay is that but that's a
different concept than the concept of
the blending no with your civilization
no it's not understand everything is its
own idea and every idea is a
reality every idea is a reality unto
itself okay
therefore any blending that you are
creating within yourself that contains
within the definition of that reality
you are willing to be the idea of
blending with other civilizations will
then be a part of that overall
idea it is like a formula like a math
iCal equation all right
but but there all right so I I I I am
alone in my universe but there are lots
of other people who are doing the same
thing yes
so from what you said it's I thought
that we can go into the fourth density
but we could go in fourth density and
not necessarily uh work towards blend the
necessarily uh work towards blend the
blending of the civilizations
immediately you do not have do right but
you know but is that your choice it's
not my choice I'm asking for in general
for the planet uh no my my choice you
are in general I understand that working
along those lines yes okay but
understand our point in general doesn't
matter you will wind up in whatever
vibratory Dimension that represents the
fourth density you you are willing to be
but you have asked or suggested to us
that we talk to our governments become
our governments and so on and so forth
yes and so we are involving others so
I'm not the only one that
matters understand that you are not
involving anyone who does not vibrate
nor exist in the same
reality okay you will not find those
that do not exist in the same
reality the ones you will find will be
the ones that exist in the fourth
density idea you are willing to
be and you never involve anyone against
their agreement to be involved no but I
interact with with them in other ways
but understand you only interact with
those that are of the same
vibration so what are you worried about
I'm not worried I'm just trying to I am
am in the process of
understanding the the the various
Concepts the involvement of various
people all right
and what's happening all right but and I
will use that word this
time recognize that what you at least to
us as we perceive what you are saying
what you are doing is attempting to in a
sense understand the reality you are
by coming to terms with the outside
illusion rather than simply coming to
terms with what you know yourself to be
and then knowing that your reality will
reflect you okay I'll think about I mean I'll do
you okay I'll think about I mean I'll do
you understand what I said at some level
I do and I've understood that for a long
time and at another level I don't and I
just don't agree with you because I what
is it specifically that you do not agree
with well I I interact with people who
are obviously their density all the
time you are on the same level then or
you would not be able to interact with
okay so but is there anything isn't
there anything that I can do
to uh suggest to them or you can suggest
everything anything that does not mean
they have to take it no they they don't
but but don't I as a human being living
here on Earth have some kind of
responsibility towards towards my have a
responsibility to everyone to be
completely who you are you do not have a
responsibility for anyone not for anyone
but yeah to towards myself then
understand responsibility to everyone is
being who you are then they will know
who they are dealing
with okay wonderful wonderful you follow
me yes okay does that clarify the idea
yes you your
interaction is always only going to be a
suggestion oh I realize that well then
but I I do have I do feel I have to make
those suggestions I have well then make
them but I do well but do not expect
anyone to listen I don't either all
right then be true to yourself and make
the suggestions if you know you are
being true to yourself you will always
attract the audience the that will have
attracted you to them who want to hear
the suggestions or they would not be there
suggestions or they would not be there
no matter what
reason they want to hear the suggestions
they want to hear them or they would not
be there whether they use the suggestion
positively negatively or not at
all okay I have a personal question all
right uh is
Aquamarine the gemstone me does that
have any significance for
me now is it not in a sense obvious
since you
asked what is the
significance you tell me I don't know
I'll tell you what happened all right I
have a I have an aqu aquamarine pendant
yes that I hadn't worn in a long time
and I decided to wear yesterday and as I
put it on I felt that something was
opening up inside of me all right and
that that things were accelerated all
right is that not symbol enough is that
not significance enough but why aquamine
but why but why but why why not you tell
me I don't know perhaps you think it is
pretty well you tell other people why
why can't you tell me understand that
the idea of when we involve ourselves in
what you call specific discussions with
other individuals will reflect their of
willingness to discuss on equal
terms uhhuh now the idea which you
already know about the idea you call
Crystal and forms color gems and so
forth will obviously be that different
vibrations carry different reflections
of different ideas and you can
understand that the blue
tones will reflect to some degree the
idea in a generalized Mass conscious
sense of
spirituality well no I see I haven't
heard too much about crystals yet I know
this on on some tapes now but understand
that all you needed to do was relate to
the spiritualized feeling it was giving
you to know that that is what that color
and stone
represents in other words once again the
answer is right there in the feeling in
the experience itself rather than saying
well okay here's this experience now let
me go looking out here somewhere for the
answer as to what that all means when
the experience in and of itself is the
answer how do you feel it feels more
accelerated more spiritual more open all
right then that is the idea that you
have imparted to the vibration of the
aquamarine acceleration spiritual
acceleration you follow me yeah I I had
never felt it before and that does not
mean that you cannot know what it is
when it happens
once again it is simply a
threedimensional third density habitual
ritual to assume that just because you
say well that never happened before that
that has anything at all to do with the
fact that you can now know what it is
now that it has happened the two ideas
are separate that has never happened
before and I now know what it is in the
present are two separate ideas and one
does not control the
other what you imp what you seem to be
implying is is that that any learning we
have done is meaningless that is not
what I am implying that is what you are
inferring okay it sounds like it
understand that it is both meaningless
and completely meaningful in other words
it is simply this any symbol is as valid
as you create it to be
period okay I'm I'm talking in general
you have said that's the second time
You' talked told me what you were before
doesn't mean anything about what you are
now and I agree with that but then
Define your concept of
learning because the idea on your planet
at this time of learning is actually
unlearning well it's it's finding out
about our environment and and what works
in the environment and how we can
interact with people and all right but
understand still what has that got to do
with the idea of learning being meaning
less what we said in this way simply we
are saying every symbol that you create
is valid is your way your
methodology of learning of teaching of
sharing and in this way you are going to
learn in general the idea through your
own unique
approach that seems to be true for
learning in the fourth density but
learning in the third density seems to
be different well where are you
third or fourth both all right then you
will give yourself a half half
reality when you decide whether or not
you are in third or fourth then you will
by acting like it give yourself the
opportunity to experience what it is
like understand that many individuals on
your planet who function through their
higher Consciousness that fourth density
self have methods of so-called learning
that in no way shape or form are
acceptable to your third density reality
oh I understand that then what
difference does it make how learning is
done what we are saying is not so much
the idea that learning in it of itself
is
meaningless but because every method of
learning is Meaningful then no one
method carries more meaning than any
other method it is not that they are
meaning less it is that they are meaning
equal so basically what you're objecting
to and that's in in other things too is
when we express ourselves in terms of of
third density density thinking and thir
third density learning then you keep
yourself in third density I'm not
objecting to the fact that you may want
to do that but that is what you are
doing when you express yourself in that
way okay because you are still in this
way creating the idea of the Habit that
was formed in third density right such
as we already gave the example of this
never happened before exactly usually in
third density that means I cannot
therefore make sense of it now whereas a
fourth density being will know that that
has never happened before has nothing to
do with the present and in the present
the experience in and of itself is the
answer and you can simply go on living
knowing that every idea is fully there
and fully complete within the experience
itself and that all will be unfolded and
revealed in the physical reality in due
course of time because you will
experience everything you chose to
experience in this physical
life yeah I understand that all right
then simply keep it
simple okay thank you thank you guys
then you
bash uh I have uh sharing first in the
form of a statement then in the form of
U
question uh I realized that uh the idea
of learning to love someone is actually
the concept of discovering that you
already do and uh the question I have is when we
do and uh the question I have is when we
fall in love there's a it feels like
there's a difference guys there are
people that I I love dearly but then I
can fall in love and it seems to be a
difference in the vibration or the
excitement would you be willing to give
me a technical explanation of what the
difference is I will keep it very simple
okay that particular idea that you are
referring to as you call falling in love
is the expression of
unconditional love both for the other
individual and for
yourself okay I understand that however
I experience unconditional love with
those that I not quote falling in love
with not
really understand we are not saying it
is necessarily negative
but because of the nature of your
specific vibrational reality of third
density that is still existent upon your
planet in your
civilization you are making conditions
all the time defining all the other
individuals and your relationship to
them when you feel the idea of falling
in love with a particular individual
that is what it feels like to experience
unconditional love
and you can if you really experience and
express unconditional love with everyone
would find yourself to be completely
falling in love with
everyone unconditional love is not the
idea of placing conditions or
definitions to the extent that many
individuals do to define the
relationship between them and
them when you fall in love you are more
likely to remove all definitions and
simply function as
one that person becomes you you become
them because you remove all ideas of
separation between the two
consciousnesses even though you
recognize in the a idea of validation
that they are another individual you are
still recognizing their individuality
unconditionally and that is is what
being in love is all about okay if I may
play The Devil's Advocate for a moment
Oh by all
means uh I have people who I I love
dearly as I said who I feel a true
excitement about the way I love them yes
but it's not of a romantic or sexual
nature in any way all right truly an
excitement about it I would say that I'm
in love with
them you are in a sense yes in love
according to the definition that is
required for this particular expression
in third density right but the
understanding still is that what you are
feeling by being in love is the fourth
Density definition of unconditional love
okay I still claim that these people
that I that I feel excitement about be
about loving and in a sense feel in love with
loving and in a sense feel in love with
I mean there's there's levels of uh of
emotion related to this as I am entering
my transformation these emotions are
stronger and stronger so what I would
have felt
as unconditional love for a friend now
would have been madly in love in the
past if you understand yes okay all
relative yes what I'm saying yes true
what I'm saying though is these people
that I feel strong love for truly is
unconditional love no well there there
there's where I disagree understand this
even if there is only one condition it
is still conditional but there is no
condition you have already said that
there is what
sexual I see your
point now recognize this one moment let
me finish the
statement recognize that we recognize
the reasons for why there are different
manifestations of different and similar
gender love and interaction upon your
planet but it is all because of
conditional love that the situation
exists to begin with I see your point
however um just
because even if one does have
unconditional love for someone doesn't
mean that they have to have sex with
them no certainly you do not have sex
with everyone on your planet no so that
doesn't mean that there's conditioned on
your love for everyone on the planet or
something in a sense yes okay I'll
accept in a sense the idea is not that
it is in an overall sense so to speak a
negative thing within the society in
that way nor within the inter
relationships and the interactions but
simply by the technical definition of
the term the way your Society functions
and to some degree the way our society
functions because we are in an overall
specific sense still differentiating
between the ideas of what we prefer and
do not it makes literally
the love conditional whereas in the
nonphysical state it is completely
unconditional as long as there is a
physiological state to some degree it is
conditional that is all we are defining
it is completely unconditional when you
are completely
non-physical because then you can
interact with every other Consciousness
without regard to the idea of preference
the idea of preference does not need to
exist in the non-physical state in that
way because everything is completely
equal therefore not in a negative sense
but as long as there is physical reality
to some degree the idea of even the
physical reality being in existence
itself is the product of some conditions
within the idea of the love that makes
creation yeah because those condition
then Define the differentiation between
this reality and some other reality or
even this relationship and some other
relationship that is the type of
condition we are saying we are not
saying it is in and of itself a negative
idea okay again The Devil's Advocate um
sometimes well as we have explored
negative manifestation in the
past we would fall in love and the love
was not all that unconditional either
there'd be a lot of conditions placed
upon the love love yet the feeling of
usually after the initial moment of
unconditional love Yeah therefore simply
recognize that all we are referring to
in answering your question is that
specific moment which may or may not
stretch over a long or short period of
time in which there are truly as few
conditions as can possibly exist in the
physical reality and more reflection of
the non-physical it may only last a
second but for that second what you are
recognizing is the unconditional love of
the higher self and channeling it
through you as best as can be
interpreted in physical reality now
after that you may if you start to see
more and more and more and more
conditions still retain or recreate some
form of memory of the initial
unconditionality but it is becoming less
and less and less unconditional MH MH
because many times the purpose for the
relationship will insist upon the
discovery of the different conditions so
that you can make a differentiation as
to the purpose of that relationship but
it was the unconditional love that you
initially felt that was the purpose for
bringing you together you see many times
individuals will create a situation and
attract to themselves a relationship for
purposes that they May somewhere down
the road because they are judging not
like but they know from their higher
conscious self that they do want that
relationship because it does serve their
purpose even if the physiological ego
later on may not like it so the
unconditional love is used to initiate
the relationship because it comes from
the higher Consciousness purpose then as
you recognize the purposes of the
relationships it then generates more or
less to varying degrees that conditions
of conditionality so as to define the
purpose that the unconditional love
attracted the relationship
for that is one of the ideas of how the
homogeneousness of your higher self
translates through the prism of your
personality and differentiates into the
spectrum of conditionality which defines
physical reality and that is the reason
for why you have created it to
experience yourself in that way but is
that unconditional love that spark that
lets you know that all of these
initiations are all being activated by
the higher
Consciousness does that Define the idea
yes it does and I got to tell you that
um quote falling in love unquote and
knowingly consciously not placing any conditions
consciously not placing any conditions
upon the love or the lover or any
requirements uh giving that person
allowing that person total total freedom
in your own reality to do whatever they
choose be it positive negative or
whatever is a very wild experience oh
yeah my experience in the past but you
know you fall in love you put conditions
on the other person you put requirements
and they can't do this and you can't do
that and it degenerates but when you
just knowingly allow it to be totally
free it is fabulous then you are
resonating in physical reality in
congruency with the idea and the origin
of the purpose of the relationship that
was initiated from the higher
Consciousness you are paralleling
yourself that's right and giving
yourself the feeling and the ability to
feel and to sense the vibration of
congruency with your higher
Consciousness and physical Consciousness
MH and in addition to that what it means
is that I I consciously know the
purposes of the relationship the
purposes that was created and purposes
that we create as we go along yes it's
it's wild yes for then you are privy to
communication with your higher
Consciousness right right totally in
line with it thank you thank you thank
you
shooting yes how are you perfect how are
you I'm well
last last week at uh as I worked at at
my desk I had a sense of um I had a
sense of your voice communicating with
me um I copied down this communication
and I'd like to have a little I I'd like
to have your comments on it was was
there something going on there is always
something going on now understand that
more and more individuals in your
Society have said recently well Bashar I
know you were talking to me the other
night you are not the only one now
recognize this what you are all tapping
into is what we have always told you is
present our overall energy being sent to
you to utilize in whatever way you wish
to form whatever connections with it to
reflect to yourself that you wish to
form you are simply recognizing the
vibration because you are willing to
take advantage of it and you are
translating it for yourself in whatever
way you wish to to form a symbol you can
relate to it is not so much that I am
specifically floating down and saying
hey but it is that we are radiating as a
civilization the particular vibration
that you are channeling into that idea
that you hear speaking because when you
tap into it it will speak to you as we
would speak to you because it is of our
vibration but because you are then
connecting to it and becoming equal to
it you are creating it to speak to
yourself as we would speak to you
because you are then also of that
vibration and therefore in a sense of
our civilization for that moment and
that is why through that particular
exercise and ability that you have just
done and described that we have always
said to you that we refer to your
civilization in the way that we consider
ourselves to be your future selves
because you are like us and like the
serious civilization a part of the same
overall Triad Consciousness and you have
the ability to contain those bands of
frequency to utilize them to utilize our
band to talk to yourself and be equal to
that idea you follow me uh [Music]
as long as you are leading yourself you
will not get
[Music] lost thank you thank you yes I'd like to
lost thank you thank you yes I'd like to
explain the the concept of densities and
what we've been talking about third and
fourth what first second Fifth and six
thank you now first of all
recognize that every density level will
not be a density that excludes the ones
previously but contains the ones
previously and that is one of the
definitions the idea that you are
becoming more aware of more of yourself
now what you call fourth density that
what you are moving into will be in your
terms for all quote unquote practical
intents and purposes as you understand
physicality fourth density will be the
last density level in which you will
experience Direct the idea as you
understand now of physical reality fifth
sixth and seventh density are in your
terms basically
non-physical in this way first and
second will reflect through the
symbology of what you call first being
the idea of mineral
Consciousness second animal and plant
Consciousness the idea of the
knowingness in basic form in linear
sense in point sense and then your third
density Consciousness in volumetric
sense of the expansion of mentality and
self-awareness and then fourth density
the idea of volumetric within and in
that way the sense of knowingness that
contains all the other three and the
fifth in this way the idea of the
expansiveness within that allows you to
begin to sense yourself as not existing
within a space but actually existing as
the space and sixth density in this way
will be the inclusion of many such ideas
of spaces the idea of the true aspect of
the multi-dimensional self but still
perceiving that you are a compilation of
existing within this idea and then
seventh will be again existing as the
multi-dimensional idea in and of itself with no separation
idea in and of itself with no separation
beyond that are different magnitudes
different octaves of ideas and this is
something that our civilization is also
still exploring see so a first density is
exploring see so a first density is
mineral will the mineral is the symbol
for that idea now there have been in
your terms consciousnesses which have
existed in that density that you would
not look at and say well that is a
mineral but it is representative of the
limitation in the mental sense of that particular
in the mental sense of that particular
Consciousness as to how it sees its
Universe it is a very fixated Point idea
whereas animal is very in this way
linear idea and what you call your third
density is very
volumetric uh I also have a question
about probabilties one more thing in fact we
probabilties one more thing in fact we
think will clarify to some idea the idea
of self-awareness that first appeared in
what you call first expressed itself in
what you call third density understand
that when you have a
volumetric reality that is the first
density level that has the ability to
look back at
itself whereas a line when turning
around cannot see all the way down the
line and a point has no reference point
outside of itself to look at volumetric
is the first idea that can look back
upon itself and hence third density
being the level of Separation now fourth
density has the ability and see through
the illusion proceed uh probabilities um one
illusion proceed uh probabilities um one
time you mentioned another reality on
Earth what we perceive parallel universe
yes question about what did you explain
that or well simply there are other
existences that consider themselves to
be just as physical as you do and it is
extensions of your whole soul
Consciousness just like it projects many
lives in this Universal Time Track IT
projects many lives in other universal
time tracks that are parallel and not
perceived between the
other in the idea as it can be described
of the idea of flickering on and off
your physical universe is what your
scientists called discontinuous that is
it exists in Street on off moments you
follow me yes flickering on off on off
on off in between what you consider to
be your moments of reality which flicker
by so fast ask you do not think they are
flickering exist all the other
possibilities they take turns existing
in the same space so to speak so they're
vibrating at a different frequency yes
it is just different vibration in the
same way that you see visible light by
definition and do not see invisible
light it is vibrating at a different
frequency and you pass right through
each other and never know you coexist in
what to each other are very real
realities and the frequency you're
existing if you what what is existing on
Earth in that frequency well one will be
your future world your future beings
that are co-creating equally with
us
approximately
approximately let us say in a very fluid
sense of
interaction well can be as little as 50
years to 100 years stretching to 300
years from now we already perceive that
that Civilization from 50 years from now
to 300 years from now is exactly
expressing itself in many of the same
ways we are
now and thus we interact with them
equally encouraging one last
encouraging one last
question now understand there is no need
for the ey aidea of being encouraging in
the hopeful sense simply because that
reality exists whether you choose to be
a part of it or not certainly you can
choose to be a part of it and then you
will be in it there is no need for the
idea of encouragement except the
encouragement to take the conviction to
choose that reality if that is what you
want thank you thank you my last
question is about uh entities or or
uh uh nature Spirits uh they've been
called very all right understand that
they do more or less represent real
Consciousness but also what you are
perceiving them to be cloaked as is a
representation of what is called
archetypal Consciousness that is your
mass Consciousness your entire
civilization the one being that you all
are in a sense has a subconscious
reality just as the individuals in it do
that subconscious reality just like your
subconscious reality from the individual
can create symbolic terms that you can
relate to it through those symbolic
clothings will be what you call the
mythological beings that come out of it
you as a god are projecting a certain
symbolic idea to the individuals within
yourself by pushing through your
subconscious a representative symbol
that they can relate to oneon-one but
which is still reflective of the idea of
the godhood that it came from and hence
will always seem to be a little bit well
off kilter from what you consider to be
normal it will be more well Spirit like
Wai like not quite so substantial hither
sither yawn able to pop in pop out
represent itself in many different ways
that reflect the different ideas that
you are communicating to that portion of
the mass Consciousness for you follow me
uh yes
think R it is drawing from a
stream the stream that
represents the ability of the God that
you are to physicalize to some
extent some of the subconscious
imaginings within the God that you are
to the individual fragments within
itself there certain places of the Earth
where like Thorn for example where
that's more likely to happen than other
places in this sense it will depend upon
many things one of which will be the
nature of the Consciousness in any
particular area and understand that the
nature of the Consciousness many times
will find themselves attracted to
certain areas because the energy levels
the vortexes of energy in those areas
will reflect an ability to interact as a
free zone an open interdimensional
doorway through which they can tap into
that subconscious stream more readily
and thus it all serves to reinforce
itself from the idea of who they are
where they are and what it is they think
they are all about
out a question all the Consciousness on
this planet as one being yes as a part
of all that is is not all that is one
being of
course but understand that since it has
differentiated itself into units there
are also the ideas of groupings of units
that form whole beings within the whole
being on an infinite number of levels so
there are whole beings within my whole
beings yes and so on and so on in all
directions this is what we mean by the
fact that you are a
multidimensional Creator is the Triad Consciousness
Creator is the Triad Consciousness
between us you and Sirus also one
yes can can you channel uh to the
parallel universities that exist in in
our off period or do you yes do you
Channel with them sometimes yes you can
interact sometimes
beings from different civilizations as
they have also in your civilization from
time to time actually make passage from
one to another and are not seen any
longer on your
planet but but you yourself are
channeling to these other beings that
are parallel to us in a sense yes
okay yes um I've been struggling with
this question and
I then perhaps that will be an allowance
to finally answer it for yourself that's
true that's true I go back and forth
between allowing myself to feel very sad
oh oh oh now do not condemn yourself for
that idea for what you are doing is
allowing yourself to become the answer
for crying just like laughing is
centering because you are releasing the
idea of your
negativity crying is centering coming
from a negative point of view laughing
is centering coming from a positive
point of view both of them get you in
the center and you are now by releasing
this as you express yourself lovingly
willing to become the answer that you
are seeking so you do not have to seek
it anymore so please continue There is
no need to excuse what you are doing it
is a very loving creative act thank you
I go back and forth between allowing
myself and and go back and forth to feel
anxxiety all right without feeling love
all right in my family situation the way
I grew up was that they taught me to
feel guilty about feeling myself and
feeling myself feeling love yes and I we
get to a peaceful place all right now
you have already said that you are aware
that you learned this idea through your
family so therefore the idea of why you
are doing it basically is
conscious yes yes well if the idea of
why you are doing it is conscious why
are you assuming that there is something
else Beyond just knowing that that needs
to be done to allow you to choose
something else you see knowing that in and of
else you see knowing that in and of
itself is the ability to change it
because you are aware of what you are
doing and
why I I have I understand what you're
saying all right now how about this okay
the times that you allow yourself to
feel love how does that feel wonderful
all right now that being that being that
you is always you yes
yes the other being is also always you
yes yes all
right allow yourself to let those two
beings the one expressing the love and
the one expressing guilt which is the
true opposite of love not
hate guilt is the true opposite of
Love let those two polarized beings be
equal since you will always be both of
them you will never be able to rid
yourself of anything because there is
nowhere to rid yourself of anything too
since you will always contain both of
those aspects
then allow yourself to know that both of
those aspects exist because there is the
potential that at any given time one or
the other of them will serve a purpose
for you that is the only reason why all
of these differentiated aspects in your
personality exist because they are all
different types of Messengers that give
you different types of messages so that
from any direction you could possibly go
in there will always be a reflection
back to you of what it is you are and
what you think of yourself and where you
stand with regard to who and what you
are willing to be therefore knowing that
all of your personality traits the
loving one and the guilty one all serve
in their own good time a purpose allow
them all to be equal kinds of
Messengers do not make it that feeling
love is more
important than feeling guilt it may be
something you prefer and something you
enjoy whereas you may not prefer nor
enjoy the guilt but the love the ability
to feel love is not more important than
the ability to feel guilt since there
are times when the idea of the guilt has
served a purpose if only to get you to
realize that you prefer to feel
L which may be the only reason for why
you are creating it but you are not
taking the final step to realize that
that might be plain and simply the only
reason why you have
assumed that the guilt needs to go
on okay allow yourself to know you have
been served by yourself and now in
allowing the guilt and the love to be
equal well then when everything is equal
a choice is easy because you do not have
to reach for what you want nor Bend for
what you want nor throw away what you
don't want it is all right here and it
is all equal so it is very easy well
this is what I
prefer this I do not prefer it is all
right here here and always with me so
that should I
decide to explore
something that
requires the ability to feel guilt that
will also be right within my
grasp because as a total higher
Consciousness being the idea of
experiencing love or guilt is all the
same it is all a tool to understand
yourself through this particular reality
and to the higher Consciousness self
love guilt all right
well it is all the same now it is left
up to you as a physical personality
however to have the free will to choose
the methodology of what the higher
methodology of what the higher
Consciousness wants to explore as a
general concept therefore can you repeat that
concept therefore can you repeat that
all right it is up to you as a
physiological Consciousness to choose
the methodology by which you will explore
methodology by which you will explore
what the higher Consciousness wishes to
explore about itself in other words the
Free Will of the higher Consciousness
chooses the overall generalized ideas or
events that you will explore let us say
the idea of
separation or the idea of separation in
love so to speak
now it is up to you to choose with your
physical free will the methodologies by
which you will explore what the higher
Consciousness wants to explore so you
can explore that idea through a positive
idea you can explore it through a
negative idea both ideas will be
teaching the higher Consciousness
something for everything to the higher
Consciousness is valid and a learning
experience but you can still prefer to choose the
but you can still prefer to choose the
positive way which will then shorten the
time it takes to experience that and
allow you to get on with another
experience separation choosing
limitation and negativity creates
separation and stretches out and creates
more time so the idea of choosing the
negative is what creates the idea you
call a vicious cycle or a rut because
are constantly creating Loops of time by
choosing the method of Separation
because you do not recognize that you
are on track and so you do not allow
yourself to act like you are follow
are follow
me now will I have simplified the idea
for you to the point where you can allow
yourself to know that there are no
interruptions in your life and
everything that you experience is a
product of your choice but it is still
up to you to choose what methodology in
which you wish to experience any overall
idea how do you
feel spy very good now recognize this as
well if at any time you know you can
conceive of a
you that
knows that it prefers to always
experience the idea of the
love then know that that you is always
there and can always be the present you
or you would not be able to conceive of
it it is you if you are willing to
Simply Be that you and act like it and
know that every idea in your reality is
equal to every other idea and so it will
be easy to choose among
them thank you thank
you you could you clarify something you
said earlier about the flickering of the
Universe on and off of different
frequencies as you understand the idea
of your physical Universe you will
understand that it is composed out of
what the idea you call Energy a
homogeneous field different variations
in the vibration of this field create
what you perceive to be the space time
and physical objects that occupy it
therefore recognize that the methodology
that you have created in order to create
a multitude of universes is to exist
within a particular vibration that
interlocks in between all the other
vibrations so that you can experience
your own uniqueness without in this way
overlapping into another Universe
because earlier you said that it was a
difference in frequency now if there's a
difference in frequency there would have
to overlap at the same time you really
mean a difference in Phase same
frequency out of phase in a sense yes
although there are also differences in
frequencies which are alternate
dimensions of experience another
question about physics that we talk
about on this planet a lot you know that
we about the four basic forces in nature
on this planet in Einstein
F now you already know if you will
discover upon your planet that even your
physicists have gotten it down to
two they
recognize that they have what is
called Quantum
chromodynamics and in this way this
reflects a unification of what you call
the electromagnetic force the strong
force and the weak Force the only one
they have yet to understand is
gravity when they allow themselves to
begin to include Consciousness into the
equation they will have their unified
field and they are on the very doorstep
of understanding that they just discover
the fifth power or something the idea of
Consciousness and what we call the
template Universe was just in the paper
the other day it's kind of anational for
what you're talking very yeah they
calling it a fifth
Force they are simply beginning to
understand that what they have long
considered to be gravity is not a
force it is a reflection of the
interaction of the vibrational Matrix
taking the pattern of the template which
is non-physical when they understand
there exists a template upon which the
foundation of your physical reality is
constructed they will know how to read
the maps have question I like this plan I
maps have question I like this plan I
like my life here I very good of nuclear
war I'm just wondering whether I will be
able to live out my stay on this planet
our perception of your civilization at
this time is that you have already
chosen to not have that
idea now understand that one of the
reasons for why you are seeing in your
terms an escalation of personal violence
is because you now know it is safe to
experience all these ideas because they
will not lead to nuclear
Annihilation that is why they have
increased so that you can live them all
out so that by the time you all
consciously agree to go into fourth
density idea you will know beyond shadow
of a doubt that you have done it all
with regard to
netiv The Temper you is that related to
the uh machine or a device that Steve
Steve Myers is
building it is reflective to some
degree of what I will call the
crystallin structure of the template
since the christalin structure of the
template is to 3sided pyramids Base to
Base point up and point
down this one figure with six
faces and Five Points will be the 11
dimensioned universe and contain within it all
universe and contain within it all
aspects that your physicists are
beginning to understand about the
fundamentals of how your physical
reality is Created from non- physicality
that one symbol is the equation that
Bridges your physical Universe with the
non-physical universe
what did you explain the symbol again
two three-sided pyramids Base to Base
sharing a common equilateral
triangle therefore one Apex is up one
Apex is down there are three points
around the middle and there is a central
point from top to bottom point that
passes through the plane in the middle
Now understand that the three points
round the middle are what you may refer
to as the x y and Z ideas of your
volumetric third density reality and the
negative x negative y negative Z of the
anti- universe in that way the polarity
expressed the top Apex is positive time
the bottom Apex negative time therefore
in this one structure you have both
positive and negative time and positive
and negative space now recognize that
the nature of this structure is why your
scientist are you familiar with what is
called in your civilization the
uncertainty principle no I'm not
understand that when scientists on your
civilization discovered that they could
begin to look into what they call the
nuclear reality there were movements
that did not act in what they consider
to be natural or normal ways any longer
below a certain threshold things do not
have to act in the way that you think
they have to act to follow certain laws
that you have always thought to be very
strict one of the things they discovered
because of this random activity is that
you cannot know both the position and
the momentum of something simultaneously
for to take a measurement of something
that small is to cause a change in the
interaction and if you are measuring its
position you can get its Precision
precisely but you will not understand
its momentum because the addition of the
energy changes the momentum the addition
of the energy of the measurement if you
wish to know its momentum precisely you
can never know its position for if you
try to fixate on it you will stop the
momentum and have nothing to measure
therefore this is a result also that can
be defined by this particular equation
or this template crystallin structure
understand if you will just regard for a
moment one particular three-sided
pyramid you have x y z on the base that
represents the ID of the coordinates of
physical space yes yes you have the Apex
which which represents the time in which
all the physical coordinates are subject
to and are related to and Inseparable
from Now understand that the nature of
your dimensionality makes it such that
you can only take a measurement off of
what you consider to be any one face of
this pyramid base or three sides at any
one time if you take a measurement off
of the base well then you will include
the X Y and Z and you will have the
total measurement of the space but you
will have no measurement of the time or
momentum if you take a measurement out of any one
if you take a measurement out of any one
side you will have total time and any
two coordinates but no complete sense of
position you follow me yes therefore
this is what the result is and why you
have discovered this idea you call the
uncertainty principle you cannot in this
way allow yourself to know in the
physical Universe both space that is
position and time that is momentum
simultaneously with regard to what any
particular aspect is liable to do this
was in your terms the qualm with your
Einstein in this way in that your modern
Quantum physicists were saying that
there is no predictability on Quantum
level whereas Einstein believed that
there was now in a sense both are
correct for in this way what Einstein
sensed was the template and your
physicists have yet to discover this but
when they do they will understand that
it is only in the physical universe that
the uncertainty exists and if they
understand that this uncertainty is the
product of the shape of the template but
understand that the template is in and
of itself complete to begin with then
knowing that completeness in a
non-physical universe will let them know
that everything can be in the
non-physical Universe certain whereas in
the physical Universe only a portion of
the template at any one time is
represented and thus things can be
uncertain then you have the idea of Randomness
then you have the idea of Randomness
that exists within your physical reality
so that you can create in that way and
have free will therefore just as by
analogy the idea of your atoms have
individual Randomness which cannot be
predicted but the total mass of the
atoms have a certain predictability
chemically so your overall society as a
mass consciousness has a certain overall
sense of energy momentum that usually
does not divert or in this way is very
unlikely to divert from what could be an
overall generally sensed prediction but
the individuals within it all in their
own random way even though you cannot
predict their action goes into making
the total mass that is more predictable
you follow me yes where are these
studies being conducted where they're
getting close to this understanding of
the template oh many many of what you
call your physics
institutions Stanford yes
Stanford yes
MIT yes CCH CCH
yes
some and also in other places other than
your own
country so is this um the two pyramids
together is that just a model to help us
understand does this actually exist in
some it is a
physiological representation in
volumetric form of the equation which
defines the non-physical template
Universe should ask a question one
moment sorry do not be sorry are you
finished I just had one other question
in physical science there's the notion
of the scientific method in in which uh
you can You can predict a certain
outcome by certain laws now in the
non-physical universe is it is there
such a scientific method or is it be
totally and understand that your again
quantum physics is beginning to
understand that what they have long
defined as the classical scientific
approach does not really exist in the
empirical way that you think it does for
they have discovered that you get the
result that you design the experiment
for and nothing
else and that if you you change the
design of the experiment you get a
different result both are real the
contradiction and the Paradox is your
first indication that you contain the
totality of all that is and within the
higher self nothing is a
contradiction yes thank you I got it
thank you
you
briefly or would you rather prefer to
wait after your break yes I would then
you may all take a short break
all right I'll
say B yes how is your energy
doing it's doing great thank
you how have how have
you
allowed your
allowance to begin to create
your particular methodology of
particular methodology of
manifestation with regard
to how you are now seeing
yourself as compared to how you were
seeing yourself
before damn I think
I'm talking so slow I'm not sure what
you said um
said um
how does how does how I feel about
myself now compare to how I I saw myself
in the past spe myself uh much more
conviction stronger um eyes um uh in
what way are your symbols forming or you now
way are your symbols forming or you now
as opposed to out the um
I'm not sure or if I'm sure I'm not
aware of it you
an use my imagination very
good you see you have the ability to
fill in the
gaps I was going to say there must have
been something to do with gaps in area
yes it's true I have um more of willing
to have more of the answers for myself
all right and it is the flow The
Continuous Flow that you are now
beginning to feel that is what allows
you to create a reality in which there
are no gaps that you fall
into but simply ride smoothly over them
and draw the obvious conclusion from the
energy that you sense in the overall
picture in much the same
way as the analogy that you are now
allowing yourself to perceive the water
in the sea upon which you are sailing
whereas before to you the smoothness was
transparent and all that was revealing
itself was the fraggy Abyss filled
bottom that you thought you had to cross
treacherously up and down and up and
down now you have filled your ocean and
so can go sailing smoothly over the top
filling in all the
gaps yeah that's a nice analogy I like
thank you I like that I created that
yes thank you for your sharing thank you
the sure yes than you than
you um I don't quite have the question
formed but well it is all right make a
statement out of it
then I would like to hear some expansion
on the
of
co-creation um condition
love and conscious conception in terms
of the birth of a being birth of a baby
on this in the transition state from the
fourth to the third dimension
now what concepts are you creating
already about each of these
ideas I still feel them separate I'm
trying to integrate the pl them as
separate ideas all right now understand
that as long as you choose to be
physical you are always going to
perceive to some degree that separ ation
that does not mean you cannot get the
unbroken nness to work for you even
while you are still generating the idea
of some
separation you follow me yes do not
assume that you are going to necessarily
all of a sudden just become one big
blank and not be able to tell any
individual thing from any other
individual thing you follow me MH simply
know that as long as you choose to
experience yourself in a physical
reality you are expressing the idea of
diversification differentiation within
the homogeneous Oneness for reasons of
your own in this way however you can
utilize the idea of The Unbroken to form
a communication link that you know is
always there between the different
levels and it takes the form of
knowingness and your imagination is the
tool that is the transl ation device
through which you can hear the higher
self speak and speak to it and know that
you have been
heard therefore with regard to the idea
of Consciousness to be born upon your
planet simply know that you are in touch
with any being with whom you are forming
an agreement to act as a parent for that
being in whatever way that you have
co-created that scenario to occur and
you can be sensitive to the
communication with that being because
there is an agreement being made you
follow me now
simply recognize that with
recognize that with
allowance with recognition of your
ability to assist that being to become
used to the idea of physical reality but
through the methodology of allowance not
restricting them over much
you can allow them to very rapidly in
your terms of time within approximately
three of your years their third year of
physical life to be able to begin to
communicate to you what they remember of
the agreement that was made since they
are not so very far from
it which many times they do remember and
you in your civilization chalk up to an
overactive imagination which is
invalidated as a real
reality simply in this way knowing to
begin with that an agreement has been
made before the physical birth and
trusting that you are also making that
agreement will allow you to carry
through that sense that notion of the
agreement that will allow you to
function within a positive methodology
in terms of what it is you educate the
physiological aspect of the child with
so that there does not need any longer
to be so very much to have to
unlearn before one can allow themselves
to know they know all they need to
know now the
now the
idea of the
unconditionality in a sense is what is
being utilized to trust that that notion
is serving the agreement that you
cocreated in that way you follow me not
quite though you are
creating conditions that Define the
purpose of specific ideas or
relationships the reason for the
creation of those conditions comes from
an unconditional
love and this is what you are doing when
you carry through the notion of Simply
knowing that you and the entity being
born knows what they are doing and knows
what type of agreement they are making
and that is what will be lived
out why thank you the
methodology of how you go about that
positive or negative will still be up to
you physically
here but in this way the more you allow
yourself to trust that an agreement has
been made and is being carried out the
more you can trust that it is all right
to assume that the only methodology that
you require can be the preference of a
positive one you do not have to fear for the
one you do not have to fear for the
child
you do not have to in the negative sense
shelter the
child but simply that your
nurturing will automatically give you
the positive shelter and guidance that
is necessary for a being to become used
to the idea of physical
reality and in this way you can grow
with the idea of the child
reflecting back to you the symbol of
your own inner awareness to have brought
forth this
agreement and see it reflected back to
you from the child so that you are
positively conscious of the circle of
the agreement that you represent always
feeding each other reflecting to each
other the idea of the relationship that
you are follow me MH now will this have
are follow me MH now will this have
clarify to some degree the idea you
requested there's one more point which
has to do with the moment of conception
or even
preconception going on the idea that
nothing is more important than anything
else yes I don't have Clarity yet on
whether it's essential that on the
moment you know at the moment of
conception conscious Consciousness be
aligned like if you with your imagin ation are
like if you with your imagin ation are
creating for yourself a methodology that
tells you it would feel right to you to
perform some sort of idea of alignment
then feel free to do so knowing that
that is a part of the agreement because
it is an expression of who you are
willing to be and know that the child
that chose you chose you because you are
you so be willing to be you and you will
be fulfilling the agreement okay and in
co-creation with the father I see that
as a trinity is is depends on how many
children you
have we understand
proceed is it
important that that's part of the
alignment in my thinking not important
is the right word of course it is a part
of the alignment and it will be still no
matter what the definition of the
relationship a part of the agreement and
the being coming through
will have recognized what it is that is
being played out in the relationship
with the male female parent and will be
there for the reason of experiencing
those ideas so they can create their own
reality by using that as a reflection
for them to choose whatever they
want okay you follow me yeah there is
always an agreement and any relationship
once created goes on forever no matter
what the definition of the relationship
is it is still the relationship even if
the definition of the relationship is
that you never see that person
physically again that is still the
definition of the relationship and
obviously serves somebody's
purpose most likely the one in the
relationship that would be my first
guess thank you thank you thear
um well I don't know how
to ex well let me just start asking all
right um I'm I'm
um I'm I'm
completely intrigued and and and have
been as long as I can remember with um
quantum mechanics physics and the
unified field Theory and have spent as
long as I can
remember playing around with the
possibility of the mathematics of the
relationship ship ni okay just just
as as the Eisenberg uncertainty
principle is the
postulate that allows you to apply the
mathematics that solves for how
subatomic particles behave what's the
postulate and how would you apply the
mathematics for how the unified field
Theory would
describe physical Behavior
now to some
degree the
idea of the template we have described
or begun to
Define when you
recognize what the template is you can
recognize that physical
behavior is a product of how the
physical reality so to speak to make a
crude analogy rests upon the template
how it overlays what is
underneath what is underneath supports
what is laid over it and the idea of so
to speak physical
Behavior will be a
reflection of the
particular now bear with us the
terminology in your Society does not
exist we will make
do if you understand the IDE of the
crystalin structure you will understand that
structure you will understand that
Consciousness itself is what determines
let us say which facet will receive more
emphasis than another facet with regard
to how much of that facet so to speak
pokes up creating an impression in the
physical reality that lays on top of
it your
Consciousness is what determines
the conglomerate grouping of laws so to
conglomerate grouping of laws so to
speak that
determine the behavior of physicality in
any particular Universe because then
that universe will reflect the overall
ideas that the overall Mass
Consciousness that is becoming that
universe wishes to see reflected to
itself okay understand that this is the
okay understand that this is the
beginnings of why we say that when your
physicists begin to include
Consciousness itself into the equation
they will automatically understand how
everything is one
thing and what is it about the form the
inclusion of understanding the nature of
the template
what what is it from that how is it from
that understanding you can apply the
mathematics that would in essence
describe the super structure of how the
forces relate to one
another you can begin to understand how
the one crystallin structure we have
defined can offer let us
say geometric
analogies for every equation that you
have created in the separate tied
mathematical expression that you have
been using to Define your Universe
within that one structure you will find
every equation that you are using you
will find some way to relate it to that
one structure and you will understand
therefore how that one structure
encompasses all the diversification of
mathematical expression you have created
in your Society
it forms an
analogy and we were using the example
before to show how the uncertainty
principle apply to that structure there
are many different equations that also
apply to the same structure including
the one that has recently Arisen in your
quantum mechanics about the idea of the
so-called universe that you consider to
be your Universe being 11 dimensioned
the six facets and the Five Points
understand that there is
not within our
civilization a use of what you call
mathematics in the same way as
discret equations rather our mathematics so to
equations rather our mathematics so to
speak to use that
term is the recognition of the
relationships themselves
our mathematics is
[Music] relationship
relationship
oriented rather than let us say fragment
oriented do you follow me yes therefore
in this way and also because there is
not to a great degree mathematical
terminology within the memory bank of
the physical Channel there is in this
way no way for us to translate into your
mind mathematical terms the ideas we are
expressing we are attempting to create
analogies but in this way the analogies
are closer to our understanding of the
idea of mathematics than to your
understanding of what you call
mathematics for to us philosophy is
reality and analogy is only another term
for the dimension of imagination which
to us is very real and it is not so much
that we need the socalled symbolic
representational equations except in a
very unified sense thus to us our
equations will take the form of the
symbolic geometric we have described to
you to us that is an
equation in our mathematical terms and
that one equation as we have defined it
will to us represent all of the
differentiated linear equations that
your Society uses to express the same
ideas is it
possible with our current mathematics to
in fact Express an
equation that would relate
to is there any current mathematics now
that can in fact be used to
express um uh the unified um only in a
sense it will require as it has many
time times in your history the creation
of a new aspect of
mathematics recognize that in a
sense one of the most I'll say in your
terms oldest
Concepts but a so-called relatively new
branch of mathematics in your Society
can be used to explain in simple terms
this idea what branch it is called
a and it is simply stated the principle
of which in this
manner whether you
have one infinity or many infinities it
is all the same the idea is if you have
a
line you recognize that it is bounded by
two points yes mhm and there are an
infinitude of points in between the the
two end points yes yes and any other two
yes and if you have a plane which is
bounded by lines you have an Infinity of
Lines within the plane and within any
volume have an Infinity of planes yes
yes well the Infinities within a line
are equal to the Infinities within a
plane and equal to the Infinities within
a volume right because all infinities
are the same right this this is the type
of
so-called logic that will be applied through a new
logic that will be applied through a new
series or let us say simply a
manipulation of terminologies that will
create for you an understanding in your
mathematical terms but it will take a
slight manipulation of the mathematical
terminologies that you are using now by
definition by
by
definition if your Society
contained the mathematics to represent
the idea of Oneness you would already
have the
equation thus you must invent the
equation to
represent when you are willing to
know what the idea of the unification is
understand that everything that you
create in your physical
civilization it comes after the fact of
your knowingness and is a reflection
that you now know MH it is not the other
way around although you created to seem
that
way that is for the purpose of
experiencing your knowingness through a
limited separated physical reality a
very clever way of Simply creating a
mirror so that you always know that you
know even though it seems that to know
you have to not know
first thus when you know the idea of the
one field and include yourself within the
field and include yourself within the
equation Consciousness then that
Consciousness which knows itself as the
one field will automatically give birth
to the equation that represents that no
this um do you I don't know where this
question is coming from do you get here
by
traveling do you mean when I use what
you call my spacecraft or do you mean in
terms of the channeling the channeling
this is simply an
identification of mentalities to form
what you would perceive to be a third
idea that you can communicate
within it does not have the idea of
exactly regard for what you call time
and space it is in your terms outside of
that so to speak and therefore is not a
method that requires
traveling which is the same as our
spacecraft um okay right but the
question that that it
formulated uh was is it is it tra
traveling quote traveling I I don't know
another word to use exactly is it is it
as
though you're moving
inside a grav gravity wave inside um Bo
I don't know how to say what I'm
thinking it is more the idea
of
beingness than what you would experience
as traveling per se mhm it is more a
recognition that traveling
within outer space is traveling
within mhm because everything is a
projection of your Consciousness
therefore it is more of a going within
and allowing the idea of the universe to
come to
you rather than having to go anywhere
right if you were to understand outside
of gravity or
yes if you were to understand the the
idea of how you um quote move unquote
your spacecraft would he understand
perhaps we view the idea of motion so to
speak through space in this way we do
not consider that an object occupies
space we consider location to be a
property of the object mhm therefore if
you can create the idea of
isolating that object say space craft
craft from one particular idea
location remove the original idea and
insert a new idea then when you
reintroduce it into the physical reality
that carries with it the idea of
location in space it will of definition
by necessity cease to exist at location
a and take up residence automatically at
location B no matter how far apart is
there an energy
relationship yes there is an energy
relationship what is it I mean how how
if if there's an energy relationship it
must be measurable how do you measure it
and and what what what scale is
it the terminologies of our technology
and yours will now allow me to choose words
yours will now allow me to choose words
that may or may not be sensible
okay when we allow ourselves to so to
speak measure the idea of this energy
measure the idea of this energy
relationship as the physical object
relates to the physical reality it is
moving around
in it
is let me say it is connected directly
to the idea that we call our form of
what you would call
navigation in this
way the relationship is defined
Mind by the
amount or let us
say pressure of focus
MH
the measurement of the distance which
any particular Consciousness that is
piloting itself feels it
contains will Define the energy
relationship as to how far the ship
jumps do you require external
amplification of the energy that of the
conscious energy that you have in order
to do that navigation there is more a
synchronization there is to some degree
amplification of what you would call
light energy to achieve the effect but
in this
way it is only allowing the space
craft to channel what already exists in
whatever quantities it requires it and
so in a very real sense is not even so
much the idea of an amplification as it
is a step down you keep talking about
channeling an amplification I find those
very nebulous and frustrating Concepts I
know I can speak for a few others that
we're capable of could you try to give
us a more technical explanation even if
we you don't think we'll understand it
give us a chance really all right
channeling and
the other concept um I was just giving
an example I exactly how it is that you
detach your ship from another location
and move it here I want do you mean
technically you require propulsion you
say you conceive of a place you want to
be
you well that's right he says all right
I know I want to know what it is
technical as you want to we'll
understand you give us a chance to see
all right no
right no
the idea is that everything in the
physical universe is made of light the light the
craft
Focus this
light and form a relationship a
synchronization with an idea for which
the craft has been designed that allows
there to be the passage of this light
through the
amplification structure that we call a
flash Matrix this will be composed after
Matrix this will be composed after
passing through the idea of the
collection Crystal which is more or less a
Crystal which is more or less a
magnesium
carbon Matrix which is formed out of the
idea of what you call cold
of what you call cold
fusion this amplification passes into
the flash Matrix which contains the idea
of gold and extracts from the idea you
call the gold a certain other kind of
energy that you have not yet discovered
within this metal upon your planet this
energy is what is called an etheric
identification format and in this way it allows there
format and in this way it allows there
to be a translation of the light into
the type of energy required for the
systems the metallurgical systems to be
able to absorb in the Magnesium what you
call copper Matrix there will be the
creation of a spinning motion within the
primary Fusion Rod or disc depending
upon the model you are using and in this
way this spinning motion will exemplify
The Vortex energy that represents the
active principle in light and will be
taking advantage of certain motions that
are observable in what you call electron
spin therefore it will radiate this
energy into a field around
itself which the fibers that are
embedded in the hole will be able to
pick up and begin to channel through
themselves much in the same way that you
understand light is so to speak Channel
through what you call a fiber optic and
in this way we'll create another type of
identification this identification field
this etheric idea this astral idea will
actually be a plugging into the
be a plugging into the
material that you have previously
considered to be and
disregarded from your equations what you
previously called The
called The
Ether in this way this etheric
energy will then create or I'll say
reinforce the idea of the physical ship but the
the idea of the physical ship but the
physical ship will now shift its
properties to the etheric ship concept
by allowing the phase if you will of its
physical molecules to be in a
sense seceded by the etheric concept of
molecules and in this way to become a
blended state in what we call a quasi
plar reality when existing in this quasi
planar reality this quasi energy matter
State then the ship is so to speak for
all intents and purposes unlocked from
any particular solid fixed reality
now the concept of the ship itself is an
amplification so to speak of our
Consciousness and what you would refer
to as a so-called computer which in and
of itself is so to speak self-aware and
is only a symbolic symbolic
embodiment of our own higher self will
utilize its now ability over the etheric
craft which now has dominion over the
physical idea of the craft and it will
call to itself its recognition of the
all that is that it is and in this way
this means simply that it is now finding
itself directly perceiving what your
scientists have called the
interconnectedness on a Quantum level it
will recognize the holographic nature of
the universe that is the potential for
any object to exist exists equal at
every point in the universe it will
understand the holographic nature of
itself and will simply recognize its
potential to exist anywhere with regard
to the idea of the locational Matrix the
XYZ factor that we described before plus
the time factor of any particular
vibration that we wish to identify with
it will then simply be a matter of
synchronizing with that vibrational
signature that represents that
particular reality that it perceives and
then allowing there to be a reversal of
the process so that it reintroduces
itself back to physiological form and
then the craft simply finds itself
reflecting the signature vibration of
whatever location and physical Universe
it identified with while unlocked from
any particular physical Universe then it
will seem to have as you say hyper
jumped from one place to another without
from one place to another without
actually having traveled the intervening
space you see to us what your spacecraft
are doing is so to speak sliding around
on the surface of space thank you very
much for
sure then
you you said before that we have many
hundreds to many thousands of lifetimes
and I was just wondering if all of these
lifetimes are to the Earth yes you have many more
are to the Earth yes you have many more
that are
not so so when people well several
people have said to me that that they
recognized me as being an old
soul so I don't know how they the idea
of old soul is not really so much the
idea of exactly how many lives per se
but what idea of yourself you have
allowed the Liv to represent present in
this particular
life it is more a reflection of attitude
than numerical
count it's like I'm learning more now
perhaps you are willing to be more aware
of more now okay okay the second thing
is um last year I was going to another
Channel and I was talking about going on
a trip to Europe and the channel and the
gues at that time said that I would be
meeting my soulmate and so I got all
excited and had a lot of expectations
about it and I went to Greece where
supposedly I was supposed to beat this
person and I met a few people and I kept
going oh this is him this is sh and then
I don't know nothing happened I didn't
feel like I ever all right we will
simply say this briefly about the idea
of
soulmates understand again that you
experienced the reality you are equal to
therefore many individuals in your
civilization will say well if only I
could find my soulmate everything would
be
wonderful what they don't realize is
that knowing everything is already
wonderful puts you on the level that the
soulmate exists because a soulmate is a
reflection of your
completeness not of your need for the
relationship in order to Feel Complete
okay so so in my expecting something
then I you were removing and separating
yourself below the vibrational level
that represents the idea of existing
with someone to reflect your
completeness to you okay well they so so
I came back and I talked to them again
and they said that I indeed did meet
this person and I'm not sure who it was
I was when you allow
yourself to be your own soulmate
first you will then recognize
the characteristics in someone else when
you see them if you are not equal to
that idea you may meet them a thousand
times and never recognize it because you
are not seeing a reflection that is
equal to that idea okay and the next
question was if would I have the
opportunity in this lifetime to meet
that individual again that is an obvious
question the idea simply is
this you are re responsible for
everything in your life you call Destiny
and dates with Destiny are always on
time by
definition therefore if that is a part
of the idea that you have chosen to show
yourself there is no way you will not
experience it because you will
experience everything you chose to
experience in this physical life how you
choose to experience it will be up to
you and you can say that if you have
socalled met this
individual that that is the Fulfillment
of that experience but if you choose not
to recognize yourself as already
complete on that level then you may not
have the positive side of that
experience even though you will have met
it will still have served the purpose
the purpose to be to show you that you
were separating yourself from the idea
of your own completeness and that is one
of the things that a soulmate does it
shows you what you are so so can you
define that terminology specifically
soulmate is that someone who is the same
as you in a sense it can even be a part
of the Same Soul it is simply someone
who is willing to reflect to you your
completeness while you are ref willing
to reflect to them their
completeness okay and in a sense in a
sense though we understand the way in
which you mean the term because everyone
actually always is equal and reflecting
any idea you have co-created a
relationship for then everyone is really
your soulmate at any given
moment because everyone is always
reflecting perfectly what it is you are
exploring about yourself and they are
all souls and you are all
M it was also suggested that perhaps the
reason that I didn't recognize the word
person because now this is going to sound funny
because now this is going to sound funny
but this is how it was put that I was
wearing red and they were wearing blue
but they were they were referring to the
Rays that we had incarnated in a sense
it was a statement of the idea simply
that you are not vibrating on the same
frequency mhm and and so this is why
I've been trying to to you have been
what I have been I have been
researching the idea of race and I I
would I would really like to know
more about it and specifically then go
ahead and continue your research
Whatever Gets you there okay I just I
just don't understand this book very
well well understand that you do not
have
to understand that with any tool you
attract to yourself you will always
understand exactly what you need to and
let yourself go on to something else
you guys four years ago our time of
being presented himself to me and said
that he would very much like me to be
his mother and at that time I told him I
was not able to agree because I had just
had another child and that to if he
wished he could hang around and come
back when he was ready and I was ready
in November of this year I became
pregnant and I was very aware that it
was he that turned 6 weeks later I had a
miscarriage and I'm understanding much about it and
and I'm understanding much about it and
there's also much I don't yet understand
and I guess my question really involved
his return and will that happen for me
it
may but understand this that may be all
a physical reality that that being was
requesting of you that's what I thought
and that is why it was all right to have
said yes before because the result would
have been the
same I understand thank you you thank
you there is in your terms a few more of
your minutes remaining
sharing yes a month ago uh you were
talking about some amount of energy
behind an earthquake in the yes yeah I
didn't hear any news of that actually
occurring but there was like
2.9 um earthquake in Santa Monica or
something I'm not sure of my data you
have dispersed and
diversified that energy quite nicely and
in this way you have already passed
through what is called the seismic
window for that particular occurrence
that particular one okay good second
question um it's understood that the
Mayans did not use Wheels did they use
levitation there were examples of that
although you will find that their
children had wheeled
toys well uh our are
understand this I will relate to you what is
this I will relate to you what is
generally considered to be a legend but
it carries with it some of the
understanding of the mentality of the
culture you call American
Indian the wheels were used as
toys and relegated to that idea alone
for in their Legend the idea of the
wheel is as such they understood the
nature of the cyclic action and knew
enough about the idea of the limitation
in physical reality to
know that for what they wished their
physical reality to be the wheel would
be something that once it started
rolling could not be stopped and this
was borne out to them in very graphic
terms with the arrival of what they call
Western culture for you see in their terminology
culture for you see in their terminology
and in their
mythology it is that wheel that has
allowed you to completely cover what
they consider to be so natural in order
that you can ride upon
it say that again last the idea of the
use of the wheel has in their
terminology destroyed the land okay and
that is why they relegated the use to
toys and wish to allow nature to remain
wheel
less okay they built a very large
structure like seven acres I I forget
yes there are some that cover 15 okay
and they had apparently the apparency to
our scientists is that they moved these
large blocks of stone without the wheel
yes is that correct how did they move
them some were in the earlier periods
that you call the levitation idea but
also there is much in the way if we may
use the terminology of the ingenious use
of Leverage in ways that your
civilization simply has not gotten
around to thinking about because they
have no need to they had a need to
discover principles of Leverage that
simply take advantage of some very
simple ideas that may seem like magic
but are
not okay there's one theory that some of
these Stones uh were um
pour there
is a few sources one of them being a
plant that has the ability to in your
terms dissolve granite and in this way
much of what you recall as the formation
of those walls were in fact poured into
place and then simply allowed to
solidify this the same plant that s's
Crystal there can be to some degree that
effect though we find there are
different species of this idea in that
Central and top South America region
M thank you oh thank
you all right you then
you have a question about the exens of
the dinosaurs there's a lot of credit
getting going to the meteor SL into the
ocean what really did happen in this way
that will carry the greatest percentage
of
accuracy recognize that you do in fact
have have a dark star orbiting your
solar system and it is responsible for
the bringing an attraction of those
ideas that you call meteorites from time
to time into your inner system but also
there were different ideas
electromagnetic fluctuation within the gravitic field
fluctuation within the gravitic field
the electromagnetic field also
caused very quick ice
ages and very drastic altering of the
electromagnetic sustaining life force
there were some
extinctions wherein the an e e
simply suddenly seemed to be paralyzed
and dropped where they stood because of
the electromagnetic shift it short
circuited the life force in that way
however also understand that what you
call your dinosaurs are still very much
with you in terms of their evolution for
they have become what you call the birds
one branch of
them another question of evolution in
physiology one qu this something I've
always wondered about and never had an
answer to Is Why does the right brain
control the left side of the body and
the left brain the right side why is
there this decus of fibers it is an
physiological exemplification of the
idea of polarity which is one of the
defining mechanisms of physical reality
and always will cause you to have to go
through the center of yourself to cause
an interaction to take place okay
another question may you give me some
advice I'm I'm involved in research with
the AIDS virus and what would be the
best line of attack with this thing now
we have already
suggested and we know that other of our
own sources and Associates that we have
come in contact with that are also
channeling through many of your beings
upon your planet at this time
also will suggest that you
explore the chemical nature of what you
call various berries Cherry blue and
black and also what you call the pits
for chemical extraction that can be of
assistance with regard to that
particular
idea you're saying that to to to kill
this virus the answer lies in the Cherry
black it will be the physiological
representation of the idea of having
discovered the idea of the Cure within
yourselves Now understand that the basic
reason for why this
disease exists in your Society to begin
with is always going to be like anything
physical a product of a reflection of a
psychological idea how you see yourself
and in this case specifically because
you have been for so long in your
Society unwilling to blend the male and
female energies within yourselves you
have created the idea of
diversifications physiologically within
your Society of the transference of
roles from one side to another and in
this way by creating them to be
ostracized from yourself yet creating
another step of trying to get rid of a
portion of yourself in this way you have
reinforced the idea of creating a
representative disease which allows you now to have
disease which allows you now to have
have to force yourself to include these
individuals as interrelating in your
Society without the separations without
the barriers for in this way the idea is
that enforced density you drop all the
barriers so that new ideas of yourself
can come in to allow you to change and
therefore symbolically with the
representation of this disease you will
find that it represents the idea of the
dropping of the barriers by the loss of
immunity but there's a specific
eological agent that causes it it's not
yes but understand that any specific
physiological agent will always simply
be created by you to reflect the psychic
reasons for why the disease is created
to begin with what about the the young
child who just receives a blood
transfusion and gets the contaminated
blood I mean there's no disease in that
child the blood yes there is understand
that a being chooses its reality with
full consciousness of what it wishes to
explore and it knows full well that it
is coming into a situation where it may
experience that type because it may want
to be of service by providing itself as
a vehicle that those that are
researching the causes and cures can
utilize understand that there is in that
term with the non-physical being a
complete and utter
selflessness with regard to being of
assistance in that way and many
individuals that give themselves
diseases do so to be of service so that
other individuals can come to terms with
the ideas for why those diseases are
created to begin with okay now the
physiological agent we have already
discussed that the idea of researching
the chemical analysis of the Cherry blue
and blackberry will have something to do
with forming a symbol to so to speak
combat the other symbol that creates the
disease but nothing will ever change
until you change the idea of yourself of
your society and allow yourselves to
blend the male and feale energies within
each and every female and
male you will find not that it is right
or wrong but when your Society accepts
its own maleness and
femaleness then individuals that are
reincarnated now from this point forward
into your society when they choose to
either be physically male or female will
not need to express the tool that you
call homosexuality for they will have chosen
homosexuality for they will have chosen
consciously what idea of the polarity
they wish to be because now it is all
right for both males and females to
allow their male female and female male
energy to be completely
equal see you keep talked about this
that social transformation has to occur
in order to cure the disease if you take
a dis disease like small poox it was a
scientific but that is only a
symbol understand what we said is that
when you know certain aspects about
yourself you are able then to create a
symbolic representation that seems to be
the Cure understand this every
individual ual gives themsel the disease
and cures
themsel recognize that nothing you
physiologically administer in and of
itself does anything it is only a symbol
for what belief system they are willing
to abide by and someone who does not
contain the belief system that they can
be cured by your most advanced medicine
will not be you go and ask your doctors
how many people die when they should not
have and how many people cure themselves
when they should be dead then why is it
that if you take a group and you give
them placebos you get only 30% response
because that is the ratio of the idea of
the percentage of the belief system in
your entire Society stud is controlled
by giving it a similar population group
of the drug with 100% we will repeat the
idea once again you get the results you
design the experiment for so what you
are calling a control is a very specific
attitude and it is designed to give a certain
and it is designed to give a certain
result that reflects the level to which
those individuals conducting the
experiment and interacting in the
experiment are willing to extend their
belief system you telling me a little
bit more about the cherries about the
berries because you know it's real
nebulous again and I want I mean this is
a real Health concern and if you know
tell us what simply once again
understand this idea we are not here to
run your lives nor are we here to be an
all giving answer machine we are here to
assist and reflect to you what you are
willing to do in your Society it is your
world now we are not in this
way also because once again of the
physiological channels knowledge and
terminology equipped to discuss the idea
of chemical equations in your language
but simply if you you will for yourself
explore the chemical constructs that you
will find in those three
substances you will find that there is a
correlation between that and an extract
that can be synthesized that will have
some effect on the agent that causes the
disease in a physiological sense but
only when the individuals who are
conducting the research are about to
allow themselves to understand the con
connections that are going on within
their own beings and when your entire
society that is involved in the creation
of that disease is on the verge of
allowing itself to understand the
reasons within its own Consciousness for
why this has been created only then will
the extracts and the chemical analysis
and everything else make sense and it
will reveal itself the moment you reveal
to yourself the reasons for why this
idea exists and many times these ideas
exist to force you to look at yourself
for the answer outside of what you
previously have considered to be the
only way to find it in the physical
reality it is not the only
way can you tell me a little bit about
God Ian is there God is all that is God
is its own being and it is the
recognition of itself as the compilation
of all of you and holographically it is
the recognition that each and every one
of you contain the totality of the whole
so that you are also all that is is the
understanding of God on your planet any
greater than it is on this planet or is
it pretty it is different it is simply
that God is all that is whereas we find
on your planet many people even when
they say well God is all powerful
somehow God is still outside themselves
or they are still outside god well God
as the Creator I mean you can't create
yourself or you say you can't you are
the Creator we are the Creator all of
you and every being in creation is also
the Creator understand that if the
Creator is all powerful then what you
can conceive as the meest concept is for
the Creator reality real reality
therefore knowing that you cannot
conceive of
non-existence then recognize that
anything your imagination can come up
with on some level of creation is
real that you can conceive of the idea
that the one can contain many and that
each of the many can contain the one in
and of itself says that that is the
nature of the Creator because the
Creator is powerful enough to allow all
of its parts to also be the
whole in the same way you have a
mythological definition in one of your
Eastern cultures that is called indra's
net it is a net of many pearls all
spherical and the idea behind it it is
that it is holographic in nature in the
sense that every Pearl in the net
because it is 360° mirror reflects all
the other pearls and thus can be said to
contain the information and the
actuality of all the other pearls and it
is the same with every individual being
every individual being in creation is
all the different ways that all that is
has of looking at
itself and therefore you are all that is
and you are a fragment at the same time
both paradoxes exist simultaneously within
paradoxes exist simultaneously within
all that is because all that is is
exactly that all that is and that means
anything you can imagine where do Jesus
into that
picture in the way that that being represented represented
a
materialization in your plane of
existence that was a reflection of one
aspect of your total
Consciousness and it was reflecting to
that total
Consciousness that the capability of the
total is inherent in each part and that
if you simply be like him you will
recognize that that being did not want
you to follow him he was expressing that
you could be like him and the only thing
he was doing was reflecting his
awareness of his connection to himself
as all that is in this
in this
way you can find that the idea that you
call your so-called Second Coming will
not be an
individual it will be the recognition by
each and every one of you of your own
Christ Consciousness your recognition of
Consciousness your recognition of
yourself as all that is that is your
second coming and that will be what is
responsible for the creation of heaven
on
Earth but that's to negate the C the
Catholic notion of Jesus as the Son of
God different are all children of all
that is yeah but the TR there's a
distinction made in the Catholic
religion are you negating that it says
that Jesus I am saying that there is an
interpretation that is valid for the way
those people look at that idea however
that interpretation is only an interpretation
interpretation is only an interpretation
let me only one religion that's right or
or all of the religions correct there is
no such thing as right or wrong the idea
is that any religion is like anything
else a tool and is valid for the
individuals that have created it and
partake in it because it shows them what
they need to see in themselves in that
particular way to understand themselves
as all that is recognize also that the
idea of fourth density will be the
recognition that that there is not only
one way there is not only one path if
there was only one path there would only
be one
person each and every one of you is a
path unique equal but
unique equal but
unique and thus you can say that out of
the approximately 5
billion people that exist upon the
surface of your planet there are 5
billion religions 5 billion economic
theories 5 billion countries 5 billion
ideas 5 billion
universes complete unto themselves that
share the common agreement that they
will interact within what seems to be a
generally common idea but which contains
infinite diversity
and it is only by the granting of
validity to all of the infinite
diversity that you allow yourself to
support the unity of all that is because
all that is is infinite
diversity for no other reason than
simply because it can
be for existence existed before there
was the idea of purpose and that which
has existed before purpose does not need
a purpose to keep on existing in the way
it always
has are you an evolutionist or a
creationist both for understand again that anything
both for understand again that anything
you experience as a dichotomy as a
polarity has its source in one
point the center of the two concepts
that seem in your physical Universe to
be contradictory still both Concepts
come from you and are Blended in your
higher Consciousness thus both are tools that
Consciousness thus both are tools that
validly represent certain ideas about
how realities are created and you will
find that in your
civilization it is both that have
interacted there is the idea to some
degree of the physiological Evolution
but there is also the idea that you
exist eternally and always have and that
there is the idea of the co- blending of
a physiologically evolved vehicle with
an already existent
Consciousness the fallacy in a sense
which causes the negative
confusion is the
supposition that physiological Evolution
itself is responsible for what you
recognize as consciousness
it is consciousness which is responsible
for physiological
Evolution briefly yes um I'm aware of a
color that seems to be a mixture of many
different Metals but has no name I'm
wondering if that if the color that I'm
perceiving is related to the Magnesium
the isotope that you were talking about
of the Magnesium can you somewhat Define
the color yes it's a mixture of copper
gold silver uh it is orachalcum pure
Crystal what you are defining is an
Atlantean metal okay the other element
is mercury all
right it seems like an opener it is an
amalgam that was created to resonate to
the vibration of the higher ideals
all right we will take this opportunity
to once again thank you for the sharing
of all the infinite viewpoints that you
represent of your civilization for to us
this is an unconditionally loving gift
and it allows our civilization to
recognize that much more of all the
different ways that all that is has of
expressing itself and so to us allows
our view of all that is to be that much
more more rich in
Awareness we will thank you for your
gift we extend to your unconditionally
loving energy for whatever you wish to
make use of it and in this way we will
remind you that your civilization and
ours are the sharing that continues
forever we bid you exciting dream lives
and we will also bid you a fond good night for