We will begin this interaction this
evening time with the idea that each and
every one of you as you are continuing
with the idea of your own transformation
of your lives in your own way according
to your own methodologies according to
your own perspectives according to what
in your terms makes sense to you. the
ideas and the avenues to pursue, so to
speak, pursue with regard to your own
understanding of more and more of
yourself, your own spiritual growth,
your own cognition, of your own
connection to much more of yourself. In
this way, simply recognize that as you
endeavor to create these scenarios in
your lives that represent the ideas you
desire to be, you are surrounding
yourselves of course with many ideas of
symbological meaning, symbological
notation, importance to you,
validity, meaning. In this way, simply
recognize that many of the ideas you are
exploring, because of the world you have
created for yourselves, because of the
world you are changing from. Many of you
will still find that you may relate to
the change in the symbols that you are
used to using from the world you are
changing from. Not so much the symbols
that you will use in the world you are
changing to. But in this way, you can
recognize that your symbols are taking
on different meanings. You do not have
to apply all of the meanings that used
to be attached to the symbols you used
to use. Even though they may seem to be
the same symbol, they do not necessarily
though they may be the same external
symbols necessarily carry anymore the
same internal meaning. Many of the
ideas, therefore, that you may come up
against, so to speak, that may make you
feel as if you are getting nowhere when
you see the reenactment of the same
symbols over and over and over again, is
simply because you are putting a certain
meaning according to those symbols, the
way you have always thought of them, and
not allowing yourself to begin to
redefine that those symbols can now be
representative of a totally new way of
perceiving your reality. It is simply
that you think that one symbol can only
stand for one thing when in fact a
symbol can have a multitude of meanings
according to how you now think of
yourself. Therefore, do not allow
yourselves in this way to necessarily
feel that just because you may be
allowing yourself to feel that you are
repeating ideas, going through cycles
over and over again of repetition, that
it is actually a cycle of repetition. It
is simply an opportunity for you to
recognize that as you change, as you
grow, as you evolve, so to speak, you
may give yourself the opportunity to
view an idea from many different
perspectives, many different points of
view. Now, in that way, the only thing
that makes it seem as if you are not
getting anywhere is continuing to judge
that those differing what are actually
different points of view are all the
same points of view over and over again
simply because the symbol itself does
not necessarily change that much. But it
is up to you to recognize that the
symbol is only a shell and in and of
itself carries no built-in intrinsic
meaning. It is you that give all the
meaning to the symbol. This is your
opportunity to recognize how malleable
your symbols are and how you can fill
the shell of a symbol with a totally
different substance, a totally different
meaning than it formerly contained. to
allow yourself to recognize it is not so
much that the idea of your physiological
world has to change that radically in
order for an internal change to be very
very different in this way. So this can
assist you and allow you to recognize
that you do not have to seek the massive
change that you desire in your
externalized symbol, but simply in how
it is you now define the ideas that will
for a while remain a part of your
physical reality. As long as you have
decided to be physical, you will see
very very abrupt physiological changes
going on in your world. But during this
time of transformation, recognize that
more often than not, most of the changes
will be internalized first. Not so much
that you need to look for an
externalized symbol as a proof that
things are changing within you. But in
this way do recognize you will get
externalized changes as soon as you are
willing to redefine whatever the
externalized symbols are that are
appearing in your life and not succumb
so to speak to the belief that you are
only repeating ideas that you do not
want to live anymore is your opportunity
to recognize that a shell is only a
shell only an illusion and it takes its
form it takes its substance from what
you are willing to define the experience
as that filling That shell with a new
definition, with a new substance is what
will allow the
formerly thought of, formerly held,
formerly defined shell to be able to
change. But it changes from the inside
out, not from the outside in. You follow
me? shooting
the uh I was noticing I was driving down
an alley and part of me was aware that
every little so often uh it was a new
scene. It wasn't just a continuous
motion uh but broken like a stroke of
uh but broken like a stroke of
discontinuity. Hey okay and every scene
was like a snap another inch another
inch was moving along. What is the is
there an actual timing of the physical
universe? What is it like a millionth of
a second or some number like that? Can
it be equated that way? In a sense it
can be but in this way you will find it
will fluctuate to some degree depending
upon your perspective and how it is you
are creating your particular point of
view of what is going on. For recognize
that the more you live in the moment the
less time you create in that sense.
Therefore the less fluctuations that you
have in that way. It can be measured in
the millionth and what you call the
billionths of seconds in that way. Even
infinite speeds can be measured in that
sense because you understand that the
idea of all the flickers that you
experience as you're on time in this
particular reality in between those
moments exists the flickers of every
other parallel reality that exists.
You follow me? Yeah. In this way,
therefore recognize it is not so much
that it can be measured in precise
increments, but it is in that way rather
infinite in speed. though there is a
pulsation to it.
Okay. Um if one if one were to
accelerate the reception could one blow
it as make it appear as though it's one
frame at a time couldn't be you can if
that serves the purpose. A although
recognized once again the idea of living
in the moment will be that you will not
create as much time and so you will
perceive that things are moving quite
rapidly. Another variation of the idea
that you have already expressed upon
your planet that time flies when you are
having fun. Understand it is not that
time is accelerating. You are not
creating as much of it when you live in
the moment in the now in the present.
Yeah. Well, does that mean what do you
mean by in the present? Does that mean
including um
I thought that just in terms of many
times what does the moment mean? What do
you mean by many times allowing yourself
to simply recognize that every single
moment of time you experience is its own
as you have just been sharing its own
moment, its own reality. just as valid,
just as insightful, just as
experiential, just as much of a learning
experience as any other moment. Then you
will not strive to
achieve future moments because you will
know that any other moment you will ever
experience is not going to be better
than the one you are experiencing now,
just different.
In this way, many times you will find
that because of the way you have thought
of time and space that the phenomena you
have described, the apparent slowing
down or freezing of a moment can occur
when you are in fact completely absorbed
in that moment. It will seem to be one
eternal moment which is what it is.
Yeah. Was there what could you define as
a state where an individual could by
will transport himself from one space or
one time to another? Is that a is there
any type of mastership or or something
where that is said to be an ability or
in a sense but it's simply all it takes
is the idea of the cognization of the
frequency of any other idea that
represents another universe. The
automatic cognition of that frequency
will place you in that universe.
So, what is it that makes someone What's
the difference between those that can do
it and those that can't?
Agreement.
Timing. You have a reason for being
where you are and staying
there. When it serves you to be that
flexible, you will be. simply recognize
that if it is something that excites
you, keep yourself open to the
possibility that it could occur at any
moment. Yes. I've heard categories of of
levels of being as Christ was like an A3
and then or an A15. Is that have any
meaning to you in terms of a not to us?
Yeah, it may to the individual doing the
labeling. Yeah. But it is only labeling.
It is only a perspective to allow the
individual to in this way have created a
reference point for themselves that they
require for their own understanding of
their perspective of their lives. But it
has no meaning in and of itself other
than what the individual gives it.
do recognize
that in a
sense from within the so-called
hierarchy there is no
hierarchy. Only from the idea of
something that considers itself to be
separate from the rest of all that is is
the creation of levels and hierarchy a
part of that reality.
You've mentioned that individual is the
reality they are creating.
Um there there I've had an experience
and I I've talked to you about this
before of being not only in the
experience but being outside as a remote
viewpoint as well. Hey you can create
that illusion. Okay. But uh in other
words viewing myself isn't that in a
sense the higher self is can be in a
sense in a sense it is still part of the
overall creation no matter how many
perspectives define it it is still one
overall point of view well um I've I've
oriented my I guess comparisons or such
by how how many actual uh steps outside.
I can be in and also outside. All right.
Then that labeling has meaning for you
and that is your unique way of
understanding the reality that you are.
For you it is valid. All right. I I part
of me has a fear of getting totally
committed to an idea for I to the
exclusion of other experiences. So I Why
would you exclude any experience that is
necessary for you to be the idea you
chose to be?
You are simply not understanding your
own terminology.
In this sense, you are by definition not
able to exclude an idea that needs to be
there to support the idea you
are. You cannot in that sense lose track
of anything that has to do with being
there as a necessary support mechanism
to be the idea you are. Whatever it is
you are experiencing, that is what you
need to be experiencing. Whatever you
are not experiencing, you do not need
it. If you need it, you will experience
it. Is it considered in
your at your point of view or your your
level uh wiser to have a a remote point
of view being inside? All points of view
are equal. All right. But that doesn't
answer the question. Yes, it does. We do
not consider any particular point of
view any wiser than any
other. It is what it is because that is
what you have created yourself to be.
Therefore, the point of view you have is
the only perfect point of view for you
at that time. All right. But I'm talking
multiplicity having being a source and
being a not source. I think you are
missing the point. Okay. The idea of
being multiple is one idea, one point of
view that may contain many fragment
definitions, but in an overall sense, it
is still one point of view. The point of
view of experiencing multiplicity is one
point of view.
Okay. Thank you. Sure.
Thank you. Sure.
In your opening, you talked about
changing externalized symbols that
change as your perception changes. Can
you give me some examples of that
related to my life? In this way, once
again, you may always use the
foundational understanding that no
situation has built-in meaning.
Everything is fundamentally neutral
until you supply the meaning. Thus, the
meaning you supply to a situation is the
effect you get out of it.
You follow me? I follow that part.
Therefore, again, the analogy that we
have used many times in this sense the
idea of attempting to be on time to
catch a vehicle to go somewhere and in
your terms, you miss the vehicle. Now,
the neutrality of the situation is that
the vehicle is moving to its next
destination and you are simply not on
it. That is all there is to it. That is
the only thing that defines the
situation in that way. Now whatever
meaning you decide to give to it as a
symbol for you negative and or positive
may determine in that way what the
experience is that you have as an
outcome. If you determine that it was a
negative symbol in that way then you
perhaps will blind yourself to
opportunities that were there for you in
a positive way. Perhaps the idea as we
have said that if you decide it is a
negative event, you will be blinded by
your judgment and your frustration and
your rage and go stomping off to
complain to somebody about it. Perhaps
having missed the idea that a friend of
yours you have not seen in 10 years has
just stepped off of that vehicle. And if
you had given it a positive idea,
perhaps you would have seen them and
perhaps that friend could have met you
with exactly what you needed. The idea
that you were going to travel 200 m for
in the first place, you did not have to
travel any longer because the idea of
your friend stepping off of that train
or whatever vehicle has given you the
idea, if you were willing to simply
understand that the vehicle has left for
a good reason and in your terms will
serve some purpose for you, then you
will utilize the symbol in a positive
way and not the negative way you may
have formerly decided to imbue it with.
You follow me? Yes. Will that have been
of assistance to you? Thank you. Thank
you. Um that reminds me um when uh we met
Um that reminds me um when uh we met
with you Terry and her mother and I and
um you gave the analogy of missing a
train and um you could judge it as
negative or whatever you might be a friend um
or whatever you might be a friend um
because you missed it. And I wanted you
to know that we had um that excerpt on
our answering machine and it was just
funny and same because it elicited um
very definite responses. Some people
knew it was you. Some people had no idea
who it was. Some people thought it was
an actor. Some people thought it was Dan
Aar. I mean, they had no idea who who it
was. But it was great because I learned
a lot about the individuals because of
their responses. Thank you for your
creativity. And um
hey, I read an article recently of a
so-called communication that was
received jointly by a Russian and
American radio receivers for the radio
authorization. And the message that had
been interpreted according to them was
something along the lines of version. We
are in peril. We are in time 159.061. I
forget the exact number. We are
in 12. We are in fourth galaxy
attempting to get the 12th galaxy. There
has been an explosion. Please help out.
Um could you explain like I don't know
the lyric of this but could you explain
how something like this could happen
where they would be trapped in time to
progress in this way do recognize that
many civilizations are still utilizing
no matter how quote unquote advanced you
may think they are ideas that involve
the idea of limitation the utilization
of the materiality of the universe. In
this way, like many incidents, there can
be within an individual a need to
experience a so-called accident. In that
way, the methodology may simply be that
the field that let us say isolates a
craft from any particular universe in
that way may undergo a type of
fluctuation that will allow them to
exist in a quasiplanar reality, so to
speak, halfway in and halfway out of any
solidification. You follow me? In this case,
You follow me? In this case,
however, what you are referring to does
not specifically refer to such an
incident. This is
This is
something that stems more from your own
civilization.
Yes and no.
Let us say it is a
conglomerate idea between individuals upon your planet to planet to
explore
semiconsciously mostly
subconsciously
desires. reading patterns into energies
that represent ideas they wish to share.
I see
but that in and of themselves do not
necessarily represent an event in what
you would call real time. Right. Right.
Okay. Uh another thing I'd like to bring
up is
the the what you call the anti-gravity
the what you call the anti-gravity
device.
I'm interested in filming that. I don't
know how much I'd be able to capture
with it, but can you give me any
pointers on what um where I could stand or sort
on what um where I could stand or sort
of thing I might might be able to
capture on video. It seems that whatever
is going to happen is going to be over
very quickly. In this way, at least 10
of your feet distance, right?
That is all. Okay.
Hey, um I just wanted to say that on
Saturday um my next door neighbor
uh drew me needed to borrow some stamps
and then quickly drew me into a
conversation to ask me questions about
um changes in her life and her job was
probably going to be ending. So I had
the opportunity to share with her a lot
of the information that I have gleaned
out of these. Thank you. This is why we
discussed this very event last night of
your time. Yeah. And uh just wanted to
say that it was it was really an
extremely pleasant opportunity to have
the the chance to feed that knowledge
that I have picked up back out to her
and to thank you for your We thank each
and every one of you for being such
lovely opportunities
sharing. Hey, can you reflect the uh the
legend Merlin energy and what the
connection? Not at this time.
There are other ideas that must become
cohesive first from other
individuals, other levels of
consciousness and other discoveries
within certain individuals upon your
world before we are in a place to share
that stream of
consciousness within our interactions
with you.
Good. Thank you. Do you have an idea of
when that might be appropriate?
More during what you would call
the 11th, the 12th, and the first month.
Also, someone asking for a while.
Hey, and what to call next? What about
the people?
These are some of the connections that
must continue. There will be an increase
in that energy during that last of what
you call the three-month period to go
through the gate of the transformation
into your new
year. There will be much attached to the
understanding of
nature and what might have been once
referred to as druidic
manifestations. For sure. Hey,
I have two questions. All right. One
question is I have a personal conflict.
Conflict. Conflict. Why? Well, an
opportunity. Yes, it is an opportunity.
All right. No conflict then. The
opportunity is to understand a decision
making process. Decision making process.
And at the same time respecting someone
else's needs. All right. If you are
functioning within the idea of
integrity, if you know that everything
is
synchronicity, if you act like
everything you interact with, there is a
reason for interacting with it, then you
will allow yourself to simply know that
any so-called decision that needs to be
made will be obvious. You do not require
a process nor a conflict. You will
simply understand that whatever presents
itself to you as an opportunity to act
upon what excites you the most within
your integrity, take it. That is what it
is there
for. You are not responsible for anyone
else. You are responsible to them by
functioning with your integrity and
being the fullest person you know
yourself to be by doing what you know to
be true for you while knowing you are as
powerful as you need to be to have
anything you desire without having to
hurt anyone else to get it right
right
a while back in looking at biblical
stories as an opportunity to learn from
I had looked at the story of Adam Eve,
hey, as as the biting of the apple as Eve has
as as the biting of the apple as Eve has
been said to do, as as humans biding
on sexuality and reproduction and
keeping them tied to the material plane,
to some degree, it is analogous to one
of those ideas. Very perceptive.
I have um my discovery I'm trying to
make is trying the discovery I'm I'm in
the process of making for
myself is
as a woman I have a little confusion
about if it's appropriate to have
children or if it's appropriate yeah
appropriate because it's appropriate
because our planet these days in some
ways it's very overwhelming planet the
planet on which I'm living who
belong to no one
but it is
yours. Each and every one of you in a
sense while you are together on one
planet live on your own planet
independently and respectfully. What is the planet to
and respectfully. What is the planet to
you? What are you choosing to buy into
in terms of other beliefs? Or can you
simply allow the planet you live on to
be representative of what you know to be
true for you?
Do you follow me? I miss you. All right,
I'll come back.
Your planet is not overpop populated.
You simply have not utilized the room
that you
have. You follow me? Yes. Your planet is
undergoing many
transformations. Whether you decide that
they are going to be positive or
negative depends upon what you wish to
make of a fundamentally neutral
observation or
situation. So what kind of a world do
you live on? What kind of a world will
you if you decide to have children bring
children into? It will be the world you
decide to live and make an agreement
with them to bear them into, not a world
you are at the mercy of. Because then
you are only believing in victimhood and
not believing in your own
self-empowerment to experience the world
you desire and you
prefer. No matter what anyone else is
living, you will experience what you
know to be true for
you. Unless you choose to buy into
someone else's belief about what the
world is supposed to
be. You follow me? Yes. But I don't know
if you're following me. Proceed.
So my confusion about having children is
is the opportunities I see before me,
right? In devoting my energy to being a
healer and
and spending my time learning that role
versus learning the role. Are you a
healer or not? Yes. All right, then.
Expanding my skills. All right.
And versus spending the time raising a
child. And I Why are you separating the
two? I've obviously chosen to separate. All
I've obviously chosen to separate. All
right. Do you think that the idea of a
child at this time would not allow you
to be the idea of a healer?
All right, then simply recognize this.
Why would you have one if it didn't fit
the idea you are being? How would you
even be able to have one if it didn't
fit the idea you were being? You would
not make such an agreement. No spirit
would make such an agreement with you.
Therefore, you would not have one if it
did not fit the idea you are being.
You follow me? Yeah. So what decision
needs to be made? If you are an idea and
the supporting of that idea does not
contain the notion of needing a child,
you will not have one. If you do have
one, then that in and of itself is a
sign that it can occur and still allow
you to be a
healer. And perhaps it even is part of
the idea of being a
healer. You follow me? Yes. So relax.
Your agreements in this
agreements in this
way will only result in the physical
manifestation of the reality that
supports you in the idea you have chosen
to be in this
life. Nothing will ever go against the
grain. The universe does not do
pointless and extraneous
things. You follow me? Yes. Only you
have the ability to think that it does
and create the illusion that it is so.
But it is only an illusion. It is only a
lack of willingness to understand that
everything that occurs in your reality
is a part of the path you chose to be
and cannot by definition be an
interruption in
it. Nothing can be where it doesn't
belong. If something is there, it is an
If something is there, it is an
indication that there are beliefs that
have invited it to be there. Therefore,
it belongs according to the belief that
you have.
Thank you very much. Thank you. Sure.
U there's a something happening here in
the state of California and also through
Mexico Florida like that there
Florida like that there
is inordinate amount of immigrants from
the south from uh Central America from
Europe from Asia and the area that are
crossing the border into California. It
is not inordinate according to the idea
of the blendings and the removal of
borders that you are creating in your
transformation. Well, I said inordinate
because there is quite a bit of talk
about and in a sense it is blending but
in a sense it is also creating
separation because there's a lot of
antagonism between the it is not
creating separation.
Your chosen judgments are creating
separation. The people in California are
creating separation with the people that
are coming in. All right. And could you
comment on that? It is an opportunity to
choose not to create
separation. What more is there to say?
It is up to you to decide how you will
interpret the blending. How do you get
to the
antagonist to get them to realize
again? You are not responsible for
anyone else. be the idea you know is
true for you. And if you allow yourself
to become active in those interplays,
then perhaps some of you will rub off on
some of them.
Oh yes, you do. So
So
what I mostly Oh, really? That is your
decision. Okay. Thank you. It is a
matter of not talking about something
you want to change but changing yourself
and interacting as that idea
idea
participating. If you find something to
be exciting to get involved with, get
involved. If you are just going to talk
about it, then do what it is that truly
excites you and don't worry about it.
Someone else is excited to be involved
in it. if not you.
Thank you.
Y my little
sister on second
birthday everything that why did that
happen? That is all she required of
physical light. Many times a so-called soul in
light. Many times a so-called soul in
this way will have ideas about what it
wishes to experience in any physical
light. Some of these experiences simply
do not require much time. That is all
there is to it. Therefore, that
individual put a timing limit. All that
was necessary. When certain ideas had
already been experienced, it finished
the balance. It finished the momentum
from the last life. That is all that
individual needed to round out their
experience and to evolve in the way they
wish to evolve as a
soul. You follow me?
Now our perception is that that
individual is or will be soon incarnate
again because they have completed their
cycle before this incarnation. In that
way this incarnation will be for the
primary purpose of service.
Can you tell me if he's incarnate
already? Unclear.
As you come back for more service to be
of service of service
in the
transformation will be recognized so to
speak as a soul of light, soul of
peace, soul of
service. In this way, do recognize that
the choice of the methodology of the
physical death, what you call
drowning, in that sense, is a quote
unquote relatively peaceful way to exit
the body. The feeling is as if you are going
body. The feeling is as if you are going
to
sleep. You follow me? The being will now
awaken into light and
love and choose the reincarnation to be
of service to bring that light and love
to your world.
There may be an opportunity for that
individual to interact with many other
individuals through the symbology of the
unconscious, the subconscious and all
the things that represent the idea that
is symbolized by water and the fears
that may be buried within it for many
individuals. That is
all. Thank you. For
sure. Yes.
I saw a tape on Luis Desperto and on
that tape he was describing
uh a couple who were attending his
clinic and the wife um was having a
great deal of anxiety and trouble in her
life and he attributed to the fact that
she had psychically
uh opened herself up and a individual
who had died had not wanted to come to
terms with the fact that he was dead and
had attached himself to her psychically
and was creating all these problems for
her. Yes. An agreement they made
together. Yeah. Um and he chose to
um remedy the situation by talking to
the individual right um who had passed
away. Yeah. Wouldn't the woman not be
open to that same sort of thing again by
not by her not not necessarily if they
had agreed in that way to form that kind
of a coalition for the purpose of
allowing that skill to be resurrected in
your society. In this way also to
understand that there are many
opportunities still left still remaining
in the physical life of that person to
allow themselves to balance out their
own understanding of their own
self-empowerment and come to terms with
their own expressions in life. Simply in
this way what was being done was the
idea the ancient so to speak idea of
what you now refer to as an exorcist.
For in this way you will find that the
original purpose is as as we have said a
spirit psychologist who allows the
spirit to know they have died and they
can go on. What is the spirit
experiencing soality world individual so-called
create an experience that they think is
simply representative of the life they
have always had. Although the majority
of them will find some quote unquote
confusion in the reality they are
experiencing things. Certain things will
not make sense. If there's a conscious
awareness at that point, the spirit
consciously aware that they created
probable individual Not necessarily. No.
What would be the what purpose would be
served by creating problems? Again, you
are calling it a problem, but it is not
a problem. It is an opportunity for
certain things to be realized in your
world. Again, they have made an
agreement to do
so. They are connected in that way. That
woman and that spirit. Okay. Let me
rephrase the question. Why did what
would be of what purpose why she would
choose to extreme negativity? Oh, simply
buying into the belief systems that your
society has taught her about her
experiences if those belief systems did
not exist in your society. And in that
way, then there would have been more
opportunity for that individual to know
that from the very beginning of the
interaction, she was perfectly fine and
not quote unquote crazy. Yeah. You
follow me? Yes. That is all an
opportunity to understand the
limitations that can occur when you
impose a rigidized structure upon your
belief systems. From your perspective,
he he was talking about in the uh in his
ability to to
make the peace of mind that either
possible he was connected with the
actual consciousness of the individual
or that he was possibly connecting to a
greater bank of knowledge that possibly
those individuals themselves were
tapping into. In a sense, it is both.
For in this way you will find that light
vibrations will cluster into a mass
non-physical consciousness and thus in a
sense form their own dimension of
experience from which this individual is
drawing and at the same time carry with
it all of the different signature quote
unquote vibrations that go into making
up that dimension. So it can be
differentiated in that way. It is like
saying you are drawing from the pool
that does contain the flavors of all the
different individuals that make it up. Thank you.
Thank you.
On the idea of the agreement that the
thanks spirit made, is that is that the
same idea as someone's in the hospital
and they are there for whatever reason
during an operation or something they're
very open and a soul dies in that same
hospital and then connects to that
person. Is that an agreement that they
made? Everything is. So it's not like
there is nothing that occurs by
accident. Why don't we treat it then like an
Why don't we treat it then like an
agreement instead of like something so
negative? You tell me.
Well, this is the first I've thought
about the agreement as being made that
way cuz most people think of it as some
kind of a discarnate gloming on to
another person to hurt them. That is the
way you have conceived of all the ideas
in your society. The idea of victimhood.
It is your opportunity to recognize that
you can answer your own question by
living the kind of life that will allow
an opportunity for individuals to
recognize that it can be viewed another
way. So the spirit can really be talked
to and then allowed to go on life. Yeah,
it's
um a couple things. First of all, with
regard to um creating your own reality
and being excited about something, um I
want to ask you um if I am I am very
excited about channeling, but if I come
into this life with an agreement that
I'm going to be at a a certain stage in
my evolvement when I commence
channeling, um many of these ideas have the ability
um many of these ideas have the ability
in this transformational life to
fluctuate wildly.
allowing in this way it is up to you to
determine the timing based upon your
willingness to simply allow it to occur.
Uhhuh. So if I don't perceive that a
process is necessary, a process is not
necessary. Correct. And then
paradoxically whatever process is
necessary will be there. Right.
Okay. Um the other thing is um I
previously say in the past that in the
transition from third to fourth density
many of us will find that um we do not
feel like we have to eat as I see
um I've basically found that I could go
through a day without eating and not
feel any weakness or anything and during
the past couple of months if I forget to
have a meal or something all sudden I
feel very weak and it has more of an
effect on me than I ever did in the past
and I'm thinking well maybe I'm just
transing backwards. Do you find that you
create a weakness when you forget?
When you realize you have forgotten? No,
no, no, no. I feel weak and then I think
all right. Maybe if I eat something and
I eat something and I feel fine. All
right. Then you're simply paying
attention to your body consciousness.
Follow your timing. You will acclimate.
Do not chastise yourself for having
missed your timing. The weakness is your
signal that now is the timing. Right. I
just found it strange because that's
never happened to me before. Not this
past. Um, and the other thing I want to
say is that I love you and I regard you
and your society as a wonderful gift.
And we you Thank you.
I wonder if you could tell me anything
about my mother's mother who died cancer
when I was very young. You could tell me
if she reincarnated. Not yet.
Do you have any information? Are you
thinking of having a child?
Yes. When?
All right. Say hello to her.
For that opportunity is open to you.
I have done
nothing. No, you have reflected it to
yourself. For you were the one that made
the conscious connection to inquire in
this synchronistic
timing. Thereby that is an indication
that you have already recognized a
connection and an agreement in the
formation between you and she.
He knows she will incarnate
that is not
decided. Our perception at this time is
that the energy is likely likely to be
female but that is not decided. Thank you.
Thank you.
Can you recommend an approach to giving
up self judgment?
Yes. Don't do it. How about
How about
beginning by not judging that you have
self judgment?
There you go. Okay. Now, in what way has
your judgment served you?
Well, it certainly has uh made itself
known to me. For what purpose?
to uh well it's given me a an increased
awareness of my inner self.
Ah then why are you judging it? The
second you recognize it has served you
in a positive way. You do not contain
self judgment anymore. It is gone.
Thank you. It is your doing.
It is that simple. It is that simple.
May I also remind you that it is that
simple.
Thank you for allowing it to be so
simple. Thank you, Bashar. Speaking of
Thank you, Bashar. Speaking of
grandmothers, I had a best friend that
was my grandmother when she died. I
never It's like the the day she died was
repeated for 8 years and just I could
think about it and go into tears. She
was like best friend. Why are you saying
was that is why you are going into
tears? Why not
still why not is okay on a physical
level I can't talk to that the part of
me that disturbed
so physical communication is the only
form of communication in the galaxy in
the universe in creation well uh okay
I'm not I'm not clear if there is a
communication there it's not substantial
enough in my why does it have to be
substantial in the terms you think only
represent substantiality why not simply allow the
substantiality why not simply allow the
feeling that you have for that
individual to be the communication
between you. Can I have that again?
Allow the feeling that you have for that
individual and the imagined feeling that
you have from that individual to be the
communication that is going on between
you. Yeah. Well, yeah, I can acknowledge
that. That wasn't enough for the longest
time. That wasn't How about now?
Okay. You don't have to settle for it.
You don't have to settle for it.
Give me a moment. All right.
Time. Do you hear your
laughter? That is communication to every
level, every
dimension. Hear hers.
Send your love and know it is received.
Let yourself know you are receiving her
love. You know, it's interesting because
that uh rift in physical illusion is
what has has drawn me into all sorts of
metaphysical uh things. Many individuals will do that
uh things. Many individuals will do that
to lure you to more of yourself. They
will form an agreement with you. They
will die first. You will go searching
for a connection to them that lures you
to more and more expansion of your own
awareness of yourself. That is why you
may be agreement that way.
Okay. One one question is a byproduct.
Sometimes when people talk about eerie
things like that. Eerie. Well, I call it
I get goosebumps. What call it eerie?
Some people call it spooky.
What? What are goosebumps? Is it like an
electrical reaction or what's the deal
there? In a sense, it is a slightly judgmental
In a sense, it is a slightly judgmental
reaction to you tapping into the live
wire of your own core experience and
core connection to all other levels of
existence and
consciousness. It is an adrenaline
surge, an excitement surge, an
electromagnetic surge that lets you know
you are in fact in touch with all levels
of consciousness that you desire to be.
In other words, because of what you have
created your society to be, it is the
shock of the surprise of getting what
you asked for.
Yes. Thank you. Thank you.
Um I found myself
uh in a period where found yourself very
impatient uh ready to make a move but
almost almost uh hesitant to. I see. Is there a
almost uh hesitant to. I see. Is there a
time where I will know that it's Yes,
right now. Because you are willing to discover
now. Because you are willing to discover
and discuss this idea, the time is
always now. In this way,
recognize you will not experience
impatience when you do not create a need
for patience. If you are living in the now
patience. If you are living in the now
moment and enjoying every moment for
what it is, you will not create the
impatience based upon your need for
patience because you think you have to
wait for another moment to come along
that will be better than the one you're
experiencing now.
You follow me? Yeah. Live now. That's
how enjoy every moment that you are.
That is how to be where you want to
go. One more time. That is how to beh.
Thank you. Thank you, Mr. Bashar. When
you say live in the now, I get the
feeling, my personal interpretation of
that, oh [\h__\h] I got to take what's
coming down the pipe. That means you
already assume that what is coming is
going to be negative.
Therefore you are creating a negative
effect. All right. Suppose well there's
I got a lot of I have very little
negativity but there is that conceptual
um expectation that live in the now.
You're not saying create the now. What
do you mean the same thing or what the
what you Okay. You are the now. All
right. I can understand. Oh. Thank you.
Thank you.
you venue venue.
Okay. Um given the fact that all the
answers are really inside of us to to
the degree that I am at one with the
idea of that is the degree that I can
pose any questions and go inside and
it is also again not necessarily needing
that interim step one more time. Not so
much that the answers are in you but
that you are the answers themselves. you
are the situation itself. When you
simply know you are the situation, you
are at the vibratory level of the
situation. Therefore, because you are
the situation, you understand
immediately everything that has to do
with the situation because you are his.
So when that woman asks you about her um
mother's mother, her grandma's mother's
and you become that situation. Yes. Then
you understand everything there is to
understand and need to know about it.
And um what is not there you don't need.
Uhhuh. Um somehow I thought you you tapped into
Um somehow I thought you you tapped into
the vibrations. Well yes in a sense but
again that's a
separation because you are assuming that
the vibrations are something that you
are not already that you have to tap
into something you are not already
being. Uhhuh. And you become the answer
to the question by u by um you simply
are the state of existence that is the
definition of the situation you are
being. So any
information that you need you become.
You know what you need to know when you
need to know it immediately without
thinking. You simply sense it. You know
it. You are it. You function from your
intuition. Okay. So to heighten that
knowingness or to to heighten my
sensitivity. Um again I don't want to this whole bit
Um again I don't want to this whole bit
of a a process process is coming up
between last night. Now
that's it. That's it.
It is that simple. It is that simple.
And that individual over there will
remind you once again that it is that
simple. That's nice. Thank you, guys. For sure.
That's nice. Thank you, guys. For sure.
Two weeks ago, I was in Washington DC
and I met three people. A person by the
name of Peg, Jean, and Liz. And all
three of us came to work for a common
purpose. At what point in our lives did
we decide and make an agreement to do
that? Both before and at the moment.
Okay. But when before
Now, in a sense, this is only going to
be a convenient
labelization with one
individual seven lifetimes ago, with
another five, and with another three.
Did you hang names on those? No. Why?
Because it doesn't matter.
75 three times ago my lifetime
a shared lifetime we made an agreement
to be in Washington DC to work on a
campaign of some sort not with the
degree of specificity you are
saying in whatever energy terms that
understanding was felt and so it was
continued and you picked up more and
more individuals along the way to
represent the conglomerate you would
need to interact with in this lifetime.
This being the transformational life.
Well, what prompt did the poor end up in
Washington DC at that time? Is that not
the idea of what you call the hub of
your government?
Well, that's true. In this way, it
doesn't correlate to the hub of the
government. Oh yes, it does. Not on a
conscious level. That's right. your
energy, your
presence. The fact that you as a
conglomerate mass consciousness crystal
radiating at the frequency that you
radiated at in that area made a
difference and had an effect on the
surrounding individuals.
You are part of an
interaction more within what you call
three of your ears. It will become more
obvious to
you as to the idea of how the
interactions of seemingly
innocuous situations can have a profound buildup
situations can have a profound buildup
of effect.
At what you call a later date, you will
find yourself drawn
back into similar situations.
This is all we can
share. Also allow us to remind
you that what we have
said in a sense is mostly symbolic.
Not that there is not literalness to
it, but we have said what we have
said as we perceive that what we have
shared with you is what needs to be
shared with you to spur the energies
within you in certain ways that you
desire to be spurred.
Cryptic though it may
seem cryptic is the way it needs to be
right now to assist you according to our
perception of the energy that you are
dealing
with. The very
notion of your term cryptic may even
play a
part in time to come. All right.
All right.
Is that all you want to share? It is all
we are allowed at this time. Thank you.
Thank you. For sure. One moment.
Would you name the three names? Okay. [Music]
What is the signature vibration of your
last name?
There is an opportunity for more
individuals to come into play in this
interaction. You have made agreements
with more than just
those. You will discover them in times
to come and perhaps in different cities
in your
country. One of these individuals can be
in the area you call either your Arizona
or New
Mexico. One in the city you call
Seattle. Others may be in what you call
other countries, but bit by bit you will
come together more and more and more.
The more of you that are present, the
more cognition you will have together as
to the reasons for why you have agreed
to share what you are sharing. Enjoy. In a
In a
sense, it is a meeting of the
board of the particular type of reality
you have agreed to be
together. You will regroup and regroup
and regroup when and where you need to
with all the members that you need to.
It will become more clearly evident the
lines and directions of
energy that will make themselves obvious
to you, that will excite you all
together, will be clearly representative
of the ideas you have chosen to explore. Once
explore. Once
again, we bid you excitement and
joy at all you will discover about
yourselves. Thank you. Thank you,
Thank you. Thank you,
guys. Um, back to the slowing down time
or speeding up time when being in
present time. Thanks. I don't quite
understand that. Maybe I'm missing the
definition. Do you not say that time
flies when you are having fun? Yeah. Are
you not having fun when you are enjoying
what you are doing at the moment without
a care of what is coming tomorrow? Mhm.
Then living in the moment is what that
means. Everything that occurs in your
life, enjoy it to the fullest. So does
that is that speeding up of time? It is
creating less of it.
Separation creates more time.
Integration creates less because you
think time is an absolute. You
experience the creation of less time as
a so-called illusion of acceleration or
speeding up. But it is only because you
are removing frames that it seems to be
sped up. Do you follow the analogy?
Are you sure?
Kind of. You have the idea you call
film. Yes. Right. Okay. If you maintain
all the frames within the film that need
to be there to give you a sense of
regular motion. Regular motion is what
you perceive upon your screen. If you
remove some of the frames, the film
seems to be sped up. But actually, you
are taking
away. You follow me? You are not
creating as much of it in order to speed
it up.
One of the ideas as you have already
said upon your own planet, it is a very
literal interpretation. It is your
invention to keep everything from
happening all at
once so that you can experience yourself
as a limited being.
Spacetime is one of the definitions of
physical reality because it is one of
the dimensions in which you can
experience the idea of separation,
forgetting. You follow me? Sure. That is
what it is.
You are a simultaneous event. You exist
everywhere and every when to give
yourself the limited viewpoint of having
a single track, you create the notion of
time, which is simply the focusing on a
particular vibratory
frequency of all that you
are looking through one
aperture at a
time. Thank you. Yeah.
Is there any way that you can
um kind of expand the gap between what
you just said, being able to focus
through that one aperture and be on
third density and at the same time be
totally aware of every when and
where. You will be as aware of as many
when as you need to be to also maintain
your agreed upon function in this
reality. However, the answer is still live now.
However, the answer is still live now.
Because when you live in the moment, you
are at the crux point, the crossroad
point, the connection point to all other
realities you are. Thus, living in the
moment is still the way to connect up to
all the other
ones. You follow
me? Living in the now, living in the
present allows you to know that you are
in contact with all other time frames.
all other frames of consciousness, all
other frames of
dimension. Only when you do not live in
the now, do you impose a wall and a
barrier that creates what you call the
illusion of past, the illusion of
future, the illusion of alternate
realities, parallel realities. When you
live in the now moment, you are only
experiencing the one eternal moment in
which everything exists.
Thus, it is quote unquote easier to see
all of the other things that exist in
the eternal moment when you live in it.
I understand that. But there's not this
there doesn't appear to be the same
amount of consciousness. I mean, it's
very real to me the concept that you
just described. But being conscious of
it, for some reason, there is a more of
a clarity. That is simply because of the
definition of the agreement you have
made to live in this reality.
Do not force
yourself. Live your life. Live whatever
it is you are aware of living in the
now. That is what will paradoxically
allow you to be more aware of more of it
when you need to in order to still
fulfill the agreement you made for this
life as well. There are certain ideas
and limitations you have imposed upon
yourselves so that you can live out this
life the way you chose to. What if what
excites me is the fact that I've um
finished the purpose of living the
limitation and then you will no longer
be here.
If you have in fact finished by
definition, you will not be in reality.
What if I finished but I want to assist
others and then you have not finished.
If you find that you can assist others
and serve by the ideas you are
discussing, then simply trust that your
imagination will give you whatever
methodologies are required for you to
explore those realms and then be of
service by sharing those experiences
with others to allow them to know there
is more to themselves than also they may
be aware of. But in this way recognize
living in the now is still the way to
find yourself in contact with all that
you ever are or will experience yourself
to be. But isn't that based on what you
said before almost a a paradox in that
you know you often say that you know
we're always looking for a way a
methodology right yes it is a paradox in
that sense but in this way what we are
describing is not so much a methodology
as it is a description of your state of
being. You only do exist in the now. You
don't exist anywhere or anyone else.
So one way maybe to assist others uh
would be to communicate that idea. The
more you communicate it perhaps the more
you will believe it and therefore the
more you will experience that that is
so. Yeah it's totally for me that that
is so but maybe not as real as it could
be. Okay. Thanks. Thank you. Sure.
Normally my dream recall is very very
very good. Very sharp. Uh thank you.
This past week it has not been so
well two questions I want to relate to.
We have discussed first of all one of
the ideas that a dream what you are
calling a dream is a symbolic creation
to allow you to know that there is a
connection between your physical reality
and your dream reality. But when you no
longer are separating them as much, when
you are blending your dream reality,
your physical reality, you no longer
need a link or a bridge symbol to
remember because they are becoming one
and the same experience.
So, not remembering your so-called
dreams is an indication that you are
beginning to live them, not keep them
separate from your physical reality, and
thereby have to create a dream memory to
know that you were busy when you were
asleep. Follow me. I I follow you, but I I'm
Follow me. I I follow you, but I I'm
even a little more confused because out
of the entire week, two particular
incidents from two separate dreams are
the only things that stay with me. the
rest of it is completely gone. I'll tell
you what those are. But before that, why
would I have any incident stay with me
if in fact there is that blending now?
Because those incidents may represent
the idea that in those particular areas
you are still creating
separation and thus it gives you an
opportunity to deal with it, integrate
it and blend it.
Thus you have cleared the board of
everything except the essentials that
you now need to face in order to allow
the blending to continue. Everything
else is taken care of itself. So you
don't need to see it. You don't need to
remember it. You are only focusing upon
that which are the remnants of the
separation. Let me tell you two
incidents. All right. One of them makes
sense to me based upon the last
conversation we had. The other one is
shaky. All right. One of them was I I
just I simply found myself putting on
someone else's shoes nice and walking in
them, realizing they didn't fit and
trying to find the person to give them
back. All right. And again, that does
have bearing. All right. The second
thing, uh, it didn't make a great deal
of sense to me. I just remember seeing
glitter on my knee and trying to brush
it off. What was that specifically?
In this way, at this time, our
perception of that particular
symbology may represent an inward
recognition of your own luminescence,
your own light, your own
magic. It is not something that you can
get rid of per se. It is something that
is a part of you.
It is something that supports you and at
the same time while being quote unquote
rigid enough to support you as is your
legs, your
knee like the idea of your
self-illumination also gives you
flexibility. The ability to
move that is our perception of the
symbology. Would you comment on the
first thought? Simply your opportunity
to recognize that you know what is true
for you and that you do not have to
accept someone else's reality if it does
not pertain to your vibration.
Thank you very much. Thank you. The
second idea simply is more quote unquote
esoteric in symbology because the
experience you had in your dream reality
that allows you to become cognizant of
that awareness of your self-illumination
is more let us say farther removed from
physical reality. So your physical
consciousness that I have as many
symbols to rely upon to create a
symbolic interpretation. You follow me?
Yes, I do. Thank you. You may all take a
short break. Thank you.
Thank you.
Thanks. Last night I [Music] [Music]
finish
that relationship and I just need some
clarification on that. I was wondering
if right now I'm
maintaining silence.
Why? Because I don't feel like relationship
Because I don't feel like relationship
good for you. What have you learned from
it? A lot but I don't feel
that beneicial in this way. Then simply
as we have suggested take back your
power and again act upon that which
excites you the most.
Well do you mean say
it is not that it will go anywhere. It
will simply transform into whatever
definition befits what you prefer to
be. Physical
proximity has nothing to do with the
fact that the relationship will
continue. It will continue even if you
never see each other physically again.
That will simply be the definition of
your
relationship. The idea is to be what you
know to be true for you.
Period. Act upon that with the
understanding that if you simply
recognize what is true for you and act
upon it, then you will attract whatever
you
need. Take back your power means stop
looking for others to make decisions for
you. Know that if you know what you
prefer, then act upon that.
If you prefer that the idea of the
relationship not be in physiological
proximity, then act upon that. Go where
you wish to
go. Be who you wish to
be. You follow
me? Are you
sure? You think so? What is not clear?
Well, given that this person, why? friendship.
why? friendship.
The relationship will continue on
whatever level it needs to continue to
be what both of you create the
relationship to be. But it will not have
an opportunity to
continue in the sense of the way you
prefer to continue until you are acting
like the person you know yourself to
be. You follow me? When you are
representing yourself truly as to who
you are, then is when you give the
relationship the best opportunity to
continue in a way that is reflective of
your willingness centered to
willingness centered to
yourself represent
yourself reality to understand you and maintain
reality to understand you and maintain
you on some level then they will. If
they don't, then that is the way the
relationship needs to be maintained from
their point of view. You have lived up
to your end by supplying all of the
accurate information about what it is
you are all about. Thus giving the
opportunity to beyond that you are not responsible
to beyond that you are not responsible
for their reactions.
Well, the last time that I was in
communication with them, I was
communicating myself.
So then what did you do?
I didn't do anything. Then what is your
so-called difficulty?
Well, I moved away. Yes. And I Was that
according to your preference? Yes. All
right. I never made an attempt to get
back in touch with
All right.
So, but I feel that if he wanted to
contact me, I could. All right. Have you
given him an opportunity to do so or the
means to do so?
I don't. Well, my old phone number had a
recording that transferred the new
number. So, if he wanted to call the
number, he could. So, then what is the
point? I don't think there's a point. I think
I don't think there's a point. I think
that the relationship is what it is
according to what you prefer to
be. There is no need to place
expectations upon what you think it
should be. It is what it is according to
what you prefer to
be. Now if you prefer something else
then be something else and act like
something else. But if you prefer the
way you are, then act like you prefer
the way you are and do not worry or
wonder about what is going on with
someone else. Well, I just I just wanted
the clarity. But you felt I should
continue as I am. I will never tell you
whether you should or should not do
anything. If you prefer where you are,
continue. If you don't, don't. Well, you
said take your power and I just
take your power means just what I just
told you. If you prefer where you are,
continue. If you don't,
don't. Do not seek within
me the knowledge of what you should or
should not do. That is giving me your
power rather than simply exercising what
you already know to be true for you and
acting upon it. Well, I just interpreted
it to mean that I should not
communicate. Why? There is nothing in the idea of
Why? There is nothing in the idea of
taking your power that implies that you
should or should not communicate with
him. If you feel like communicating with
that individual, do so. If you know that
you can communicate with that individual
and still be who you prefer to be, do so
if that is what you wish to do.
Communicating with that individual in
and of itself does not mean you are not
being who you prefer to
be. It does not have to mean that you
are not functioning within your
integrity, that you are not living up to
your principles. It depends on how you
define the reasons for why you are
communicating with that
individual. You follow me?
All right. Thank you for Hey, you speak
of what excites you a lot. That's the
driving force or something. It is the
manifesting force. Can you elaborate a
little more on it because I don't feel
excitement, you know, every day of my
life? I don't know many people that do,
but that's the driving force.
You do not feel excitement. Not a lot. I
associate it with you know Christmas
morning or you know what is today
arrives what is today
today yes that's today the usual usual
usual why it's life gets routine routine
life does not get routine you create it
to be routine so we should create
excitement even at the expense of others
or how can the creation of excitement be
at the expense of others I don't know
some of the things I think of would
such as
well I don't know like burglarizing
something the creation of excitement
within the expression of integrity
does that change the definition for you
again the idea of
excitement fundamentally is recognizing
that you are as powerful as you need to
be to do anything you want without
having to hurt anyone else to get
But we create it though. I mean by doing
what you want to do within your
integrity by discontinuing the assumption that you
by discontinuing the assumption that you
have to do certain things that do not
excite you in order to
live. Thus you will not create a
routine. You will be spontaneous within your
You will be spontaneous within your
integrity and that will be exciting.
Do you understand? Yes, I do. Thank you.
Are you more excited?
I'll tell you tomorrow. I will take your
laughter as a yes. Yeah. Thank you.
Thanks. Uh in that same context, I find that a
Uh in that same context, I find that a
lot of
times a lot of happiness or excitement
runs through my life and I feel like I'm
just uh not worrying about tomorrow or the
uh not worrying about tomorrow or the
next day or Yes, there is no reason why
you should. So just take the excitement
and run rampid with it. Huh? Live it.
Thank you. I see. quite you or sorry
question. All right. Um very happy with
my life now and uh but I cannot remember
much of my childhood. But it's all
right. Um but it must have been good. I
mean I had good all right if you do.
Yeah. Why why wouldn't I be able to
remember if it was good? Maybe because
you don't need me to because you are so
happy now.
Any other reason you might think? No. I
I don't know. I don't know why. I feel
sometimes that you maybe something is
wrong because I can't. Oh, people tell
me that it might be wrong because or
maybe you know something's wrong,
something's lacking. You know, try to
analyze something maybe missing. Do
remember that no matter what the reason
for the socalled lack of
memory. The idea of existing in the
fourth density is that you will
disassociate from remembering the past.
You will simply recognize that memory is
created in the present.
And you will know what you need to know
when you need to know it.
You follow me? I do. Thank you. Thank
you. Then you are right now a happy
childhood. You follow me? Yes. Thank you.
Yes. In trying to assist others. In
what? In attempting In what? In helping
others. Thank you.
As I may remind you, I am becoming
selectively third density deaf.
One of the uh one of the situations that
one encounters I have to be careful what
I say. No, you're not. Okay. Um one of
the situations one encounters I I thank
you. um is that people do tend to give you
um is that people do tend to give you
their power in the in the way that was
expressed with your interactions
tonight. All right. Um it seems to be a
habit um that we have and this does not
mean that you cannot allow yourself to
know that the word habit is simply a
belief that something is difficult to
change and therefore does not no longer
have to be a habit.
Well, we seem to have a propensity to to
I I
Okay, I I I seem to notice that uh that
the interactions that we've had with
people that have come along to try to
enlighten um is we we tend to um you know crucify
um is we we tend to um you know crucify
them or something along there. Well,
that is simply because you do not
believe in your own self-empowerment. do
not believe that they are a reflection
of you.
Okay. In trying to uh in assisting
another Yes. If they try to give you their
Yes. If they try to give you their
power, you don't have to take it.
Do you? No. Definitely not. Then you can
reflect to them that they are attempting
to give their power away and you can
very lovingly and politely say no thank you.
you.
You you keep your
power. Then we will be on equal terms
creating as equals. You will have
whatever you want. I will have whatever
I want. And what you want and what I
want will serve us both. And what you
want will not take away from what I
want. And what I want will not take away
from what you want. What you want and
what I want, we will both have. And the
having will enrich us
both. Because we also both want the
other to have what the other wants.
Okay. Has that assisted you?
Um to some extent. Would you like to
explore further?
Uh yes. Go ahead.
In assisting others then we are
assisting ourselves. In teaching others
we are teaching. Okay.
Thank you.
Sure. For sure. I've uh simplified the
definition. Help for me is assisting
somebody in the direction they're going.
a you know and uh I just look where
they're headed and what they've chosen
and assisting them. It's see help I see
it used to be real confusing. Help I had
a model. What is help? Well, help is
getting somebody on their feet and
helping them make money and stuff and
that may not be help for some people.
Correct. Help for some people like
giving them a you know good swift kick
in the ass or something that might be
just what they needed or wanted or you
know that's that's my sharing. Thank you
very much.
You can always maintain your assistance
within your own integrity.
Sure. I have a question. All right. On this
I have a question. All right. On this
man's talking
about I meet people in my practice.
Who who seem to want to be sick and of
course they come to me and they say,
"Please help me get well."
And they don't and I sort of I
apologize. I looked at you and I said,
"Well, you need to assess what you get
out of being sick." All right. Some
people don't like to hear that, though.
Correct. But there's nothing I can do. Correct. I
But there's nothing I can do. Correct. I
just have done what you can do. Yes. Do
understand that there is a reason that
they have come to you. So, they have
gotten something out of it. You have
done something. Whether you might
recognize for what it is or not doesn't
make a difference because they have
interacted with you. They have gotten
something out of it. Otherwise, they
would never have showed up on your
doorstep at all. Thanks, Ben. Thank you.
Thank you.
Sure. I'm sorry. Thanks. Um it was suggested
I'm sorry. Thanks. Um it was suggested
to me by an entity that if a particular
opportunity um comes to be offered to me
that um it would serve me and I agree um
well to function from the standpoint
this is it quote unquote
um and just take a firm stand and go for
something so to speak
um from a practical standpoint practical
right I want to make this
differentiation between practical and
effective because I see if you insist
Okay, from a practical standpoint, the
opportunity that perhaps could be
presented is desirable, but I recognize
from um the standpoint of what really
excites me that it's not as desirable as
a practical standpoint. And because I
know that I'm not truly at one with the
opportunity is the opportunity that
presents itself, the most exciting thing
that you are able to act upon at the
moment it presents itself. Uh-huh.
then that is a part of what excites you
the most. Whether it seems like it's
going to get you there or
not. You're only judging that it has
nothing to do with what excites you the
most. If what excites you the most does
not give you a manifestation that
presents itself in an obvious
connection, then whatever does present
itself as the most exciting opportunity
is still representative of that path
whether it seems to be or not.
We are saying act upon what excites you
the most in what is available for you to
act upon right at the moment. That will
lead you to what excites you the most.
Okay. Thank you. For sure. Yes. What
purpose is serve when an entity makes
you predictions disaster or
predictions disaster or
can be for many different reasons some
of which we perceive you already
recognize. In this way, it can be an
opportunity for individuals to quote
unquote fall back on their own habits or
take their own power and say it doesn't
have to be that way entity that is not
my reality. Thank you for giving me an
opportunity to see reflected in your
idea, your presentation, your gift, my
preference that that is not my reality.
And thus I can be of radiant assistance
to others by sharing with them how I
perceive that it is not my reality so
that they can also choose that it does
not have to be theirs. That is one way
you can look at
it. There are
situations without quote unquote naming
names where individuals that you call
the channels may also be filtering their
own belief systems into the
information. Thank you. Sure. Sure.
Nice. Uh, a day or two ago, we had a
pretty good earthquake.
And, uh, another gateway release,
crystallization. We had one a week or so
ago. Uh, is the mass consciousness of
the Southern California area in your
perception to bring upon uh, this area
some sort of a disaster for? In our
perception, it is that you can recognize
and do recognize that you can rechan the
energy in many different ways, causing
there to be the idea of what you call
minor releases and rechaning the
majority of the energy in constructive
ways. That is our perception. What is
yours? Well, I don't know that much about
Well, I don't know that much about
earthquakes. You do not have to. Do you
prefer in this way? Well, of course, in
this way, you will find that a majority
of individuals living in what you call
earthquake prone areas will find that it
does not so much bother them because
they like the energy. They like the
excitement. They like living on the
edge. That is why you are here.
You are rechaning the edge of one
reality and another. You are rechaning
that energy. Well, if the mass
consciousness believes that the
catastrophe is the best way to get from
third to fourth
density, that probably what should
happen. Probably. But also recognize
that the mass consciousness of what you
call your immediate area has long been
noted in your own society for looking at
things differently
than the rest of the mass consciousness
of our world. Oops. Nice.
Thank you for enjoying your spookiness. To some
To some
degree, some degree
sometimes we can quote unquote keep you
posted as to manifestations of some of
the release of that energy from time to
time in different ways.
Maybe. Okay.
Sure. You want to be safe? Nope. Hey.
Uh, speaking in physical physics terms,
if you were to get in your spaceship and
travel in a linear direction in linear
time, uh, the conines are the definition
of the physical universe. What happens
if you keep going? Is it is it finite in
that sense? Would you just pass pass on
to a void or something?
Speaking in those terms, I know you
don't like you will find that there is,
as has been described by your
scientists, a curvature. Yeah. Travel
far enough and you will wind up back at
the same point. Okay.
Does that answer your question? It does.
Thank you.
Shooting. Sure. Great question. Um, I believe that
Sure. Great question. Um, I believe that
there are there are people just like us
probably sitting in a room just like
this somewhere else in this space doing
the same thing we are. Is
there do they talk communicate like us?
Look like us. Yikes. There are many
parallels with many similarities.
Does did that is that against the the
belief uh that uh that many people have
you know the creation of this world?
Some yes. So what do you believe?
Whatever you
want. Fair enough. All realities are
real. There is no one background against
which to measure for accuracy.
The truth is composed of all
truths. Believe what you
wish. It is all real.
Yes and no. Sh.
Sh.
I've got a short-term uh I guess you'd
call it a phrase to back up what you
were saying. U if it can be experienced,
it exists. You cannot experience
something which doesn't exist. Correct.
Well, I thought I'd give that to you.
Thank you. Now, understand what your
definition of experience may mean.
However, when you say that that it's not
necessarily restricted to what you call
physiological experience, right? Thank
you. I thought that that includes the the
I thought that that includes the the
nuances and the subtleties of thought
and thank you. Has that been of some
assistance? Yes, very much.
Thank you very much for your reflection
and your assistance to us. For in this
way, every individual makes a
difference. Thank you for your service.
Hey, that doesn't mean that if a tree
falls in a forest and you're not there
that it didn't fall. It may mean there
is even no tree.
No forest. How about a bear? No falling.
Understand once again that the idea of
your mass conscious telepathic net will
support the occurrences in physical
reality that no one may physically be
around to witness but which you know on
some level are still being created to
take place because of the overall
interaction that it needs to fit into.
So as you have defined your reality,
whether there is anyone physically
standing around or not, generally
speaking, a tree falling in the forest
will make a sound that will fall simply
because that is the reality you have
defined. But it is no more or less of an
illusion than anything
else. You follow me? I do. Thank you.
Yay. What if
What if
um you're the kind of person Oh, what if
what if what if you're the kind of
person who finds something exciting that
is also at the same time
self-destructive? What if? Yeah.
What if? Yeah.
Well, what if? Well, I then you will be
excited by your self-destruction.
Well, you keep saying that uh you keep
talking about if you find something
exciting within your integrity. We are
simply giving you the understanding,
sharing with you the notion that if you
wish to be consciously
aware of the fact that you are creating
that experience, then doing it within
your integrity is the way that can allow
you to maintain a connection to
conscious awareness of the fact that you
are creating that reality. The idea of
being excited of things that are outside
the integrity will many times allow you
to play the victim game and think that
something else is creating the
circumstance rather than you. Thus not
giving you an opportunity to know that
if you should get to a point where you
find that self-destructing is no longer
very exciting. You may not be aware of
the fact that you can stop it just as
easily as you started
it. That is the difference to the
infinite soul that you are. Ultimately,
it doesn't make a difference because you
are eternal no matter what you do with
your physical life and everything is a
learning experience. You follow me? Yes.
How can one become more aware of what's
going to be ultimately uh either
self-destructive or healthy?
How can you be aware Mhm. of what is
self-destructive or healthy? Yes.
I mean, sometimes you sometimes I do
things and I think it's it's really good
for me and I think I'm I'm doing the
healthy thing for my life and then a
couple of months later I realize that
I've sabotaged myself once again. No,
no, no.
Understand your question implies that
there is something going on in your life
that is not the product of your creation
of
it. How can I be
aware? which implies that there is some
mechanism turning that you have no
control over. You can be aware that everything
over. You can be aware that everything
in your life is healthy by choosing to
believe that it is so. Period. And not
choosing to believe that something that
occurs in your life is in fact sabotage.
That is your choice to choose that point
of view. That choosing of that point of
view is what creates the situation to be
sabotage. You are sabotaging it to be
sabotage because you choose to believe
that the situation is
sabotage. You are aware that it is
healthy by choosing to understand that
everything in your life everything in
your life serves you positively. Thereby
you allow yourself to know that no
matter what happens, it is for a good
reason and is not an interruption in
your path because it can't be because a
path is not what you are on. A path is
what you are. You can't be off
yourself. That is how you become aware.
You follow me?
You simply choose to understand that
every situation is fundamentally
neutral. No situation has builtin
meaning. There is no such thing as a
fundamental situation that is in and of
itself simply because of the definition
of the circumstances a sabotaging
situation. The only thing that created
to be a sabotaging situation is your
judgmental perception of it in that
light. It is only your judgment of it
that creates it to be what you judged it
to be.
When you stop judging the ideas to be
negative, when you stop judging that
they have no place in your life, then
you will assign to these neutral
situations a positive symbology. And
that is what will allow you to see how
the situation in fact positively served
you by being there rather than give you
the impression or you creating the
impression that it has no business being
in your life and is an interruption in
the path you think you should be being.
That is
how. Does that make sense? Mhm. Thank
you. Then I will at this
time remind each and every one of you
individually and
collectively. All you need to
do is allow yourselves to
believe that it is that simple.
You did not have to do anything special
to deserve
existence. Exist you do. Exist you
always will by
definition. All that
is granted you existence from
unconditional love and unconditionally
loves you forever.
Treat yourself with the same respect by
understanding that everything in your
life is something that serves you and is
not there to destroy
you. Choose what you prefer out of all
the choices you give
yourself. We bid you exciting dream life
and life
dreams. They are one in the same
reality. One and the same.
We bid you a fond.