I say how are you all the seeing your
time as you create time to exist very in
this way you
way you
may this light of your time commence the
interaction between us in whatever
manner you see fit
in our efforts
to accelerate and become more sensitive
to our movement
Third density, fourth density.
Is it meaningful for us to look at
altering our attitudes and behavior or
is the absence
of being attached to the view of fourth
density existence sufficient in itself?
Now you can understand that the idea can
be approached from either direction and
will result in the same effect in this
way. If you simply can know that you are
attached to fourth density reality then
your habits your attitudes in this way
and your belief systems will
automatically change. You can also give
yourself the opportunity if that is how
you choose to explore the idea of simply
allowing yourself to express attitudes
that are reflective belief systems that
you know to be reflective of the being
you think you will be in fourth density.
You can work it from either direction
and the effect will be the same. You
follow me? Yes.
um if that's the case
um and approaching it from both
directions makes
sense. Uh one of the things that that
I'm curious
about is if we can look at altering our
is if we can look at altering our
attitudes and
behavior and that's an effective
approach as well as the beingness as
well as experiencing simply the
beingness of being there. What is it in
the context of say
um oh let's take politics
uh is
there I I don't have a clear
understanding let's say from a political
point of view of of necessarily the
attitudes andor behaviors that are more
closely aligned with the fourth density
existence. Now in terms of what you call
your political structure upon your
planet, you may find that in fourth
density it will not exist at all. That
may be why it is difficult to imagine.
Okay. Um understand again in our
civilization we have no political or
economic system as you understand it.
For in this way each and every being is
simply being of service to every other
being exactly when and where they need
to. Uh how about if I looked at the
Uh how about if I looked at the
religious or sexual realm? The religious
idea will also change. Not so much the
sexual realm except in the idea of the
attitudes between yourselves in forming
the relationships that you form.
How would you how would you if how would
you suggest then that we might more
rapidly approach a fourth sense of
existence? How is it that we could align our sexual
How is it that we could align our sexual
attitudes and behaviors to more rapidly
approach fourth density? First and
foremost, in this way, allow the
relationship as they occur in the form
in the manner that they occur to be the
manner in which you want them to occur.
Allow the relationship as they form in
the way they form to serve you rather
than putting expectation upon the
relationship to become what you think it
should be
following. In that way you will then
allow the relationship to serve the
purpose for which you attracted it to
yourself and then it will transform in
whatever way that will be obvious for
you to reflect to yourself the idea of
your own force density acceleration and
momentum. And along with that in
relationship the idea can also be
created within your attitude that you
know that you do not need a relationship
in order to be complete. In this way you
simply know that you are complete as you
need to be and you can attract an equal
relationship in which you can share with
each other the idea of the completeness
you already are. You follow me? Yes.
Those attitudes will be the essential
foundational attitudes within what you
call relationships in density.
Yes. Um I guess what I'm looking for
is a greater
um greater understanding or specificity
on specific uh attitudes or behaviors as
far as let's say religion respects them.
All right. But again understand that in
fourth density religion will not exist
in the manner it exists now at all. And
so again it may be difficult to form an
idea of what that would be like.
Understand that the idea in your
vernacular of what you usually term
religion is not something on your planet
that expresses itself as a person living
their belief but a person following what
another person says they should believe.
You follow me? Yes. And so that is
fundamentally the difference of the the
essence of the difference between
religious uh uh attitudes between third
and fourth density. Yes. In fourth
density, the idea is to live the life
you know reflects the life that reflects
the being you are rather than what
someone else tells you they think you
should be doing. Right. Sure. Then
understand that because of that one
idea, you will recognize that all the
structures that you call religious and
political will dissolve. Yeah.
You will be taking responsibility for
yourselves in that way. Not in what you
call a state of anarchy, but in this
way, you will simply allow yourself to
take back the responsibility for the
fear that you have refused to live
through, to come to terms with within
the being of your physiological
consciousness. And in that way, you will
not give that fear over to someone else
to take care of for you, to take care of
you. for you. You follow me? Make up
online. Suggestions will always be beneficial.
Suggestions will always be beneficial.
But in this way, no one no one knows
what another should or should not
do. Every being in creation is a valid
path. If there was only one way to do
something, only one path, there would
only be one person. You follow me?
Therefore, simply recognize that you as
you are are the expression, your unique
facet of the multi-dimensional crystal
of all that is that you chose to be. So
be it
fully. Liz, be following.
Thank you. Sure. Sure. Thanks. A several
questions about the process of
channeling. One, how do you know when
Daryl is ready to go into a trap? In
this way, what you call the link between
our consciousness is always open.
So were you in the process of doing some
other activity when it suddenly became
apparent to you that we were all
gathered here this evening and we were
in a sense I will find that I will
simply have a sense of the timing and I
will know that when I prepare myself the
timing is correct for nothing else can
be possible. Okay. Once you said that
you're using
the Daryl's vocabulary and so forth,
would it be possible for you to cause
Daryl to speak words, say English words
that he himself does not know, or are
you limited to his vocabulary? In this
way, it will be usual to limit to the
vocabulary. There are times when the
energy if it is willing to be trusted to
that extent can extend beyond the
mentality of the channel. In this case
that will be rare. What you call the
idea of speaking in tongues will be an
example of the level of trust that will
allow the mentality to transcend into
the super mentality and in this way will
have access to anything the mentality
can have access to. You follow me? Yes.
In this case, because of the level of
energy, because of the terms of the
agreement and the purposes being served,
it will simply usually restrict itself
to the
vocabulary and his own datab bank. Now,
concepts can be something that the
channel does not know. But again, it
will require let us
say the
assemblage to describe that concept out
of the vocabulary that exists within the
channel. Okay. Could you take a moment
briefly and describe how the process of
channeling is achieved? I do. In this
way, you will find that the
consciousness of the physiological
channel and my consciousness will in a
sense accelerate towards each other and
blend to form a third identity. This
functions to create pulses in a sense of
energy that in the physiological channel
will activate the motor nerve and draw
from it the responses that are
reflective of a concept being channeled
through the physical form. You follow
me? Yes.
So the relationship between Daryl and
the third entity created by your
consciousness and Daryl's consciousness,
is that similar to a relationship
between the person's higher self and
their own physiological form? It does.
Yes. Does it also mean based on your
Does it also mean based on your
description that there will inevitably
be a certain amount of filtering so
that you when you channel when Bashar
comes through another person another
physiological form will how much of a
difference would there be? There will be
differences according to the experiences
of the physiological channel to some
degree and the degree of willingness,
the degree of trust, the degree of
understanding. I got it. Thank you. Thank you. Now you
I got it. Thank you. Thank you. Now you
mentioned speaking in tongues. Isn't
that sometimes a collect connection with
past lives? Again understand it is a
connection to what you call the super
mentality which encapsulates all
physical reality that you have
experienced or have yet to experience.
You follow me? Thus including the idea
you call past and future lives in the
physical sense. Do you think that it it
often has connection to past life or not
that often when it happens?
That can be one through which the
understanding is allowed. If that is the
easiest route for the mentality of the
physiological channel to allow there to
be an understanding how such a thing
could be possible then it will happen
that way. But understand once again that
all connections whether they be in the
idea of the super mentality,
subconsciousness, unconsciousness or
consciousness that are made to any ideas
that you call future or past are still
all being made in the present since
everything is simultaneous.
Please join
I've been exploring the idea of um I
become aware that I manifest my
preferences by thought intellectually
and I have a sense that in fourth
density you I would manifest more with
my total being not just from in a sense
now you can begin to realize first of
all however that by the time you have
the thought that is not the first thing
you have done you follow me. Yes. What
is the thought is a
recognition of that which already exists
within you as a belief in terms of what
you
prefer. Therefore by the time you have
the thought it is a reflection of what
already exists within you. Knowing that
can allow you to begin to simply feel it
from the levels of your being that are
above thought. You follow me? You are simply
thought. You follow me? You are simply
shifting your focus as to where you
allow yourself to recognize that you are
that idea. You can recognize that you
are an idea from thought. You can
recognize that you are an idea from
feeling. And you can recognize that you
are an idea from belief. And you can
recognize that you are an idea from
knowingness. Whatever frequency you choose to
Whatever frequency you choose to
recognize yourself as an idea
from, that is the symbology that you
will use to represent the method by
which you think you have arrived at that
empress. You follow me?
Uh-huh. Um, I would like to uh exercise
other ways of manifesting other than
thought, more through belief and
feeling. All right. Again, as we just
said, if you understand the concept that
to have the thought, it has to go
through your belief first, then simply
recognize that by knowing that you can
begin to function in that way. Because
if you have the concept at all, you are
then the being that is functioning in
that way or you would never have the
idea. You can only perceive what you
contain. You follow me? Yes, I do. for
you. Thank you. So sir, go ahead. On
along the same lines, um I it's my
understanding that that you have said
that idea creates thought which creates
emotion. Is that is that understanding
correct? Something like that. It can be
work in that way. But in terms of what
you may call the linear progression,
there is existence, there is then
knowingness, then there is belief, then
there is emotion, then there is thought,
then there is physicalization. Okay. The
reason I asked that is because it's my
understanding that that who I guess is a
counterpart of yours in some
way, feels that emotion
pre and the thought. That is what I
said. Oh, existence, knowingness, belief,
Oh, existence, knowingness, belief,
emotion, thoughts, physicality. I see.
Okay, that's where I was. Okay.
Yes. I would like to ex get a clearer
understanding or of your perspective of
the relationship between a spirit, a
person himself, a spiritual being if you
will, and the body. It's
my a concept a conceptual framework that
I am comfortable with at the moment but
I'm not certain it aligns with your
percept perspective on all right is that
there is a body and it's kind of you
know it sort of occurs through sexual
intercourse and reproduction and so
forth and a spiritual being who is
capable of existing with full
consciousness independently and separate
from the physical re realm makes a
conscious decision to pick up or assume
responsibility for this particular body
and it might happen while it's still in
the womb or after it comes out. That's
immaterial. But what I'm driving at is
that conceptual framework of the
relationship where my this physical form
that I'm animating and operating through
that is valid for how it happens in the
third density structure that you have
created your universe to be. Yes. Okay.
Do you have a different take or
perspective on it? In a sense, you will
find that our perception extends to the
idea that what you call the physical
body in this way and the totality of
physical reality is simply a projection
of the belief system of the
consciousness in this way and also that
what you call a physical body is in a
sense actually spirit. It is the soul in
physical terms.
Not so much that a soul literally exists
in it, but it is an expression of the
soul in physical
terms. Well, first of all, those two
concepts seem quite different. Yes and
no. Okay. Is it true that a body could
have a life of its own independently of
its oversoul? There is
There is
consciousness that goes into let us say
creating physical reality. And there are
types of manifestations that can be in a
sense body without the same type of soul
consciousness that you would normally
recognize. It is within so to speak an
individual. Those bodies, those
projections in your vernacular are
usually referred to as by locations.
I don't know where. All
right. You can in this way look at it
this way. Now again understand all this
is in a sense very arbitrary and a great
deal of labeling goes into this idea.
But as it fits into the structure of the
reality that you have already defined,
it works this way. You as a physical
being may have an idea of yourself that
may be more than can be contained in the
single body you have created it. But it
is an idea that still partakes of the
form in which you have created yourself
to be. So what you will do for usually a
very brief period of time is you will
duplicate your body and it will be out
walking around in the world. In your
terms, it is not the original you but it
will act much like you. Individuals who
are sensitive to oric field may not feel
it to really be in a sense alive in the
same way they may feel you are. And to
them they may feel it is a hollow body.
It is animated by the idea you are and
not in and of itself the recipient of a
complete soul form as you are. But it is
an extension of the soul that you are in
this body and it serves certain purposes
and can act them out and then usually
will disappear or vanish in this sense.
Therefore, you can look upon it as let
us say a simolacum, a model or a golem
if you will. I understand everything
you've said, but I'm still grappling
with the what seems to be a reasonably
large difference between the
relationship between my experience of
myself as a spiritual being. I
conceptually feel or the con the
conceptual framework within which I've
operated for a number of years is that I
can exist independently. I that I that
my consciousness is not the product of
physicality. No, it is not the product
of physicality. No. And and that in fact
physicality is the product of your
consciousness. Right. Right. And that in
in fact who I am my personality is
something I define independently of the
body. All right. I understand your
terminology, but also understand that
because physicality is a product of
consciousness, physicality is also who
you are. It's also who you are. Not
exclusively, yes, but also in addition
to everything you are. Physicalness is
also who you are. It is an expression of
your consciousness and cannot be
separated from your consciousness except
by the illusion that it can be. And how
well what now let's maybe that's the
point. the illusion that one I describe
something and you said well in terms of
third density that's appropriate but in
terms of fourth density my description
of the way things are isn't will simply
begin to understand or have the sense
that as a
soul perhaps an analogy let us say there
is a
framework like unto what you call a
doorway big enough for you to walk
through all Okay. There is within that
framework however entirely filling the
framework let us say a sheet of rubber.
All right. Okay. Now you stand on one
side of that doorway facing the rubber
sheet. Okay. You are in fourth density
reality. Okay. Let us say on the other
side of the door is third density
reality. You follow me? Yes. Now you
walk into the rubber sheet and from the
other side someone viewing you would see
the outline of your floor. You follow
me? Now what they would see would be
considered to be the physical body.
Right? It is taking its imprint from the
idea of the body on this side of the
doorway. Okay? Now when you choose to
step backwards then the physical body in
a sense disappears back into the
homogeneous field out of which it was
created. Therefore, understanding is not so much
Therefore, understanding is not so much
that it is truly in a sense separate
from you, but it is intimately connected
to your willingness to take the step
into the other dimension beyond the
framework of the doorway. And then you
can say it is in a sense a reflection or
a projection of your soul as you choose
to stand, however far you choose to
stand in that doorway on the other side.
Thank you. I got it. There's just one
more. I mean, I really got it. There's
just one little piece, which is I
understand that conceptually I have no
problem. But then at the same time, I
see within third density reality that
for example, this body that I have and
presumably all the other bodies in the
room were created as a result of an
ongoing sexual reproductive occur. But
that is all part and parcel of the fact
that you as a non-physical entity, the
oversoul together with all the other
oversouls designed the universe to be
that way. And so it is still only a
projection of consciousness no matter
how much of a law it seems to be from
the physical point of view. Yes. And
that's not my problem. All right. The
point I understand that collectively we
create this game. The game seems to have
a certain amount of automatic pilot to
it. Of course, it's just cranking
forward and all of a sudden this body
arrives. But the automatic pilot is your
oversoul. Well, but at what in other words, you
Well, but at what in other words, you
have spoken about Let me put it this way
from the oversoul perspective. It is not
automatic. It is consciously creative. I
I understand and ongoing. It only
appears to be automatic from the
physical point of view because you do
not see the source of the engine that
drives it. I understand that right if
you have spoken of for
example you gave us an analogy about if
the oversold decides that your
personality is going to experience a
hall then you're going to experience
that hall whether you're running
skipping jumping laughing flooding it
with water swimming whatever therefore
the hallway is what you are finding to
be the automatic or predestined
mechanisms but my experience that I have recalled
but my experience that I have recalled
if you will or picked up alternate
whatever I remember my birth. So what?
Well, so it seemed as if it was at that
moment that I decided or a little bit
before that moment actually sometime
before I decided as a spiritual being
with consciousness sort of operating a
little bit off from the visibility. I
decided that these two people were going
to that I was going to have them as my
parents. Thank you. Understand there are
Thank you. Understand there are
also levels of existence in non-physical
reality that have been created as well.
And you can have a perspective in
non-physical reality that is very
similar to physical reality in the level
that is just above physical reality.
That level is the astral level and is
not the oversoul level.
What you are remembering is a memory in
the non-physical astral realm.
Well, okay. How many levels between
astral and over? In a sense, seven in
that sense from physicality all the way
up. Could you enumerate them? In this
way, you will have created the idea of
what you call a physical body, an astral
body, an etheric body, a causal body, a
mental body, a spirit form body. In that
way, a godlike body in that sense. There
can be variations even within several of
the different levels. It is quite
holographic beyond a certain point. And
in this way, some of the separations can
be created to be more than what is
usually experienced or it can be created
that they are less. In some realities,
there are not that many levels. Simply
understand that you have created several
of these ideas to
reinforce the idea of this physical
reality by surrounding it with a
non-physical reality that also partakes
of the idea of some degree of separation
to allow yourself to remain within the
physical reality to experience what you
chose. So you will find that many times
in between lives so to speak you do not
go all the way up so to speak let us say
to the complete overview of the idea but
only a little way up so that you will
still remain within the understanding of
the focus of what physical reality was
all about otherwise you would lose that
idea altogether. I got it thank you. I
just now wonder if you would define more
completely each of those other levels
like what is the astral level, the
etheric level and all that because these
are terms I've heard in the past and
never knew what anybody was talking
about. All right.
Now let us say the definitions will vary
to some degree throughout the different
cultures upon our planet and throughout
different civilizations. But in this way
you can understand that the astral level
will in a sense be made of a different
kind of matter a more rarified matter
but there still will be some degree of
the idea of the experience of
materiality to it. The astral level will
represent nonphysical fourth density
reality. Fourth density is the last
density in which you can experience both
physical reality and non-physical
reality. So the astral level will be the
fourth density non-physical counterpart
in that way. You will find therefore it
is more highly accelerated than physical
matter. But many of the experiences
within it though far more ranging in the
freedom in which you have to create what
you experience and be a little bit
outside the idea of time and space will
still carry with it some of the
experiences that you would find familiar
so to speak within this reality you are
now in in physical terms. The athetheric
body in a sense is to some degree a
mediator between the idea of the astral
body and in a sense your mentality. It
is an expression of your mentality and
is not in and of itself so much an
experience unto itself a world unto
itself like the astral realm is but it
is more let us say a connective form
that you have created. It is in a sense
what also creates the oric field. In
that way, it is more an expression of
embodiment as the mentality. In other
words, an expression of the
electromagnetic fluid, so to speak, the
energy field by which you all find
yourselves to be mentally linked in
physical reality.
In this way, the causal plane will be
connected to what we call the template
identification and will be yet a little
bit less physically material and will
begin to understand itself in ways that
is more towards the classic oversold
point of view in the sense that it
reviews many ideas of the connections to
many lives simultaneously and feels
itself to be in this way connected to
all of them in that way. Simultaneously
in the different levels in that way
above that you find that what you begin
to experience is yourself as all the
different dimensions and alternate
realities in which you exist. Above that
you begin to experience yourself as the
dimensions themselves. Above that you begin to
themselves. Above that you begin to
experience the idea of yourself
as living within all dimensions of
experience. And above that you begin to
experience yourself as all the
dimensions of experience. And above that
you begin to experience yourself as only
the oneness in which all the dimensions
of experience are created.
Yes. Could you explain the transition
from third to fourth density relative to
what? This is a physiological
transformation. Your material form is
becoming even less dense and in this way
you will have towards the middle and the
end of the fourth density experience
what you will call a light body in a
sense. It will be very highly refined
and in a sense will almost at the end of
the fourth density experience be nothing
more than an outward appearance a shell
so to speak.
Ow yourself to know that you are the
very same type of being. And if you can
perceive that type of energy, simply
live that way on your own planet. And
then you will be allowing your energy to
reflect to all other beings on your
planet that they can also choose to live
that way. And then your planet will also
live a shell, so to speak, which will
take 2 to 3,000 years approximately as
we read your energy at this time.
Correct. And when we say it is a
refinement of the physical materiality
you are used to living as now. And is
the consciousness more closely aligned
with the seventh level?
Let us say it is more aware of its
alignment and the seat of
and the seat of
consciousness
change action. What what is change? What
in consciousness of consciousness? Is
that also moving? Not so much. The
change is not so much occurring in the
higher level since the higher levels
already understand what they are in that
sense. But the idea is that fourth
density physical reality becomes the
final physical reflection that the
physical universe is aligned with all
the other levels. Whereas third density
does not know it is aligned. That is the
difference. Fourthly, physical reality
is the expression of the physical
reality. That is the understanding that
physical reality is also an extension of
the soul and not something truly
separate. The greatest change is in the
physical density, not in the
non-physical ones in terms of the point
of view.
Thank you. From third to fourth, the
greatest change is going to be the
greatest change in the transformation
from third to fourth density is within
the transformation in physical terms
itself to the higher levels of yourself.
They are not changing. It is the
physical portion of themselves that is
changing the most drastically.
Sure. All right. um moving on.
You're talking about choice points in
terms of when you say one say what are
you willing to do when you know the idea
of your future self your first and we
can hold that that means we allow
it that means we're partially already
out of the moment that we're
and in order to realize that when we
make it actual down to the physical You
simply have to allow yourself to know
that in the moment you conceptualize
that you are in that
state. Then do not make and create the
assumption that you have to do something
to become that state. Recognize that in
having the notion you are in the moment
at
state with those levels that there are
more subtle changes. Once I would like
to give an example um with the passing
of the island of dark um in the middle
of the night I went into a paper state
and created a donut that I during the
process of releasing good and I also had
the experience of listening to your
voice and translating and explaining
what he was saying to other people.
Okay. Um and it wasn't in my awareness
that I from what you say I interpreted
that the pain and the fever which was
not something I failed to make
uncomfortable and there were judgments
going on otherwise it was simply
habitual remnant of separation and the
point is at what level it didn't happen
when I was it was judging understand
that what you are doing right now each
and every one of you in terms of the
transformation from third to fourth
density is existing in a quasi planar
reality, a quasi limbo state in which
you are not exactly one and not exactly
the other, but the idea of the
transformation itself. And thus many of
these experiences will always be felt an
experience when you allow yourself to
recognize that you are in the
transformational mode.
um mode to smooth
this. I'm very well aware of the pain.
Simply allow yourself to experience what
you have chosen to experience and know
that the more allowing you are the
sooner the idea of the pain will no
longer be necessary and it will
alleviate. And it feels like where I
tend to be pulled is to want to know
consciously what the judgment is in
order to that is not necessary. It is
only in the idea that you are habitually
still making comparison between the past
you and the so-called future you are
becoming. So I'm making a comparison and
I'm making understand you can look at it
this way and perhaps this will allow you
to assist yourself in bringing to
consciousness the idea of the
transformation an idea we discussed last
night of your time. First of all for now
if you must make any separation at all
then simplify it in the
extreme. Let us drop the labels
subconscious, unconscious, higher
conscious. Let us just say for now that
there is physical consciousness and
non-physical consciousness. All right?
So let us say in those terms there is
only one physical consciousness and one
type of unconsciousness. All right. Now
if you can understand in this way as we
discussed last night is your time
that let us say if you feel you do not
know something
consciously and that you do know it
unconsciously you would say it is in
that sense unconscious
knowingness. If you allow yourself to
balance the equation, put an equal sign
after that equation and reverse the
formula on the other side, then you will
understand that what is also equal to
the idea of unconscious knowingness is
conscious unknowingness, which means you are
unknowingness, which means you are
choosing not to know.
Therefore, if you find that you have
unconscious knowingness and not conscious
knowingness and not conscious
knowingness, then recognize you have
conscious unknowingness, which means you are
unknowingness, which means you are
consciously choosing to not know in the
present. Allow those ideas to be blended
and balanced and you will find yourself
to be at the center of both creations.
You yourself are the equal sign. You
yourself are the crux point, the
crossover point of the infinity symbol
between the microcosm and the macrocosm.
That is why the infinity symbol has that
shape. You are at the crossroads of all
ideas without time, without faith in the
now moment in which the microcosm folds
back upon itself to go through you. The
equal sign to balance out and create the
macrocosm on the other side which folds
back into its out and goes back through
you to create the microcosm and infin
item. Allow the ideas of the future you and
Allow the ideas of the future you and
the past you to blend within the
understanding that you are the equality
and are the creation of both ideas. And
in that way as you allow yourself to
exist within the center of your being
within any experience that you have that
willingness to know will allow you to
experience whatever judgment remains as
quickly as you possibly can and you will
acclimate to the energy to follow me.
Yes. Is it the understanding that
whatever judgment has remained is
working itself out? Of course. Of course
it is. And I'm curious about why
I don't know why I'm curious or drawn to
it, but that it is in conscious
unknownness. And I have conscious
questions saying, "What is it that
caused me to feel pain that way? What
can I do to stop that skill change? Is
it I am feeling also understand that all
of those ideas in the perspective you
are creating are also remnants of the
habit and they will change as well. The
more you allow yourself to simply be no
matter what you choose to be, the more
you will allow yourself to continue to
simply be and you will be an answer not a
be and you will be an answer not a
question.
following. Thank you, Michelle. Good. I'm having
Thank you, Michelle. Good. I'm having
confusion with Good. Yes, I think so
too. With the notions of acceleration,
time and timing. All right. Why is there
I understand why the construct of time.
I'm ready to let go of that one. Timing
is simply the event you choose to
experience. Why must there be timing at
all? Because it canotes some sense of
time. No. To me, time is subject to
timing, not the other way around. Timing
is the higher self function. The
knowingness of the event of the
relationship that you are, that is
timing. When all the factors come
together and attract themselves to form
an
event, how you choose to view the event
determines what type of time it takes to
experience the event within a lot of
time, a little time, good time, bad
time. You follow me? Yes. It seems
though as as if
I'm floating along in what feels like a
fourth density idea and then I'll find
myself back in my habitual ritual and it
seems as if I've used time in order to
get back to the habitual ritual and I
want to know why I bother to do that. It
seems like it's timing that in a sense
you can be creating the idea that if you
are judging that you should be going
faster than you are then it is the
timing that in a sense will allow
you to allow everything else to catch
up. Yeah. You follow me? Yes I do. Thank
you. But it is the sense of feeling like
you must rush ahead that creates the
type of time to allow the timing to
occur that perhaps you do not enjoy.
Step one.
Now in this way recognize also simply
that timing is the idea of the events you
timing is the idea of the events you
chose to be in this life. They are in
your terms, as we have said many times,
the idea of your dates with
destiny. You cannot by definition miss
them. You follow me? Yes, I do. Therefore,
You follow me? Yes, I do. Therefore,
relax and enjoy exactly where you are
because exactly where you are in the now
moment is exactly what is going to get
you to where you want to be. I
understand. Thank you. Thank you. When
you were describing the when you were
describing the infinity symbol, you used
the word you. Which of our many selves
were you referring to by that word?
Thank you. All of you. But specifically
because in this sense we are talking
about the physiological manifestation of
what you perceive to be the physical
universe microcosm and macrocosm. I was
specifically referring also to the
physical expression of yourself to allow
yourself to know that if you know the
physical expression of yourself is also
at the center of the physical universe
then it is also aligned with the center
of the you on every level which is
always at the center of beingness.
Did you follow that? I did follow it.
I'm but I'm still grappling with this
other conceptual framework that I'm
trying to figure out how to integrate it
to this larger understanding. I Perhaps
you are creating it to be more complex
than it needs to be. Understand that all
you really need to do is to continue to
live your life and do what you enjoy.
No, I understand that. But conceptually,
the kind of concept that you're saying
you are at the center of everything says
to me, oh, you mean the oversoul.
That is true for every level.
Now, now always has been. We're just quick.
now always has been. We're just quick.
You see, it seems to me that a
physiological personality doesn't have
normally the people you meet on planet
Earth here don't have the level of
awareness and understanding and it does
not mean anything whether the
physiological personality is aware of
its creator or not. It is still the
creator of the physical universe that it
perceives. My conceptual framework that I've been
My conceptual framework that I've been
operating with is that it's the it's the
and I didn't see that there were I mean
I didn't understand that there were all
these different levels. It was just
oversoul physiological personality
nothing in between. So my conceptual
framework was it's the oversoul that is
the creator. The physiological
personality is just sort of like a
puppet. Let us say this no not really.
The oversoul is the creator of the
concept of physical reality. The
physiological consciousness is the
creator of the experiential physical
reality. In other words, the physical
consciousness fleshes out so to speak
the physical concept the oversoul
creates. The oversoul creates the idea that there
The oversoul creates the idea that there
can even be the concept physical
reality. But to the oversoul it is only
a concept. What gives it solidity is the
consciousness of the mythical
consciousness. And what relationship is
there between I as an oversoul whatever that
between I as an oversoul whatever that
is and I as this physiological person
that's the relationship in a sense again
you can simply view if you wish to view
it in this way that the physiological
personality is a creation of the
oversoul but also its own creator its
own free will is manifestable in
physical reality. ity. In other words,
the oversoul has created the physical I
I
concept that the physiological creator
will experience that helps a lot and other
experience that helps a lot and other
people have questions. I didn't grapple
with it. Right. Yes. Um I had a dream
which I would like to share with you
which seemed to in some way partake of a
lot of the things that were said here
tonight. All right. and see I would like
to comment on okay I'm in a room and in
the next room there's a young boy at the
blackboard and on the blackboard using
just the number one he is showing the
many different ways that you can express
oneness with just using one he begins to
list a whole bunch of things he shows
one he shows square root of one right 1
* 1 and 1 / 1 and 1 2 and so
There's a lot packed into that that I
would like to know more about. More you
wish to separate from the oneness.
I am I I experience myself as separated
from the oneness and I am the idea of
moving toward the oneness of becoming of
being oneness. If you say
so. Do you
know that you are the little boy? Do you
know you are the wonder in the dream?
Uh I know in the little boy I
in the dream you are the boy. You are
the chalk. You are the chalkboard. You
are all the ones on the chalkboard. You
are the room the chalkboard is in. You
are the entire interaction and event of
the boy writing on the chalkboard.
Therefore, you are the oneness that can
experience itself as the fragmentation
of all the different symbols, let us say
props that you have created to create
the scenario of oneness. But you also
understand that because you are also the
dream, you are also not only all of the
props that go into making up the dream,
but you are the dream itself. So, you
are at the same time not the idea of
needing to be this or that, but you are
this and that. You are both all of the
pieces and the oneness that all the
pieces express.
This dream occurs now at the eyes of
March and it seems that it's related to
that. Of course, as we said, that idea
of that date symbolically for you
represents a doorway, an elevation, an
acceleration of the momentum of the
consciousness of your entire
civilization. Therefore, it is not
surprising in this way that many you
have experienced openings in that sense,
in whatever form your consciousness saw
fit in whatever form your physiological
consciousness was comfortable in forming
to recognize the oneness that you
are and allow you to see the integration
in whatever terms you would find it
acceptable. So as you are saying these things and
So as you are saying these things and
I'm creating the imagery as you say them
I see the possibility of moving all
these props into blending into a
oneness. All right. But understand that
all the props are already a
oneness as
well. Understand that all that is knows itself
Understand that all that is knows itself
as a oneness and also knows itself as a
combination of all the individuality
within it. To all that is there is no
dichotomy, no contradiction in knowing
itself as oneness in that way. It does
not force all the pieces to merge
together in an unrecognizable fashion
for it to recognize its own oneness. It
recognizes its own oneness in the
infinite diversity within
itself. So the the the all that there is
that's doing it that you
said as I am dreaming it then the all
that is aspect of myself which is one of
the top of the ladder that you just
described a bit ago is
function function there. Yes. Perhaps
what you are calling in your
civilization the confusion comes from
this idea. Perhaps you have the notion
that as you allow yourself to recognize
oneness, you will somehow not recognize
all the pieces anymore. And that is not
the
case. It is in the granting of validity
and complete recognition to the infinite
diversity within creation that allows
you to create the sense of the oneness
it all goes into making up.
In your term in a sense you can look at
it
scientistically
always the idea of what you call synergy
on your planet that the whole is greater
than the sum of the
parts. In other words you have the
parts. You can recognize how working
together they form the idea of a whole.
And in this way you can look at it
simply in that way and you can also
recognize that because you can look at
it in a sense also as the unit it forms
in addition to the functioning of its
parts. And you recognize that it has
oneness intrinsically in and of itself. And
intrinsically in and of itself. And
without the parts there would not be the
oneness. And without the oneness there
would not be the
parts. Both of them are necessary to
have the oneness and to have the parts.
It is not going to be a this or that
scenario. It is going to be a this and
that scenario. Each higher density does
not eliminate the density it has been.
It contains
it. It adds it to the understanding of
itself. It validates completely all it
has ever
been and recognizes therefore that it is
in the recognition of all the
individuality it has experienced that it
will allow itself to know itself as the
oneness that embraces all of that
individuality. Is this clarifying the
idea at all? Yes. Thank you. for you.
You then you when you
mention you put out but what's happening
when you say is that somehow related
to us? If you wish in that way to make
that analogy, you lay.
Okay. So that so that and in this way
recognize that not every being upon your
planet pronounces it.
So that the the sinuses actually
represent my language.
You may also in this way if you wish to
be symbolic about it and you may look at
it in whatever way your imagination
created for you for that is valid for
you and attuned to your vibration also
as the idea that every single component
that goes into making up the sum which
becomes greater in this way is a symbol
a sign. Therefore the idea is sign
energy if you
wish. The energy of all the signs go
into making up the action that is the
oneness of all the components.
Thank you guys. the the
actual location, right?
location, right?
First of all, the first idea.
Oh, yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
It is quite normal. And uh
And uh
also quite bubbly. your normal everyday
moment by moment activity
um full of laughter.
It is made of
love. It is made of
ecstasy. Therefore, all the effects of
everything that we do is always going to
be an act of
love. Always will be centering in that
way and therefore always expressed
joyfully. Your expression is going to be
manifest to a degree. Although we do not
have exactly the form you call painting
in exactly the same way that you do, but
we have similar ideas. Yes.
Most of your
time that we understand.
Um but Um,
all of it.
Most of it. All of it. Okay.
What we call an ecstatic explosion of
coincidence.
Not only physically.
Okay. Energetic. Okay. Energetic. We
ought to embrace continuously
energetically have that experience
of rather than separating. Okay.
Are you familiar
with our perception of the terminology
is a recognition of a state of being.
But the actual term does not exist
within the physiological channel
vocabulary. What do you find? Chaos is
another place in another galaxy which
has very similar
um
all right. Now understand in this way
again we will usually recognize as we
have said most places like that as
states of being but in this way also
recognize there are many many many
many civilizations within our own galaxy
that also exist that way.
Do you feel your feminineness and your
masculine male aspect and your female
aspect are all conscious? Yes. When you
embrace each other's femaleeness and
male and acknowledge it and is that part
of the manifestation of
okay that is obvious by definition.
If there is one myth, there is obviously
blending of any idea of polarity within
the being. Now, planet Earth is sticking
to the concept of
activity. What how would you best
describe what you do? Because I can't
use the word activity that is not in
your terms a word that really is let us
say so far off the mark. We are always
simply creation, action, act of doing.
Therefore, activity in this way is not
really a term that will be so very
different from our
civilization. Now, do you mean activity
in a negative sense? No, I mean
activities um for example,
we do not so much sleep as we are living
our dreams and there is not so much
separation between the physical and the
non-physical reality. The alignment to
your higher self in the non-physical
reality is the majority of the reason
why you think you need
sleep. Say that again. What you call
sleep is more simply a time allowing an
alignment from the physical level to the
non-physical level so that you will
allow yourself the opportunity to
sustain in that sense the physiological
energy. But it is not so much the idea
itself of the act of sleep per se, the
physiological act of sleep that
replenishes the physical form. It is
being in touch with your higher self
that does it. So the more in alignment
we become with our higher self, the less
um what would a typical day be like?
You will find there will be opportunity
in this way to share with many
civilizations what I am sharing with
you. Now first of all you follow me.
This in your vernacular let us say is
one of my choices. If you wish to call
it a job all right but there is no
negative connotation in this sense. Although I
connotation in this sense. Although I
will find myself immersed in many ideas
having to do with what you may call in
your civilization in your vocabulary
technical
engineering. You follow
me? Also there will be sharing in
various forms of activity with many
different beings. There will be sharing of
beings. There will be sharing of
experience.
There will be manifestations of love in
various forms. Whether it is in the idea
of simply what you may call
interpersonal relations or the idea of
expression in what you may call
part that will be usually
difficult. There will be also
exploration of many different areas of
spaceime and some other alternate
dimensions of reality.
Will that have answered your question?
It answers. All right. So, I'd like to
get a sense of what it's like to live a
new. Then allow yourself to know that
you are the very same type of being. And
if you can perceive that type of energy,
simply live that way on your own planet.
And then you will be allowing your
energy to reflect to all other beings on
your planet that they can also choose to
live that way. And then your planet will
also live in exodus.
Okay? If you wish to see anything on
your own planet change, change yourself
first. Become and act like the reality
you desire.
All right. Okay. Now this is a
very do you have habitat do you live in
or do you create from time to time there
are structures they will be more
malleable than your own and they will
from time to time serve purposes but
they will in this way be relatively
sparse as you would say upon our planet
the majority of the surface of our
planet in this way will not be in your
terms artificially built up but will be
very parklike. You will also find that
at any given time so to speak fully
twothirds of our population will usually
be in spacecraft and not upon the
surface of the planet.
Anyway at
[Music] basically yes you would be able in your
basically yes you would be able in your
terms with a very slight adjustment to
live in our space
and on this planet. Yes.
And you manifest at will.
In what sense do you mean that? You
manifest whatever your thoughts want. In
other words, evolving you wanted
exhabitat and then thinking we are the
ecstatic explosion of coincidence.
Whatever idea we know ourselves to be,
our physical reality will reflect by the
interactions of all the other
individuals and situations and
circumstances within it quite
automatically. Obviously yours is too. But you have
Obviously yours is too. But you have
become Yes.
You are becoming conscious of it. And
that is why many of you have begun to
experience physiological synchronicities
more and more and more of it.
Yes. We
We
can do it all. Yes. What's your name?
favorite. I do not have a favorite. You
like the moment. What I am doing in the
moment is my favorite. In the next
moment, that is my favorite. Otherwise,
I would not be doing it. Okay. You
require food as in no food. Very very
sparsely and it is not exactly like you
understand food anymore at all. It is
more of a symbol and it is mostly energy
absorption in a sense.
Uh do you hear food directly? Do you
process it in any way?
No, direct.
Um
you manifest your food. Yes.
Very good.
good.
simply by thinking in a sense as we
would say what we call the primary
example of our sustenance is a creation
of the mass mentality of our
planet. It was brought into existence by
our understanding. But you could
actually have to have your physiological
forms go out and pull something out of
the ground or it grows in a sense as a
natural idea as a natural what you would
perceive as a let us say fruit vegetable
combination idea but again we are at the
stage in our civilization where we are
also beginning to not need that tool as
well. In in involving your physical
manifestation, do you feel the bone
expressing in an overall agreed upon sense? Yes. Do
in an overall agreed upon sense? Yes. Do
you as an individual know when you are?
Do you mean within my individual life?
Yes. Not so much in the realm of time, but
Not so much in the realm of time, but
within the realm of timing. Yes.
Um, have obviously you've already chosen
when you're going to trans. You're not
quite clear exactly when that's going to
be. There is no need for the clarity of
when. What is clear is why and that is
what the timing is.
That would be file.
Yes.
Um there's a lot more questions but this
has been very nice.
Thank you for an introduction into the
unique expression of all that is that
you happen to be. Thank you. Thank you.
Last night I think it was last night you
said that you people do not go
that you people do not go
through repeated physical physiological
reincarnation in the way that we're
doing on earth. We have had and to some
degree to some degree some individuals
maintain that idea simply it is more
conscious than what you have created. It
is a clear choice to do so for specific
reasons that are still manifesting
positively and do not create the need to
do it but simply it is done out of
conscious choice. So the majority of
your population, your civilization
continues to do it out of conscious
choice in order to maintain a tow hold
if you will in physical reality in order
to be able to communicate with people
like it is our joyous choice.
Another thing you said about
reincarnation, he said that the corpuses
for dolphins are the only other
physiological form that goes through uh
repeated reincarnation. No, no, no, no,
no, no. All life on your planet reincarnates
no. All life on your planet reincarnates
in that sense. But what you call the
dolphins has created like you as the
only other species to have karmic
reincarnation. What is the difference?
Simply that which you understand to be
the animal life forms that reincarnate
do so on a completely knowing level.
They do not create the idea of the
separation so much that you have created
to think you are in a cycle that you
cannot get out of. Now the dolphins in
that way are not exactly recognizing
that idea to the same extent but they
are similar to what we have just
described to you with regard to our
civilization tied to you in that way and
so make the choice to have a karmic tie
with you and reincarnate because of
that. In other words, simply look at the
dolphins as water humans.
You mean so bears and lions and
giraffes are continuing? I mean one
giraffe body dies and the consciousness
of that giraffe body goes and picks up
another giraffe in a sense. Okay. And in
this way it is a part of the flow of the
consciousness of the cycles you have
created but they are only reflecting
what you as the cocreating species upon
your planet have chosen to create your
planet to be. You are interacting with
the dolphins and they are interacting
with you as water human and land human.
Okay. But then do giraffes and cats and
dogs and lions have those different
levels? You know they do they have
astral bodies and appear and cause? Yes
in a sense again. But understand they
are this expression in the knowingness
of consciousness. They do not need to
think about themselves.
You think about yourselves. So do it
also. Does that mean that we are worse
off than to ask?
No. Are we more spiritually evolved or
less spiritually evolved? Let me put it
this way. Only
way. Only
you only you think of the idea of
spiritual evolution.
They are what they are and that is all
they need to know. They are not less or
more. You have the ability to choose to
think that you can be less or more. Why
do you bother?
Because you choose as the creator which
you create all that you can create. Then
why would you create first? Because you
can. Because it is an experience that
you can have. Understand there is no
judgment about
about
us. But in the the larger perspective,
we're going through a transformation
from third to fourth density.
What density are animals? They will in a
sense go with you, but they go with you
as reflections.
They will reflect your attitude. In
other words, as we have said, the
animals upon your planet are territorial
because you are. The animals on our
planet are not territorial. What do you
mean territorial? They do not lay claim
to sections of
land. They transpire and transverse
wherever they will according to whatever
climate they appreciate in that way. And
they are not in a sense now at this time
on our planet basically predatory. They
are symbiotic.
They reinforce each other as we
reinforce each other within our society.
As long as you fight each other, your
animals fight each other to reflect that
idea to you. They are reflections. They
are guides. They are extensions of your
creator consciousness in a very loving
fashion to give you something to relate
to as your natural automatic self. Okay,
I can understand that humans and all the
animals are simply fragments of an
entire planetary consciousness. Is that
what you're saying? The animals and what
you call nature in that way are
fragments and the humans in that sense
are also fragments but they are the
fragments that also created all the
other fragments.
When you say human though, are you once
again human? Which of the levels of uh that
human? Which of the levels of uh that
you spoke of before are you referring to
merely the physiological, the oversoul,
somewhere in
between? All right. How about this? Let us
Let us
say on the oversoul level you
are for the sake of
definition relatively
homogeneous. You project a particular
idea of yourself to create the idea of a
fragment in physical form. let us say
with some of the remaining material that
does not specifically
focus into the human
into the human
form then out of that remaining
homogeneousness there is the assignment
placed upon that homogeneous energy that
it can become a physiological reflection
according to how the physiological human
needs to see it reflected. So that is
animal mineral vegetable consciousness.
The impregnation of it into physiological
impregnation of it into physiological
form then comes
from let us say the higher self which is
a more rarified let us say perhaps the
astral self to make it clearer form of
the human form and it chooses the idea
to create the impression of whatever
forms in nature are needed to reflect
the particular human manifestation that
has been interjected into the physical
reality. Okay. Put it in an earlier session you
Okay. Put it in an earlier session you
spoke of in evolution through density.
First there was minerals and then there
was plants in a sense. Yes. But this is
something that has nothing to do with
intimate reincarnational cycles. Evolution cycles
reincarnational cycles. Evolution cycles
of the soul and reincarnation cycles of
the soul are two different concepts.
Well, could you help me understand how
they're different in simply you will
find that there are opportunities for
the idea of consciousness to fashion
itself in many different ways in many
different densities. You can have
consciousness that expresses itself as
the idea of mineralness and it may
create the idea of an advancement to
vegetable and animal in this way and in
a sense to a human form
expression. But within each evolutionary
stage there is then within that stage
reincarnation only as the same thing.
Basically mineral mineral mineral
mineral mineral yes vegetable vegetable
vegetable animal animal
human with some idea again of what you
call two man dolphin interaction since
you are both in the overall sense human
possibility of inner species dolphins
are human in some way not so much in the
physiological sense no but in the
consciousness we're talking about body
but not talking not speaking
physiologically or communicating
physiolog. Oh, you can
communicate in this way simply not
reproduce physiologically.
I know that there have been people over
the years, the last 10 or 15 years,
there's been a great deal of 20 years
interest in communicating with the
dolphins that attempt to do that. Yes,
most of them have come. You are
awakening to the fact that they are your
brothers and sisters. And if you were
both let us say to use your term out of
your bodies, you would see each other as
the same kind of soul which is different
physiological forms. Not out of the
body. What? If you were both out of the body,
What? If you were both out of the body,
you would recognize each other as the
same kind of soul. They just happen to
have different physiological metaph.
So they are aliens to you. You are alien
to them but you are occupying the same
world. Is there some advice you could give us
Is there some advice you could give us
on how better to communicate with them?
They obviously
with your imagination but they actually
have a language a symbolic language.
Yeah. But in this way it is also a
physiological reflection of their
feelings and imagination more than the
idea of analytical thought as your
language is. How can I for instance
follow a dolphin feeling like okay there's a
a dolphin feeling like okay there's a
place where I've gotten to myself where
up to this last point up until this very
moment I have lost the
communication now I can feel more
channel then simply go and interact
now understand you can
create ideas and symbols in their
language and they will respond. What is
their language? The idea that you spoke
of physiologically.
What you perceive to be the clicks, the
whistles. You can learn to speak each
other's language to a certain extent.
Physiologically to a certain extent the
complexity of theirs to you will not
manifest in your mode exactly and the
complexity of yours to them will not
manifest exactly. You may create let us
say human dolphin
combination. If you wish to communicate
physiologically at all it can be done in
this way. You will still understand that
the basic fundamental understanding will
come from the telepathic and emotional
connection. There's a place where I tend to where
I can put so much emphasis on words. I
need you to hear words coming through
this channel that I think what about
what about
action? Do you not yourself say that
actions speak louder?
Well then
good for understand in this way. Let us
say if you wish to start off on your
best foot forward. You may simply always
feel free to begin by expressing
unconditional love to them. They will
respond. Thank you.
Thank you.
But your planet in our same galaxy, the
Milky Way. Yes. But not in your density
vibration. So So you cannot see it physiologically
So So you cannot see it physiologically
yet.
But at one time you said that if Well,
here's another thing. Can do you need to
make a shift to see yours? No. Do you
need to be in spaceship to travel
through space and time or could you just
man just pop just appear into the
something we are also learning. There
are civilizations that do that. What
disappear in physical form wherever you
want to be. But you still need to
travel. We recognize that the ship is
only an extension of our consciousness.
But in this way, we create that idea
again to serve many purposes. One of
them also simply because we enjoy the
idea and another simply because it gives
you something to relate to. Well, if you
were to come with your spaceship as you
suggested may be happening in the near
future. Yeah. Could we in our physical
form go on your spaceship, go to your
planet and see your planet? Yes.
Understand that there will be a shift in
density that will be made in the
journey. You will not know the
difference. You will simply think you
have gone into the ship, traveled and
stepped out and you are in the same
universe, but you are not. I mean, are
you taking us?
No. In this way, recognize that the idea
we have expressed many times is simply
that when your civilization is willing
to consider itself equal to all other
civilizations, then you will allow us to
meet you equally. As long as you
consider it to be something more,
something better, something more
spiritual than you have here, then you
yourself are allowing yourself to negate
the invitation. 2 are not functioning
equally with the idea of our
civilization. I understand it seems my
perception of
the speed of growth going on on earth
here that it's going to be 50 or maybe
that's 50 or 100 years before the planet
overall will be ready to do what you're
suggesting. Understand first of all in
our perception as it stands now which is
the only type of prediction that can
ever be made. Right? Simply our
perception is that by what you call
1,996 the majority of the population on
your planet will be aware that your
planet is in communication with other
planets and that will have an effect
that will accelerate your estimation.
That's good. But previously you
suggested that perhaps you or other
people would be arriving in Satia by
1996. Yes, I do. But if that's only
if understand what a difference that
idea can make, you can all literally
change in the flash of a second, right?
But I can understand that having the sky
on Earth littered with hundreds of
spaceships would cause a lot of rewiring
to go on. But that's the card before the
horse. One moment. Yes. The rewiring
will occur and then you will perceive
the ships that are already
there. Understand that around your
planet there are thousands of ships.
Are there people see those ships? some
from time to time because they move from
from Yes. Yes.
I know this has been asked of you the
last few nights, but I have to ask it.
It has never been asked before. Good.
Because you are you and you are a new
you and everything you ask is always a
new question. Thank you.
I I wish to refer to a being that seems
to be coming through me um and has
presented himself with the name Monoc.
I've been working with this person and
is this number two or three?
Three. That's what I mean. He's getting
busy. Very different. Um I've been
working with someone who evidently asked
about it Tuesday night and then someone
else asked about it last night. Okay.
What I am interested in is who is that?
Is that something? Our understanding for
now is the recognition of innocent an
oversoul that is beginning to awaken
consciousness within all of its
fragments. Plus, it's calling on everybody. Okay.
Plus, it's calling on everybody. Okay.
Everyone that it is in physical terms.
Well, then does that mean that the
people that I'm talking to about that
are counterparts to their counterparts
of myself?
Well, but the oversoul is myself and
that self and that self.
This it is one of the markers of the
beginning of the realization of the
synchronicity that can begin to occur
when the fragments of the physical
consciousness are willing to align with
the consciousness of the oversoul so
that it can manifest itself consciously
in physical terms. Conscious as all that
it is. Mhm. Do you have any idea of the
purpose of monarchy
to know itself? Oh well that's
everyone's perfect. Yes. Okay.
Understand again simply it is choosing
that symbolic formula to identify itself in
symbolic formula to identify itself in
that each and every fragment of itself
is one path in a sense one eye a monle
into physical reality. single sight.
single sight.
Okay. You are all of its
eyes. In the same way that every being
in
creation, every being, all beings are
all the different ways all that is has
of looking at it senses. You are simply
seeing this enacted out in a sense let
us say on a smaller scale one oversold
conscious manifestation
for sure I had a few months
ago had a being in energy form appear
twice within a period of a couple of
weeks and uh I had I felt
Why are you bringing this up now?
Well, it it was interesting to me that I
continue to forget about bringing it up
to you before to discuss it. All right.
I would seem to conveniently forget
about it. All right.
Uh and uh have you forgotten again? Yes.
Yes.
Continue. Anyway, this guy
Um, I had the feeling that I was being
both times pushed out of my physical
body and I was wondering if there was
any enlightenment. So once again, simply
understand that to some degree that is
accurate. But understand that all
assistance and all guides lure you to
yourself. So in a sense you were being
coached to do your own pushing.
No one else can push you. Right. I do
understand that. They can lure you to
push yourself. That is the function of a
guide. Right? So that all that you will
find will be your own selfmpowerment and
you will not rely on the empowerment of
someone else.
Right? Therefore, all that you are becoming is
Therefore, all that you are becoming is
allowing you to
align with more of yourself so that you
are beginning to recognize that you are
in communication with other types of
guides that are around you that coax you
and encourage you to
accelerate. Yet again,
use your imagination.
That is the doorway between your
physical and non-physical reality.
It is the channel. It is the translation
device specifically attuned to the
frequency that you are in both
directions. It is where the blending
occurs. In your imagination is where you
exist as the dimension of all that you
can be and
are. Uh a little bit more on that.
Uh was that a future
self? What you perceived as the
potential within the energy in a sense
was let us say that in terms of what you
felt to be assisting you part of it was
and part of it was not. But again, it is
our preference that these labels be
considered quite arbitrary. I understand
that. Thank you.
Thank you.
Sorry. In your
conversation, um, no one has
anyone or no one has ever experienced
temporary death.
There were, let us say in your
vernacular, times past when some forms
of the idea of separation were
experienced in what you would call our
history. But in this
way, and again, in no way, shape, or
form is this meant to be
judgmental in our civilization, simply
not to the extreme that your
civilization has chosen to create it. In
the now, no one can give experience of
now, no one can give experience of
separation. Correct. Except to the
extent that we choose to to be of
service to you and other consciousness
in
creation. And there is that type of
separation. Since we are in a sense in
fourth density physical reality, we
still do recognize some of the ideas of
separation to create a physical universe
from a non-physical one. But all the
manifestation, all the realization of
our separation is positive.
Oh no, no, no, no.
So understand in a sense to interact
with you, let us say, if you will allow
me to be colloquial for a minute, I have
had to create a model of all of the ways
you perceive your reality so that I
could understand you. Otherwise, many of
your concepts do not translate. And
And
also in the now
it is not a tool we need.
There is no
not as you understand it though.
So you're born as born in history. You
are born solving the conscious at this
time in our civilization.
Yes. And therefore we are in
communication with the souls before they
are born and are in positive
communication with them through the
entire process and on through life and
after. entering into.
There are two types of individuals upon
our planet. Those that we have called in
essentially the permanent
population and there are some natural forms in this
and there are some natural forms in this
way. One being what you call a Kia.
Look it up.
also refer to what you call to be the
ancient Egyptian civilization for they
utilized some of that substance in this
way and made blendings of it in that
sense.
Where can I be found?
Probably by those individuals who have
made it their business to find it.
You follow
me? You have what you call in your
society privilege.
Thank
you. They may also recommend two or
three other suggestions. Okay. Um,
Um,
we've come together
to communicate with you
and many other groups that have come up
here today and One of the things that I've
today and One of the things that I've
never heard someone
ask is what is it that we can do in our
coming together group? It has been asked
many times and you do it already.
[Music] Thank
Thank
you. Thank you. Coming in when? Coming
in April is now understandably that that
is an overall understanding but I will
give you a specific one. You have to
be. If you're willing to share who you
are, then you may be radiating like a
beacon the idea that will attract others
that are also radiating on similar
vibrations. And you will discover within
any group you are in all
that. And you will therefore be provided
a service to others by being who you are
and letting them know what is available
in your society.
You, each and every one of you have a
wealth of
information. The only reason you may not
know it is because you do not [Music]
[Music]
properly. Each and every being is a
reflection of each and every
being. When you are willing to share
what you are, what you know yourself to
be, you will then be giving another
individual an opportunity to
reflect the idea of what they represent
to you. And
you when you form your group, [Music] [Music]
My name
is If you wish an analogy in this way,
the situation has occurred many times
and does occur in our own
civilization. Simply there can be though
it is now more mental and simply known
in times past again the beginning of
this idea was simply for individuals
when they found themselves coming
together to simply state all the ideas
that they were and allow the connection
to and then they would go on about their
way
to I am the idea of I I am the idea of
this. Next, I am the idea of this. I am
the idea of this. Oh, my this and your
that plan. All right. Would you like to
do something about that? Yes, I would if
I segment of
conviction. The sharing
time I experience [Music]
Thank you. Thank you for viewing the
idea and thank you for sharing it with
us. [Music]
You guys in association many
times many times we are also working
with your higher and your mind your
future. [Music] [Music]
How about
about
understand in your vernacular
definition, an angel is a level of
conscious entity that has never
manifested itself in your understanding
of physical terms.
So recognize this. An angel has in a
sense not yet experience all there is to
experience. Please follow [Music]
[Music]
again. It is our perception that what
you are calling an angel is a form of
consciousness that is nonphysical and
has never
been. You have some idea where all of
that demolished associated with Christianity. It's
just created out of mind. Many times it
is the product of your
knowingness of all that is. And so when
you choose what you wish to relate to
and very often cloak the interminology
that reflects the separation you have
created upon your planet.
You may be in touch with understanding
innately, let us say unconsciously, that
there are such things as consciousness
that does not have a body and never has.
So you will cloak it in a form that is
fitting for the understanding at the
time it simply is understood.
thought it came from a time when the
only way you could understand it was to
give it some sort of ethereal nature and
give it
wings because you understood it was
unlimited. Above you in that sense and
therefore obviously the only thing above
you in the sky at that time was a
bird. It is a combination projection
symbology from your archetypal math
subconscious. [Music]
It is also a projection of
archetypal submass
consciousness. It is also some other
thing. It is also a recognition that
there are from time to time beings and
civilizations that do cross over from
one density to another in this way. and
explore and project yourself from time
to time in your own density. Also it is
projecting some signs of your own
consciousness that you quote in a manner
you can understand according to the
subconscious manifestation of your other
type of energy which is only an
expression of let us say that's part of
your naturalness that you simply are not
naturalness that you simply are not
conscious of of
[Music]
your qualify as an angel
by the definition. [Music]
[Music]
What you call ghost is an astral form.
More often than not, what you call poker
night phenomena
99.9% of the time will be extensions of
your own
[Music] energy. Okay. There are measures on our
energy. Okay. There are measures on our
planet relating to the fact that require
other civilization
living. It is not ignored density. It is
in a slightly shifted parallel reality.
But are they living
underground? But as you enter that
domain, you are not within what you
would consider to be your Earth
vibration any longer. even though
it okay but in their I understand it
would require a vibration shift to
perceive them in their reality they
perceive the idea that they inhabit the
interior of a life and that somebody
inhabit the exterior of the planet that
they inhabit some of them yes and do some of
inhabit some of them yes and do some of
them
so they have just as many multiple
parallel realities as you do so why are
they choosing to inhabit this of the
planet simply a reflection of the idea
that they are expressing the
civilization that
exists as opposed to that
[Music]
exist I don't really
[Music] understand in this way in a general
understand in this way in a general
sense I cannot give you
everything that might do so but you may
understand that there is been externally
on the surface of your planet. Then you
have an outward looking direction. They
have an inward looking one. Okay, they
are self contained. One other question
about um there
um there
is about the valley of the blue
moon which is either in the Himalayas or
book called and recently I just read a book
called and recently I just read a book
called display the value of the moon
in that is because those ideas exist in
both places. They are again other
density realities that touch your world
and there are doorways to them. So it
wouldn't be you might walk right through it and
be you might walk right through it and
never know it. So So a person could find
the wrong balance. Oh yes. But they
would have to have walked through it.
[Music] You can now understand that you're
You can now understand that you're
proving you all
time. All the doorways you walk through,
however, are expected by you to create
the type of reality that seems to be
continuous with the one you just left.
It does not have to be that way. And
sometimes it is not.
[Music] That is a slightly different
That is a slightly different
manifestation that is above all the
empty doorways we are talking about. I
am actually referring to the idea that
you have one type of physical reality
and that you can by shifting your
perspective actually walk into a
parallel physical reality that you
[Music]
believe. Again, it is really a matter of
the idea of what you believe of attitude
of perception of perspective of the idea
you are willing to leave. Again, many
times you will find that individuals who
do this may not even be consciously
aware they have done
so. Now you can be conscious of it first
and foremost because now the idea that
it might be possible is now in your
conscious reality. Now what you would do with that
reality. Now what you would do with that
idea is
[Music]
you obviously if you didn't it would be
otherwise you would have no reason to do
so. everything that you
do. Thank you.
There is always in a sense a way to a
portion of that possibility.
[Music]
They represent symbolically to us the
idea of the manifestation of our
blending from physical to non-physical
reality. So that we are becoming fourth
and fifth
density as you are becoming third and
fourth.
There is an aspect of it that is sixth
in this way. That is the one we relate
to. so that we can cause the interaction
between our fourth and their fifth to be
the fifth which we will occupy.
[Music]
Can we in this game recognize that
fourth density will be a physical
manifestation where you see through all
the illusions of the third density. You
will know yourself to be the greater
physical reality. Fifth density in this
game will be the experience of yourself
in non-physical reality. And there may
be many experiences that will seem to be
physical but you will know you are the
creator. You will be a thought form in a
world of thought forms in that sense.
And you may have some manifestation of
physicalness in the sense of what you
choose to create as an experience. But
you will know it is not physical in any
way, shape or form at all. The idea of
the fifth density will be to experience
yourself as the dimension that you
previously thought you were in as the
fifth density. You become the dimension
itself. And in this sense, the fifth
density will then view itself as many
dimensions, a multitude of
dimensions. It will view itself as
separated into the dimensional aspect.
Seventh density in that sense will
recognize itself as all the dimensions
that were previously experienced
separate portions of yourself as a [Music] six. Okay.
Now the idea simply was for the
experience and the expression of the
idea of the crystallization of yourself
and the gathering together of the idea
of your own transformation, your own
springtime, the idea that all the
seasonings are contained within you. And
as you create yourself to be the seed
from which the new you grows in that
sense, you will always know that the
potential of the totality of all you
will ever be is within every season that
you are at a
[Music]
moment. There will be a few more minutes
of your time frame remaining for the
interaction. [Music]
That is similar in the sense that it is
a dimension unto itself that contains,
as you have said, the totality of all
that you are. simply the concept of
being the past and the
future. It is at once your
potential and your real
[Music] ideas and your
[Music]
existence. It is the
cultural. It is the
Uh do you have a a
reality an awareness of the octave above
the octave that we are in? Only some.
What concept do you have?
Oata is what is called as we have
mentioned quasi plain reality. It is a
different phase of the understanding of
the entire seven levels that prize what
we share with you to be the idea of our
universe. It is another phase, another shift,
It is another phase, another shift,
another recognition, another aspect and
focus self. We only recognize at this time
self. We only recognize at this time
that within the next octave, there are
also magnitudes of what we call
11. Now, in this
way, there is not even in our
terminology the idea of a way to explain
this as of yet. I do understand that.
Thank you. Thank you. [Music]
[Music]
Okay. Our physical
body microbes or fungi or
viruses extensions of your
consciousness. They all are of course
there is nothing that is lost.
Therefore, we have the option to add and
move over and add. If you are not
attempting to get rid of them, but
acknowledge the purpose you have created
them to serve, then they will no longer
need to be there. If you are willing to
serve the purpose in another way, but
service you
will one way or another.
When you find out about what their
purpose is, your imagination and also by
acknowledging that the way you have
already manifested it is serving you is
showing you something. Accept and
acknowledge the light you have created
and then you will be able at your own
leisure with your own imagination to be
able to understand what the purpose is
for everything in your life. You will
allow yourself in relationship to your
physical life to become
clearance, clear. You will understand that the
clear. You will understand that the
tantality of all the symbols you have
created. That is one of the ideas of
fourth intensity to be able to see
through the event for the reasons that
they represent and then prefer and choose
represent and then prefer and choose
other ways that the same
purposes can be rather than in negative
pressure. But only by first acknowledging it that
But only by first acknowledging it that
you have created something to serve a
purpose. Will you allow yourself to
allow that symbol to transform into the [Music]
[Music]
next in this lifetime I
experience being separate from
other being located in a point of space
and time? Okay. independently of this
body and actually watching it for some
moment for that that in that moment I
was experiencing that you were experiencing
experiencing that you were experiencing
that type
of my experience of it was [Music]
[Music]
really and that that is part of the
experience of what you
call dead
located anywhere in space independently
of any particular physical correct and
has perception like
body correct correct
extend our
joy at your believer to interact with
this way and share of your with us so
that we may receive from you the gifts
of experiencing the consciousness you
have chosen to be so that we may learn
all the different ways that all that is
has of expressing itself in nature. We
thank you for your gift. We thank you
for allowing us to share the idea that
you are. We are sharing that forever
now. We b
you with you.
[Music]
Thank you so much.