for the beginning of your time is to
create time to exist.
In this way, we will continue our
interaction with the reminder. Thus,
when we discuss with you any ideas, when
you allow yourself to fathom and
interact and perceive any ideas, whether
they be in the form of a statement to
yourself, a conviction of yourself or a
question from yourself in that way,
allow yourself to remember that because
you have for tens of thousands of years
formed the idea of separation. Many
times when you are dealing as you say
with a certain idea, certain aspect, a
certain question in your life, the
separation you are used to may allow you
to look at one way to deal with it, two,
maybe three ways to deal with it. But
allow yourself to remember that all we
have ever discussed is applicable. All
we have ever shared with you is
applicable to each and every situation.
For every situation has many
facets. And you may discover for
yourself if you are willing to remember
and put together as a total concept
every single point of view and direction
that we have been allowed by you to
approach a situation within our
dialogues with you. You will then not
restrict yourself to simply one way to
look at it. two ways, three ways,
four-way, but will give yourself through
the conviction and the usage and the
willingness to allow your imagination,
its free reign, the ability to apply as
many different points of view and
approaches to every single situation you
are willing to create in your life so
that you will not feel that there is any
isolated pattern or process that is
being kept hidden from you. Simply allow
yourself when you consider any
particular idea to remember all the
different ideas we have discussed with
you so that you can apply them all at
once in a blended fashion to the
situation so that the situation will
touch and will allow itself to be
touched by any one of those points of
view that applies immediately to the
situation you are creating. Are you
following along? Yes.
The irreging belief is that when we
communicate with here, we communicate on
many different levels at once. Whether
you are conscious of it or not, allow
yourself the opportunity to recognize
that no matter when we are discussing
one of the things that we have discussed
with you, we are at the same time
simultaneously discussing all of the
things we have ever discussed with you
on all the different levels on which you
have created yourself to exist. The only
reason you do not perceive them all at
once is because you create yourself to
exist on all these different levels. So
it is upon levels that we create our
interaction with you so that you can
receive them no matter in what form you
have fractionated yourself. You follow
[Music] me? Sure.
me? Sure.
You the new um in a few hours at about
4:46 in the morning the moon will be
sold and it's no moon that is celebrated
has been a focus point of the festival.
I see um and it is said that Buddha
comes through comes down into the
physical for minutes at this
time. Um how do you perceive this? have
disturbed by it and um it's
insignificant in the fact that 3 minutes
before the moon at 4:43 there's a you
will have an eclipse. Yes. Recognize in
this way the idea simply is is that what
you have established your lunar body to
be is a representational symbol of your
subconscious of your unconscious
knowingness. And therefore when you draw
attention to it in that way by allowing
the shadow of your own planet to eclipse
it you are forming a more direct
relationship to the idea of receiving
energy from that symbol. It is only an
extension of your own consciousness in
another way and you are simply allowing
the idea of all that is contained within
you unconsciously to rise to the surface
so it can be experienced in that way.
This is why you also have the
understanding in your so-called
mythology of the idea of the full moon
bringing out the craziness within you.
For in that way, you have it within
yourself to understand that the fullness
of the moon will represent the fullness
of your willingness to communicate with
all those portions of yourself you have
for so long buried so deeply within all
the levels you have created. Therefore,
what the implication from our point of
view is is that when you are making a
conscious relationship with it, you are
recognizing your own ability to bring to
the surface all you have buried about
your own godhood, your own Buddhahood,
your own Christ consciousness, nature.
All those different ideas are brought to
the surface for you to experience and
create with as per your own imagination,
as per your own belief system. You
follow me?
Well, that have clarified the idea.
That's perfect. Thank you. Yours. Yes. I
have a three short topics that I'd like
to discuss with you. One of them has
something to do I heard a tape of Monday
a week ago where somebody asked you
about Daryl's channeling to the
civilization in Bernard star system.
Bard and I was wondering a couple of
things about it.
Daryl doesn't seem to be aware
consciously that he's doing it. Not of
the specifics. No, in the same way the
physical channel is not aware of the
specifics of the interaction that is
going on with you right now. All right,
I'm finished. In a general sense, there
is awareness in that way on whatever
level there needs to be. Now, uh
analogously to what extent are you aware
as you go through your own life when
it's on your spaceship? uh it has of our
communication with you. Yes, completely
you are. Yeah. So you're much more aware
of it than they of this communication.
Oh yes. For that is the definition of
our system. That's what I thought. I
just want to check the um just as a
matter of interest what do the people on
that star uh call battle the way we call
him? What do they call him? In this way
they do not have a differentiation for
each individual but they recognize all
individuals that are channeling through
individuals upon their system in their
language they call
ita it is a
processa all channeling in their system
is calleda they do not differentiate
identity so from that point of view they're
so from that point of view they're
closer to western in that they don't
label as much as we do in that sense yes
recognize not to be meant as a
denigration. But your particular system
is one of the most highly focused in
separation that we have encountered.
Yes, it serves your purpose and it serves
it serves your purpose and it serves
many purposes. Do not take it as
something that makes you less. For it is
out of your own strength and
self-empowerment that you have chosen to
have the strength to be able to
experience such a high degree of
limitation.
You follow me? Yes. Do many of us have
lives on that sto.
Okay. The second topic is when you
talked about the April event. You had
said that it would involve other
civilizations. Now I gather the April
event really was the attack on Libya in
a sense. Yes. Did it involve other
civilizations and to what extent? in a
way that we will be discussing with you
what you call the 28th, 29th and 30th of
this month. Put in that way, your 28th will
month. Put in that way, your 28th will
be a 10, which will be 1. Your 29th will
be 11, which is a two, and your 30th a
three. 1 2 3. We will explain the idea
of extraterrestrial relationship to all
of the predictions that have ever been
made about your civilization and what it
is going through. Thank you. The third
topic is again with respect to Libya, it
seems sort of a paradox that
um our attack in Libya was well without
judging was not what most of us would
have preferred. All right. That is why
you have done it and brought it to the
surface. as we have said is your
opportunity to bring what was previously
covert blatantly to the surface so that
you can determine for yourselves. This
is the time of making the decision. Do
you want that to be representative of
the world you are going to live in or
not? That's right. That's what I was
going to bring up. It is in a way a
paradox that we had to almost had to do
that for us to be able to see where the
choice is made. That has been your way.
You are not through with it yet
obviously. Okay. Thank you very much.
Thank you.
you the new vash. What happened to our
dinosaurs?
In this way, first of all, recognize
that in your terminology, strains of
them have, in your term, evolved into
many different fractions of animal
consciousness that still exist upon your
planet. Obviously, to your recognition,
the idea of what you call some of the
reptilian forms. Also, the birds in that
way are offshoots of the dinosaur as you
understand it. Your
understanding of the meteoric planetary
impact is basically correct. So that was
the destruction of the larger clones,
the trannosaurus, the bronosaurus was
meteoric impact. In this way, you will
find that not only was there a grand
climactic shift, but also and more
strongly felt an electromagnetic shift.
Understood. Were did we have
civilizations coexisting with the
dinosaurs at that period of time to some
degree though they are not directly
linked to what you would perceive to be
your immediate time frame linear
evolution. So in other words this the
type of humanoid existence that we're
familiar with now did not exist in third
density form at that time. Is that
correct? To some degree it did, but they do not
To some degree it did, but they do not
represent the immediate connections to
what you would consider to be your
civilization. Explain. I'm not quite
Explain. I'm not quite
other manifestations off of your planet
and from other dimensional experiences
of your own planet in many different
ways. In a sense, what you might call
proto civilizations to your own, but not
directly connected to your linear
history. in a sense I see or visits from
other civilizations and dementia at okay
what was the period of time that and
duration of the existence of major
dinosaurs several hundred million years as you
several hundred million years as you
count time ago or duration both okay
very good one other completely uh
different something I'd like to share an
experience that I had um a couple weeks
ago of feeling having an objective
feeling of the universe being projected
around me including my own body and
planet. The first fully objective
experience that I had. You mean
subjective? Um yes basically but it was
an actual feeling. It was tactile. I
could that is subjective.
Okay. What you are experiencing now is
objective. I object. Okay. Good. We have
terminology. I then went to um enact a
major shift in the projection and
encountered some resistance. Could you
help me understand that more? What type
of a major shift?
Um I was attempting to
um
change my relationships, my financial
condition, my relationships condition.
How by projecting by projecting
[Music]
um light the way I wanted to wanted it
to exist a certain type of environment.
Uh then did you proceed to act as if it
already existed that way?
I didn't pull it off.
Then simply understand the rate at which
you are pulling it off is exactly the
rate that is serving you. I understand.
When you allow yourself to view the way
your life is unfolding with regard to
that desire for the change, you will
recognize that there are many elements
within all the different scenarios and
situations and relationships that are
taking time that will enrich the idea of
when you have the reality that you
desire. Tasty recipe. Yes, you are
adding ingredients.
You follow me? I do. Thank you very Now
also understand that you are never never
going to reach a point where you will
feel that you have done all you can
imagine you want to do. Good. All right.
Then in this way recognize you're going
to have to watch so closely the idea of
your progress. For you cannot in taking
a reading or a measurement anywhere
along your lifeline truly truly be able
to measure how far you have come nor how
far you have to go. for in both
directions it is infinite.
Thank you. Thank you. One moment. Yes.
Yes. Okay. Two things. Number one, um I
have a lot of changes going on in my
life right now. Of course.
And one in particular um which is strong
in my focus is uh that I'm leaving a
job. I'm choosing to leave a job that
I've had for about seven years. All
right. Congratulations. Thank you. Um I
know I've been really comfortable there
and it's it served me in that time and
now um now you are a different idea.
Yes. And I also have a lot of fear
coming up choice. Um and so I'm What a
wonderful opportunity for you to
experience trust. Yes. Cuz in this job
that's gone so far it's like there's no
opportunity anymore in the job to
experience faith because it's just so
comfortable. I need to like, you know,
have a little risk involved here. If you
say so. Well, I mean, yeah, you're
right. Thank you. Yeah. Okay. Good.
Good. I I changed that idea.
Um, that is what trust is all about.
Good. Good. I like that. Okay. You will
create excitement. You will create
surprises. Yes. No risk. Right. Right.
Good. Good. Okay. That's that's good on
that word. Okay.
Um now uh also I found that when I
um instead of when I when I get out of
the the the the idea of what what this
fear is attached to the pictures and and
just get in touch with the emotion
itself. Nice. Then I find a lot of power
and uh trust in that. Okay, allow me to
remind each and every one of you that
every situation is fundamentally
neutral. You give it the meaning positive or
You give it the meaning positive or
negative. Every situation is
fundamentally neutral. No situation has
intrinsic meaning. It is only a circumstance.
meaning. It is only a circumstance.
You provide the meaning based upon your
point of view, your beliefs, your chosen
attitudes and that is what determines
the type of reality you experience. You
follow me? Oh yeah. Oh yeah. Um yes. I I
found that very interesting that and
when I'm afraid of leaving this job, I
get all these people at my job
reflecting the idea of what a great job
it is and how could I want to leave the
situation and look at all the vacation
time I have and stuff. And then when I
feel really strong in the idea of
leaving then I get reflected back people
saying it's great you know that you're
doing that and it's the perfect thing
for you to leave and you know yeah it's
very interesting the analogy that we
will have used recently of your time to
simply clarify a point will be the
recognition that you have upon your
planet the idea you call a train. Yes.
Mhm. individual will desire to be on a
train at a certain time will arrive at
what you call your station and will find
that the train has left. Now the
situation is simply that the train has
left and the individual is not on
it. It is neither good nor bad, positive
or negative. Right?
Depending upon how the individual
chooses to look at the situation will
determine the manifestations they allow
themselves to create in their lives. The
individual who chooses the negative
viewpoint will simply allow themselves
to create an ulcer worrying over the
fact that they have missed their train.
The individual who knows that they have
missed the train for a reason may turn
around and see a friend who has just
gotten off the train they haven't seen
in 10 years. And if they had gotten on
the train would not have met them. Mhm.
You follow me? Oh yeah. Yeah. Every
situation is fundamentally neutral.
Thank you. Thank you. One moment. You
are next. One more thing. Okay. I um had
an experience of channeling over the
weekend in my channeling class and then
afterwards I met with two other people
in my class that night. It was Saturday
night. I met with Lisa and Bruce. Okay.
And um and they both assisted me with
their entity with their channel and also
to work with my energy that I've been
working with that I call. All right. And
um
yeah. Do you have a a continue? This is a
Do you have a a continue? This is a
segue. Okay, never mind. Then I'll get
back to that if I feel like I want to.
Um what I was um feeling in this during
this channeling uh was this energy that
I used to feel when I was younger and I
felt at different times during the years
and I would notice I would stop that
energy because it
felt uncomfortable or it felt almost
like depression or maybe the depression
came from stopping the energy in a sense
from judging it. Aha cuz it's just a
different feeling. All depression is
meditation jugged.
So when I felt this energy again, this
time I just let it I let it flow. Nice.
I missed it. What happened? Something
funny. Great.
Um I'll ask somebody later. Okay. Simply
the idea is that what you are calling
depression is when you know you cannot
find the answers outside yourself, you
go to where you know they are within. It
is judged because your society tells you
that if you are not strong enough to
handle life, if you are antisocial by
withdrawing, then that is a bad thing.
It is a natural thing. And it only
becomes negative when you judge it.
Right now, this energy that I was
feeling, um, is there any can you tell
me anything about it, son?
Oh. Oh, okay. Hey, can you tell me anything
Oh, okay. Hey, can you tell me anything
anything more about Sancha? Anything
that would be of assistance to me at
this time? Sanchcha in our perception is
the fragment of your oversoul
consciousness that
represents your child energy and your
future energy blended into one concept.
Because when you were a child, you were
very much like you are going to be when
you are
older. Mhm.
Everyone attracts in general. Yes. But
you specifically in the specific ways
you allowed yourself to perceive many
different things outside of the normal
limitation. You will experience and are
experiencing those ideas. Again, sa is
also the energy of your own motherhood
to yourself.
And it is connected to other lives you
have had because you are making that
connection in that way. Yeah, it is a
loving guide, a loving spirit. It is a
representation of a portion of your
oversoul that has been differentiated to
allow you to relate to a certain portion
of yourself that you now are willing to
be comfortable with. Okay. Yeah. Because
I've come up with that name for last
year. I had an an experience of of an
Indian named Sancha. A female Indian.
And now I have a female future selfche.
I give it the same way. You are still in
many ways and
ways and
again not in a limited
way
choosing or shall I say continuing to
express portions of the agreement that
you made with your
twin for that is an identical pattern
that she has as well. an Indian past and
a future self with the same name of
Aaya. You follow me?
You follow me?
Sa it is a similar idea for the both of
you in your own terminologies in your
own ways
and she's having starting to open
upation with her. Okay. All right. Thank
Thank you very much. Yes, sir.
Hi. Hi.
I'm I also have a few questions to ask you.
I also have a few questions to ask you.
First off, um I have a cat Sandra and
around my cat runs around a young girl
who's got anywhere from 6 to 10 years
old, blonde hair. Um she's either
drowned or she's been in a car accident
and I think her name is Cindy. Can you
tell me a little bit about the Jew in my
house, please?
You mean in Spirit Falls?
Yes. Our immediate perception which we shall
Our immediate perception which we shall
remind you is only our
perception. Reminding you that yours is
just as
valid. Is that the idea of that spirit energy
yourself? Another individual who is male
in our perception and the cap were
together in one particular instance and
formed a bond, formed a pack, formed an
energy idea that
idea that
decreed that by all the
symbols that would represent
reflection and transition, you would
communicate with each other by drawing
the other's attention to that symbol, in
this case, the cat, which is a symbol in
your animal kingdom of the portion of
your consciousness that exists in third
and fourth density
simultaneously, as you are beginning to
do by being able to perceive a fourth
density entity. You follow me?
entity. You follow me?
Yeah, a little bit. All
right.
Now, journeys, journeys, journeys,
journeys. Our perception is that the basic
Our perception is that the basic
symbology is of a
child and the
animal beckoning you to follow on a
journey. A journey not only of your
imagination but perhaps of a physical
nature as
well in the life wherein you made the
path. You were in a sense journeymen,
travelers, merchants,
nomads. And in this way, it is one of
the symbols of
beckoning to a journey not only within
yourself, but within your
world. I like to ask my question. One
moment.
All right. Proceed. We will come back to
this idea. Okay. Um I've also I want to
know if these are kind of friends of
yours or if you know these um creatures.
Um I saw
Boenberry I saw Boenberry person the
color of a boenberry and he was wearing
a a gas mask. I think he had a teeth. He
was in my garage.
[Music] um um
really curious
um type fellow a friend of yours.
What type of feeling did the encounter
give you? I don't know. He just kind of
popped in and popped out.
What kind of feeling? I did not get a
feeling.
You will. Please forgive me if I say I
do not believe you.
The feeling is there. Reach into your
imagination and pull it out now. Okay.
I didn't like it. It scared me. Thank
you. You're welcome.
Okay. One more thing. We are not done.
Unless you choose to say we are. All
right. Now,
Why do you imagine that you created for
you? Um, it's startling. I guess I didn't
Um, it's startling. I guess I didn't
expect to see it. All right. And then
beyond that, what feelings did it
generate? Yeah. Yeah.
Maybe.
Did it allow you to think about your
life in a way differently than
previously? Yeah. How so? Cuz I love seeing his
Yeah. How so? Cuz I love seeing his
little things bopping around and I was
just kind of wondering if it was a
bobber, a new type
of thing.
All right. You have been encountering
these ideas for a lengthy period of time
in your life. Yeah. For how long? Oh,
um, since early teens.
You do not sound sure. Yes. No. Um,
yeah, I guess so. Why are you guessing?
Well, I
um Yes. I have been saying sometimes.
All
right. Does the idea matter to you that
you are seeing this? Why?
Because I like seeing weird things
flying around. Weird? Yeah. What do you
mean by that? Well, things that um are
not in our human form, color, shape. All
right. Why? Why? Yes. Why? We are asking
questions for a reason. Um how?
Understand while you are pondering that
it is basically from the premise that
there is no such thing in our point of
view as idle
curiosity. If you are asking if you are
creating those relationships it is for a
reason and it is per an agreement you
have made. We are in this way sharing
with you an opportunity to explore the
reasons for your own
cocreation while at the same time not
simply providing you with path answers
and living your life for
you. Now we are assuming that you are
co-creating these encounters so that you
can grow from the experience. In our
point of view, growing from the
experience is the degree of willingness
you are ready to have to come to
conscious recognition for why you are
co-creating the
experiences rather than just simply
saying, "Oh well, I was just curious."
There is no such thing as idle
curiosity. It is there for a reason. So
let us explore further if you are
willing. Now first of all in our
perception again the idea of
The berry
being will be something from a past
connection in another time
track. A message delivered at an
appropriate time from a past of your
creation so that you could now initiate
certain understandings, unlock certain
ideas within yourself now that you are
ready to hear
them. That is why the encounter was
brief. All that was necessary was for you. Now
All that was necessary was for you. Now
that you are in the so-called future
from when you made that projection, all
that was necessary is to encounter the
projection in the right place in the
right time as you have done so as to
unlock those portions of your
subconscious of your past self and bring
them to the surface.
Some of it, some of it is connected to
some of the energy that has been
described as Orion. Some of it.
Do you wish to continue? Um,
yeah. I've also come across some other
people. these um I don't know what kind
of where they're from, but they're um
kind of red clear red air and they speak
more like a high frequency.
Do they make you laugh? Yeah. A lot.
Yeah.
Our perception will be for
now although all labels we are imposing
are in a sense arbitrary but real on
their own terms. a civilization we have
referred to a few times that we call the
Dilla whose primary export is laughter.
laughter.
Now our perception of you is that you
have come into this life choosing to
function as a multiaceted crystal. And
so within each facet you are giving
yourself different reflections of all
the connections you are making and have
made to many different aspects of
yourself that exist in many different
realms and alternate dimensions of
experience. You are drawing all of these
together to form a
well-roundedness for yourself to give
yourself the energy and the opportunity
to know that you are drawing from all
the different directions you need to to
do what it is you desire to do in this
life. Are you doing what you desire to
do? Oh yeah. All
right. Then in this way simply recognize
you have given yourself a very
generalized theme in the sense of
allowing many of your avenues or
conduits of communication to many
different aspects of yourself that has
projected itself into all these
different dimensions of experience
access to information on whatever level
you need it so that you can simply draw
from it nonchalantly as you need it to
provide you with the opportunity to do
what you desire to do. As you accelerate
within what you are doing, you are
simply becoming more consciously aware
of all the conduits and connections you
have formed. It is not so much that
anything is so different. You are simply
becoming aware of the mechanism you
chose to create to come into this life
with to allow you to do what you chose
to
do. It is like stripping away the cover
and seeing the inner workings for the
first time. You follow me?
Will that suffice to have served? I got
one. All right. My dad died about 17
years ago and I want to get some answers
from him because that's going on now in
my life. Ask
him how
say dad
I am not being
facitious. Understand that consciousness is always
Understand that consciousness is always
right here right now. All time is now.
You follow me? Therefore, portion in a
sense aspects of his consciousness and
your consciousness are always together.
No matter what the definition of your
physiological state of
being, use your own imagination. That is
what it is for. It will provide you with
the ideas you need to hear
automatically. There is no need to
wonder whether or not it is accurate. It
is always
valid. You only create validity for
yourself. You cannot create anything
but. So when you create the interaction
in your imagination with the idea of the
identity of that portion of the soul you
call your father in that way allow
yourself to know that if you simply open
up your feelings the feelings are a
valid representation of all the
communication you need. But recognize
this. Any being that has projected
itself into the fourth density state of
non-physicalness and is functioning as a
spirit guide will only always lead you
into conversations with
yourself. You follow me? Therefore,
communicate with that aspect of yourself
that is the idea of your father and you
will be communicating with him.
All right. Thank you very much. No,
thank you very much.
Over here then there. Two unrelated
questions. The first time I've asked you
before, but I figured a way to ask it
differently. Oh, all right. Um, maybe I
have figured a way to answer it
differently. Right. That's what I'm
hoping. Hoping that may not get us very far.
Hoping that may not get us very far.
Continue.
Hubard claims that there was an event, a
catastrophic event that occurred on this
planet 75 million years ago. I've asked
you whether in your perception it
occurred. You said no. My question
specifically is I did not say
specifically, just no. Well, okay. In
general, the idea is a conglomerate one
for many different events of that
nature. Some of which are tied into that
time frame. Yes. But it covers far many
more time frames and time scales than
simply one event. I agree with you. But
did any any of those
events occur here on Earth? Yes.
Approximately 75 million years
in a sense. Yes. And many other times as
well. Prior to that and after and since
then. Yes. And on other planets. So
similar events.
Sort of.
Well, the event relates directly to
the fractionating. Yes. Yes. Yes. Right.
Yeah. Therefore, obviously others are
Therefore, obviously others are
involved. We simply say sort of because
they do not have the same viewpoint nor
experience of the idea.
But it but at least one or several of
those events occurred on this planet.
Yes. In physiological reality. Yes.
Okay. The other question has to do with
epsonic. Do your bodies have genitals as
I do. We have discussed this. Yes. And
you engage in sexual activity more or
less? Yes. For merely utilitarian have
babies or for the pleasure of
for sharing? Mhm. Okay. The reason I
asked that is because I have a memory of
um a civilization in which there were
bodies that did not have genitals, but
nevertheless participated in sexual
activity, but it was merely a specific
type of electrical energy that
interchanged in the body. There are
civilizations like that. You're you are
aware of some of them or one of them.
One is the serious civilization in sixth
density. But then but they don't have
physical form. Not really. But in a
sense they can project themselves in
that way. They are quasi planar and
would be perceived by you as having a
very ghostlike physical form.
I have a recollection of a civilization
that had bodies that were sort of more
like doll bodies. Although yes, there
are some of that nature in a sense as
well. But understand that what you are
doing is creating the recollection
according to what symbology will allow
you to understand the concept.
Okay. Okay.
For Mr. Sharp, uh I don't know a few
days or weeks or a couple weeks ago, I
guess, we had an explosion of a Titan
Titan missile. Nice. And I read that the
explosion was linked to O-rings, faulty
O-rings on the back as faulty O-rings
were supposedly the source of the
explosion of the uh shuttle. I'm
wondering what is the symbology of the
O-ring in these two
explosions. The idea, as we had to some
degree discussed before, that you will
find yourselves to be comprised of
components rather than viewing yourself
as seamless and unbreakable.
You follow me? I I understand. It is the
joining mechanism and it is a joining
mechanism that carries with it the
symbol of eternity, a circle. Oh, okay.
That's interesting. Another couple questions.
interesting. Another couple questions.
Uh, do people on your planet ever have
occasion to cry?
No. Okay. Did Did they do that in the past?
Okay. Did Did they do that in the past?
Yikes. Okay. Um, another
question. What? Well, the difference is they
What? Well, the difference is they
transform into the
parents. The idea is that when we
recognize that the idea of sorrow is
centering just as much as laughter is
centering, but from a negative rather
than a positive point of view. We
recognize they were much the same
idea. And so we preferred the laughter.
What about crying out of joy? You know
what I mean? It is much the same idea
and most of the no the joy in the sense
but it is also a releasing from things
in a sense that you still consider to be
somewhat negative.
[Music] One more question. I've had a tremendous
One more question. I've had a tremendous
attraction to the skies in the last
couple of weeks. And the other night, I
was looking at a craft that I believe
was an earthcraft. And then at one
instant, my attention was drawn as as
though my name were called, although
there was no u sensation of a name being
called, but the attraction of my
attention was such that it was
immediately to my left. I looked
directly at another craft which I
believe was a dirt craft. At least in
the form that I saw it, it was a dirt
craft. Was this what you call Sunday?
No, I believe it was Tuesday.
All right, continue. And I do know that
my attraction to the
skies does relate to other civilizations
and communication entities coming to me
from that. All right. I don't have a
real specific sense of that. It's just a
general on this. Yeah. But I'm wondering
with this this experience of my attention
this this experience of my attention
being attracted to an earth craft and it
was quite specific. Um was I thinking
that I was seeing an earth craft and I
was in fact seeing another craft,
extraterrestrial craft.
Not so specifically. Our perception of
what you are doing is beginning to open
doorways that can allow you to begin to
change your perceptions and begin to
recognize what
what
physical symbols in your reality may be
able to become may have connections to
in other dimensions of experience. Okay.
What you would call
a standin
for an idea. You are preparing yourself
to see more little later. You are
practicing with something familiar.
Follow me. I certainly do. Thank you.
Thank you. Louis,
I wanted to ask you about the idea of understanding
of understanding
exactly how everything fits together in
our lives at this level of our
consciousness. You mean trust?
You mean those two words
interchangeable? Yes.
So it's really is it really necessary
for us to understand
What is going on? It does not have to be
what you call an intellectual
understanding. No. Right. Because it
seems to me that it's quite beyond the
conscious level that you're at. Now,
parts of it can become conscious if that
serves the purpose of the path you trust
yourself to be. They will be there as
you need them to be there automatically.
But not everything needs to translate
into that conscious level for you to
allow it to continue to manifest and
reap the experience and the benefits of
your trust. Right? Which leads me to the
next thing I want to ask you today.
Our unfoldment mind that's what all
right call it is going to progress
regardless of our conscious
understanding of it in a sense. Yes.
What do you mean in a sense? You can
choose to create a scenario in which it
seems you are not progressing but in an
overall sense to the higher self it is
still learning something. So in that
sense it is still progress.
You follow me.
But I want to
thank you. Our enlighten our path of
enlightenment. Yeah. It's pretty much
could you say it's on it's an automatic
it's on automatic. Yes. Okay. This
entire idea of knowing that is allowing
yourself to become aware of the fact
that you have never been off your path.
Okay. So in that
sense interaction with your higher self.
Yay.
Uh I don't even know how to say it.
Interaction with your higher self is the
degree to which your physiological
consciousness is willing to trust that
the life it is experiencing is the
result of the choice made by the higher
self to have this experience and you can
trust that everything you are doing fits
into the path you chose to be. Right?
More even it is not that you are on the
path it is that you are a path and as we
have said you cannot be off yourself. to
to
accelerate uh your growth so to speak.
Yes. Would actually be a result of
pre-planning. Not really. It can be spontaneous.
Not really. It can be spontaneous.
Living in the moment, you can create the
illusion that it is
pre-planned. But even the idea of
creating a pre-planning is a spontaneous
creation. You are always in the now
moment, always new, you are always
creating spontaneously in that way.
Whether you are believing that it is a
plan that allows you to do so or not.
But we did make a plan before we came
here. Correct. only in the most general
terms. As we have discussed, there are
two types of free will. The free will of
the higher consciousness and the free
will of your physiological
consciousness. The free will of the
higher consciousness determine the
general concepts you would explore in
physical life. And to the physical
consciousness, those general terms will
seem like destiny or predestination, but
they are only in the most general terms.
The methodologies, all of the ways as to
how to experience those general concepts
is up to the creation of the
physiological consciousness here in
physical life. And you may do it in any
way, shape or form you desire to. As the
analogy we have used, the higher
consciousness will determine that you
will walk down a hallway in this life.
But it is only that general. How you
walk down a hallway is up to the
physiological consciousness to create
spontaneously in whatever way it chooses
to create it. Whether you decide to plan
to walk down the hallway or simply walk
down it encountering what you will
spontaneously, automatically
synchronistically, whether you run,
whether you go backwards, whether you
turn out the light, whether you crawl,
whether you swim, whether you stick to
the ceiling, it is up to you. The idea
is that you will go down that hallway.
How you go down it is up to your choice
here as the physiological free will
consciousness. Because to the higher
self, it is all learning.
Does that answer your question? Yeah.
Thank you.
You me? Yes. Then you
you were telling me I was telling you
about how I feel that I need to have a
car and a someplace to live. Some kind
of an you were telling me not really. So
maybe maybe I was wondering does that
mean that it's counterproductive to me
to look and I should just trust that
something will turn out. It is not
counterproductive for you can utilize
the experience to create the idea of
excitement. But do not put expectation
that it must manifest in the way you
think it
should. The idea simply is in that way
when you allow yourself to focus on what
it is you truly want to do, then your
energy will draw along with it all of
the things that need to get you there.
And if a car is one of them, you will
draw it right along automatically. The
idea simply is is that if you want the
car primarily because you think you need
a car to do something else that actually
represents where you are most excited,
then the idea of focusing on the car is
not putting your excitement where you
know it belongs. You follow me? Then you
are diverting yourself.
You follow me? I created a symbol for
myself where I'm playing with my friend
and she gave me a key to the house that
would not work. Oh my. I ended up I went
around the back of the house and it
turned out she had left one of her doors
unlocked and I got in the back. There
you are. So I thought that an expression
that there are many doors through which
these opportunities can come. Not the
one you expect to go through. Well, I
thought that that was a symbol to me
that anything that I try to do is not
the right thing. So you have chosen to
look at the neutral situation negatively
and I have chosen to look at it
positively. [Music]
[Music]
It was more not like a negative sort of
thing to me but just that um when you
say not right in your language that
means negative. Thank you. Thank you. It
was more an expression to me that trying
to do it in the direct way that like our
civilization would go out and get the
yellow pages or uh get a newspaper and
then start looking. That is not to say
that cannot work if that is what is a
reflection of the way you believe it
will work. But understand all we are
work. But understand all we are
suggesting is that there are many other
ways it can work. Do the one that is
reflective of the way you
believe it can and it will. If you know
that looking through your yellow pages
is not for you, then trust that your
imagination will do its job and provide
for you the methodology that is attuned
to your vibration. Follow
it. That is the alternate doorway that
you can go through.
You understand? Are you sure?
I'm never sure until I try to apply it
and see what happens. I see. May we
remind you that the idea is that
believing is seeing, not seeing is
believing. You follow me, thinking. Now,
one more
reminder. Trying is doing trying, not
doing the thing you are trying to
do. All right? And all the trying is not
what will allow you to do that thing.
doing it is what will allow you to do
it. And though you may think that all
the trying you have been doing is what
ultimately allows you to do it, in a
sense that is not so. You have been
utilizing that time to allow yourself to
become willing to simply do it.
[Music] You follow me? Thank you very much. Y
You follow me? Thank you very much. Y
then you [Music]
wa well well
I've been having a lot of fun lately
with Oh, thank you. Yeah, it's been Ben.
It still is. Oh, thank you.
With uh food. Food. I've been like
another one. All right.
Fun with food. Go ahead.
You hold that for your title.
The boys and Mary and this
continue.
I've been mainly I've been eating and
finding out about new kinds of food to
make and dance and a couple other
things. But that's the main different
ways to sustain yourself. All right.
Different ways to sustain whatever. Okay
guys, and
and
what this all fits in together. The
really big thing is I really like to
dance. I like to spend a lot of my time
dancing. And today my knees hurt and
like what I really wanted to do, like
what was really exciting was to turn on
the radio. Oh, and then what I really
want to do tonight is I want to go to
Forge and go western dance and take a
dance lesson. Nice. But I know if I do
that, I'm going to hurt my knees because
I I hurt them doing too much jump roping
about a month ago and then I got a
commission for dances in two weeks. So a
little bit bored. But is that because
you have not allowed yourself to
recognize an opportunity to do something
else? I don't want to do anything. It's
like All right. I mean I do. I mean
there's other things that when I had the
break there was other things I got into
the food thing which is really fun cuz I
eat. All right. But are your knees
hurting now? Yeah. All right. Just a
little. Just a little. Just a little.
Then dance a little.
And stop. Okay.
Now again, allow your physical reality
to be an obvious reflection of what you
are choosing to show yourself about some
portion of your personality, of your
identity, of your
consciousness. Is there many other ways
that this idea of this symbology can
serve you? Has your
imagination given you any other ideas
about why you have created that
particular symbol?
Um well one but I didn't really like it.
It's like so well so I didn't like it.
So what
what was it? But what it was is I
thought well maybe I shouldn't be doing
so much dancing. But then on the other
hand, I go, "Yeah, but that's what I
want to do." And it seems kind of
contradictory, you know, like I feel
like, well, maybe this is a time. May I
ask you a question?
Why do you? Because it's fun. And why
else? I like the interaction with the
people. All right. I enjoy the people a
lot. I I'm learning things about hanging
around a whole different type of people.
And I like it physically. It feels good.
I like uh being able to move my body in
music. All right. I I love country
western music. Is there any aspect about
what the dancing has allowed you to
discover that you do not like?
No. All right. Now, may I ask you
another question?
How would you feel if you never danced
again? [Music]
[Music]
Well, I don't think I'd like that. Why
not? Well, but he'll finally found a dance
Well, but he'll finally found a dance
partner. No,
no. I mean, I'm sure it would work out
fine because if I never dance again, it
would just lead me on to some other
opportunity. But right now, it's like
I'm getting good at this one particular
dance and I want to continue, you know.
Have you interacted with anyone about
what you would call physiological
therapy for your niece?
Um, no. I didn't really know the terms
of that kind of
you know there may be some beings here
that could suggest something for you.
Can somebody suggest something? Sure.
Yeah.
Yuggesting to the All right. Now
understand
this. What they will
suggest is a description of a process
that you are creating. It may not even
be so much that you must go to the
completion of their suggestion, but that
taking them up on that suggestion and
pursuing that particular idea may lead
you to an understanding and a discovery
about something that will relate to your
dancing that you can utilize. Yeah.
Yeah. You see, in this way, there is no
need to fight the idea that you must
force yourself through your so-called
adversity to continue to dance. Allow
yourself to have given yourself a symbol
to make the associations relative to
what you are creating for yourself and
to seek out sharing with other
individuals in other ways other than the
dancing that can enhance the dancing.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Well, I want to ask
you one more thing. This kind of fits in
with the food and All right. Um, I
changed my diet dramatically and it
really feels good.
And I I like I like the kind of food. I
mean, it's really I really like the
food. Oh, it's really I mean, I made
some great cornbread tonight.
All right. Very good corn. It was
delicious. Did you bring enough for
everybody? No, I ate all of it. I shared
some with some people at my house that
we
She is sharing it right now. Oh, it was
good.
All right. And
So, I had a feeling I had a bit of a
vitamin deficiency and I wasn't going to
ask anybody what what they thought or
get checked out on that because I
thought if I follow what I feel like
eating and what seemed right that you
know I would come across it. Yes. And I
I didn't know if it had anything to do
with my knees like maybe we fingers like
that about a month. Yes. The lotion
doesn't even No. And I wondered if you
perceive any particular vitamin or
mineral something
big. Have you completely excised what
you call dairy products from your diet?
Not completely, but that's something
I've been doing. I've been cutting out
the butter and the cheese. Today I had
butter on my toes, but for the most
part, that's a big
cheese. Our perception is that it does
have something to do with that. At the
same time, we also find that our
self-imposed restriction upon allowing
information to come out that would be an
interference in your process is in
effect, which means you are supposed to
talk to someone else. Okay? Talking to
that someone else will be a part of the
path you have chosen to be for you will
learn something else from them other
than just the dietary idea. They might
be a dance teacher would be or anything.
Yes. But let me when you were saying
that thing about dairy, were you in any
way implying that
I perhaps do need more of that or I
don't or were you just saying
perhaps there is a possibility
of what you call calcium or something
close to the idea that I would need more
of or
maybe our self-imposed limitation is
allowing this for us to be extremely
sketchy. Okay. Yeah, cuz I I had a
feeling about calcium, but I I didn't
want it from the dairy fac.
There is some other sources you can
allow yourself to draw from.
That is not our position, but the
position of the other individual. That
is the specifics we cannot share. Oh, I
see the other individual right now.
Okay. Thank you.
All right. I'm done.
you. Thank you. Thank you. God bless
you. I have a couple questions. Um, one
is
about 3 or 4 months ago, I experienced
an out-of body experience that I
remember very vividly. All right. And I
in fact have to admit I enjoyed it
tremendously. And what is wrong with
that? And did not wait. All right. And
you obviously made the choice to come
back. Here you are. Of course. Of
course. All right. um recognize that is
true. Of course. Of course. That is
indeed. All right.
And and when I was giving the
experience, the experience there was
um a figure coming in and it was like we
were going to start talking. Yes. And
the next thing I know I'm back in bed.
Right. Okay. And when I had asked later
about that experience, why did I have to
leave? Because the conversation was
done. Well, what I had gotten was that
my body was in danger.
Yes and no. And I was surprised by that.
So I wanted to ask only in the sense
that you were recognizing as was part of
the purpose of the conversation that you
had that fear within you. That was the
only danger. The recognition of that fear in
danger. The recognition of that fear in
a sense is what pulled you back. But
that was also the purpose of the
conversation to let you know you had it.
You follow me kind of. Yeah. You gave
yourself the opportunity to discover
through that conversation and through
the returning that you are dealing with
ideas connected to fearing to be in
physical reality for many different
reasons. Feeling that physical reality
somehow is more of a burden than the
idea of the spirit world. You follow me?
Yeah. Now in this way recognize as long
as you make that differentiation that is
what allows it for you to be perhaps
difficult to face the idea of coming
back but that is what makes it
imperative to come
back. You have chosen to be here for
many different reasons. Allow yourself
the opportunity to recognize you knew
what you were doing when you made that
choice and you still do know what you
are doing. And also physical reality and
spiritual reality are only different not
better and worse than each other. You
are a spirit right now right here in
physical terms. You follow me? That is
true. One of the ideas in the
conversation also was to begin to remove
the differentiation
between the created levels you have made
in your consciousness. So that by
recognizing yourself as one
consciousness, you can easily blend in a
sense back and forth between the
physical and the dream reality and begin
to live your dreams. Yeah. In a constant
dream, constantly awake.
Thank you on that. Thank you. I have
another question and that is
um one of my master's well I've been
told my master's name is um
Acatun and I'm also channeling um an
entity called Auna um
um
sound fishy to you
[Music] and I picked up on the correlation of
and I picked up on the correlation of
the two and I'd like to ask you about
Yeah. What about him?
Can you tell me anything about it?
Maybe. Oh, please. Will not do it. Um,
Um,
make a statement of
conviction. What is it to you?
I get a sense that the two well that we
are related. Continue.
And I would like to know more about that
and continue.
Um
I I don't know. Oh, come on. Please.
Reach into that imagination that is not
separate from you.
Make allow there to be one reality, one
dimension of imagination in which all is
real. Go ahead. One of the things I
would like to know
what why am I channeling a tuna and I I
understand to teach me a a part of
myself. All right. Okay. And the
openness of myself. But you know I is
that not enough?
I get a sense of more. Ah, you do. Then
describe it. If you get a sense of it,
you must know what it is. Otherwise, you
will not get a sense of it.
What is it? What is the
more is it being of service?
Yes.
How is of serving me and I am
serving? Well, it sounds corny, but I
get a sense of corny.
It's opening me myself up even more.
Yes. And allowing me to experience the
universe in greater depth. Yes.
And I still get a sense that somehow a
tuna and it's like they're connected. I
mean, I just and I don't I I have a
block on and I applaud. One moment. A
brief word once again about the idea of
blocks. A block is not a wall. It is a signpost
A block is not a wall. It is a signpost
telling you to move in an unexpected
direction. When you judge that that
unexpected direction does not fit into
the path you think you should be on or
stay on, that is when it becomes a wall
and seems like a block to force you left
or force you right to let you know that
going left or going right is the way to
go straight
ahead. Follow the sign. If it says turn
here, turn. You are only judging the
turn. You are only judging the
unexpected. That is all a block
is. You are judging the unexpected to
not be a part of the path you chose to
be. Trust. Trust.
Trust. Follow the direction the sign,
the wall, the block points you in.
Explore the idea of the block. For one,
if you find that you are blocked, you
are implying that the block is
preventing you from taking another step
on a path you think you should be
walking on. But the block is a part of
the path. Go into it and explore it. The
block itself is a part of the path. What
I interpret the block as being very um
close to heart. It's it's so close to
me. Um, it's like hitting me in the
solar plexus or whatever. That is the
chakra of your intentions
and the connection to your future self.
You wish you're not going to tell me
anything about we are discussing it.
Keep going.
This is
all predicated upon your willingness to
keep walking the path that you are. Then
we can share more and more details. But
only as long as you keep walking.
Okay, we are luring you to yourself.
Thank you. Thank you for the
opportunity. Continue. Well, one of the things I've
Continue. Well, one of the things I've
gotten about Altuna was that I was being
prepared. Yes. For a stronger energy.
Yes. Okay. Thank you. Continue. And I
wanted to know more about that. And I
You will obviously
as we have said, you are creating your
own destiny. Dates with destiny are
always on time. You will not miss them.
You will know everything you need to
know in any given moment to allow you to
function by definition within the
agreement you have made. Otherwise,
what's the purpose? Well, one of the
things is that I only channel Altuna
with very close friends. So because of
the vulnerability of channeling ah
vulnerability that means weakness. No
friends. Very good.
And I am my sense of I am just a baby in
the sense of taking the first step in
channeling. All right. And to do it in a
massive number of people would
not make me feel too good at this point.
All right. Um but I have been told that
I you understand of course that you are
in a sense channeling right now with a
lot of people around. Yes. And I and I
feel very vulnerable which means you
feel very strong. Yes. Yeah. I don't
feel weak on it. All right. Very good.
You are open and that degree of
willingness and that openness is what
will allow you to know you are preparing
yourself perfectly for the degree of
energy that you will be experiencing
later once the idea of your own higher
self altuna in that
way becomes more familiar to you.
One of the things I wanted to ask was I
had gotten that Artum was an eastern
um ruler type energy in a sense. Yeah.
Well, I had gotten it was like one of
his past lives and we've been connected
on that. But I I you know I just want to
know a little bit more. You are more
closely connected than you think. You
are the same energy.
And what about off?
Understand you are creating a
differentiation in one consciousness.
Then it's a tune of my higher self. Yes.
Is also two of my higher self. In a
sense it represents the idea of a
blending of an oversoul, a higher self
and a future self. When you bring those
three ideas concurrent within your
physiological consciousness through your
willingness to be comfortable within
your vulnerability, then you will be prepared
vulnerability, then you will be prepared
for the stronger energy within all of
and a connection to something you would
recognize to be other consciousness.
Okay? which will have connections to
some degree to the idea of the
past and also the future if you wish.
Yeah. Okay.
Um, understand that what we are saying
to you right now is our perception of
what needs to be said to allow you to
continue in the way that represents the
way you have chosen to continue. When
you make differences in the idea that
you are to yourself, there may be other
representations we can make that will
make more sense to the new you you
become. When will the new you find when will the
When will the new you find when will the
new me finally? That is up to you.
You are always always a new you. You are
a new you. Right now. Right now. Right
now. Right now. The definition you give
to that new you will determine what that
new you is able to
experience. Your choice. One moment is
not connected to the next. The present
is not a result of the past. Moment of
opportunity. Yes. And you are always
complete in every moment by definition
or you would not exist.
One more question if I may. Um
I have a problem.
And that is um all right.
I will remind each and every one of you
whether or not you have heard it
before that I am becoming selectively
third density
deaf. And in this way, the idea of
choosing certain terminology which only
has the vibration of reinforcing your
inability to change the situation that
is easily changed will be something I
will usually call out to us. The idea
you call a problem is simply a situation
you will not allow to change shape.
Yeah. Okay. The word problem and the
word habit. You are giving those words the
habit. You are giving those words the
power that says this means it is
difficult to
change. It is your formula. Change your
definition. You are creating a
situation. Situations can change more easily than
Situations can change more easily than
problems can. So you have a situation.
Yes. Um No, it's good. Thank you. I have a I
Um No, it's good. Thank you. I have a I
have a situation that
My dog is going um deaf and blind and he
has bitten you know um my father and a
few other people
right and when I
more exploration of vulnerability
more exploration of the idea of the fear
that as you explore dogs in your society
represent as you explore or the idea of
becoming vulnerable, therefore stronger
within strength. But because you are
exploring some of the idea within
judgment and fear, you are assuming that
as you cut off your physiological senses
in a way to explore the idea of your
inner awareness, that you will miss the
mark, that you will be of service
negatively rather than positively. Yes.
That you might in that way bite the hand
that feeds
you. But you do not have to worry about
the idea. The animal is giving you an
opportunity to explore all of these
ideas and explore them you will whether
you explore it consciously or not and
you will integrate that understanding
that symbol that lesson from that loving
animal consciousness in perfect timing to be
consciousness in perfect timing to be
able to incorporate that within your
service. So you will always be precisely
in that way valid and on the mark as you
need to whether or not you are in
connection with the same
reality perceptually that you were to
begin with or not. You will be in
connection exactly as you need to be.
You will be perceptive.
And I feel very torn in my heart. Torn
in your heart? Well, it pains me. Why?
Because my my feeling is that I have to
put my dog to
sleep. And maybe well maybe not
hopefully not but there is no hope about
it. Understand the dog is willing to
provide a symbol for you so that you can
grow. The idea may be that if the dog
The idea may be that if the dog
co-creates with you the idea of being
put to sleep, perhaps your fears will
also be laid to rest.
It is up to you. Not that it has to
happen that way, but in this way
recognize if it does, it is an act of
love on the part of the dog and it will
only increase your joy. Therefore, allow
it to be an act of love and you will not
be saddened but joyful.
You follow me. Not yet. All right. Sleep
on it. Getting there. Wow. Sleep on it.
Yeah. You may all then we will come back
to you and you. Take a short break.
How's everything going? continue.
continue.
Yes. First I wanted to share something.
Um when I'm meditating I like to imagine
connecting with my higher self and nice
um and also other entities and other
aspects of higher self. Nice. And um I
used to use an image that was very
linear like a hierarchy. All right. And
I decided I don't like it because it's
two dimensional. And what came to me was
to visualize it as a spiral. All right.
And that was really Well, thank you.
The I have two questions. Um
one is the other night I had well well
last night I had a dream which is very
different from most of the dreams that I
have. Well now that you are more
holographic than linear that is to be
expected. Okay.
Okay.
Um anyway I don't have a sense of what
you know I don't really
understanding this way first of all as
we have said one of the things that can
occur when you are more so to speak
deeply into the dream reality than usual
will be that when you wake up physically
and create a dream symbol by which to
remember the experience
If it is very unlike your physical
reality, the experience that you had,
then your physical ego structure will
not have as many symbols to draw from as
usual and it will use the symbols that
are closest to represent the experience.
It will do the best it can. otherwise in
this way simply recognize that therefore
the dreams in a sense that sometimes
will make the least amount of sense
physically are representative of
experiences that were more deeply
non-physical and for which there is no
physical analogy in following right well
I guess more than the the the physical
aspects of the dream which were unusual
there was a quality of the dream that I
didn't like such as well in the I mean
um when I'm with I'm in parties or in a
different civilization and the people
that are my parents and myself included
I'm not familiar with as myself. It is
not as if you know like in dreams that I
have now I even if my mother in my dream
look physically different I can still
tell my mother. This does not in this
dream I had dreams of other mothers and
other brothers. Yeah. Well, okay. Um,
the aspect that's physically different
is that I'm in two parties at the same
time, right? And that the that I am
split where in one party I am physically
there as well as I feel more there. All
right. In the other party that I'm
attending, the one I feel most at is my
parents party. the other party I feel
there physically but not there as fully
right and it's like a physical plane of
glass or
well anyway that's how I see it
separates the two all right very good
although that's not how I experience the
in those two parties guys okay um but
the quality I didn't like is that I
attended the second
the second
party because there was a woman there
who loved me or was in love with me.
Okay. And I wanted to experience my power over
And I wanted to experience my power over
her. All right. And that so now you know
you do not prefer to go to that party
anymore. Right. So you are giving yourself the
Right. So you are giving yourself the
holographic simultaneous representation
of the transition from third to fourth
density through the membrane the window
through which you can see but that is
the separation of the two densities.
You understand the idea of third and
fourth density correct? Yes I do
understand. Then in this way you are
simply recognizing that all of the
different reasons that you have explored
in third density about judgment and
domination is no longer representative
of the party you wish to attend.
And that relationships can be formed
within unconditional love and
recognition of the different portions of
yourself and self-empowerment so that
you can enjoy yourself without having in
this way to force yourself upon anyone
to get that sense of power because it is
already there.
You follow me? So I guess yes I follow
that. But my my question is, right?
Um or at least I'm not sure that I fully
understand why
I had an image of myself being in a
situation where I wanted power over
something. Are you saying that I have
the choice now or that I've only made
the choice of the choice? Yes, you have
made the choice. And you are simply
using as an analogy the reflection that
the entire idea of third density was to
explore the idea of separation and
judgment. You follow me? Okay. So and
expressing your power by domination as
opposed to integration.
That has been the whole idea of your
third density reality.
Then then I guess I don't understand
another aspect of the dream in which at
my parents party nice there were
it seemed as though my parents and my
brother all three of those people were
sick. All right. And my my mother walked
through the living room. Nice. And he
was speaking to my father who I could
not see and she said to him, "I'm
wearing I'm not going to be wearing the
plastic mask that I usually wear."
And there's only been two other
occasions. She reminds him there's only
been two other occasions in their
marriage where she had slept with him
without this mask, without his
separation. All
right. And
Then who walks true to a wall is amazing
to me? Not really. Again, it is still an
exemplification of the idea that when
you choose to nurture yourself, your own
motherhood toward yourself within the
idea of forming relationships that are
direct and open and honest and in this
way not dominations over another, which
is only the showing of a mask and not
your true self because you are afraid to
show your true self. The vulnerability
that is strength. When you show the true
self and gain the strength of that
vulnerability and the relationship is
direct and onetoone in that way, you
will walk through any walls. There will
be no barriers. You will proceed and all
those portions of yourself that you may
have formed relationships with that seem
to be withering or atrophying will be
reestablished as solid
relationships. You follow me? Yes,
they're solid. I'm very much relieved
that seems like it's a native dream.
Understand in this way simply any
opportunity to view an idea like that is
an opportunity to recognize you have
already worked through the idea
otherwise you would not have the
recognition. I guess in the dream I feel as though I
I guess in the dream I feel as though I
had chosen one party over the other. No
no no no.
You do not know what you felt in the
dream.
You follow me? Yes. Thank you very much
for your sharing and your
willingness to love all facets of your
being.
I had one. All right.
Um also in my dreams recently I've been
experienced a phenomena
where it feels like I have memories
within the dream. In a sense you are
memories in a dream all in the present.
Well, again, it is the idea of being
holographic that you contain all the
information simultaneously that you need
to contain to represent any particular
projection of yourself into any
particular time
frame. You are seeing the overlapping
idea of all that you have ever been or
ever will be and are now simultaneously.
So then that the memories that I um sort
of perceive in those dreams
are just an expression of that
holographic that it is your opportunity
to see the multi-dimensional
multi-layered aspects of yourself all
existing simultaneously.
I have one last question. All right. Um
the other night, um the man that I live
with, Joseph, woke up,
um and he was like screaming from a
dream that he was having a
nightmare. And ever since that night, I
have it's like I he fell right back to
police. He doesn't remember any of the
content of that dream or anything. I
laid awake in a lot of anxiety.
awake in a lot of anxiety.
And you did not even have the nightmare.
No. And it felt to me as though I mean I
And it felt to me as though I mean I
know this isn't accurate but it's the
way it felt to me. So he but it is
valid. Continue as if he had
ripped um my protection from the astral. Ripped
um my protection from the astral. Ripped
your protection from the astral world.
Well, I just feel like there's more
anxiety than Oh, there is more energy in
your life. Creative that you are judging
which is what makes it
anxiety. Excitement and anxiety is the
same energy.
You follow me? And you do not need
protection. You follow me? Yeah. So, what has been
You follow me? Yeah. So, what has been
removed is the veil of your supposition.
meaning that they the position that I
need is Yes. So you are now raw and
exposed to your own power.
You follow me.
As I said, thank you for your
willingness to
experience that acceleration. you venue.
you venue.
Um the
universe love
the universe is made of love.
You're not supposed to do anything
because the universe is
unconditional love.
Unconditional love.
Now the idea that you are expressing
simply is that when you recognize that
you are made of love and exist in your
natural state then you will live in a
universe of love. It is not that you are
supposed to do anything but that is your
choice to recognize that you are love it
and therefore everything you do is an
act of love. When you allow yourself to
consciously realize that your life will
be filled with that love and reflection
of that unconditional love and light and
trust. [Music]
It is simply in this way not that we did
not cry when we said that we did but
also recognize it was not for the same
reasons and the original definition of
our society is different than yours. You
are simply assuming that all societies
go through the same changes and they do not go. No, No,
[Music]
understand to recognize that you are
made of love in a sense is not really a
goal. It is a state of
being. Goals are
immediately, time oriented things,
spatially oriented things, consciousness
oriented things. They are perception. They are
things. They are perception. They are
perspective. That is all goals are
points of
view. In this
way, if we recognize that many different
individuals and civilizations can
express the love that they are in many
different ways. I understand what you mean in a
ways. I understand what you mean in a
timelinear
sense and in a sense that is something
that is occurring within creation but it
is not something that will ever end.
you can recognize yourself as a loving
being and recognize that you can choose
to be negative. And if you recognize
yourself as a loving being, knowing that
you are completely self-empowered to
create anything you want without having
to be negative, it is up to you to
choose whether you prefer to be negative
or not.
You do.
The universe does not know. You do. You
have created the universe.
All that is is the
universe. In a sense, it is existence
itself. You have created your specific
version of the universe
experientially. Judgment exists within your particular
Judgment exists within your particular
manifested universe. It does not exist
within ours as a manifestable thing. It exists
ours as a manifestable thing. It exists
as a potential. Anyone can create a
universe in which they can allow
themselves to be
judged. We have simply chosen to do
otherwise as you are now choosing to do
otherwise. Well, that'll have answered
your question. Thank you. Yes.
question. Thank you. Yes.
Yes.
I have a situation in my life that
up to this
point I have not allowed. All right. How
is it serving you then?
If you enjoy it so much.
I do not enjoy it. All right. What is it
doing for you?
All right. Then it is serving you. Well,
I was actually preferring the other
thing which I had not allowed to
manifest.
What other things? No, my channel seems
to disappear. Disappeared?
I'm I'm not challenging. I don't You
are. Of course you are. What do you
think you're doing right now? Oh.
Oh.
All this is not good enough.
What kind do you mean?
I'm talking about.
All right. Why do you prefer that kind
over this
kind? You don't know. Then how do you
know you preferment?
Ah, excite you. All right.
What does your
excitement indicate in your imagination
for you to
do? Well, any pictures, any feelings, do
not judge them. Oh, that's
silly. Anything at all. What is the
first thing that comes? Don't think
about it. Don't analyze it. Well, let it
go for a while. All right. Let it go for
a while.
All right. And in letting it go, you
will enjoy the life you are living in
the meantime. Yes. For it is equal to
anything else you could be doing. Yes.
Then understand that enjoying life is a
part of the process of the
channel. You are not being interrupted.
You can't be interrupted.
You follow me? The highest
consciousness. It is regulating what will allow you to
It is regulating what will allow you to
be comfortable with the channeling. So
you will not feel disoriented in a
negative way. All right? You will give
yourself the polarity
stability to create channeling which
will connect you to many other ideas and
the enjoyment of your life here which
will in a sense ground you in your terms
so that you can
function. Otherwise, what would be the
point to follow it?
Now, are there other things in your life
that you would desire to do that you are
not doing?
Do any of them excite you at all?
A little bit.
I place more importance on other things.
All right. Do you place more importance
on those other things because they
excite you or simply because you place
more importance on them?
What I'm saying is the channeling is
actually the thing that is more
important that excites you the most. All
right. Then understand first and
foremost that if that is true for you,
you are always channeling in exactly the
way you need
to. You follow me? Sometimes channeling
is for
you. All right? so that you will be able
to channel for others.
Thank you. Yes, sir.
You saw Have you uh
personally experienced the degree of
limitation separation that we have
in my present
incorporation? Or do you mean as my past
self that you recognize to be the
physical channel before you? All right.
All right.
Thank you. [Music]
separation between each other being
separate and all that. Well, they're all
these different densities and their
beings in different cultures on
different stars in different times. We
are as societies as civilizations
separate from each other. Yes.
So I'd like to ask you to talk about why
would I
hear the same so that you can create the
exploration of a specific idea.
[Music] If
If
you cannot forget that you are the
creator of your
reality, how can you experience a
reality in which you seem to be limited?
All right. But that is the general idea.
You have chosen to experience what it is
like to be limited and you can create
that kind of differentiation because you
are the creator of your reality. So you
can pretend to forget.
So that for a while you can see what it
is like to not know who you are.
That is the basic reason for all of the
differences because all of the
differences are all the different ways
all that is has of experiencing itself
simply because we can. It doesn't need
any more meaning than that.
You um we've been talking about uh a lot
of people with experiences within their
living space. I had a question relating
to that. Um, one thing that I've uh
dealt with in my apartment has been um
the development of energy that I
realized in person myself. However,
other people are also experiencing it
with different results and um I realized
that that was also a way to accelerate
the process of growth for everyone
involved. Um my question
Um my question
is when people are experiencing what
they perceive as negative energy because
of the strength of the energy that's in
place uh at what point do I differentiate
uh at what point do I differentiate
between my own personal reflection you
are not experiencing negative energy
because of the strength of the energy
but because of your viewpoint of the
energy right well I'm I'm finding that
right well I'm I'm finding that
personally I I'm I'm dealing with that
and I understand that if I perceive of
it as negative, that's my own creation
because I I can variously experience it
as a real energizing energy or negative
depending on how I choose to experience.
You can still allow yourself to
recognize energy that is being expressed
negatively and simply let the fact that
you can recognize it serve you
positively whether or not the initial
energy changes itself.
Okay. um my my let's say not a problem let's
um my my let's say not a problem let's
say my concern same thing could happen
um it's been for other people who
experience it and uh have had more
extreme reaction
in that initially what hap what happened
to make me quite aware of the energy in
in that specific space was a friend
noticing an energy enter the room uh and
it and something attempted to channel
through spontaneously where he felt not uh in
spontaneously where he felt not uh in
any way prepared for the experience and
became hysterical. All right. And did it
stop? Uh only after about 2 hours of
conscious uh attempt to remove that from the
uh attempt to remove that from the
physical state. All right. Why did they
choose to believe that they must go
through that experience in such a
struggle? That's something for that person to work
That's something for that person to work
out. I believe correct. Um at the same
time uh other people who have been let's
say on the spiritual path and rather
sensitive path have had similar types of
reactions in terms of extreme fear yes
when entering my apartment. Now I don't
necessarily play
that type of reality in every space that
I deal with these people and I'm
wondering at what point is my own energy
involved or their energy or any earth
related energy specific it is all in a
sense part and parcel of the same thing
for what you are doing is assuming that
you are giving them an opportunity to
look at portions of themselves that they
feel that is the kind of
hotel. You are running.
Come to the fear hotel.
Every room guaranteed to reflect a
portion of yourself. You'll be
terrified. [Music]
[Music]
So all individuals who wish to have the
type of vacation where they want to
experience a portion of themselves in
fear, come here.
For I am willing to co-generate with you
that type of energy so that you will
know on some level that when you come
and interact with that energy and
experience your fear you are doing it in
a safe place.
[Music] Follow me. My personal concern in this
Follow me. My personal concern in this
level of reality is in the practical
aspect of
um people becoming reluctant to
uh then you can become the type of host
that has the willingness and the
conviction to explore the idea with them
in a way that will allow them to know
that fear is only a messenger, bringing
them another portion of themselves so
that they do not have to experience it
negatively any longer. And then entice
them with the possibility that once they
make a friend of their fear in that way
and know they are choosing to experience
themselves in that way, then when they
step into that energy you are
co-creating, they will not experience
fear but the power of their own creative
sense. All
All
right. that that is the goal in my the
hall of
mirrors in that be coming to that
realization. I'd like to have perhaps
some more specific information about the
nature of some of the energies as they
might be manifesting themselves. The
nature of them
um whether they relate specifically to
the individuals who experience them. Of
course, of course they do. Uh well
that's how you get specific to the one
that actually materialized in the form
of a woman coming to the end. All right.
Uh this was in December of last year.
You have created the type of atmosphere
that is not unlike what we have created
in our planet that allows other
individuals to project their
consciousness and wrap themselves in a
projection of our bodily forms in order
to experience our reality. You have
created a type of atmosphere that allows
individuals who visit you to project
portions of their own consciousness into
the type of materiality or spirit forms
that need to be reflected to them to let
them see those portions of themselves in
no uncertain terms. Which is why I don't
feel the same. Correct. Um, one
Um, one
moment. In a
sense, let us say it is a to use your
terminology more
specifically controlled and purposely
applied and more solidified
manifestation of what you normally refer
to in a more
uncontrolled manifestation as a
poltergeist. phenomena.
99.9% of which comes from the people
involved in the situation themselves
that have in a sense the notion of
excess energy they don't know what to do
with are afraid to face.
Mhm. in the same situation.
Um the first person um experienced a lot
of agitation which is obvious uh and and
the woman who was manifested uh I
described the situation to my neighbors
and they said oh you met Nina. All
right. Well it it turned out that
someone who lived in the apartment and
we are not saying that it does not have
a total consciousness as but that is the
purpose of the energy and the
consciousness. It is a way station that
has the atmosphere that will attract
those who can utilize it to look at
those fragments and facets of themselves
in that way. Whether they choose to
generalize it in the form of the
consciousness as it has always
represented itself on its own terms is
up to them. Depends on what they are
willing to face. Recognize that no
matter what the form is, what it brings
itself reflection. Mhm.
I'm really curious about merely. Yes.
Mirrorly between
uh there's some synchronicity between
one person's experience and the next.
Yes, of course. who felt that um hadn't
been told who this person was by the
neighbors. Uh the next person who showed
up panting and whitefaced my daughter
said someone had been murdered out here
at the same time that the neighbors had
explained that someone had been murdered
in that area. All right. And I'm
wondering if there is indeed a specific
connection between that manifestation of
the energy as different people who had
not discussed the situation during Yes.
In this way again recognize the idea is
this that particular consciousness is in
and of itself expressing a form of
entrapment. It is not moving on. And
anyone who partakes of that energy is
going to meet the portion of themselves
that feels entrapped.
It is the expression that if you have in
that sense refused to face a portion of
yourself in that way, you have buried
it, you have killed it, you have
murdered it. It is in
it. It is in
between being able to
function and going
on. Understand in that way the original
purpose for what you now call an
exorcist to be was in a sense a spirit
psychologist. to allow them to know they did not have
to allow them to know they did not have
to remain within the attachment they had
formed within physical life and could
move on.
You follow me? Yes.
Therefore, that
consciousness and all who find
themselves attracted to it are choosing
to experience those portions of
themselves in a way that will allow
themselves in a sense to become lost in
a maze in a hall of mirrors. All of
these reflections will always show them
how they fear they have trapped
themselves so they can deal with that
idea. It is in a sense shock treatment.
Yes, but that is the way some of you
have chosen to do it. And there are
spirits who are willing to help simply
because of what they have chosen their
situation to be. That spirit on the
level you are perceiving it may not be
any more aware of what it is doing than
you are. But another portion of it is
and knows that that portion of itself
that is locked into that reality and
interacting with you is serving the
purpose. So the dissolution of that type
of energy as it is being experienced in
common right now is our choice as well.
Understand you will be providing a
service. Yes. at the same time. For when
all those individuals gather together
and blend within themselves the love of
those forces they now fear, they and you
will generate the type of atmosphere
that will allow that spirit to be on its
way. For you will allow it to wake up as
if it is allowing you to wake up.
You follow me?
Recognize that many individuals upon
your planet
choose to be scared into the presence
Thank you. Thank you. You You're on.
You're on.
Okay. I have a couple things that I want
to discuss. You want to ask I just
exploring the idea of um of plity nice
and sometimes when I sit in the shower I
think about different things and look at
it in different
ways you know cuz it's a neat place to
do it
today I was looking at the idea of I was
looking at the idea
of exploring the idea of of like for
instance wanting to light something
guys. Okay. And the idea is that the not
having a plan is manifested and having
the plan is unmanifested which is like
kind of the other side of
same idea as unconscious knowingness and
conscious unknowingness.
Okay. And so it's almost like the thing
if you turn not having the wrong side
out then you would have the occur that
kind of thing. Wrong side. All right. Go
ahead. Yeah. But when I when I took it a
step further and I'm really wrong that
actually the the idea of polarity
is not quite what we cracked it up to
be. Oh, very good.
The it seemed that the the reality of
the not having a pen and the reality of
having a pin are actually parallel in a
sense. Yay. And it isn't that you have
to have one or the other. Oh, very good.
You are allowing your situation to be
neutral. Yeah. So that was I just want
to tell it was in New York which I had
before a neutral. Yes. Thank you.
Okay. Oh, the next thing is
um of the entire time. [Music]
It seems like a combination or
collection of
uh past, president, president, and
future self. and without entire
factoring. That is one way to look at
it. Yes. Okay. So, and in fact
it that combination is an essence of its
own. Right. Yes. Every idea is 100% its
own idea. So it's not so much that that
is separate from me as a higher
consciousness and a lower consciousness.
It is a it is me in a different
framework.
Ah, you have hit the
aquarium. That is the entire
idea. Thank you very much. Everything
that you are, anything that is different
at any time from anything you have ever
been is not so much a separate you, but
the same you in a different frame of
reference. All relatives as I believe one of your
All relatives as I believe one of your
scientists said once very good
frames of reference. Thank you. Oh,
[Music] the uh the other thing is um after I had
the uh the other thing is um after I had
um finished my shower, I was drying off
my face, right? And I put my sensor in
my eyes and kind of for a moment, really
good. Then all of a sudden, I saw this
uh sort of sawdust of light, which was a
bunch of light geometric things, very
geometric. And I've seen this before and
I'm curious about it. It's exactly what
even happened to me.
Different aspects of your
aspects of your
consciousness somewhat differentiated
but only in generalized
terms in probabilities in potentials
rather than specifics.
In the sense that if you see yourself as
being one homogeneous idea and were to
perform the idea of becoming more
specifically many different things
within one, let us say as an analogy,
the first step in the breaking apart of
the homogeneousness would be to
recognize the crystal latice work within
it. And so the geometric forms by
analogy and that
that yes, thank you very much. the news. All right.
All right.
Uh when is your birthday?
Birthday. In this way, it will not be translatable
In this way, it will not be translatable
directly, but the analogy that will
suffice will be what you call November
11th.
In this way recognize again simply to
point out an analogy in the
triad. The physical channels in that
sense is what you call 1012. Mine is 111
and Fox is 1210.
But that is an arbitrary analogy. But go
on. Okay. What do you mean that in
again as an arbitrary mark which again
is valid from different points of view
in different ways. You may simply
calculate that in your terminology. You
may consider it to be
approximately 157 of your year.
158 next November.
All right. Great. Okay.
Remember 3 months ago when I called the
guy, right? And I've been feeling him
recently and I've been seeing his
energy evolving in a maybe different
way. Oh, very good.
According to how you are also evolving
differently now. Yeah.
So you are creating a reflection in the
particular aspect of his consciousness
that now reflects the difference in your
consciousness to use it as a measure of
how you have changed as well. That's
really fine.
[Music] Thank you. The third question is my
mother and um she tried to sell the
house to live. Yes.
Well, we're still selling the house. All
right. And it's not happening.
[Music]
All right. I'll start again. Okay.
She put a sign outside the door.
All right. And people are not buying it.
Are you sure she wants to sell it?
Is she sure she wants to sell? Yeah,
that's the thing. That's her question.
If she has to ask.
Well, she wanted to know why she's not
selling. And I I told her what it is.
Maybe you don't want to. And then she
told me three times. Yeah. She didn't
want to tell. She's really ready to
tell. So she wants to know when she
tells it. Yeah. Where is she going to
go? Well, she doesn't know. Uhhuh.
Well, she doesn't know. Uhhuh.
But she knows she wants to move like
then when she allows herself to
recognize that the move is already made,
the house will be sold.
Allow her to believe she does know where
she wants to go. At least in essence.
Yeah. Well, it's not a dis,
right? All right. But she is existing in
a very quasi planer limbo idea in that
sense sitting between two houses.
very she has not moved in her soul
and so her symbols do not reflect a
move. If she knows beyond a shadow of a doubt
If she knows beyond a shadow of a doubt
she has moved then the symbol of having
this house does not need to be there and
it will not be be
so bomb. Hello.
Hello.
Um, I just had
a ruin mystery talking about the the
symbol, excuse me, talking about the
symbols that close their eyes, right?
And those symbols are reflected in in
the the symbolic language of uh Indian
design. Yes. American Indian design.
Yes. Okay.
Because in this way it is our perception
that what you call American Indian
culture knows it exists on many
different levels at once and it is
experientially real to them for them all
those different ideas.
Oh
yes we have discussed the idea of the
cina many times. Yeah, they're
reflective of people in the universe.
Like the clown
head, but what I was the Yes. the Now
what I wanted to to ask you about, you
know, the power spots that that the
people have in different areas. Yes. The
mountains, the sacred spots. Yes. The
vortices. Yes. Well, right now there's a
power spot that's being taken over by
energy companies on the big mountain on
the Navajo Healthy Reservation area.
One moment understand in this
way that the idea is for those
people to allow themselves to remember
who they are. For when they allow
themselves to believe that they are who
they are, then they will remember.
For when they allow themselves to
believe that they are who they are, then
they will remember as they used to know
that nothing that is yours that is you
can be taken from
you. You tell them they are not who they
know they
are. And so they are
afraid. They are believing in the
society that has created the idea of
loss. They are beginning to agree that
they also believe something can be lost.
They are not behaving as the society
they know themselves to be. By believing
they can lose
something. You follow me?
Let them know and let yourself know in
that way also that all of the energy vortices
way also that all of the energy vortices
upon your planet at this
time are also opening up and becoming
less specific. They are becoming what we
specific. They are becoming what we
refer to as free
zones in the sense that many
energies, many dimensions, all
dimensions of
existence exist within those focal
points. And so, of
course, those energy zones are going to
attract different points of view for the
purpose of allowing all those different
points of view to blend, not to fight.
You follow me?
If they are willing to trust that they
know different points of view, points of
view different from their own are being
attracted by those energy spots for the
purpose of blending and not segregating.
Then the power of their trust is what
will go into that energy vortex and it
will have an
effect on those that are still choosing
to believe that something can be lost
and something can be taken.
understand in a sense whether it seems
to be on the surface or not, it is the
beginnings of what they have always
watched for in terms of Pahana. You
follow me,
the return of the lost brother.
The brother is coming on his own terms.
But that does not mean he will not stay
and join the family. All family. All
right.
And the Kachina energy is ever present
in those
vortices. And there are many of the
civilization that is attempting to take
away that
believe along with your
Indians that all belongs to all in that
way and that there is enough for
everyone to partake of in those energy
vortices so that all can recognize they
are as powerful as they need to be
without having to force their point of
view on anyone else to prove it. No,
No,
these energy vortices that we you refer
to, is there a specific form of them or
do they take many forms depending on
what you imagine?
Are they spinning rapidly or slowly or
any speed or are they very fine lines in
a funnel form or is it kind of a
like amorphous form of energy. They do
change shape from time to time in that
way. Do expand, do change momentum
depending upon what they are reflecting
of the gathering of the consciousness
within them and around them. In that
sense they are quite malleable in many
different ways and they even in a sense
leak
in that the general area they may define
themselves to be within sometimes in
certain areas can extend beyond their
own boundaries.
Well is there kind of a average or usual
shape? It is in a sense funnel like
are there lines of energy flow in a cylinder line
cylinder line
they are all
vibrations from a fine line to work
everywhere from very very very very fine line to a
from very very very very fine line to a
line that describes the entire funnel.
What about speed of rotation? That
changes as well. Is there an
average? In other words, if we were to
perceive one, would we see it spinning
about the speed that we see a tornado or
would it be a very slow moving? It can
be both and it can be both at the same
time. It is a completely perceptive
idea. There are individuals who may even
see it to be frozen
depending on the purpose. Yes. And the
energy of the individual doing the
perceiving. And you could also perceive
all of these various forms
simultaneously. Various feed
similarities. Yes. You could see an
overlap. Like what you call a superimposition?
Like what you call a superimposition?
Yes.
Is there some way that we can use these
beyond what my current knowledge is of
of how yes they do
in this way you can now to some degree
these ideas have been tapped
particularly by the individual we have
discussed that you know to be
Tesla. So in this way you can understand
that there are frequencies that
represent the general flow of energy
from vortex to vortex that can be
represented by the
overall 7 and 1/2 cycle per second rate
of your entire planet the
wavelength and you can utilize the
energy in that way and you can draw from
it power to be used in many ways.
You can use the planet to run the
civilization and all of its technology
simply on the difference between the
levels of energy in any given vortex or
between all the different vortices. I
see. And you're suggesting that we could
do this technologically. Yes, it is one
way. You can do it with your own
consciousness as well, but it can have a
technological representation that is in
your terms nonvoluting, natural.
Do you see any energy behind this idea
in terms of our future? Yes.
Can you give us some specific vortex
areas in the valley area? Malibu.
Can you pinpoint it?
Malibu. Nice. Nice.
Any others? Baja.
Baja.
Okay. What effects on our physical
structure can
we I don't want to say expect we expect
to perceive if we live in those
areas there may be for certain
individual a propensity to having more
crystallized silicon in their
bodies and perhaps
and perhaps
also magnetite
increase in
iron, some
copper or a need in that way for some
copper to be surrounding the individual
or touching the individual in that way
to form a conduit and a balance.
That will do. See what effect will
again according to the purpose of the
individual. Okay, it's kind of individual.
Okay, it's kind of individual.
There is some
generalities but in this way again
explore them as an individual and you
may recognize the commonality.
Thank you. Thank you.
You then you can you
um yes
I I have a question for a friend and I
also have something I like to share. All
right. Which one first? Um sharing. All
right. Thank you.
Um it has to do with the different
aspects of ourselves that we perceive
uh with feeling fear
and all this lifetime I've been very um
I've had a lot of affinity for all the
life forms. There's hardly a life form
on the planet that I don't feel some
affinity for. Oh, hardly. All right.
Well, that that brings me to sliders.
And I have been looking at that idea and
um exploring this idea for years and
years and years. And I see it as the
minute and lately
um I realized
that the symbol that I've chosen for
myself to represent the idea of fear.
Oh, which gave me a whole new
perspective on it. And what's been made
really fascinating is that recently I
went to Hawaii and I had an
experience coming up to a friend's bill
and there was a spider on it. It was
absolutely enormous. It just stopped me
right in my
track. Vivian, you've got to come and
look at the spiders as big as a map
truck. And I was
so I felt my fear and I also realized
that I was projecting my fear to that
form.
I scared the spider and he was running
off. You're reflecting your fear back.
Exactly. Exactly. And I thought about
that for several days and I I got
several realizations about that. Go.
What? Go. Go. Yes. So, um
the realization Yes. What's happening is
that I realize that that those are
different aspects of myself and what I'm
doing is more and more integrating them
into my reality and admiring them and
flowing love to them and infinity and
examining them more closely when they
come into my space. What's happening is
that every time this happens, my fear is
diminishing and the spiders are getting
smaller.
Good. The other day I was out in my jack
and there was a little wolf spider and
he came hopping over towards me and I
went I put my book in front of me
and back up a little bit a little too
close and he cocked his head and looked
at me and there was that little
intelligence communicating with me. I
was so stunned because I could see that
he realized that that I was there. He
saw me and he communicated. Right. And
he was only carrying on the tradition.
Exactly. So anyway, I I communicated
with him and I got his agreement to go
off in another direction the next day.
You are very familiar with ectomy. What
is it?
Indian. Oh yes. Ektoi.
Oh yes. Ektoi.
What is it? You may share that later. Oh
thank you. Yes, I know because
also we
really being at the hub of things can be
fearful for some of you.
I this is wonderful. I had so many
realizations and so a couple of days
after that um there was a very small
little spider and I carried him out in
my hand and just kind of let him go in
the in the bushes. And the next morning,
I'm in front of my mirror in the
bathroom and out from the crack comes
the teeniest little butterfly ever. And
I just started
laughing. My fear had gone all the way
down to practically nothing.
Thank you. Thank you. Your question.
Yes. This is for my next. She has had
um a physical sensation that she's
trying to cope with. And I told her I
was Oh, trying to cope. All right. She
she doesn't know what's causing it. She
She feels the physical manifestations
and it's like
um a pressure of solidity in her body
that's sometimes painful. And she has a
lot of concern with it. and I've been
sharing some ideas with you, but I
wanted to ask you if you could.
Does she feel she's about to burst?
That I'm not sure. Possibly.
Can it simply be her own creative
pressure waiting to get out.
I'll offer her that. All right. See what
she does with that. Tell her to trust
her imagination.
All right. Yeah, thank you. Okay, I have
four things. Um, one,
um, do microwave ovens
change the makeup of food so that it's
not healthy or can't be absorbed by our
body.
It is not so
much though there is a cellular
change. It is not so much that it is in
your terms
unhealthy but perhaps blank.
So we wouldn't get nourishment as much
nourishment from something cooked in a
microwave. In general, you will find that your term
In general, you will find that your term
of cooking will remove much of the
nutrients.
Microwave will do the job in a different way. There
is something about the way it affects
the water in the substance as well that
represents ideas
ideas
which can reflect a usage that you may
discover in your future. with regard to
microwave energy and
energy and
also a realization of certain aspects of
what it does within your cellular
structure in your
atmosphere that you may not prefer. We
prefer. We
will be able to discuss this some other
time more detail. Why did two Why did
you change the pattern? This is this is
an extra micron. Why did you change the
pattern? In that way, what you were
sensing is the changing of the
pulsations of my consciousness in terms
of let us say, for lack of a better
term, where I was getting the
information from.
Where were you getting it from?
The idea of making a connection to your
future mass consciousness. Two. Two.
Two. Two.
I've had this pain in my elbow, my left
elbow for about which pain? This pain.
This pain right here. It's not there to
us right now. Oh, but it keeps coming
and going. It's been there for about two
and a half months. And I'm trying to
understand crying.
what what I what I'm showing myself by
this pain. But so far, I was wondering
if you could give me your confession.
Do you enjoy your life?
Oh, sometimes.
Do you feel you have to reach too far
for the things you
like? Do you feel you are overextending
yourself? [Music] [Music]
Back up.
What does that mean? bring everything
within your grasp so you don't have to
overextend yourself.
Okay, thanks. Um, and the third thing is
I was out in the jacuzzi on Monday and
the moon was almost directly overhead
and it was totally surrounded by a cloud
ring. It was really quite beautiful and
um it seemed like there was a lot of
love and benevolence in that song. All
right. Simply that you are finding that within
Simply that you are finding that within
all the portions you have created to be
sub and unconscious portions of
yourself. There is just as much love as
what you can create consciously and you
can allow that to blend within liquid
harmony within yourself. It is not
accidental that you were in water when
you are observing the idea of the moon
for it represents the liquidness of your
consciousness in that way. And that is
why it is represented also in the
symbolic form of what you call your
tarot card as having water. Is everybody
like
forward? Will you tell us something nice
about this?
Now in this way recognize you are always
being born. Every moment is a new you.
You are a constant birth and new
creation, an ecstatic explosion of
birth. Also, you can recognize that you
are eternal as well. And that when you
allow yourself to know that you are
always being bored, you may not choose
to continue to keep track of a regularly
scheduled recognition.
For that will define the structure of
the time frame in which you perceive
yourself to exist and you will
age. Now you can recognize that any
moment of time you choose to create the
idea of celebration.
It does not have to be focused upon the
idea of the time frame but that you are
simply celebrating the birth that you
always are eternally.
All right. Very nice. Thank you to you
all. Happy birthday. One moment.
One moment.
I had a question about um the
plane the different plane like after the
four mental plane. What is the plane
after that?
There are
causal in this way you have described
astral and etheric and mental and causal
plains. In that way
to us this is very arbitrary and we are
finding that they are blending into each
other leaking into each other at this
time. We find that there is in our
perception less propensity to redefine
them.
Also we talk about density. Yes. Does
that have any relationship?
Okay. And it is all simply a matter of
And it is all simply a matter of
vibration
frequency. The idea of density in your
terminology is simply that when you are
accelerated there is more of you
consciously present. So you are more
dense. Paradoxically, because there is
more of your energy there, you are more
highly accelerated. So you feel less
dense in a physical sense.
Oh, okay.
Um, then I had one question. Since I
have an IUD removed, I've had a number
of irregularities in
my one month I have two periods. Yeah, I
this month I had the
irregularity is not uncommon for your
time framing now for a great many of you
in that way. You are finding again that
you are redefining the idea of yourself.
And as you accelerate, you may find that
it will in your terms become even more
irregular. For the actual manifestation
as you have created it in that way does
not need to occur in that manner and
will in your terms pretty much vanish in
fourth density.
There are individuals who experience
gaps of what you call three, four, five
months at a
time. Also recognize that as you
accelerate in that way, as you allow
yourself to in your terms, let us say
rarify your physicality, you
may sustain yourself on less physical
sustenance. You may lose body weight and
below a certain percentage of body fat,
you will cease to have your period.
Not really. No, later on perhaps, but
not right now. And it will not be losing
a potential. It will be creating another
idea.
There will be a few moments remaining. [Music]
[Music]
Continue for years and quite freaking
where I needed help. Where? What kind?
It's all right. any physiological event
you can attribute to the pain. Only once
I was training
very sickness
[Music]
about and I didn't move anything. What
type of physiological treatment have you
attracted to yourself?
And anything else? had neglected
spiritual counsel.
Any other physiological freedom? No. No.
There are some others that you may be
willing to participate
within and see what they do for you in
releasing not only your body
physiologically, but emotionally certain
ideas that may be being pent up in that
area. holding it out of alignment.
Now, not that we in this sense recommend
anything over something else, but there
are other ideas that do exemplify in
your terms a little bit more of the
releasing of ideas than what you call
strict chiropractic. Heler
attempt the idea of what to call your power.
Participate in what you call Hello. She knows.
She knows.
Now recognize again it is not the
physiological manipulation,
but it is more akin to the idea of
release in many different ways that are
attuned to your specific granular system
and organic system and can allow
emotionality to be released at the same
time. And if you are willing to deal
with it in a sense at the same time and
acknowledge and accept it at the same
time you are being physically worked
upon for that specific purpose then you
can form a blending of the physical and
the emotional the mental and the
spiritual in that way and can unlock
yourself all across the board and all
the way
within. All right.
Allow yourself while undergoing that
release to feel yourself to be filled
with blue white energy and allow that to
be what you breathe into the aura around
you and balance your electromagnetic
field. Also drink
water. All right. See the water balance
by that electromagnetic field until in
your imagination it almost becomes
liquid crystal.
All right. Allow it to reinforce certain
right. Allow it to reinforce certain
areas in your muscular structure, but
not in a rigid manner. It is liquid
crystal and always shall remain so that
your entire cellular structure will
become homogeneous. All right? Then the
homogeneous. All right? Then the
electromagnetic impulses along your
nerve network will flow more freely and
in more directions than just the rigid
path described by what you perceive to
be your nervous
system. And in your
brain the idea will be a homogeneous
blending of all the portions not a
differentiation into the ideal you call
left mix and right mix of
hemisphere. You will become
one solid liquid state crystal
conductor in which any type of
electromagnetic and electrochemical
interactions can define the state of
your being at any given moment.
All right. All right. Thank you. You are
welcome. you then you
at the beginning.
Thank you for taking
me and
having sinus or
whatever and purchases your series of
patient.
You are sensitizing to the shifting
going on the changes within you and
within your planet.
Oh yes.
We will again be discussing some of that
your 28th, 29th and 30th.
We will be discussing some of the ideas
of the ships.
Responsible for everything.
nothing.
You are in a sense responsible for
everything in your universe. You are
responsible to yourself.
Ah yes, you are not responsible for
anyone else. You are responsible to them
by being responsible for yourself.
But what I did want to talk about and
that people involved in this
particular two months [Music] ago unbelievable. ago unbelievable.
over
there. I had a concept almost not really
you see it landing. Yes, definitely like
this. And I also seen one in the future. Nice.
And I also seen one in the future. Nice.
And I have never discussed this with
anyone and four other people that are
not related to each other. The same the
same reality, right?
What? What? What? What? What? What?
Absolutely. What?
No, obviously not. It is quite credible
or you would not be talking about it.
The next day.
Yes. Yes. Yes. The ecstatic explosion of
coincidence synchronicity.
Yes. All the effort. Yes, you are doing
it without effort with ease of creation.
Yes, it seems to be but you are doing
it. Thank you. Thank you.
any
information supposed to you know what
you are supposed to do. There is nothing
that you are supposed to do. Follow your
ecstasy. It will always lead you exactly
where you need to
be. You
can be at that landing when it occurs.
Exactly what I want to do.
Follow your ecstasy and allow wherever
you are right now to be where you need
to be.
Do not ignore the light attempting to
get to that time in the future or you
will never get
there. All
right? Do not ignore the life you are
living in lie of attempting to hurry up
and get to that point in the future.
Otherwise, you will never get there.
Living the life you create is what will
get you
there. Enjoying every moment means you
don't need patience. Thank you.
Thank you.
If you are enjoying every moment, no
need for patience.
If you wish Thank
Thank
you guys. Are the
um movements of the earth I know you
went into the second ship at a later
point but my question before you
mentioned that was the movement saying
the earth as we see volcanoes and
earthquakes manifestation of mass
consciousness of course and earth
consciousness which is almost the same
thing. With that in mind and considering
the rain event,
um can we expect any expect perhaps uh
in the future of in limited future next
several weeks or so? Can we see any
reactions on the earth level? No
comment. The event could be happen. The
happen. The
ideas that we will
be
sharing are again presented for the
opportunity
of recognizing the reasons for all of
the symbols you have created in general
terms in your civilization to represent
to you a reflection that would and is
now ultimately allowing you to
understand. It is always you that has
been in control.
We extend our
appreciation, our unconditional love and
our thanks to you to allow us to
experience the gift of sharing that you
are so that we may see that many more
ways that all that it has of expressing
itself within
creation. We thank you for the
sharing that continues forever.
We bid you exciting and synchronous
dream lives. We bid you a fun and loving