All right, I'll say how are you all this
evening of your time as you create time
to exist.
Allow us to begin this interaction this
evening of your time with the
furtherance of conviction, the
furtherance of the idea of proof as you
call it within yourselves about the self
you choose to be. Once again, allow us
to remind you that in the world in which
you exist, very often you are called
upon to furnish what you call to be a
proof of the ideas you believe within.
Recognize once again that in an
essential fundamental way, there really
is no way you can prove anything to
anyone. You are your own reality. They
are their own reality. And anything that
they choose to believe in their reality
is the product of that choice. And
anything that they experience in their
reality is the product of their choosing
to create it in their own reality to
begin with. Anything that you create in
your reality in order to be experienced
in any way, shape, or form in their
reality must be chosen by them as one of
the ideas they already believe can be a
proof, a reality, a truth for them. In
this way, therefore, allow us once again
to put forth the suggestion and the
notion that while there is really no way
you can really prove anything to anyone
else simply because you being your own
universe do not
necessarily have the ability in physical reality to
have the ability in physical reality to
know whether you are communicating with
another consciousness or with simply
your own projected hallucination. And
thus you may in all the convincing that
you are doing only be talking to
different facets of
yourself. In this way therefore
recognize that the only one individual
that you can truly prove in your sense
of the word anything to is
yourself. In this way the idea rather
than going about asking other
individuals to prove to you the things
that they know to be true for
themselves. simply take it upon yourself
to recognize that at any given moment,
anything you desire to experience in
your life as a truth, you can create
your own proof within your life of that
idea. You can always recognize that many
of the things that we share with you in
this way are not given to you as the
idea of proofs. They are given to you as
the idea of perspective, points of view,
suggestions, sharing, probabilities,
possibilities, possible ways that you
may also choose to create a perspective
in your life to understand the idea that
you are expanding your own awareness.
But in this way, never do we nor can we
offer any idea of proof simply because
at this time the idea is that there is
no way to prove anything in the sense of
forcing anything upon you. Any
individual who simply does not wish to
experience an idea, no matter what you
may furnish as a proof, will not
experience that idea. No matter how in
your terms blatant a proof may be, if an
individual chooses not to experience it,
experience it, they will not. In this
way, therefore, the idea is to simply
recognize that at any given moment,
anything you
desire, anything you wish to explore and
experiment to determine whether it is in
your terms true for you or
not can always be subjectively
experienced, subjectively proven by
yourself in your life to your own
satisfaction to work as a proof for you.
But it will always be your own version
of that idea and will never be the other
person's version of that idea. So even
if you in your terms buy what they are
sharing with you as their proof, you are
still creating your version of that idea
in order to experience it in your
reality. Thus the only proof you are
ever buying anyway is your own. You are
only convincing yourself of the validity
or reality of any situation regardless
of what anyone may share with you as
their proof. It is never their proof.
You accept it is
yours. In this way, many of the ideas we
have shared with you about your ability
to create the type of lives you desire
to create. We cannot prove this to you.
We cannot prove that anything we say
works. However, you can. The idea is
simply that what we suggest to you out
of belief, out of faith, out of
knowingness, you can put into action in
your life and you can see that your
reality can be allowed to be ecstatic.
Does not have to be made or forced to be
ecstatic. Cannot be forced to be
ecstatic. but can be allowed by you to
become the desired creation you wish it
to be. And you can create and generate
in your life your own proof that life
can be simple, life can be easy and that
you can experience yourself as the
creator of the universe you are.
All of these things that we share with
you can be experienced by each and every
one of you individually and
collectively. But it is up to each and
every one of you individually to choose
to believe that that can be an
experience. As we have shared with you
many times, it is not seeing is
believing. It is believing is seeing.
And the idea is even though we
understand the habit that your society
has of how it looks at things, the idea
that's saying well all right I've had
the experience and that is why I now
believe that such an experience is
possible. But
recognize because you are not in touch
many times or have not been in the past
with the non-physical higher
consciousness portion of your being that
in actual fact is what you utilize to
create the physical existence. Then many
of you simply do not realize that any
physical experience you have in life is
the product of what you already believe
whether you are consciously aware or not
of that belief. All your emotions, all
your feelings do not appear from
nowhere. When you have a
feeling it is not simply because well
that's just the way I feel. There is a
reason for why you feel the way you do
in any given situation. And the reason
why you may feel at any given time about
any given situation is because your
feeling is the product of what you have
been taught to believe is true about
that situation. The way you have been
taught to view that situation. So
ingrained and so automatic are these
beliefs within you that you do not even
recognize that you have them many
times. In this way, therefore, the
feeling may seem to be the first thing
you have to go off of. And that is why
many times you think that the feeling is
the first manifestation of your
relationship to any given situation. It
is not. It is the second manifestation.
The first manifestation is what you
believe to be true. What you believe to
be true is what you experience in your
physical reality. Then what you
experience in your physical reality as
the product of what you believe to be
true creates the reaction of feeling an
emotion within you.
That emotion may then reinforce the
original belief which may then recreate
the situation to give you another
reaction. But the idea first and
foremost is that you have your own proof
to begin with. Anything that you
experience in life, you experience
because you believe that to be a
plausible, possible, and the most likely
reality you can experience at any given
moment. whether it is positive or
negative. Now it does not necessarily
mean that you have a very specific
definition that oh yes I exactly
precisely believe that I was about to
stub my nose. The idea simply may be
however that you may have a very
strongly ingrained belief in the
experience or needing the experience of
pain perhaps to remind you of something
to wake you up to shock you into the
center of your being.
And that manifestation will then occur
in your physical reality along the path
of least resistance. The one that is the
easiest and quickest manifestation of
the ingrained generalized
belief. Are you all following along?
Yes. In this way, therefore, with the
idea of anything you experience in your
reality, since it becomes from your
belief system to begin with, remember
this. What you experience in your
physical reality therefore is not in
your physical reality as a
representation that you are stuck in
that physical reality. It is not a
situation that is in your life as a
representation of the idea that you have
failed in something else in your
reality. The situations that are in your
life are in your life to act as a mirror
of the beliefs that exist within you. So
you can consciously know what those
beliefs are. The physical situations
that occur in your life are there to
show you what beliefs you have bought
into. And if you don't prefer them now
that you are aware of what they are,
change them. The situations that occur
in your life are there to give you the
opportunity at any given moment to
recognize what it is you choose to
believe in and what type of a reality
you desire to experience. All these
situations that occur are the feedback
reflective mechanisms to allow you at
any given moment to be completely and
utterly in touch with what you believe
your reality to be. In no way, shape or
form do situations occur because you are
stuck or condemned to repeat them or
because you have failed to create
something else. They are there simply to
point out the perspective and point of
view you have and if you don't prefer it
to then recognize that you can take the
perspective and point of view you have
which is very easy to know what it is
because you simply look at the situation
around you. Look at the physical reality
in your life. That is appropriate
general definition of what you believe
and you can then having the definition
now redefine it. That's what your
imagination is for. It is the key the
tool to unlock you from any reality you
do not
prefer. And in this way orient you into
the reality that you do
prefer. And of course allow us to remind
you once again that when we say prefer
and not prefer, we do not mean that you
invalidate the reality you no longer
prefer. For to invalidate that reality
is to cut off a portion of your being.
And that action only puts you more
squarely locked into that which you deny
as a part of your
being. You all follow along.
Thus in this way we simply give to
you our suggestion along with whatever
assurance is available to
us that not because it comes from us but
simply because it is the way existence
is that you are all
absolutely without exception guaranteed
100% by the universe, by the infinite
creation that anything you truly believe
is true for you will be the reality you
experience. Physical reality is the
shadow of your soul, the shadow of the
idea you are at any given moment.
All you need to center in on these ideas
and see them manifest in ecstatic
explosions of synchronicity and
coincidence in your
life is the ability to
trust that what you believe to be true
for you is true and workable for you and
manifestable for you in your life
without struggle, without strife,
without effort, automatically with ease.
I'll follow along.
Sure. Scar. No, that's me. That's not
it. [Laughter]
[Laughter]
Proceed. Yay. I got right into you there
for sure. Things are going terrific.
Wonderful. Um, wanted to share that.
Thank you. Uh, thank you for your
reflections and you as well. My
pleasure. Um, you answered this once
before. My friend recently came up. One
moment. One moment. Yes. Yes. Allow us,
if you will, as you say, a brief
advertisement. No.
Once again allows to remind each and
every one of
you that any other individual you find
yourself able to
perceive any group that you find
yourself interacting with. Any
opportunity that you have created to
hear what any individual has to say has
merit for you as well. Anything anyone
says can be applied to the understanding
of the growth and expansion of your own
being. There is nothing frivolous,
nothing extraneous and it is no accident that
extraneous and it is no accident that
you will hear anything that anyone else
has to say. It can always be applied. It
may have relative degrees of what you
would call immediacy or importance to
you. But always anything anyone has to
share is a gift and an opportunity for
each and every one of you to recognize a
way in which to turn that phrase that
they have shared into one that has
relevancy for
you. We remind you once again there are
no boring situations only bored minds.
Proceed. Nice promotion. Bashar, the
real motion of a pro.
Reflect again ways in which we can
handle nuclear waste on this planet.
Now, first of all, recognize that in
allowing yourself to equalize with what
you call your governments, that will be
one way for then the sharing and the
service that will go on between you will
allow you to listen to each other and to
cease to promote the ideas of the
devices that promote that type of what
you would call a hazard. That is first
and foremost fundamental communication.
Second, the idea in this way that if you
are simply of a certain vibrational
density and that vibrational density
does not contain the idea of the harmful
effects of that substance, then you will
never feel
it and in that sense you will allow it
to vibrate out of the reality you
vibrate into. You follow me? Beautiful.
Third, we find that there is a high
degree of probability of two
methodologies available to you within
approximately potentially the next
decade. One will be the idea of a
substance which is similar to what you
would call a polymer construction,
plastic construction in this way whose
organic matrix will have the ability to
directly absorb absorb
the
radiated elements and in this way not
allow them to pass that barrier by
becoming locked into the matrix of the
polymer itself. And with this you can
build containers that will be in your
terms leak proof. Another methodology
that we sense may have great potential
coming up in your civilization will be
the use of what you colloially refer to
as a specific type of force field. one
in a sense that will have should it be
perceivable from the interior a highly
reflective surface because of the modulation of the
surface because of the modulation of the
electromagnetic field into a form of
bubble and in this way that can also
contain the idea and not allow it to
expand beyond what you would call the
skin or shell of the electromagnetic
bubble. You follow me. Thank you. In our
culture, um what technological research
is is has the best momentum in that
particular those particular areas? Many
of ideas that are now being undertaken
with regard to also what you would
colloquially call the research into
anti-gravity. For in this way you will
find that the generation of many of the
isolation fields necessary to isolate
any craft from the gravity field of your
planet will also function to isolate the
idea of any hazardous material from the
rest of the environment. Excellent.
Thank you. It will in a sense be like
removing it into another dimensional
frame of reference
where it can radiate freely causing no
harm. You follow me? I do. Thank you. you
You follow me? I do. Thank you. you
would you please share with me your
perspective on my inspiration my channel
in this place can you speak up please
would you please share with me some
ideas along the lines of my exploration
of my channeling
all right thank you our
basic perception at this time will be to
remind you that you in many ways are
still gathering together the different
members of the family units that you
perceive yourself to be to function as a
whole in that way. Thus, as you have
already discussed, our suggestion would
be continuing the idea of the reliance
upon your own abilities rather than the
extension of what you may immediately
perceive to be the abilities of
something beyond your own immediate
consciousness. For in this way it will
put you in touch with more familiarity
of your own being and a familiarity with
all the portions within yourself you
have created to represent the different
ideas of the family that you are many
times symbolized by your actual physical
family around you in many different ways
and some of what you may call your
friends for they are also part of your
family. And to simply see what each and
every member of that family around you
represents to you so that you can be in
touch squarely in touch with that
different portion and aspect of
yourself. And then by inviting all those
different portions of yourself to gather
together as one idea will you then put
yourself once again squarely in touch
with your full potential as a
sensitized being in that way. For many
times you simply find that you create a
reluctance to be sensitized to the
points of views of others in that way.
In this way, it is nothing we are
chiding you for nor chastising, but
simply that the particular idea that you
chose within this physiological life
that you are nearing the end of the
cycle of is the idea of the
fragmentation of relationships within
the idea of the being that you are
specifically with regard to what you
would call the familial attachments. And
in this way, therefore, as you gather
the being that you are together as your
own family, then you will see all the
reflections of your sensitivity to other
points of view within the family that
you have. And in this way, as you become
that one family within yourself, you
will be sensitized to everything you
also can consider to be your family that
is extended in space and time. You
follow me?
Thank you very much. Rashelle, you
I would like to talk to you a little bit
about um a perception I've been having
and see what you think about it. Maybe
well that maybe it's up to you. Um you
know the book you've uh been channeling
and have is being transcribed. I and
some of the sessions are being
transcribed too. I and I've been
assisting in proof reading the
transcriptions. Thank you. And yes, I
enjoy it very much. And um now the
process of
reading when you when you process
information while you're reading
compared to listening is very is very
different. And uh as I'm proofreading
it, it occurs to me that sometimes
uh some of the sentences and this is not
a judgment. This is just an observation
uh are extremely long. And uh the
transcribers doing are doing a very good
job punctuating and so once in a sense
they are editing while they're nice
punctuating. Um now I know you have an
agreement that nothing should be
changed. Oh that is not so oh I I was
wondering the idea simply is is that it
may be in your terms
perused for final acknowledgement no
matter in what form it winds up. Uhhuh.
But in this way it is also up to you to
trust in the way that you find it best
to condense the understanding for all
things change. Our mode of delivery
changes along with the availability of
changes to occur within the channel
along with availability of changes that
occur within you. It becomes as you say
more direct more succinct. In this way,
many of what you may find to
be the
[Music] roundabout sharings that we have had
roundabout sharings that we have had
with you are the product of many things.
One, do not forget we are not speaking
your language, but we are modulating
what is available to us within the
vocabulary of the channel. And we also
learn how to be more concise. Right? I
understand that very well.
Secondly, you will find that much of
what may appear upon simple
observational reading to be a very
roundabout statement when it has the
particular type of
inflections and energy patterns that go
along with it will actually be an
extended conversation. And perhaps in a
sense two or three of what you would
call sentences run together because we
are speaking to you simultaneously from
many different points of view. I
understand. And it may come out as one
long sentence when in fact it is in fact
two or three. I understand. But as you
find yourself within your own intuition
and in your own centered
being condensing the
idea and putting it forward, then we
will in this way simply once
again as you say peruse the final
results, perhaps make a suggestion or
two, but the idea is for you to treat as
anything as an in the moment moment
creation and not something that is
rigidized or fixated in time for then it
would only become as you say stale and
outdated. I thought perhaps um first the
first proof reading I do or somebody
else does, we do it exactly as it is and
and then perhaps two or three people
might look at some of the sentences that
are that appear quite awkward and maybe
get together and rephrase it or maybe
change a few words here and there and
then then ask either Donald to look at
it or or check all Since the link
between us is always open for that type
of observation. But simply also
understand many times what may seem on
the surface to be awkward is said in the
way we have channeled it through for
specific reasons. And what may seem to
be awkward in this way may also be
necessary for a certain type of
understanding or inflection. I
understand. And and those of us who are
used to the way you talk, we pick that
up as we're reading it. But if the book
is going to be sold, would understand.
Yeah. Then then perhaps simply proceed
as you will. Okay, great. Thank you very
much. Thank you guys. One moment.
I would like to thank you for the
reflections and insights that you sent
to me that helped me to relate to, feel,
and integrate the intense emotional
experience of my husband's transition
from the the spiritual pardon me
physical dimension into the spiritual
one. That is no error. All right?
Physical dimension is just the
spiritual. All right?
Um, I wanted to thank I I have not been
here on Wednesday night for a few weeks,
but some friends did um present this
situation to you and you sent some
feedback which I did get and I that is
what I wanted to thank you for. We thank
you for your willingness to open up in
the ability you have to sense that life
always exists and simply transforms in
many different ways and that you are
always in touch with whatever facet you
need to be in touch with. Thank you. May
I ask a question? You do not have to ask
if you can ask otherwise you have
already asked and we shall move on.
I was planning a trip to San Francisco
this weekend. have a good time. And all And all
right.
Um, my question had to do with the trip
because I was feeling that I didn't want
to take the trip after all. That is up
to you. Okay. We have nothing to say
about whether you should or should not
take a trip. The idea is to simply
follow what excites you the most and
trust that at any given moment, if you
do so, it will always lead you squarely
to where you need to be led by yourself.
If you change your mind, so to speak,
then simply be in touch honestly with
yourself as to why your mind has
changed. If it is simply that you
recognize that something else truly is
more exciting now, then go with it. If
you have changed your mind because you
feel you might be fearing or running
from something, then examine that
honestly and get in touch with the idea
that many times things that you fear may
simply be the excitement that you feel
about going, but you are putting
invalidations upon it. And so it comes
through as anxiety or fear because
excitement and anxiety are the same
energy. One that is judged and one that
isn't. You follow me? I do. So simply get in
You follow me? I do. So simply get in
touch with the idea as to why your mind
has changed. Whether it is because you
are running from something or because
you are going to something else.
Thank you very much.
You nice. Okay. Um I got a letter this week
nice. Okay. Um I got a letter this week
from a lady named Jean Prince in London.
when she was in Los Angeles, she came to
hear you and she sends you blessings and
she asks if you know of any channels in
the London area you would recommend for
her to
hear. We cannot in this way call by
name. There are several. The idea,
however, will also be to trust once
again her own instincts and recognize
that if such an interaction is
necessary, all she has to do is open up
and she will attract herself into that
situation. The one that is in accordance
with the vibration she is at that given
moment, one
moment. What we find may be
The most narrowing we can do at this
time in sensing the flow of that energy
or potential interaction will be to
recommend the area referred to as
Southampton. Thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you for
Yay.
Good evening. It's Switcher. Hey
Switcher. Um, I have a sharing, an invitation, and
Um, I have a sharing, an invitation, and
a question. My My
The sharing is, uh, I've just completed
writing a play. Oh,
did you have a comment? Oh, okay. That
was it.
Very significant.
It's a uh full length dramatic comedy.
It's a lot of fun. Oh, we thank you for
allowing it to be full length.
You're welcome. I I did that
specifically for you. You find it. It
would be quite fascinating to us should
you be able to come up with a play that
stops halfway.
I did that first.
I did that at first because the people
in this town in in Hollywood are used to
a lot of half-assed things and so but I
thought no uh Bashar would like it to be
fully asked. So
I anyway uh it's a lot of fun and uh
it's a transformational play disguised
very well as a modern mainstream society
piece and uh anybody who's
Thank you. Anybody who's transforming or
understands a transformation will go hey
this is a transformational play. Anybody
who doesn't understand that consciously
will just experience the transformation
without necessarily a conscious
recognition of it. All right. Should be
a lot of fun. Thank you. The invitation
is that we're looking for a theater uh
small theater 99 seats or less and we're
looking for funding. So I invite anyone
who would like to to read the play,
contact me, read the play. If they have
a theater or know somebody who does or
is interested in providing funding or
know someone who would be interested in
doing that, I invite their
uh they're contacting me and they can
contact me through uh Steve. Okay,
through Steve uh or else contact me
here. I know this tape goes out to a lot
of people. So I invite anybody who hears
the tape also to do the same thing. The
uh that's the sharing and invitation.
Not and the question the question a
different subject altogether. Do you on
your planet have a technology for
creating tractor beams? I how do you do
it and what do you use it for?
The idea in this way will be once again
simply a modulation of the gravitic
dynamic tensor fields. It is not so much
in the manner we perceive that you most
often think of the application of that
idea. It is more of a field than a beam.
But in this way, what it is utilized for
is to not only form but hold in place
what forms upon the energy template for
our spacecraft to suspend them in space
in a sense and time so that they may
grow crystallize upon the energy
template which is also in a sense a
version of that idea. For it is
attractive to the crystallin form in a
certain way, holds it in a very
rigidized pattern, so to
speak. You follow me?
Yes. Do you do you use this ever to uh
to draw something that already exists
closer to you from time to time? But
again, it is simply that we
redefine tractor beam as you would call
it is more of what you may term actually
a tunnel than a beam of attractive
force. It is that which allows the
gravitic dynamic tensor field of
spacetime to be bent or ticked so that
something will slide downhill toward us.
You follow me? Uh yeah. Is it does it
then involve gravity or is it more the
idea of um it is the bending of the
gravity wave in a sense rather than an
actual beam itself. It is a
tensor relationship. I don't understand.
It is a distortion if you wish rather
than an actual beam of force. A
distortion of the already existent
gravity dynamic field. Okay. In simple
terms, could you say then it in effect
increases the gravity by doing this? No.
Okay. It distorts it.
It distorts it.
Okay. It is simply another application
of the way our craft move within
spaceime. At sublight speeds, we distort
the gravity field around us and slide on
it. That is why very often you will
notice that our spacecraft when entering
your gravity field above your planet in
your atmosphere may bobble and weave as
if it is bobbing up and down upon water.
You follow me? Uh yes, I do. Because the
gravitic field is
distorted like a
lens and allows the ship in that way to
hover by constantly creating a type of
depression or
ripple which fluctuates to some degree
in which the ship rests.
Okay, I'm I'm getting the picture now.
Would it be possible
to extend a microwave field such as you
use to uh to transport your ship, extend
a microwave field out to um another
object, change its space, time,
location, the way you change your
spaceship and but this is rarely done
without very
precise as you would say calculations.
It can render the object outside of the
spacecraft because it is in what you
would call an
asymmetrical balance. It could
possibly well as you would say render
its structure
structure
inadverently out of alignment. Oh, I
see. Okay. Thank you. Bashar. Oh, venue.
Okay. Thank you. Bashar. Oh, venue.
Basher, I had asked about a friend of
mine that had left the physical had died
uh 3 months ago now. Um a friend of mine
had died three months ago.
And I would like to have more
information about how we on this side
can help him on his path as he continues
in his evolution. Do you love him very
much? Then you are helping him. Mhm. The
idea is to simply send all the love and
support knowing that he is still a vital
being, still very much alive, still very
much in life. And if you simply send
your unconditional love and your
knowledge of his vitality, that will
spur him on and provide for him the
foundation that he requires so that he
can allow the so-called attachments that
may still be remaining to the physical
reality to change so that he can
transform as quickly as he
can. You follow me? Yes. Also,
um, his death has seemed to affect a lot
of people in a lot of different ways as
always. And I'm wondering how his death
is speeding up or altering the work that
many of us have to do on this planet.
That depends upon the individual. But
many times you will find just as a
general foundation that sometimes when one
foundation that sometimes when one
individual as you say transforms into
non-physical reality before many others
to which they are attached you will find
that it may simply be for the purpose of
allowing those individuals still
physical to stretch their senses into
the non-physical realm because now a
piece of themsel they know exists there.
So, it broadens and expands your
sensitivity and your ability to
communicate with more portions of your
own non-physical self.
Has my connection with him spanned a lot
of lifetimes?
Yes, quite a few.
Can you tell me something of the most
recent? Why?
I guess in gathering all my parts
together in my relationship to him. All
right. Now, allow us to remind you of
something before we
proceed. The idea of this understanding
of your past lives is very valid and can
be of great assistance to you. However,
our hesitancy in this idea first of all
comes from two basic reasons. One, you
have the ability to sense that those
ideas to which you find yourself most
attracted, most drawn in your
imagination with regard to any past life
are the ones that are most valid for
what you need to look at now. And you
have the ability to sense them out for
yourself. Secondly, many individuals in your
Secondly, many individuals in your
society still think that what they are
in this life and the power they have to
be what they wish to be in this life
comes from what they have done in the
past. And it
doesn't what you have done in the past
so to speak you can gather together and
learn from by all means but what you
have done in the past in no way shape or
form controls nor determines your
ability to be whatever you desire to be
in the present. And so many times we
will exhibit a reluctance to take people
out of the present and place their focus
on the past simply because they are not
yet willing to recognize that they have
right now at any given moment based upon
whatever sensitivities they are aware of
the ability to be whatever they desire
to be regardless of anything they have
ever been in the past. The present is
not a result of the past in a controlled
way. I understand. All right.
Therefore, recognize that the idea of
what you sense as the connections
between you may also not necessarily be
exhibited in a linear sense and what you
would call the immediate past life.
But in this life, the life you are now,
what will stand out to you will be the
past lives that you need to understand now in
lives that you need to understand now in
order to continue to be what you are
now. You will create certain
relationships with the past lives to
stand out according to at any given
moment what you think of yourself in the
present. As you change, perhaps
different lives will stand out. You may
now think, well, it seems to me that the
life I had five lifetimes ago is
definitely the most important life I
have had recently. 10 years from now,
you may say, well, the life I had 20
times ago now seems to be more
important. It will change and shift with
the idea of your changes and shifts in
the present. You follow me? Yes. What
are you attracted to now?
the lives surrounding Atlantis. All
right. Well, that is no surprise in
general, for many of you are, almost all
of you are reincarnated Atlanteanss. For
in this way, you will find that your
United States of America is an almost
exact historic parallel of Atlantis. And
many of you are now undertaking similar
not the same similar ideas once again so
as to experience the transformation you
went through before from as you say the
other side of the coin and allow
yourself positive integration rather
than the idea of negative
destruction. And do not forget many of
you we understand are prone to say well
what was my life in Atlantis? Atlantis
spanned thousands of your years. Many of
you have had hundreds if not thousands
of lives in
Atlantis. What idea attracts you the
most now?
The idea of the priestess. All
right. What can you learn from that
particular facet or reflection of
yourself in the idea of what you are
becoming now?
How to manifest more quickly. All right.
All that takes is
trust. Trust that wherever you are at
any given moment is where you need to
be. And that what you do
desire if you are directly honestly in
touch with what you believe you need
will always be seen to be manifested
almost instantaneously.
Now we will also give you this. Once
again, though we rarely recommend, we
will in your terms recommend that there
is already many powerful impactful
techniques that exist within your
literature and society for the idea of
getting in touch with your belief
systems and creating the ability to
manifest what you desire.
One of these comes from the
consciousness you already call Lazarus
and exists in the form you call tape. We
would suggest that you perhaps if you
wish do not have to avail yourself of
this understanding simply because it is
so very focused and so very precise.
Other than
that we would turn you over to your own
imagination and your own
trust. Understand something. Many of you
have heard us many times simply turn
back to you the idea of trusting your
imagination. Get in touch with the fact
that when we do suggest that you get in
touch with your
imagination, we are not simply being
philosophical. Your imagination is the
key to anything you desire. It is what
you can always always
always any exceptions no none
always rely upon to provide you if you
need a method if you need a technique if
you need an exercise if you need a
ritual your imagination can provide you
with the technique the exercise the
ritual that you need. Your imagination
is a dimension unto itself. It is the
dimension in which you exist, so to
speak. It is the door and the gate in
physical reality through which all
recognition and awareness of what is
possible and potential for you can
come. It is keyed to the vibration you
are. That is why if you rely upon your
imagination, you will always find that
your imagination is able to supply you
with whatever method will work
specifically for you. Otherwise, it
would be someone else's imagination.
You can always rely that if you feel you
wish to get in touch with a certain
idea, certain thing and you wish to go
about creating a method to do so,
relax, center, breathe, meditate, open
into your imagination and say this is
what I desire. I believe I would like a
particular method for the manifestation
of this idea.
how will work most quickly for me. Then
pay
attention. How it comes to
you will be perhaps in many different
ways. It may come as a picture. It may
come as a feeling. It may come as a
knowingness. It may come as a
synchronistic situation in your life as
an action that you do. It may come in
many different ways. Do not put too many
demands on how you think it should come
to you. Let it come in the way that
represents the path of least resistance.
You follow me? Yes. Trust, trust, trust.
It does work if you let it. Many of you
may simply be out of the habit of
listening to the subtle communications
that always go on between your higher
self and your physical self. But they
are only subtle because you have been
taught to not believe that they are
there. As soon as you begin to listen
and trust what comes to you first in
your intuition, then it will become much more
intuition, then it will become much more
expansive, much less subtle, much more
obvious, much more transparent.
All you need to do is begin to
listen to the being that you are and you
will find that you always know what you
know when you need to know it. You don't
need to know it before you need to know
it. When you need to know it, you know
it. So when you put yourself in a centered
So when you put yourself in a centered
position in a relaxed and open state of
unconditionality, whatever comes to you
is what you need to know. Act on what
you get. Thank you. And trust that that
action will
always flawless in this life. All right.
Thank you. Hi. I haven't been able to be
here uh physically for four weeks. It is
all right. Well, great stuff. I listened
and the shark came in my dream and at
times when I was working and so I feel
um wonderful things have happened. I
have two things I want to talk with you.
One is yesterday was the 18th
anniversary of my father's death. Oh,
what? And this morning in a very loving
meditation group that I belong to uh a
lot came up for me about his his death
and my loss and feeling what the loss I
feel in not having him here. Although I
do contact him he does feel like he's
coming as a spiritual guide. Uh but
today was a lot of feelings about where
is he? Um what's happened to him? Uh I
have a sense sometimes he was a a
magnificent musician and music teacher
and I have a sense that my youngest
nephew uh is somehow connected to this because
uh is somehow connected to this because
all of is a part of the same whole soul.
Yes. But not exactly what you would call
a direct complete reincarnation. Okay.
Because two years ago he began to play
music. Yes. And just began to write
songs. But there was much communication
in the non-physical reality.
before that creation of the split off of
the soul occurred. That being in this
way therefore contains the memory of
that communication and a tap a direct
tap into that ability. But the idea of
the overall energy of the being that you
would have recognized in this way much
of it quote unquote. Now this is all
colloquialisms in the terminology that
makes sense in your language the most.
Most of that individual still exists in
non-physical reality in the vibratory
sphere, if you will, of that of like
attracts like and is interacting as many
other individuals and spirits that
express themselves musically upon your
world. Beautiful to know because I feel
like somehow my my father died too soon
that the world should have known his
music and didn't. There weren't tapered
cars and that kind of thing. So that I
that's what was was the way it was.
What how did he die?
The idea of the life as he lived it was
what it was. Period. There are no should
have been.
It was what it was. And what it was was
what that soul needed to experience.
Period. No regrets. That soul experiences no
No regrets. That soul experiences no
regrets. Why should you? Well, that does
sound like my dad, I'll tell you that.
And you would be hanging out with
musicians. That would be for sure.
Um, okay. I I just I just really was in
touch with a lot of feelings about him
this week. All right. But again, allow
us to remind you when you say, "Well, I
was in touch with a lot of feelings,"
allow yourself also to let those
feelings put you in touch with the
beliefs that create them. And if you
find that the feelings are negative,
then get in touch with the beliefs that
are negative so that you do not
necessarily need to have negative
feelings. Mhm. So that you know there is
no loss except when you believe in
separation following. Yes very much. Thank you very
following. Yes very much. Thank you very
much. Thank you. I wanted to um say one
other thing though. Um my husband and I
have recently co-created a company that
we have named Atlantan Waves. All right.
And he's talked to you a lot about his
life one of his life in Atlanta. Nice.
And the thing that came up very strongly
for the first major project for this
company is we are hosting uh a
conference with Bashar down in San Diego
where we now live. Nice. And the um
everything has been very synchronistic.
The channel is always home. At the
moment I need to call him about an ad or
something like that. Nice. a good friend
who's here tonight, Fletcher, came in at
the right moment in our life to begin
helping promote uh and advertise the
conference. Uh San Diego is now waiting
with baited breath for Bashar, who we
talk about all the
time. I threw that. I threw that in. I
threw that in just
um and I wanted to know the conference
is December 8th. Things are going
beautifully. We're expecting a lot of
people. Um, I would just like to know if
there are other things that um you would
like to see happen or you'd like to see
us do at this point or can share with us
about this conference. It feels I this
is one of the most exciting things I've
been doing in the last month. It's
really great. Well, I do. No further
comment. No further comment. Okay. Well,
we'll see you in San Diego. Yes. Okay.
I would like to know a little bit. Speak
up. I would like to know a little bit
about the plan trans transformation on
the inner and outer core from social to
super consciousness. A little bit about
that. All right.
All right.
Can you be more specific? Um maybe just
something that maybe the whole group as
a consciousness would benefit from.
You obviously have a cognition of the
idea of the transformation from third to
fourth density within you. You obviously
have a version of this idea that
vibrates within your very
core. What if I may ask you, do you
imagine you will be doing in this
transformation that will represent the
idea that your world has changed?
How will you reflect all of the changes
that you do know are going on? For going
on, of course they are.
Be in totality of allowance of the love
that I am.
Would you repeat that a little louder?
Be in totality of allowance of the love
that I am. I see. Well, thank you.
In this way, therefore, recognize that
that totality is what will quote unquote seep
totality is what will quote unquote seep
into the total awareness of your
collective consciousness.
But remember
this, many individuals in your
society have been taught that in order
to allow the mass mentality to become
blended in order to become one
world, one collective consciousness that
you have to give up your identity and
individuality. No, just the opposite.
No, just the opposite.
For just as
you are an individual and yet you have
are an individual and yet you have
created yourself to be represented by
many different personality fragments,
you know that you are the strongest
collected individual you can be when
each and every one of those fragments
within you that you have created is
equal to every other fragment and
equally strong. You follow me?
Thus, the ability for you to
become a super conscious civilization in
that way, the ability for that
particular level of existence that you
are, that particular oversoul that you
are to have the fullest cognizance of
its existence as a singular identity
will come from the equality and equal
strength of all the individuals of which
it is composed.
So the stronger you are in expressing
yourself as your individual, as the
individual facet of the
multi-dimensional crystal you chose to
be in this life, the more opportunity
you will allow for the blending of the
superconscious to occur and manifest
itself in your
reality. Each and every individual that
does this makes a difference in the
ability of the total whole to accelerate
into that blending.
And when one individual makes an
impactful difference, two
individuals, three individuals, four
individuals add a geometrically
accelerated ability to the entire
society to be able to choose that
reality for themselves as well.
This whole idea of the compounding of
acceleration is one of the primary
motivating energies that will be
experienced in fourth density
reality where you will
access more of the totality of your
being. And that is why you will find
that you will create less and less need
for time in which to experience that
totality. And so while you have
experienced the idea of limitation and
separation and segregation for hundreds
of thousands of years, now that you are
laying the foundations for
integration, centering within the now
moment and living in the now moment and
creating less time in which to
experience the idea and the beingness of
yourselves, you will find that fourth
density reality will generally, as we
perceive it, not need to cover more than
approximately 2 to 3,000 of your years
further. And beyond that, you will have
no need to exist as a physiological
culture anymore. Many of you may decide to, oh,
anymore. Many of you may decide to, oh,
let's say stick
around and function as spirit guide for
the next group who choose to incarnate
physically upon what would have been
your older. And in this way, it will then be
older. And in this way, it will then be
the creation of a new cycle.
Many of
them in being sensitive to the existence
of your non-physical assistance may
start thinking of
you as oh let's say the nature spirits
that came along with the
territory. Will this have been of
assistance? Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Uh just completing a uh video project
that will include a booklet and an audio
tape. The audio tape will include
various samples of uh channels and uh
how did you feel about allowing some of
the channeling that is oddly heard here
to be represented on that tape to give
the uh people's an oversight of various
different modes and the variation of
facet. We are always willing to allow
the participation to be shared in that
way. As long as the idea of what you
call the integrity of the original
information whether literally or not is
maintained, it will be thus in this way
always once again since the link with
the physical channel always exists. In
this way, as you are ready to proceed,
simply share the format you have created
with the physical channel and without a
blending without a connection will
always come the intuitiveness and the
understanding as to whether or not it is
in the format that does in fact reflect
the original integrity. Thank you.
Hey, um my mother has been visiting uh
California. She's been here for a couple
of weeks. She's had lunch. pick up.
She's had lots of positive change and
expansion. All right. And in two days,
she goes back to the east coast. I see.
And she is now ill. All right. Um the
symptoms are diarrhea and vomiting and
stomach discomfort and stiffness in her
limbs. Can you give me some reflection
insight on this if it has to do with uh
energy vibrational changes? Well, to
some degree although it is also to some
degree the idea of what you would call
the flu but in this way still recognize that
flu but in this way still recognize that
any physiological symbol even something
that may seem to be quite ordinary to
you always has a consciousness reason
for having been attracted to that being.
Some of it may be a lack of willingness
to
[Music] return to the original
return to the original
environment. Some of it may be an
acclimatization to the new environment
in which they are have been as you say
residing of
reason. It is an orientation and that
individual will find that even when they
return things will not be the same. They
will have a different perspective, a
different point of view and they will
actually be able to bring some of the
ideas so to speak with them. And in that
old environment, well, some of what will
represent the new understanding they
have of
themselves, well, let us just say they
may find that the ideas they are willing
to share in the old environment may have
a certain infectious quality about them.
This is true. She's taking tapes back
and articles on channeling into a
totally new environment that has not
been sharing in this simply allow her to
recognize that anytime any individual
places upon themsself that particular
type of manifestation. It is only to
allow them to acquire their bearings and
make sure that they are in a sense
buffered in a way that will allow them
to shift the gears without trauma to
relax to center in the energy that she
feels to be true for her. And once she
orients herself squarely in the
direction of that flow of that energy
then there will be no friction anymore
between a new idea and an old idea which
in a sense is all that is causing the
fevers within the body. Um is there
anything else I can do particularly to
or you know on a physical level to help
you can share of your electromagnetic
oric energy blue white energy
surrounding each other in this way
interacting sharing of unconditional
love and recognizing that you are an
energy being an electromagnetic being in
this way you are a being of light she is
a being of light can allow yourselves to
see yourselves as blue crystallin energy
spheres that are homogeneous balanced
flowing without any particular portion
of them standing out above and beyond
any other portion in color, size, shape,
intensity. And once you are balanced in
that type of electromagnetic flow, you
can allow yourselves to be aligned much
like a battery. And then in a body that
is centered and aligned
electromagnetically, all the cells will
be oriented along the line of flow of
the being that you are becoming. There
will be less friction. The being will
become superconductive. And in this way
the energy will flow freely and quickly
through the body. And in this way a body
that is centered and flowing has no room
for the definition of disease.
You following? Yes. Thank you. All right.
All right.
One of the things you talked about was
imagination as a solution
as a methodology. Yes. I'm in the middle
of an eviction notice and a company
takeover. All right. But instead, how
exciting. Instead of looking for an apartment or a
Instead of looking for an apartment or a
job, all that I keep coming up with is
the idea for a new book. All right. Go
to it.
Where do I live in the meantime? Who
knows? But
But
if the idea of the new book truly
represents what excites you the
most, then all you need to bring along
with you as your luggage is the trust
that doing what excites you the most
will always attract to you the ability
to allow you to do it. And if the
ability to allow you to do it means that
you have to have somewhere to live then
somewhere will be provided.
You follow me? Maybe maybe just a
suggestion just as an example just by
analogy certain individuals may find
that let's say all right to take your
example I wish to write a book but I
need a place to live. Well maybe maybe
not. Maybe the
book will be written because of many
travels you will take. And since you
will be traveling, you need no permanent
home. You will stay wherever you need to
stay and you will attract to yourself
whatever you need to provide you with
the ability to be the idea you are
being. The universe always works and
always supports you 100% always in
whatever idea you are willing to
be. You can always flow with your
trust and you can always flow with what
excites you the
most. Pay attention.
There is no trying necessary. I am thank
you. Excitement. Remember excitement what
Excitement. Remember excitement what
excites you the most you can always
trust that you can act upon because
excitement is the physical
translation of the vibratory energy that
represents the path you chose to
be. That is why it is always effortless
and your life unfolds automatically when
you simply do at any given moment what
excites you the most. Excitement is your
signal, your arrow, your barometer, your
gauge, your indicator to let you know
that no matter what the surface
situation may appear to be like. No
matter how disconnected one situation
may appear from another situation, if
they both contain the idea or have in
their own timings contained the same
idea of excitement, it is the excitement
that lets you know they're a part of the
path you chose to be and are
connected. Follow it. It will always
attract to you the ecstatic explosion of
coincidence that is necessary in your
life, knowing you're at the right place
at the right time. interacting with
exactly the right individuals to allow
you to be the individual you need to be
so you can be of service to them and
they can be of service to you
automatically, coincidentally,
effortlessly, not accidentally. There
are no
accidents. It is all orchestrated by you
spontaneously orchestrated. And in this way, you can
orchestrated. And in this way, you can
always find yourself, if you act upon
what excites you the most, attracting
yourself into what may seem
analytically, intellectually, to be the
most unlikely of circumstances. Well, I
am really excited about accepting, let
us say, this invitation to go here. But
what has that got to do with the idea
that I need a place to live? I refuse to
follow my excitement because I do not
analytically believe in my ego that that
is where I should be in order to go
about trying struggling to find a place
to live.
However, if it is what excites you the
most and you simply accept the
invitation, you may run into exactly the
individual who will perhaps provide you
with a place to live. Maybe they're
going out of town and they want somebody
to stay there
[Laughter] [Music]
free. Maybe they will provide you with a
job that will allow you to actually get
the writing done more quickly and will
allow you to travel as you say to
boot. Who knows? The point is you do not
have the need. You do not have the
analytical need to have to know all the
different ways consciously that you
could be provided for. So why even
bother to try and focus on the details?
Let the details fall into place by
allowing yourself to focus on the trust
and the excitement. You follow me? Yes.
Does that assist you? Yes. will allow me
to assist you a little bit further by
suggesting that you have a very lovely
break. [Music]
How's everything going? All
right, I'll say shouting
you.
All right. Now, we have to some degree
already done some of this. that already
exists in some of what you would call
the literature or forms that exist of
our discussion. We will simply in this
way allow you to fill in the details but
we will give you a
brief idea. In this
idea. In this
way, your
society in having created itself to be
one that has refused to examine the
that has refused to examine the
polarities within
itself has not allowed the blending of
the male and female energies to take
place within each and every individual
on an equal basis.
Thus has created the opportunity for
individuality to create within their
lives an
expression of what seems to be to the
mainstream if we may use that term of
your society an imbalance of expression
of one side or the other of their
sexuality. And in this way it is as a
reflection that each and every
individual both physically male and
physically female contains the ability
of the expression of both
energy. Your society in still refusing
to see the symbol for what it was and
recognize it as a reflection as an
opportunity to see that male and female
energy exists within each and every
individual. thus continue the
perpetuation of the
idea of allowing certain individuals to
choose themselves to represent the idea
one way or another in its seemingly
dichotomy expression and in all the judgments and
expression and in all the judgments and
invalidations placed by the mainstream
of the society upon that portion of
themselves. Then those individuals
reflecting the containment of both
energies took it upon themselves in this
way many times subconsciously to believe
in those invalidations and therefore to
create within themselves a cutting off
of a portion of their own blending an
extension of that invalidation in the
form of disease.
very simply and concisely
put, the inability of your society to
allow certain ideas of blending and
balancing to occur within it thus has
now cocreated the dropping of all barriers
cocreated the dropping of all barriers
and
immunities to that recognition. Now you
have created yourself to be forced to
deal with the blending of the energies
of male and femaleness within your
society. So that when each and every
individual chooses to allow that to be
equal within their own being no matter
what they physiologically are and can
function as a balanced being in the form
of the expression that they have chosen
to exist physically. Then there will be
no more need for the forcing of the
dropping of these barriers to force them
to interact with those individuals who
have functioned as symbols of expression
that each and every individual does
contain both sides.
Then when there is that blending and
that balancing and let it say that
marriage of the energy within the being
that you are, there will no longer be
any need for the idea of the expression
of what you generally call. Not that is
right or wrong, but the expression of
homosexuality in this way will simply no
longer be necessary as a tool. Simply
because each and every being will be
balanced and blended within the
expression that they are and will
consciously be aware of how they choose
to express that energy when they become
physical. And therefore the physical
body that they choose will be a direct
reflection of the way they wish to
express that energy. And also there will
be no need when you blend and balance
that energy within yourself. No need for
the disease as well. And we are not only
speaking of the disease you call AIDS
but of any
disease. Now will this assist you to
some degree? Yes. The main reason I I
wanted to ask about it uh is number one
I noticed that a lot of people are
reluctant to be affectionate on a
physical basis.
um you know kiss the lips or whatever
and I know a lot of it has to do with
the fear of getting a from okay and the
other reason is because of the article
that came out in the LA weekly last week
about channeling thanks and comment was
made about Rona I know that you don't
like or don't comment about other um
entities but uh comment was made uh in
reference to AIDS being a way of wiping
not homosexual or something to that
effect. All right. And that's why I
wanted to ask you about I know that you
have commented it is let us say put in
our framework the idea that many of
these individuals may be creating the
idea of their self extinction because
they have taken upon themselves the
judgments of the mainstream of society
and in that sense therefore do not see
any other way to balance themselves in
the overall equation other than taking
themselves out physically. You follow
me? Yes. Now, if your entire society is
willing to become balanced and blended
and deal with the energies that you are
now forced to deal with within
yourself, then the entire scenario can
turn around completely, as you say, 180
degrees. And those beings in your terms
that are dying need not die.
You follow me? Yes. Thank you, Basha.
Guys, I have a situation at home that's
that puzzles me and I was Well, put the
pieces together. Well, yeah, that's what
I'm going to do now. All right.
Uh, a couple of weeks ago I noticed that
I had a rat that came into my kitchen
and I think it lives in the wall and it
also uh there is also a rat that goes
into the guest room and I think it may I
thought it was the same
rat. Well, anyway, I I feel very
strongly about not killing anything. All
right. And so, uh, it was getting into
the food. So, I thought, well, I'll feed
it and I will I will start showing it
the way out. All right. And I've been
laying trails of food from where I think
it comes out at night uh through the
kitchen to the patio. Well, sort of
smart. It doesn't like to go out. It
stops eating right by the door.
But I thought, well, I'll I'll do it
again and I'll I'll try different ways
to do it and so on.
And then I found out also it was in the
guest room and it it ate some of the dog
dog biscuits I was throwing
there. So well I got the dog biscuits
out and I thought since it was the same
lad and I fed it in the kitchen, it
won't go in the guest room anymore.
Well, tonight I got my I got my warm
coat out. Yeah. And I noticed it had
started to chew on my brand new coat. Oh
my. And I was I was very upset about
that because I don't mind sharing food
with it and I don't mind.
But I don't want it eating my clothes. I see.
I see.
Now I
talked I did talk to it. Oh, why? I even
I even went on the coal plane, but I
didn't quite know what image to generate
to to have it outside my house. And see,
obviously, it's a nice place to lay.
I would assume so since you live there.
So, I I can't tell it's um you would be
better off outside because I don't think
so. [Music]
[Music]
May I take this opportunity to to extend
our appreciation for being willing to
amuse your friends.
doesn't ask him to pay half the rent.
I dreamed about it, too. And it's got a
beautiful golden brown coat. Oh, and
it's got, you know, the rest of your
coat.
Very pretty eyes. And I don't know what
to do because I really don't want to put
in my coat, my pose in his coat. I
I
mean, sure it's funny, but it's I don't
really know what else I can do. Oh, the
only thing that I wondered about was,
you know, Dreamer when Dreamer talks he
said uh uh not all dolphins have that
kind of
consciousness. And I was wondering, it's
not that they do not have that kind of
consciousness. Many of them simply have
not chosen to express themselves in that
particular manner. Oh, okay. All right.
But but you can still communicate with
the other dogs. Okay. So So there is no
barrier to my communicating with the
rest. No. Okay.
Now, what does the coat represent to
you? Warm. Warm. I I just bought it. All
right.
How do you think of it? I think of it as
uh well like you know when I come here
it gets to be late and it's real cold
and I thought you'd be perfect to come
to the show sessions with all right or
if I have to go back east or whatever.
All right. So in a sense for you in terms at
right. So in a sense for you in terms at
least of temperature it is a
form of feeling
centered feeling secure. Yes. All right.
right.
In your understanding of your
relationship to nature.
Can you allow yourself to feel that
warmth coming from within to the degree
that will allow you to perhaps just a
suggestion not need the coat?
coat?
Well, just asking.
Not really. Not really. All right.
Well, perhaps. Do you
Do you
think that rats likes to eat
strawberries? [Music]
[Music]
I know they
like because it's accep of the guavas I
had. Close enough.
[Music] Now
Now
then, do you think you would
[Music] mind having a little
mind having a little
helper to remind you of some of the
ideas that may still be crawling around
inside the walls of the house that you
are in between the walls that you have
not quite gotten at Oh, yet
that may emerge from time to time to
give you a gentle reminder here, a
little subtle reminder there, and just
very slowly nibble away at all of your
old conceptions until perhaps you find
conceptions until perhaps you find
yourself truly relying on just you, just
you. Rather than having to, now again,
we are just speaking in analogies. This
does not mean you cannot have a coke.
But rather than relying upon the idea of
external symbology for the warmth of
centered security.
[Music] Yes. Right. If you begin to
Yes. Right. If you begin to
explore these ideas and also allow
yourself to set up a possible
exploration in your dream reality with
this being and the reflection it is
being to you. Then perhaps you can see
from its point of view and go exploring
from its point of view and get a
first paw
paw
understanding of the way it sees you of
the way it thinks of the way it
motivates its consciousness with respect
to you.
And then as you
identify identify with it do not forget
that the idea many times of when we
suggest that you talk with an
animal the easiest way to do that is to
identify with it
to talk as it
you hold it. Yes I do. Thank you very
much. And in this way there falls. When
you allow yourself to have that
perspective, you will then see both
sides of the event and you will be able
to relate the reasons for the ongoing
interaction. Then you can transform him
into other ways that will not
necessarily have to seem to be
destructive on the
surface, but will be beneficially
supportive in the overall ideas that you
are and allow you to rely upon the power
that you have within you. So that
everything will become transparent and
nothing will be hidden between the walls
from you anymore.
What what's the symbology? Uh what do
west represents in our to some degree
some of what we have been saying the
idea of
hidden concepts sandwiched so to speak
in between areas. areas that you have
created to be recesses into which you do
not believe you cannot go, but which
many, many different portions of your
consciousness course through at all
times, popping out now and then to
remind you here and there, that they
exist, they have never gone away, and
that at any given moment you will always
find that they are ready and willing to
emerge.
urge to give you a little bit of
incentive here and a little bit of
incentive there always to keep you on
your toes if you will. But when you
allow the whole idea to become
transparent and they do not have to
scurry around as such. They do not have to peek
around as such. They do not have to peek
out as such from time to time. They can
join in the overall consciousness that
you are
see and speak as them. Okay.
All right, I will take it over. Now,
because you are willing to provide so
much good
humor with this
idea, then we would suggest that in the
continuence of that idea, your tape for
tonight is called Rat.
[Music] Thank you. Thank you.
[Music]
you are
are
to some degree. He mentioned a few weeks
ago that in the process of transcending
this plane rather than expanding in
size, it's the process of of imploding
within the atom into the nucleus into
the proton and is a cork called truth.
Well, that's one way of looking at it.
And um I was just curious, my
understanding of the proton is composed
of two up quarks and one down quark. And
I was curious where exactly the truth
particle the only evidence is in proton
anti-roton collisions where there um
thank you thank you thank
you now to us this is all
symbology it is valid for the
terminology you are using if that is the
way you wish to look at it but the idea
to us goes further into what we call the
template representation or manifestation
what you call quirks
basically basically are the first fundamental
basically are the first fundamental
representatives of the non-physical
trinary template because the template is
fashioned in tetrahedral structures
always in
free of it. Yes. Thus the core, the
gateway, the black hole if you will,
that in a sense you are actually going
into is the very center of that little
tetrahedral pyramidal
idea. That is the gate, the borderland
if you will, between physical and
non-physical reality. It is also one of the reasons,
reality. It is also one of the reasons,
this little geometric idea or structure,
so to speak. It is one of the reasons
why many of you upon first perceiving
the idea of the causal plane will see it
as a collection of geometric
shapes because you are seeing it first
as the first primal representation of
physicality upon a very geometrically
oriented template. The gateway is in the center
template. The gateway is in the center
of that tetrahedrin and in the center of
each and every tetrahedrin of which
there is an infinite number in any given
spot. You follow it? Yes. Will this be of some
You follow it? Yes. Will this be of some
assistance? Um, yes. But where then is
the truth particles in the structure?
Exactly. You're saying it is in the
[Music] center with there are two up quirks and
center with there are two up quirks and
one down quark. We are not in this way
ascribing the terminology that you are
using. If you wish to look at it this
way, then consider the tetrahedrin to be
our version if you will of an elementary
particle. The idea thus being expressed
as follows. Three factors of space and
one of
time. Each of what you call the base
point of the three-sided pyramid will be
the factors of the what you call xyz
coordinates of space. The apex will be
the force factor that gives sense to
time. Each and every minute tetrahedrin
thus is in of itself a minute concept of
the idea of spacetime.
All four points, the three that define
the base and the one at the top are
necessary to have a manifestation of
physiological reality. In this
reality. In this
way, in many different ways, the quark
analogy can be fit on this template in
many different points of view and
perspective and many different
structures. But the
But the
idea is that that one tetrahedral
structure is all that is necessary to
define any and all interactions that
take place within physiological reality.
It is the prime
equational let us say format.
self. It is therefore because of this
structure that physical
reality is what you basically refer
to. One moment [Music]
as a 10dimensional universe.
This structure in the reflection of what you
structure in the reflection of what you
would call the lines that form the
structure and the planes that form the
structure give you the understanding of
why there are only four dimensions
visible and six invisible to you in the
10-dimensional infolded
universe. The six are implied by the
interaction of the planes, the four
sides of the pyramid.
In this way also enforced within this
structure is what you would call the
so-called random factor or uncertainty
principle in following it. For in this
way you will find that you are only able
to make observations from one particular
plan or point of view at any one time.
An observation that you make as you
already understand will either give you
position or momentum but not both. You
follow me?
This is also apparent in the tetrahedral
structure because if you will take at
any given moment any one of the faces
that represents the three-sided pyramid
you will understand that you either have
one whole face the base that contains
all three XYZ physical spatial
coordinates and none of time or you will
have a face that contains the one time
coordinate and only two of the XY or YZ
or ZX coordinates of space. Thus, at any
given time, you either have totally the
momentum or totally the position, but
never both. Unless you go
fourthdimensional and read the entire
structure all at once, which from third
density reality it is unlikely you will
do
physically. You follow us? Now, is this
being of some assistance?
Thank you.
I have two
questions as the aircraft passes
over. First question is uh several weeks
ago you said something
like the consciousnesses that reside
beneath the surface of our planet or
within the core of our planet. I'm not
sure which. In any case, it's it's uh
subterranean. were in a slightly
different vibrational frequency. If
they're slightly different, does that
mean they also experience a physicality
which is just not congruent with ours to
some degree? Yes. Does this mean that
they physically in their dimension
reside beneath the surface of uh their
their version of Earth? Yes. Is it like
in caverns or uh to some degree also
there is an expanded understanding of an
entire interior area that would be
likened unto
one great cavern so to speak but it is
not in your physical dimension. I see.
So uh but in their physical dimension
they're lit literally living underneath
the surface of a planet. Nice. Uh
although in many ways some of them do
not consider that to be so for there are
many ideas and ways of perceiving that
they have that would allow them to
believe that they are in a sense on the
surface. How do they do that?
How do they do that?
It is simply their mode of understanding
that the quote unquote ground they walk
upon must by definition be the surface.
Oh, and the entire rest of the universe
is on the inside.
Okay. Are they unable to see uh their
sun? Some beings perceive what you call a
Some beings perceive what you call a
central
star within their domain
somewhat as though their central star
would be in our favor of preference
within the center of the planet. Yes,
that's very interesting. Is there is
there truly a a
proximity such that they are very close
to their sun then relative to the
distance between us and our sun? Yes.
That's wild. But it is in your terms not
a son of physiological manifestation in
your manner. And thus in this way it is
neither of the same
size nor of the same type or quality of
light. But it does produce light for
them. Yes.
And nurturing energy for all that grows
around them. But it is a more ethereal
astral idea. Are they physical as we are
in their own in their own connotations
to some degree? Yes. Though many of them
also have the conscious ability to
transcend that physicality quite
readily. And many of them also recognize
the relationship between themselves and
you and sometimes therefore appear in
your physiological spectrum. Uhhuh. By
accelerating and or quote unquote
decelerating their vibrational
wavelength. So that uh maybe some of them would be
So that uh maybe some of them would be
undergoing channeling sessions and going
mean they're actually people who live on
the surface of the planet.
Some of them most of them are cognizant
in a very different way of your
existence simply because they represent
many different forms of time track
awareness of the civilization that you
are now in times past.
Would they um my last comment was
actually more of a joke, but this was
more serious, very serious. Do they
perceive us more in terms of
uh instead of us living on the exterior
of their
planet, they may perceive us more as
living on the interior of their planet?
That is what we suggested earlier. Some
of them, not all of them, some of them
perceive you to be on the interior.
Yeah. Yes. Thank you. Second question,
guys. Um, some people stand with their
pelvises rotated rearward so that their
buttocks protrude to the rear and others
stand with their pelvises rotated
forward. I'm wondering if if that has
any relationship to uh kundalini energy
and the release of it or the action of
it from time to time it can.
for the idea of your physiological
posture can be one of the symbols to
utilize what you believe to be an
alignment within you. So sometimes it
can other times it will represent other
ideas or attitudes in that way. I see
which would which would represent the
alignment uh position basically forward
to some degree
center. Okay. Thank you. Thank you. you.
Thank you. Then you
Okay. Are you familiar with the Astro?
The Astar Command to some degree, though
not exactly in all the different ways
that it is
represented symbolically in your
society. For many individuals in your society
For many individuals in your society
will put certain connotations upon that
form of consciousness and describe it in
symbolic terms that are more connected
to many of the ancient rituals that you
have upon your planet or religious
connotations which do not actually exist
in what we would perceive to be the
consciousness that you are referring to.
Okay, thank you. Second question, what
is your perception of transsexuals?
There can be as many reasons for that as
there are the individuals that may
partake of that
experience. There can be the idea of
individuals who have experienced many ideas of one
who have experienced many ideas of one
type of manifested life or another. And
in this way, in their exploration of
perhaps what they now perceive to be the
opposite physical form, they simply do
not find themselves comfortable with it
and rearrange the idea of their physical
structure to be more in the modality
they are used to. That is one idea. You
follow me? Yes. There can be many other
ideas and it can be all having to do
with once again the exploration of the
polarities male and female within each
and every one of you at this time. Each
according to their own interpretations
and understandings of their relationship
to that energy.
Thank you. I Okay. I have a question
about the coal plane. discovered
recently that when I go into the causal
plane and uh create something whatever
and drop it into the physical what
actually has been occurring a lot of
times it's been it's been uh coming out
not in the physical but on the astral
plane now I recognize that this this is
very interesting to me because I
recognize that what I've actually been
doing is I feel a need to blend more the
is I feel a need to blend more the
physical and the astral on very good you
are placing it in the dream level
reality so that you can also meet it
halfway right exactly and um also the
energy that I have been channeling I
recognize it's a very magical kind of
place and I recognize that it's very
well blended in that in that place and
um it's it's like they're all together
astral physical and causal plane and I
wanted to make sure that was possible
because so the separations are only your
so the separations are only your
perception of them as separated levels
on another fundamental level they
obviously are all one
idea they all stem from one
source do not
forget even the non-physical levels
though they are of course
real are simply different connotations
and ways of the oneness expressing
itself. So everything is still here and
now so to speak.
Okay. So uh anything that you can say
that would help me to uh blend this?
Simply follow your excitement. You are
doing fine. You are simply setting up
whatever type of lure is most enticing
for you to be able to allow the dream
reality and the physical reality to
become one.
Okay. Thank you for sharing. You are
welcome. Thank you. Yes. Uh I have a
question for a friend who called me from
Washington and Oh
yes. Did you want to say something about
that? Then you'll have better call up
that friend and ask them the question if
the question is for them. Actually they
called me and I called them back and we
discussed this question.
Just teasing teasing.
Yes, I know. Oh um
I shared quite a few ideas with him. Oh,
what? And but he still wanted me to ask
you. I think he wanted this sort of from
the horse's mouth, so to
speak, since we're dealing with animals,
right? Um,
basically, he wants to know why it was
that for two years he was very excited
about the idea of screenwriting and did
a lot of that and it was was actually um
with the intention that that would
support him. But in spite of being
excited about, in spite of doing it, he
says that that did not happen. And now
he's working on the construction, which
he's done so many times, he's bored to
death. And he feels that he's right on
the verge of understanding how to
manifest want. First of all, recognize
that many times when individuals do a
certain thing that excites them, they
still may create the idea of a certain
expectation as to how they think it
should support them. Is the individual
still alive? Oh, yeah. I assume during
the 2-year period, the individual still
had the ability to eat and was always
fed. I pointed that out to him.
Now again, the idea is that with any
given idea you are excited about, you
will be supported in whatever way you
need to to be that idea.
If that individual was let us say mixing
ideas saying oh wow I am very excited
about this and it will lead to this
which is actually more
exciting. You follow me? Yeah. Then what
you are saying is the thing that truly
excites you is not actually the thing
that most excites you and you are simply
using that as a means to something else
instead of simply doing the other thing.
You follow? Yes, I do. Now allow that
individual to be completely honest with
the idea of what their beliefs about the
screenwriting were when they were doing
it. Is it something that they did and
were excited about doing, but primarily
so that they could become something else
that was actually more exciting? Or was
the idea of the writing in and of itself
all they truly needed at that time?
Well, this is um what I
was getting him to look at as a matter
of fact because I said it was it the
idea of writing that was exciting or was
it the idea of being supported by
through your writing being a quote
success and earning your money that way
because those are two different ideas.
Yes, they are.
Well, he maybe you could share
something. I think we're at the crux of
it because he was not quite able to see
or wasn't able to show him exactly how
they're not the same idea. So maybe you
could explore that a bit. What we will
say right now
is if the being is willing to simply sit
with themselves in openness,
vulnerability of
strength, trust and honesty and to truly
define what it is, what the idea is that
they truly find most
exciting. That is necessary first.
All right. Yes. Thank you. I will uh
call on that and I'll also send them the
tape. You can also allow the
You can also allow the
individual, if they wish, to open up
into their dream reality and allow
themselves to create a scenario in the
dream reality that will allow them to
very very clearly understand that they
have a very bright spotlight on the path
that they are and at any given moment
can truly see which way the path bends
and can simply follow it.
Good. Thank you. Well, they've moved to
a absolutely beautiful area and I think
they're enjoying their lives. But all
right, one other thing. Yeah.
Many times because of the expectations
and the invalidation that you may place
upon an idea, even if you do recognize
that that idea is exciting, the idea may
be exciting not necessarily for the end
you think it is
for. Mhm. You will create certain
situations to be exciting so that you
will go into them so that you will get
out of them what you need for
later. Now along at that time you may
think well I must be doing this for a
reason. Ah well it must be this that
might just have been a guess and not a
true understanding of what it was he was
writing for.
Yes, the idea once again is to allow
everything that occurs in your life to
fit into the entire spectrum of your
life. Not only what has already happened
but what is yet to
come so that you will allow it to find
its place to allow you to be the being
you are becoming. And then perhaps
somewhere else as you say down the road
you will say ah now from where I am I
understand why I needed that then
because it allows me to do what I am
doing now you follow me not only follow
you I I totally agree with you because I
find that happening more and more in my
own life. It's fabulous. Now,
um I would like um your help in
exploring something that I've been
experiencing off and on for the last
three or four years. And that is up and
on. Yes. Off and on. And I have and up
and down.
Exactly. I never know when it's going to
happen again. Oh, good. Or for how long.
Oh, exciting.
And that is hot flashes. I feel like my
own little Chernobyl
Chernobyl
meltdown. And um I've had a few ideas
about this which I'll share with you and
then you can share what you have. Okay.
Um, one is that I, it occurred to me
that maybe if I was doing more writing,
which is something that I feel excited
about and I
I tend to put off when I do it, I love
it. I really enjoy it, but maybe if I
was doing more of that, maybe uh that
would help integrate all this energy.
Maybe. So, that was one idea I had. And
another one was
um that I have been accelerating at warp
speed lately. So maybe maybe that's part
of it. Maybe uh and that also might be
connected to the possibility of
some friction as you've mentioned with
still connections to old ideas maybe and
so I accelerate into the new ideas
maybe. now. Oh, oh, oh, definitely. Maybe.
Okay, Michelle. So, anything else you
want to share with me? Maybe. I'm ready.
I'm definitely ready. You are? Yep.
Ready for what? Anything you want to
share? Anything at all? Anything at all?
Anything? Anything. You are giving me complete
Anything. You are giving me complete
and total freedom to suggest anything at
all. You got it. No matter what.
That's right. Why?
Because I feel equal to that idea. Oh.
Oh. Oh, clever. Then what do you have to
suggest? All things being equal,
All things being equal,
I saw this coming. Good sign.
It's great. I was actually up there
looking back this way. In and of itself,
that is your answer. I saw this coming.
Realize that you see far more than you
may analytically think. I know that's
true. Yes. Let yourself continue to know
it. Let yourself continue to see the
reflections that show you that you know
it. Live. Live. Live. Live.
Live.
Life. The living of your life
fundamentally is truly the only process
you need to understand everything in
that life. I love it when you say that
because I agree with that so much.
I mean I have spent like a lot of people
here I'm sure but let me speak for me by
all means
and anyone else wanting to speak for me
I spent so many years learning this
methodology and that methodology and
this process and that process and now
what I love most about you well maybe
not most but what I love immensely about
you that you enable us to realize that
we can be what we want to by being it
and living it. And we don't there isn't
we don't have to create a process unless
we feel we need it. And even that then
even if you believe you need it can in
and of itself be quite enjoyable.
That's true. But I like to deal in
concepts. And so often in the past I've
gotten in
into I was going to say arguments. a lot
of arguments, discussions with friends
who like the analytical approach and and
my analogy is it's like they they like
to go down through the valleys and climb
up the hills, but I like to leave from
mountain and look under every little
rock and find some very interesting
and find some very interesting
things, maybe
rocks or strawberries.
May I ask you a question? Of course. Oh,
thank you.
Now you said for many years you have
been doing this. How many in your terms
of counting? Have I been exploring
methodology? Yes.
Well, eons actually
eons. [Music]
I asked you before about our tourists
and then I went back and listened to
that tape. Is there anything you'd like
to share with me us? Me us about that
energy. Mhm.
Tonight before you
sleep, envision, if you will, the blackness of
envision, if you will, the blackness of
space, both externally and
internally. See
yourself at the fulcum point of
infinity. You follow me? It is equally infinite
You follow me? It is equally infinite
outward as it is
inward. Envision that background, that
Envision that background, that
blackness, if you will, and recognize
once again that it is not a void. It is
not a vacuum. It is not empty, but it is
full of
everything. Upon that
blackness
extend from the center of your solar
plexus equally outward and equally
inward a cone of orange
light. All right. In the very core
center of that
cone, inward as well as outward, a very
strong, intense, and highly focused
laserlike beam of white
light. Let yourself simply feel these
vibrations. Now if you feel them to be a
little raw then simply surround yourself and
raw then simply surround yourself and
buffer yourself and immerse yourself in
the blue white crystallin sphere of your
electromagnetic energy to function as a
buffer. All right. Feel the vibrations
of that energy of those colors in those
shapes in this meditation.
Open yourself up to
communication. Then let yourself while
you are feeling this
energy have whatever experience you have
in your imagination or simply drift off
to sleep. All right.
Thank you very much for sharing.
Funy for sure.
You two questions. Um speak up. Yeah.
First of all, for about a year or so now
in our time, I've uh been working with a
group of people uh down at near the
beach in uh place called Venice. Uh the
area that we work has been called the
healing circle because people do various
forms of body work down there. Now over
about the last 8 months, 6
months a lot fewer people seem to have
been attracted to
experiencing the services that we offer.
We offer it on like a donation basis
that people can come and and give an
offering of some sort if they wish to.
Time for a change. I was perceiving
this. Time to recognize that everyone is
beginning to realize they are their own
healer. time to share the idea with them that
time to share the idea with them that
they are their own healer. Let them have
the experience of getting in touch with
that that is necessary to allow them to
know they can always heal themselves and
always do and that they are not coming
to you so much for something they cannot
do. But for you to reflect to them that
which they
are, you will have them in droves
once because that is all they need.
Thank you. I've done nothing. Sure. Yay.
I have one. One moment. [Music]
Um, every time I've asked a question
here and in other group
[Music] interactions, I seem to create a strong
interactions, I seem to create a strong
fear within myself. My heart starts
beating really fast. And why do you
think that's fear? Why not excitement?
Why not acceleration? Why call it fear?
I guess because I labeled it that way.
Guess so.
Would you prefer to label it another
way? Would you prefer that it could be
the idea of excitement? Yes, I would.
All right, then allow yourself to
recognize this. There is nothing
this. There is nothing
nothing. What was that, Basha? Nothing.
Oh, thank
you. There is nothing that you could
ever discover behind the fear that could
not be used to add to the overall
understanding and expansion of your
ecstasy. Why fear? Your
Your
society has already
created in vocal form the saying that
many of you think is a wonderful
philosophy but do not realize is
actually a description of the mechanism
of all of the invalidation that you
experience in your
civilization. You have had an individual
say the only thing you have to fear is
fear itself.
It is the
belief in the power of fear that creates
any situation to be fearful and only
that belief. There is nothing inherently
fearful about any
situation. The only thing that is
fearful in any situation is the fear of
that situation. That is it. You create a
situation. That is it. You create a
belief that there is something about
that situation that would cause you to
believe you are not going to remain
self-empowered and in control. But you
are always in control. Even when you
create a scenario in which it seems you
are out of control, you're controlling
that scenario. There is nothing you could
scenario. There is nothing you could
possibly discover behind the facade of
fear that cannot be added to the
understanding of your being in a
positive way.
All you have to remember is that no
situation has any meaning built into it
and that all situations are
fundamentally neutral. The meaning you
supply to a neutral set of circumstances
determines the effect you get out of it.
Positive meaning, positive effect,
negative meaning, negative effect. You
follow me? Yes. So invite your fear for
your fear only shows you a portion of
yourself that you have not yet looked
at. And as soon as you begin to pay
attention to the portion it brings you,
it will transform into ecstasy and
excitement. Many times it only comes in
the guise you call fear simply because
you have not been willing to pay
attention to it when it came more
subtly. So it gets
noisy. So you will pay attention. You
follow me? Fear, if you will do it no
other way, fear will almost guarantee
that you'll start living in the moment.
When you are willing to live in the
moment through ecstasy, then you won't
need to do it through
fear. So, we choose to perceive that the
rapid acceleration of your heart is
simply an increased sensitivity to your
own accelerative electromagnetic energy
and that what you are experiencing is
the acceleration of the blending and
communication with the idea of the being
that you are with what you call your
higher consciousness. you are blending
and forming into your future self right
now in the present and that you are
extremely ecstatic and excited about
this prospect. Peter Peter,
I'd love to hear a joke about Peter. All
right, then you find you. There's a
string that walks into a bar and the the
strings go to the bartender, I'll have a
beer. And the bartender looks at him and
says, "What are you talking about? We
don't serve strings in here. Come on,
get out of here. So the string is all
dejected and he leaves and he runs into
a friend who goes down in the street
says, "Hi, how you doing?" The string
says, "Oh, I was just in that barn. I
wanted to get a drink and they wouldn't
serve me and goes, "Oh, that's silly."
He goes, "I'll get you in." He goes,
"We'll just disguise you a little bit."
So he takes the string and he pulls him
apart a little bit and he ties him in a
knot on his head and frays him a little
bit and turns him around and he walks
into the bar and sits down. He says,
"Uh, I'll have a scotch and water and uh
my friend will have something." And the
string says, "I'll have a beer." And the
bartender looks at him and says, "Wait a
minute. Aren't you the string that I
just threw out of here?" And he says,
"No, I'm afraid not. [Music]
[Music]
Thank you for stringing us
along. Most enjoyable. Long moment,
Long moment,
mail. Okay, thank you. Uh, Bishar, we're
moving into a house in Ohio. It's really
beautiful and there's a there's a back
and front yard with a lot of plants and
trees and they they look like they want
a lot of love and I want to give it to
them. And I started talking to the tree
in the back and that's what they said.
But there's a I know you don't
understand. Now, a pine tree all this.
The pine tree in the front looks very
dry and it's very barren. And I was
wondering, is there something that you
know that I could do to uh help him? You
can hug the tree. I do. You can share
your energy, your electromagnetic force,
your life force in that way. Wrap it
around the tree. Begin to communicate in
that way. Once again remember as with
animals communicate by identifying
as the being you are communicating with.
Communication is identifying as.
You follow me? Yes I do. I do that with
pine trees. I lean against them and we
have great communication. They do that
with you as well. Water them with your
love along with of course some physical
water and allow the crystallization
energy within the water that is
activated by your electromagnetic aura
to allow the
tree to crystallize in that way.
Sometimes you may find that a crystal
you are attracted to if you need an
assistance may also be implanted in the
soil near the base of the tree and can
also draw energies. Focus them from the
earth in that way. Do not need a very
big crystal. Very small one will do. To
focus them into the vibratory patterns
that now represent your understanding,
your energy, your vibration. So that in
a sense, let us say by proxy a little
piece of yourself is always funneling
energy into the
tree. So it becomes an extension of you
in that way. If you are in your own mind
planted in rich soil, then the tree as
an extension of you will reflect that
green vibration.
Nice shape of I did that to a small
little uh ill tree up in Arrowhead. I
put a crystal in the in the soil. I'm
failing. I'll go back next year. I want
to look at it. Oh, could I put also I
did this on could I put a crystal on the
end of a hose and as I'm watering would
that that very imaginative
Thank you. Thank you.
You venue.
Um the other day you shared with us a
story uh between the dolphins as a very
beautiful story. I want to thank you for
that. And I was wondering if among your
And I was wondering if among your
people, you might have a story you could
share with us tonight that has something
to do with uh water and moving with
living water. Water and moving with living
water. Water and moving with living
water. All
right. Do you wish to ask your question
first?
Yes. All right, done the story.
My question is this. Uh my question is
this. In the last few years, many
wonderful uh dreams have come true for
me. Wonderful gifts have been I've been
able to express, right? Uh but it seems
all of a sudden all these wonderful
gifts I have lost. No, no, no, no, no,
no, no. I can't find something. That is
all right. Then maybe you don't need it.
I um I have been able to sing most of my
life. Yes. I have people consider me to
be a very good singer. Nice. And what do
you consider yourself to be? A good
singer. All right. But suddenly I can't
I can't seem to find this voice that
I've had for most of my life. Can't find
it. I can't find it. Well, where do you
suppose it went? I have no
idea. But I have other wonderful things
that are happening. But why should this
this one disappear?
Maybe it is simply resting while you
discover many other wonderful things
that perhaps you would have overlooked
by focusing on the singing. Could be.
Could be. But I miss it very much in
What about the excitement inherent in
all the other things? Oh, they're
wonderful. Oh, they're wonderful. Yes.
Maybe it's just your opportunity to sing
a different tune. I am bringing it in.
I'm just not willing to give up what I
had before. You are not giving up
anything. You are changing the idea of
the way you will express
it. You are redefining it. It is let us
say in the shop floor repaired. Oh, it
needs repaired.
The idea is simply that you are defining
yourself as a different
being. You never lose
anything at any given moment. The way
you express yourself is the way you need
to express yourself to come to terms
with that portion of your
being. Recognize that you are always
yourself a song of
creation. Everything you are is a song
of creation.
Sing in that
ecstatic mode and
mode and
then you will allow yourself
spontaneously to find that you have
never lost the voice. And when you
experience that voice, what will come
with it will be a depth, a richness of
experience that was not there
before. Relax.
Do not go chasing after it for it is
right with you. You cannot lose
anything. It is simply
shifting. Relax. In
Relax. In
relaxation will you create the
oxygenation and the breathing patterns
necessary to allow you to align with all
the energy you need. And then you will
be as crystal
clear as a belllike tone. Find your
Find your
flow. Listen to your
tone and reflect it.
Center within all that you are rather
than going chasing off after pieces you
think are
lost. And you will always find that it
is
there. Simply shift it into a different
key. Turn the key and allow it to come
Turn the key and allow it to come
pouring
out. All right. Thank you. Energy is
with you and you may avail yourself of the
you and you may avail yourself of the
energy of all beings that share in the
song of the creation that you are as a
society, as an
individual. Sing in your dream. And when
you create your physical reality to be
your dream reality, one in the same
idea, then you will sing as sweetly as
ever, for life itself will be sweet
beyond measure.
Thank you. We thank you.
Story
water in our civilization.
We have had many transformations. One transformations. One
transformation
involve the
exploration of our physiological
world at a
time when in a sense we were not, let us
say, globally oriented, though we were
not what you would call especially
politically fractionated. But in this sense, the
fractionated. But in this sense, the
exploration like yourselves of our
world, much of it took place upon the
water in what you would call ships of
various types. And there is the
types. And there is the
story of an
individual, well several
individuals upon one of those
ships who set
sail for a particular
destination. And when they had
passed, 30 of our
days, the water, the wind, and
everything stopped
still, and they
floated in the middle of the vast ocean
of our
world, seeing no land.
And a great
fog
appeared completely covering the
stars. And after three more
days, they had no
sensation of where they were, which
direction to proceed, how they may be
facing. For there was no current, there
was no wind, there were no
stars. All of their instrumentations
told them
nothing. And they were a
drift in a timeless
void. In this void they
spent another 30
days. And upon
the 31st day from the
center, what would be in your terms the
64th day of the voyage. They
voyage. They
discover the flow had started
again, but they did not know in which
direction. They could not tell where
they were heading.
And when once again they spotted
land, they made for
shore with all their power. And upon
arriving on that
shore, they stepped off the
vessel and went
exploring, for they had at least arrived
somewhere. And in their exploration,
they encountered many beings like
encountered many beings like
themselves and shared with them the
story of their
travel and the time that they had spent
in the void in the middle of the great
ocean. Bit by
Bit by
bit, they began to realize that the
beings that they were sharing their
story with were the
were the
children of the
beings that they knew as friends when
they left upon their journey only 64
days previous.
And thus they had recognized that not
only had they traveled across the ocean
of the world, but across the ocean of
time. They had not
aged. Yet here were the children of
their
friends. And thus did they
realize that in many ways all oceans and
all currents flow into all other oceans and
currents flow into all other oceans and
all other
currents. And they are all intermixed
and all
one. And setting out on a voyage in any
one medium can allow you to very smoothly
medium can allow you to very smoothly
blend into all others.
And in this
way within them this opened
up a whole new understanding and an
expansion of
thought, a whole new
experience and the
beginnings of the explorations of the
flows of time and
space as instructed by nature upon these
beings with the flow of the waters of
the world.
And the understanding that when all
directions seem to be the
same then in a sense it does not matter
in which direction you are going. It
does not matter how you are
proceeding but that going with the flow
at
hand is what will always bring you to
the realizations necessary for the
services that you wish to provide.
and that all
rivers, all streams, and all oceans flow
into one
another. And in their own
ways, though different, ultimately
all lead to the same
flow. Thank you.
Will that be of assistance at this
timing? We will therefore flow to
you, our unconditional
love in wave after wave of ecstatic
energy. Allow
Allow
yourselves to feel these waves within
you so that you may float and
flow upon the waves of the ecasy. Our
ecasy. Our
love and
our reminder.
Wake up and
dream. We thank you. A bond and
unconditionally loving good night, good
day, good life to you all.
Good night. [Music]
How'd it go?