all right I'll say how are you all this
evening of your time as you create time
to
exist we will begin the idea of this
interaction this evening of your time
with a bit of Illumination regarding the
other species upon your planet that
exists within the
idea of the same level soul that which
call the whale in the dolphin in that
way you being the idea of the land human
leing the idea of the water cuman you
are the same soul type you have the same
degree of ability intellectually in that
way you are different in terms of your
application but in this way there is
more than a little potential for you to
communicate very openly very
easily recognize in this way that they
have have been receiving communication
from other Civilizations for many
thousands of your
years you have been receiving these
communications but only now are you
beginning to pay
attention in this way recognize the
dolphins that sensient for has much to
share with you about the methodologies
of allowing yourself to open up your
sensitivities and receive communication
that is being sent to you
always for is mostly upon the wavelength
the frequency that you would call
empathy that you will feel these
communications it is emotion
feeling that will allow you to activate
those facets of your imagination Crystal
that will give you the recognition that
you are in touch with many forms of
Consciousness by definition by existence
by
right in this way you are never out of
touch you are always in connection with
everything you can
you can
utilize interaction whether physically
direct or
emotional or through your imagination
Doorway to invoke assistance
from the satation like form you call
dolphin and
whale simply in this way go with
him and invoke an image in your
imagination of a dolphin form floating
before you it may appear to be as you
understand it natural lifelike in that
way with skin coloration to match or you
may see it as an aetheric form a
ghostlike Sparkling Image either silver
or
golden in this way you may also from
time to time invoke this image as a dark
silhouette filled with stars as if the
dolphin shape is in itself a doorway to
many different connections many
different Consciousness and
recognize they are ready and willing to
assist you in this way and you can't
allow yourself to utilize their energy coupled
yourself to utilize their energy coupled
with your own through the dimension of
your own imagination which is the
dimension of the existence of your
soul of your basic fundamental reality
your imagination it is real allow
yourselves to rely and Trust upon the
idea that as you invoke any feeling any
image within your imagination you are
traveling inward into a reality no less
real than that which you experience to
be your physical reality for that which
you experience to be your physical
reality is only but the product of your
imagination anyway it is that what you give to its
anyway it is that what you give to its
solidity that makes it seem to be more
than what you normally call your
imagination and that is the only
difference it is your beliefs and your
bias towards thinking that the idea of
the imagination that you are perceiving
as that portion you call your physical
reality has more substance than the rest
of it and it does
not you create the illusion that the
linear time frame structure in which you
exist cannot allow there to be such a
reality as your imagination being that
it is etheric in nature in that way not
substantial as you would call it but now
you are beginning to enter a phase of
your existence
your transformation into fourth density
reality that is the beginning of
allowing you to know that all you have
ever perceived for many tens of
thousands of years has only been the
product of what you imagine your reality
should be it is that malleable we are not
be it is that malleable we are not
speaking in analogies it is that literal
it is that simple you are right now
dreaming in a very real sense of the
word no different from when you in a
sense dream when you are asleep but in this
dream when you are asleep but in this
way this is a focused waking
dream and as we have said in many ways
the more limited of the dreams for when
you are in your dream state you are
unlimited and very much more aware of
more of the being that you actually
are your imagination is the key the
bridge the length the conduit the tunnel
the channel through which you can link
the physical dream with the non-physical
dream and see how the physical dream is
but an extension of all that you are as
a non-physical being as an eternal
being in this way allow yourself to
allow the imagination to be a conduit
and allow it to provide you with
communication from your dream non
physical higher self Soul over Soul
reality to your physical reality which
is but an aspect of the totality of the
being that you are and trust that what
you perceive within your imagination
whatever methodologies you
require whatever process is You may wish
to create in life to allow you to
ascertain and appreciate and experience
and explore your own spiritual growth
can come to you through your imagination
your imagination is specifically the
tool that is tuned to your vibration and
can only by definition give you what
will work for you do otherwise it would
be someone else's
imagination your imagination is the tool
the Primal Crystal the Primal
tool anytime you need a method anytime
you need a way to do something trust
your imagination to give it to you for
it can only give you what by definition
is the vibration that represents the
path you chose to be if you are willing
to trust and not judge it to be invalid
you will always find that your
imagination will always underline that
an infinite number of times
always keep you consciously on the path
you chose to be you follow me
yes are you all alive yeah thank
you now this night of your time in the terms
now this night of your time in the terms
of what you call after your break there
will be sharing with serious energy and
in this way will be an
opportunity to explore the structure of
your imagination and begin the process
of going within and allowing your
imagination to begin to blend in your
physical reality so that your life
becomes a waking
dream always and constantly Blended
within the idea of the higher
self there will also after that be the
opportunity once again for what you call
the third time this week for very
specific reasons the opportunity to
explore within your imagination what you
would call a visit to one of our
craft in this
way it will be an exercise in reality
but an exercise that will allow you to
stretch your senses beyond that which
you normally consider to be your
day-to-day series of events it will be
real and you will experience what you
will experience and that which you will
experience will open doorways within you
the doorways that need to be open at
this time we will explore this idea
after your break for now let there be
the continuation of the sharing that
continues forever sharing Shar sure I
have uh three things number one is um
I'm feeling the sensation um over the
last few weeks in my throat area that I
start coughing it's like a yeah um many
individuals upon your planet are now
experiencing some transformation in the
throat chakra area that may allow to be
first dry then hot it may transfer into
your sinus area as
well okay now is this connected also
with my channeling it all yes for there
is the opening in that area for all of
you not so much that you need to channel
any specific other Consciousness in
order to have the experience but that
each and every one of you is becoming
willing to have the conviction to State
Forth what it is that is of your own
Essence that you will be channeling in
that way to State the convictions that
represent the life you know yourself to
be to speak up for yourself in that way
the strengthening of the throat chakra
the balancing of the chakra of intention
in your solar plexus and the blending of
the two that will allow you to state
with conviction the reality that you
perceive yourself to be without judgment
but only with preference and equality
continue okay now I was talking to a
friend of mine on the phone tonight and
I was coughing a few times and she said
do you have a cold and I said no and she
said let's explain to her what I you
know was going on and she said well
sounds like you sounds like maybe you're
stopping something stopping the energy
you know and I I said well I you know
it's any idea that you will be
experiencing of this nature and what you
call a way of discomfort will be
representative to some degree of perhaps
minor ideas of judgment or blocks that
still exist within you but but it only
is representative of the ideas that
exist within you as a collective Mass
Consciousness it is not something that
you are specifically blocking in that
way as a personality but simply that you
are sharing ideas with the mass
Consciousness that you are allowing to
be released now through the experience
you are having okay each and every one
of you is proceeding at your own pace
within the overall Pace in the
transformation so some of you will reach
that point before others okay thank you
number two um I was listening to a ran
take uh night and on in it he was
sharing with someone the idea that when
you when something about okay and I
don't remember the exact wording but
something about the pituitary gland
right and a frequency that's allowed
that um into one part of the brain that
allows you to
receive whatever receive
information um could could you tell me
more about that expanding that idea
simply in this way what you call theary
and the penal and also the idea of the
base of your brain in that
way will form a trary foundation that
will create an apex at your crown chakra
when you become allowing and linked in
that way and sensitive to the vibration
of your planetary Force the Earth in
that way 7 and 1/ half cycles per second
and allow yourself to infuse the idea of
that cycle of vibration within your AA
you can become in touch with all other
mentality upon your planet and extend
your senses out through the top of your
head in the crown chakra and be in
connection with all other levels of your
Consciousness as well it forms an energy
pyramid that allows you to function in
the moment as the idea of receiving
constant communication from all levels
of your being and extensions in your
Society okay I I felt like he was saying
that you know you can't receive unless
this is open I mean is that in a sense
that is correct well um is your anything
to do to assist in that or just use your
imagination just to be okay all right
well I mean but that sounds like you
can't re I mean that sounds kind of cut
and dry when you can't receive any
information unless understand that
anytime you do allow yourself to be
conscious that you are receiving
information Those sensors are
functioning together and are open oh
great okay well that thank you okay
simply by definition when you are tuned
to that fre you receive a similar
frequency if you are not tuned to that
station you do not get the
message okay well that okay thank you
third thing is for um a friend of Erica
asked me to ask okay for a friend of
hers named Noel and uh she said that her
friend Noel's cat has been going to the
bathroom in two particular places and in
her house okay um by the desk and Erica
believ the other place place was by the
window and only those two places and she
was wondering if there's anything any
information all right only this as her
friend is exploring the idea of her own
freedom and her own
self-imposed let us
say enslavement to certain ideas she
will allow herself to recognize that
first and fundamentally the idea of what
we have talked about to be your cat
symbolically represents the idea of the
trans from third to Fourth density a
being that exists in both levels at the
same time and so will usually be in many
instances the representative animal to
reflect to you the ideas that you are
exploring with regard to more freedom of
expression in that way for what she is
going through at this time that will be
the understanding that the idea of her
work in this way may carry with it
images of being enslaved or being
Chained and may invoke within her many
longings for in this way simply opening
the window and allowing herself out to
freedom in that sense there is a
connection being formed with the idea
that she feels that what she is
processing through herself in this way
is something that is being processed in
a
manner she does not enjoy too
much you follow me I was busy writing
down this information I missed that very
last sentence the animal is showing this
individual that the processing in and
what comes
out is something that is reflective of
how your friend is viewing her process
of being chained to things she does not
enjoy and creating the wishing that she
could simply open the window and escape
to
Freedom okay those two areas are being
pointed out in a manner that reflects
how she feels about the process and her
ability to digest it so she when she
realizes this and the cat no longer
needs to reflect that idea when she
allows herself to know there is no need
to pin herself into the idea of
drudgery but that she can allow herself
to know that all Endeavors that she
undertakes are part of the path that
allows her to know she has always been
free right so no judgment judgment okay
thank you sure thank you one
moment shut myself back here okay um I
have a question the last couple of
nights well actually for about almost
two weeks um I've been waking up
occasionally with severe migraines all
right what time about 3ish 4ish no
earlier later later all right uh more
like 8 all right sometimes 7 in the
morning all
right um sometimes they're coincident
with dreams or what might be bad dreams
um sometimes not but there always I
always get a lot of tension in my neck
all right and today I've had what do you
feel about the so-called bad
dreams do you feel that they represent
something that is reflective of
something you may have to encounter in
your physical
life or that you are going through in
your physical life no not really not at
this what do you feel then to me
um the dreams nice well like this
morning's dream it just it seemed an odd
way of processing
anger um you do not need to process
anger anger is in and of itself not
intrinsically negative you may be
processing judgment
judgment
okay so so then um the migraines are
just judgment yes all pain is judgment
[Music] um understanding this way there may be
um understanding this way there may be
an
assumption deeply within you that the
idea of what you
are processing in that way is allowing
you to experience the idea of the
process in your dream reality where you
can handle it rather than allowing
yourself to manifest it in your physical
reality and be faced with a physical
ruin in that way allow yourself to
understand you are doing yourself a
service by processing it in in your
dream reality and in this way you can
know that what you may be feeling as the
so-called migraine is in a sense the
release of energy but it is releasing
through the filters of your judgment and
so causing a great deal of friction in
this way the friction is what causes the
pain and so do you have a suggestion as
to how to avoid that nice allow yourself
the opportunity to recognize first and
foremost that what you are calling your
nightmares are certain in you okay allow
yourself to know or ask yourself would
you rather experience the idea in
physical awake reality or in your dreams
in the dream all right then allow
yourself to understand this as well
paradoxically your dream reality and
your physical reality are one and the
same thing one is an extension of the
other back and forth vice versa as you
say there is no need to create such a
differentiation such a barrier between
the two it is all right for you to begin to
two it is all right for you to begin to
realize that you can realize your dreams
the pleasant
ones okay you follow me yes I do yes
thank you for sure one
moment may I ask a question
yes do you have positive
dreams that you would like to have
realized in your physical reality that
have not yet manifested yes yes um my
ask you another question yes what do you
imagine would happen should those
positive dreams manifest right now would
you feel that you were ready to live
though oh I wasn't expecting that
question
um why are you hesitating well it's like
I mean I just can't imagine them being
real thank you very
much you have your answer when you allow
your imagination to function as an open
link between your dream and your physic
IC reality then you will let your
imagination do its job you will not
constrict the passage of the flow of
information and you will not feel the
migraines that are only the
representation of the energy from your
dream reality attempting to force
themselves through into your physical
reality open the conduit will the
channeling class I'm taking help to open
that obviously
okay since your own
imagination has instructed for you to
know that that might be one tool that is
valid for you trust that your intuition
to take the class will be and is
representative of your knowingness of
how you need to manifest the opening of
that conduit okay you follow me
everything that you decide to do in your
life is significant and valid or you
would not have conceived of it at all
okay you can only by definition conceive
of the things that are pertinent to your
existence you follow me yes I do thank
you thank you
sharing you thank
you Dr pebles mentioned the uh relative
equality and consciousness of the Yeti
to the uh doin in a sense they are of
different density vibrational
civilizations but they share the idea of
instinctual knowing great another question uh just
knowing great another question uh just
the other day I won a uh trip to
Hawaii the place of the heart yes really
I was wondering if you could tell me
something about uh I just
[Music] did all right that's is in your terms
did all right that's is in your terms
the heart chakra of your planet yeah why
yes I was considering selling the trip
in order to get the cash to do some
things here but I believe it is up to
you yeah I know but I believe that if
you can recognize that your chakra
points your Vertes your energy
vortexes are all beginning to blend and
shift and one is not so much anymore so
distinct and separate as it used to be
you have the ability to call forth where
ever you are all of the energy of all of
the vertices upon your planet and all of
the chakras at this time you can do it
wherever you are but if you would enjoy
going there by all means do so yes I
would enjoy going there thank you but is
there some uh some is there something
that I'm trying to tell myself that you
could tell me at this
point don't you want me to spoil the
surprise thank you I have no intention
of doing so than nor can I interfere in
your process great that's
good I have a high percentage a high
percentage of my friends and Close
Associates are having severe car trouble
lately guys this will not be uncommon as
you each reexamine the
idea of your vehicle in
life what has formerly transported you
may not be what transports you from this
point [Laughter] [Music]
[Music]
what should we be looking to for for
oh
have you have but to open up to your
connection to all that is and you will
automatically Grant yourself any
methodology of transportation that is
necessary at any given moment in
time great thank you thank
you you uh first I want to share um my
perception of the
symbology of this the nuclear situation
as being an opportunity a neutral
opportunity for a new or neutral new
clearing and in a sense and it is as we
have said tied in with the idea of your
shuttle incident your livan incident in
this way it is the polarity point in
that nation which represents the
polarity in your Society to you to have
the same type of incident that opens up
the idea of compassion around the world
and exposes their vulnerability as you
exposed your vulnerability quite out in
the open so you now can begin to allow
yourself to share and communicate
equally out in the open for all to see
can you comment on the energies that as
they're perceived at the moment
all is in a state of motion and will be
for quite some time there are some ideas
that are beginning to
Anchor but they could change at any
moment this is a time of limbo in this
way a time of infinite probabilities it
is all completely up to
you thank you thank
you hello I have hello
hello I have hello
[Music]
I have a question all right um several
weeks ago I felt as if um the the most
clear way I can say is I felt as if
someone climbed into my jar with me all
right and is it
cozy all right and uh I experienced for
the first time that feeling of total
absolute complete unconditional love oh
than you and what uh the question is is
is that person still in me or did that
person leave nothing is in you in the
sense of occupying the space you occupy
but you can take upon an associative
vibration and in that sense all that you
desire to be with you is always with you
all that you have no need of in that way
is always with you but in a non-
interfer of way you can tune into and
out of what you will all associations of
that nature are through
agreement it comes in the fashion that
serves you when you no longer need it to serve
you when you no longer need it to serve
you in that fashion the fashion
changes but it is always with you not
because you need it but because you have
agreed to share an idea and become an
experience with it you follow me yes
then be of service and you will be
allowing the energy to
flow and you will manifest all the
answers you need for yourself with
regard to any agreement you have made in
life you have something else yes you're
so
receptive um it is simply that you are
very
open um I had a feeling it came from the
dream and then it evolved into theory
that we can somehow to utilize the
radiation excuse me one
moment now I know this is going to be
very creative on your part and we are
not denigrating your
methodology of
cognizance but from our point of view in
this way if you have a dream and it goes
into a theory that is a devolvement oh
not an evolution
okay it was very okay I'll go back to
dream then it was wonderful all right
experiential dream in which the
radiation empowered us and brightened us
and made us very strong nice very good
then you are choosing the fourth density
perspective with regard to knowing that
all situations serve you and that the
vibration you allow yourself to be will
only allow
that effect into your
reality for all situations are
fundamentally
neutral you give them meaning positive
or negative and when you assign a
meaning you invite that
reality all situations are fundamentally
neutral thank you very much for your
real eye
thank you B
yes tell us about health
insurance auto insurance and how it
relates to having trust or no trust you
obviously already understand the
principle completely for you already know that it
completely for you already know that it
is implied in your question in that way
that if you believe you need to be
protected you are inviting the attack
now that is not to say in that way that
if you know you have that belief within
you and you feel you should listen to it
then listen to it do not go in the face
of your belief but you can change
yourself to whatever degree you are
willing you can experiment to whatever
degree you are willing and you may find
that you may be willing to understand
you may not need the idea of insurance
which implies that you will have an
accident it is up to you to determine to
what degree you are willing to share
that reality you follow me right how about
reality you follow me right how about
where the law requires you in the case
of Auto then again in this way it is up
to you to determine that if you have
created yourself to exist in a type of
society that demands it of you in that
way then allow yourself to decide
whether or not you you will but you will
know it is going to be according to a
belief that is within you that it could
come about that you will be faced with
the aspect that you have created it to
be against your laws and you may have to
face that idea it is up to you got it
thank you bash bash yes thank you there
was a man here that lived in the 40s and
30s in America his name was uh nicoa
Tesla yes he had a dream of the generation of
yes he had a dream of the generation of
electricity yes um in
unlimited amounts yes uh how based on
the S and one half cycle per second
understanding of your planetary
vibration how close perfect he
understood it completely yes I
understand that he had that concept how
close are we to developing you could do
it
tomorrow understand it is not that you
have never been close to it it is that
the information has been
suppressed yes you have had the technology for at
yes you have had the technology for at
least as long if not longer than that
individual was
alive understood um can you show us what
we need to do to complete
it in other words I've got the concept
of the cyclotron and the KRON and
various tuning devices that can take the
cosmic energy and step it down to a
usable form where we can plug our tape
recorders and toasters into understand
in this way the idea was simpler than
that you are using the energy of the
planet itself and you are simply
broadcasting a wave whose length is the
measurement of the 7 and 1/2 cycles per
second a circular wave so generated will
find that the crest of the wave will be
equal to the circumference of your
planet at the equator and it will go
around to the the other Pole where it
will bounce back and reinforce itself
and amplify itself when it reaches the
primary generator at its source this
amplification can continue with a
regulation in the oscillation that will
provide for you a reflective
amplification that will allow you to tap
into that wavelength that is generated
but understand the equipment that exists
upon your planet at this time would be
completely burnt out by that generation
of that wave you would need to dispense
with all all of that equipment and
generate equipment that would withstand
the function of that
wave thank you now also understand this
you can determine very easily the idea
and this will give you a clue as to the
fundamental nature of the vibrational
gravitational Dynamic tensor field of
existence out of which your material
world is created for recognize that the
idea is that if you take what you call
the speed of light which is the
fundamental definition of your third
density reality the vibrational limit of
your third density reality and you
divide it by the circumference of your
planet you will have the frequency of
the planet in your case 18630 m/ second
planet in your case 18630 m/ second
being the speed of light divided by the
circumference of your planet
approximately 25,000 of your miles will
result in the terminology 7 and 1/2
which will represent the cycles per
second thereby showing you the innate
thereby showing you the innate
relationship of the vibration of light
to the size of Any Given planet and the
determination of why that planet has the
frequency it
does you follow me yes explore those
ideas and see what you'll come up with
keep it simple trust your imagination
and understand this Tesla is more than
willing to
help thank you very much thank you
yes uh since the uh earthquakes off the
of Alaska this evening uh they said that
there was going to be maybe a tidal wave
hit uh La around 11:30 you see any uh
any type of uh action around that time
is there to some degree this will be
disappea by then Sur will
be there will be a slight increase in
activity there will be a slight increase
in the idea of what you call atmospheric
moisture as some of the energy is
dissipated by your emotionality into the
sky rather than into the
Earth okay thank you another thing I
want to ask you was is there such a
thing as a half step okay you go from
third to Fourth density is there
something in between you are in the in
between now is that what you call the
quas to some degree yes but more it is
the limbo
State the state in which all probable
realities for what you can possibly
allow your civilization to become all
exist equally right now as you begin to
choose more and more of your preferences
they become more and more
solidified and you are less likely to be
able to choose something else or you
will simply not exist in this
reality thank you thank
you um is is there a a society of beings
that have their bodies have three long
fingers instead of four yes they are
actually quite a few
oh why
why
because um I remembered this week that I
had forgotten to tell you some stuff and
um and it's funny I came here tonight
this is exactly what you're going to do
but in September
I had um actually about August one night
I decided to go to your ship oh what and
I did and I never told you about that
all right we have many visitors all the
time I know but anyway then why after
that one night I was just getting ready
to go to sleep and I had like it wasn't
a dream because I was wide
awake
that it was his be was there in my room
with me and he had a
body and he had and his hand had three
long fingers and a thumb and he was he
had like grayish skin kind of or you
know lighter lighter skin you and I was
just wondering tall or short
tall and he was wearing black
there are many focal points within that
communication many connections within
you to different ideas of
origin there is some primarily
serious you understand so that that
communication line was connected with
serious yes thank you do the Zeta
reticuli have bodies anything like that
okay then let me ask much shorter is
that the same being because about a week
before that is when um I had seen
a UFO I had gone out to Oxnard and I had
the distinct impression that that being
who was communicating to me at that
moment was in the ship that I seen why
what what is the purpose of that contact
I'm really D to open up ideas within you
so that you discover more of yourself so
that you allow yourself to live the
purposes you agree to live can
you were you willing to talk to me a
little bit about the purposes I agreed
to live if you are I am then what are
[Music] they okay well I've been thinking about
they okay well I've been thinking about
that a lot recently all right when are
you going to do something about it well
I feel that I am oh such as well I feel
and I've always felt like in in this
lifetime I've always had I've always
been aware of having a slightly
different reality than you and everyone
reality than you and everyone
else well yeah okay but I mean it's like
we are not demeaning you we understand
exactly what you are saying what we are
probing for is what you are doing with
that sense of difference well my idea is
that is that you can bring light into
anything of course how are you doing it
well I am doing it by communicating
about it and by actually living that
point of view thank you and um and like
in what's often considered like very
conservative situations guys and um
working in an environment that's
considered very conservative and just
just saying you know um exactly what my
reality is so you enjoy being in that
environment yes
I enjoy doing that kind of thing is
there something about the environment
you do not enjoy well see I'm in the
middle of changing jobs right now oh so
there used to be something about that
reality I environment that I was in that
I didn't enjoy I found it very difficult
to deal with and so now you are trusting
that you are going to make the move that
is appropriate as a reflection to the
path you chose to be exactly well thank
you there there's no more to it than
that
Now understand simply that there are
consciousnesses that are simply willing
to assist you and allow yourself to so
to speak elevate your awareness to
different levels so that some of the
information coming through you can take
on the
nature of ideas that will be Reflections
to other individuals for what they need
to hear through you you may simply have
agreed to act as a spokesperson in that
way for those beings so that other
individuals who have similar connections
can hear them through
you good do you think you would enjoy
that yes and as a matter of fact that's
exactly um the job that I'm changing to
um I'm in a position to do that very
very much oh what a coincidence and in a
really big way cuz it's for the LA times
thank you very
much you can become a media medium
thank you for your sharing and your
willingness to form connections to more
of yourself
yourself
okay sure as I have several things I'd
like to get that all are one one moment
yes you will have more communication in
your dream
realities all right right thank
you continue this is my first time in
this location being conscious of you all
right I know you all right what you say
I understand all right so I have two
basic questions one non density or no
density and how does it relate toward
the viewing of other densities once you
can achieve that
position are you referring to the idea
of non density as being all
densities yes all right then that is one
and the same your question and your
answer all right I the idea is that when
you are infinitely accelerated you are
everywhere at once which is exactly the
same feeling is standing perfectly still
which seems to be a non- density but is
actually all
density all knowing then we're looking
then at complete Consciousness yes which
leads me to my second half I have the
feeling that I have been acting in a
very unconscious mode which I believe is
self-induced and I have just the feeling
that if I was just to look a little bit
to the right a little bit to the left
yes there's one thing that if I could
see it would end all of this illusion
I'm under and give me back the control
that I know I've had before you think
so I believe so oh very good
why do you believe
so it's an knowingness that I can't
describe to you very good an
knowingness then if you know that you
know this then by
definition there is
absolutely nothing stopping you can you
offer any help for your idea of where
I'm at now that I can
pursue well my first inclination would
be to tell you are exactly where you
need to be need to be and begin to enjoy
it and live in the moment then you will
not try to be somewhere else and that is
what will let you get there so then I
just go ahead and create the way that
it's fun for me to create yes thank you
I enjoy that ecstatic explosions of
coincidence and synchronicity shall fill
your life and allow you to know you are
living as the representation of all that
is in that way joy and ecstasy living in
the moment living in the now will mean
you do not require patience nor will you
create impatience for you are too busy
having fun enjoying every single moment
and because you enjoy every single
infinite Eternal now moment you will
hardly feel the passage of time at all
again paradoxically it's the game
yes thank
you yeah um this goes back to my friend
Mr Tesla now I talk with him all time
it's just that I don't understand what
this man says I I mean we talk about
frequency and how about getting it in
pictures like he did do you understand
how he invented what he invented no I do
not his
imagination was so well lived
in that he was able to Envision the
actual device solid in front of him see
it in running operation and then all he
did was copy
it okay so get the picture and copy
it understand he had the ability to see
an image and if the machine were not
running properly it would be an
indication that his idea of it was not
in exact proportions he would simply
jocky the idea into the exact
proportions until he saw the machine
running properly acting as his barometer
and then he could in his imagination
completely and totally take the machine
apart see where there was wear and tear
see how to correct that improve upon the
idea that is why everything he built ran
the first
time yes and this does clarify a point
for me because I was trying to get from
him his idea which he was not letting me
know what you're saying is I have to get
my own idea and create from there but
understand it is not that he was not
letting you know it it is that you were
expecting it to come in a certain way
and also yes he is not going to give it
to you without you proving quote unquote
that you have the conviction to create
it for yourself which is the only way
you can get anything no one can give you
anything you have to create your version
of it because you are your own unique
100% universe and anything that you share
universe and anything that you share
with someone else any common similar
experience is because you have agreed to
create your version of it in your
reality right okay thank you for your
recognition thank you yes uh I see U
most uh people as mechanical and uh very
automatic um there seems to be a premium
on uh in in the society especially on
being clever and um calculating
um and things like that I have trouble
being that and I have trouble living
with that all right but understand
simply you are recognizing that many
individuals have their way of exploring
the idea of their existence that does
not mean you have to live that way
yourself nor does it mean that you must
judge the way they are living as invalid
for recognize if you are busy judging
that what they are doing is less than
what they could be doing you are the one
maintaining the existence of those
effects and those realities in your
reality because you are focusing upon
them you follow me uh yes how do I um by
choosing what you prefer and letting
everyone else have the right to live the
way they want to knowing that the way
they live has nothing to do with the way
you choose to live and it will not
affect you if it is not what you prefer
you if it is not what you prefer
preference is not judgment judgment is
invalidating everything you do not
prefer but understand when you
invalidate something you become equal to
it and thus what you do not want you
become you can only in that way be equal
to any vibration you are judging that is
what your biblical phrase judge not L he
be judged means it does not mean you are
being judged from outside it means that
you become the free frequency of
judgment and are locked into a equal
level of judgment with what you are
judging you become what you hate does
that thank you thank you very much you
have but to know that what you prefer is
simply a representation of the vibration
to recognize to be true for
you that is what you will live
living that means everyone else's choice
you can see it for what it is but it
will not have an effect upon you because
that is not the frequency at which you
are functioning allowing everyone to live
functioning allowing everyone to live
the lives they choose is granting
equality and validation to everything
all that is granting equality and
validation to all that is mean that you
as a part of all that is are
automatically supporting everything you
do and letting all that is support
you if you choose to invalidate any
portion of all that is how can all that
is support what you are doing you are
cutting yourself off from that
communication of
support by making something more than
something else or better than something
else or worse or
less follow me yes will this have been
of assistance to the
yes thank you thank you very much yes hi
uh hi to what extent uh I'm thinking now
as you of you as your own being on your
spaceship on always Sor us as creating
what you're telling us and the third
thing you interacting with d now you as
your own being right to what extent are
you aware uh about how well we
aware uh about how well we
understand the concepts that you're
imparting or to what extent we distort
those all right to some
degree we can feel the fluctuations
dependent upon again your willingness to
share the ideas you know yourself to be
the percentage determination will in a
sense be up to you more or less but at
the same time our view of you is that
you are doing exactly 100% of what you
need to be doing recognize this you all
are functioning completely within
synchronicity but many of you choose to
function within negative synchronicity
rather than positive synchronicity you
always function within synchronicity you
are always still at the right place the
right time to interact with exactly the
individuals you need to interact with
should you choose a negative reality
then those situations will be negative
Reflections but it is still created from
your synchronicity you are still
reacting only with the individuals and
within the situations that reflect the
way you choose to look at life so you
are still utilizing the synchronicity
okay yeah no I I quite agree and I
understand that part of it the question
was sort of triggered by something I
heard that happened I think on Tuesday
or maybe on Monday uh somebody asked
you about Leah and Jamie and
that it it sounded like what
Leah that what Jamie was saying was
probably distorted and also what people
are hearing was distorted and if I could
talk to Leah directly without all those
distortions I would hear one
moment we understand what you mean but
recognize in this way we do not so much
see anything as a distortion uhhuh yeah
for a distortion implies that there is a
single truth against which you can
measure something and there is that's
true recognize to us it is simply all
the different ways you have of
interpreting for yourself your own way
of looking at it your own perspective
there are many perspectives of one idea
to us they are not distortions okay
that's true that's true but but uh would
Leah be aware of of how people to some
degree yes and again our ability to
perceive what is going on in your
mentality is the product again of your
willingness to communicate on an equal
vibratory level with us there are many
things we place within ourselves not to
know so we will not interfere with your
process we are of assistance to you when
a reflection is given that we can
reflect that conscious un knowing this
in a sense yeah uh something else uh I
also heard about how wonderful it was on
Monday night and I had a very very Vivid
dream about a a channeling which was at
Steve's house but it wasn't Steve's
house it was a very different room and
and also about you all right and I was
wondering if even though the time was
probably wrong when I had that not wrong
no I mean it the timing was probably
right but the actual time in terms of
Earth time was probably but in the dream
stay that will be meaningless I that's I
realize that I didn't think about it no
in the morning I so well I interpreted
this dream in terms of what I know but I
wonder if it meant that perhaps I was on
the spaceship then I talked to Lori that
day and she told me about the blending
and I thought oh I wonder if I in a
sense if I joined you yes in a sense
although it was a different timing uhhuh
okay a different
conversation at at times during the
dream there seemed to be a lot of people
and times there were very few people ni
it was it was very strange
why question are there not at times a
lot of people around you and then other
times a few people well because I was in
the same room and do not people come and
go sure it
was it
was number
three sweet did I say
sweet did I say
sweet with regard to the idea you said
of myself and the
channel oh no no yes because we you as
you chel now you
have probably okay that's my imagination
probably okay that's my imagination
probably a different perception of
what's going on than what you have as
you yourself on your spaceship of course
because the idea of the blending of my
Consciousness and the consciousness of
the physical Channel creates a Third
identity right okay that that's what I
was thinking about it now guys as I have
said the idea of my experience of
communication with you is that I
experience you and this interaction in
my imagination but since I know my
imagination is real then I know the
interaction is going on oh okay
than um two things one in answer to a
question just a moment ago you said if
we take it's all synchronicity if we
take it negatively or positive we'll
depend on you as the phrase you used the
word you I was wondering whether you
meant our physiological personality as
opposed to our higher self yes okay
second question
um perhaps it has become an
answer look for it there and see if you
can make a statement in say um
say um
just at the moment went out of my mind I
had to do
with oh yes you said you channeling
through two other physical channels on
planet Earth besides
Daryl five five others besides Daryl
which would Daryl would make
six five including okay are any of them
in others of the other four are they in
the United States
no did they call you Bash
they will refer in that way to the
identification in their different
languages they will all have the same
relative meaning for the idea of our
terminology that we have chosen of what
you call Bashar is not a name but a
title it translates roughly as
commanda thank could you tell us what
countries the other channel no
no
guys can you tell me uh how I can fly
down Hollywood Boulevard on a
broom in your imagination can it be
pulled off in this physical
dimensionality what is the
difference my degree of clarity of
perception your degree of willingness to
believe that there is no difference
willingness to your degree of willingness to not
to your degree of willingness to not
care what other people will
think part of my imagination is
including them creating them as think
things you in your reality will perceive
them as enjoying what you are doing
right you may have quote
unquote what is holding you back might
be
a belief within you that you know that
you will be experiencing the reality and
all the individuals sharing that reality
with you will be experiencing that
reality but you might fear that a
portion of yourself will still be
perceived in this reality to simply be
insane I flew down holywood bouard last
night on my
broom oh sure oh
sure oh
really all right walk him
well understand the hesitation May
simply be this individuals in your
society as we have discussed many times
who you call insane are experiencing
other realities and what they are
experiencing is no less real than yours
what they have not allowed themselves to
understand is how to
communicate back and force so that your
reality can partake of their experience
as well what you make be waiting to do
is to establish the balance within
yourself because it is important to you
that you do not isolate yourself from
the individuals who would label you as
crazy you give them enough time to
acclimate to the idea that what you are
going to do is possible so that when you
do it all will be able to partake in the
experience this is very true I it's not
it's not that I'm afraid they'll think
I'm insane it's more that I want to
remain in communication and love and
sharing with them all yes they want to
breach a reality that
would cause them of necessity to create
a breach of affinity thank you very much
yeah you're welcome thank [Music]
[Music]
you question about
relationship right I I seem to be like
uh I open myself to relationship and I'm
totally open and trusting and yes and
then uh I get hurt and then I become I
thought you said you were totally open
and trusting initially and then oh
initially why did you change your
mind well if something happens and I I
guess do you understand that if you are
in a state of complete unconditional
love and trust you can't be
hurt I guess I'm not in the state of
thank you very much now i get hurt and
why do you choose to be
hurt I don't know and and then I become
bitter and vindictive and then I close
the door and I'm kind of locked what are
you looking for when you open yourself
up to a
relationship uh love uh I mean somebody
to love me equally as I love them and
are you sure you are loving them
equally no why sure of anything oh all
right why
not what are you sure
of uh right now I'm sure that I'm I'm
locked in this
vindictiveness you are sure of that yeah
and I don't like it because it's it's a
lonely place to be may I remind you of
something sure if you were completely locked into
sure if you were completely locked into
it in a sense you would not be able to
not like it you follow
you follow
me you can only know you do not prefer
something when you have an inclination
that there might be something else and
knowing that there might be something
else means you are by definition not
completely locked into the thing you do
not like it is only up to you to determine
like it is only up to you to determine
that this something else is just as
equally real and that you can prefer to
live that way
and experience that reality as opposed
to the one you are choosing to
experience that will allow you to
experience it I have uh perhaps a hunch about it
it I have uh perhaps a hunch about it
but I don't have clarity about what
that's something else that is simply
because you think a hunch is something
that is not clear what is your
Hunch what there there are other ways of
being because like what other people
like what well like not being vindictive
and being forg not ask you like not what
I ask you like
what I understand you desire to not be
vindictive how do you desire to be to be
forgiving and forget forgive forgive all
right forgive I don't know how to forgive you
forgive I don't know how to forgive you
don't I I am yeah I'm very unforgiving
may I ask you a
question yes what is there to for
forgive uh somebody hurting me how can
somebody hurt you if you are choosing to
be
hurt the one you need to forgive is
[Music] you well if somebody leaves me and I
you well if somebody leaves me and I
miss him in a lonely that is your choice
to miss
them you are choosing to be
hurt you are not functioning from your
self-empowerment and that is why you are
attracting relationships that can only
reflect that you believe you need a
relationship to be complete and you do
not believe you are complete without a
relationship when you know you are
complete within yourself and attract a
relationship to share as true equals
each being in the relationship being
complete then an individual can come and
go and you will feel no loss because you
know you are complete and if an
individual comes and goes it is an
accurate reflection of the complete of
the relationship and it serves the
purpose of the relationship and is not
an interruption in the
relationship you follow
me you are simply assuming in this way
that you need a relationship to be
complete and so what you are always
going to attract to yourself is a
reflection of your
incompleteness so you will attract
someone who will act incompletely to
remind you that that is what you believe
yourself to be
understand the idea as we have discussed
of a so-called soulmate individuals in
your Society say if only I could find my
soulmate everything would be
wonderful but understand you only
attract what you are the vibration
of so if you know you are complete if
you are already the vibration of knowing
that your life is wonderful
anyway then you are the vibration that
will attract a soulmate because a
soulmate is only a reflection of your
awareness of your own completeness and
Perfection and your own self
love now has any of this been of
assistance to
yes you are of course applauding
yourself
yes I receive uh Earth as being a green
planet and and the serious is being a
crystal white and trying to see a color
of
asani in a sense you would find it to be
transitory green
blue wonderful for sure you I I wanted
to ask you how two I just fit
together thank you one is the idea of
the way way you say you are
always in exactly the right place at
exactly the right time meeting exactly
the right people and the other one is we
before we come here we plan our lives
only in the broadest terms yes it seems
like one is very minute in minute to
minute and the other is only
broadly as we have said there are two
types of free will the Free Will of the
higher Consciousness and the Free Will
of the physical
Consciousness the Free Will of the
higher Consciousness determines the
overall General basic events you will
explore as a physical
personality therefore because you are in
a sense going to explore those
events you will determine that the Free
Will of the higher Consciousness is what
will seem to the physical Consciousness
to be Destiny or predestination in the
broadest sense the way you explore the general
sense the way you explore the general
theme picked by the higher Consciousness
is completely up to the physical
Consciousness by analogy the idea as we
have said a few times the higher
Consciousness says you will walk down a
hallway in your life this particular
hallway you will walk down and nothing
can make you change out of walking down
that hallway but the hallway is
blank it only represents a basic
idea how you walk down the hallway is up
to your physical personality whether you
walk whether you run whether you with
your eyes open your eyes closed in the
dark in the light on the ceiling on the
walls swimming floating walking
backwards positively negatively with joy
with sorrow with pity with victimhood
with Ecstasy with Friends
alone it is all up to you to determine
how you live out the general theme
chosen by your higher
Consciousness so as long as you're
within the hallway you're in exactly the
right place at the right time and you
cannot be outside of the hall right okay
now on one
exception suicide suicide is being an off of your
suicide suicide is being an off of your
path suicide is removing yourself from
the hallway before you get to the end
what if that was part of your path in a
sense it is but when you recognize what
it does as a part of the path from the
higher level so to speak when you reach
there you automatically understand what
the whole purpose was and you usually
will put your yourself right back in
okay so most beings do not come here
with suicide as part of their plan
correct okay
so understand that basically all death
is suicide
anyway yeah right but it is the idea of
running from yourself and not taking
responsibility for what you have created
in your life and believing yourself to
be the victim that type of suicide is
what puts you right back in the gate
right okay so there really aren no no
mistakes they AR no not even ultimately
the idea of the suicide for it goes into
the overall learning of the Soul right
okay so uh the car broke down the other
night with a friend of mine and and me
and we walked to the place that we were
going to we had planned on going which
wasn't very
far uh I just I failed to see the
purpose did you have a nice walk
everything was fine I had I didn't
resist any of it it was all very nice I
just failed to see the purpose if there
was one it does not always have to pop
itself up right away but also many of
you may be looking for more meaning than
there has to be yeah I have a tendency
to do that all right simply recognize
that in and of itself it may be an
opportunity to recognize that having a
nice walk with a friend is reason enough
to have done
it there might have been many things you
shared that you would not have had time
to share had you driven more quickly you
follow me yeah you were a different
person on arriving where you were going
than you would have been had you gotten
there sooner and that may have made all
the difference in the world into the
interactions that took place when you
got there a lot of these ideas may not
seem to be consciously obvious and they
do not have to be for as you simply live
your life there is not really any need
for a lot of them to be obvious in that
way simply that they allow you to live
and function according to the plan and
that is simply that you are trusting
that the plan is all always being
lived you follow me yes thank you thank
you y just want to let you know I'm
y just want to let you know I'm
exactically happy exactically
happy thank you very
much me
too feels great guys
that is why I choose to do
it
yes voice
voice Yes sounds different and it sounds
similar to how it was during the
spaceship there is energies being
prepared so you are sensing a little bit
of a
blending and is there some strain going
on no it is simply a
dislocation are you on now I always am
the mothership yes oh
not always am I on the Mother Ship but I
am on the Mother Ship now how far away
is
it our standard idea approximately
150,000 miles in the
neighborhood I I believe that I uh saw a
craft on Saturday would you time it on
that no what are the physical dimensions of
no what are the physical dimensions of
your mother C approximately 7,000 ft in
length 1/10 the
diameter um I'm asking this question for
my friend Elizabeth who's here and she
is Polish and doesn't speak English too
well she's very concerned about her
children in Poland receiving a lot of
radiation and she would like to know if
her kids would be coming here to the
United States for therapy or should she
go to Poland could she help them by
going to Poland she has already been
there when she
sleeps do you understand that
yeah when you visit them in your
imagination in your dream
reality allow yourselves to Simply know
that if you can be
aware that you are in
touch with
purposes reasons in
light the ideas that you are exploring
right now in and of itself being willing
to explore these
ideas means that you can function as a
psychic family and allow yourselves to
know that you all together can exist
within a
vibration surround yourselves with a
vibrational idea of energy that will
allow any type of other radiation that
does not fit in that frequency to be
neutralized is that
clear send your unconditional love but
not your
fear for it is the fear that draws the
negativity unconditional love will allow
all individuals who have chosen to
experience that radiation to experience
it as they have chosen to and simply
know that that vibration has nothing to
do with you thank
you what's it mean if you wake up at
4:00 in the morning what's the
significance of that there can be many
reasons but in a general sense simply
recognize that many of you are finding
your sleeve patterns changing because
the idea of your natural patterns in
that way will simply be that 3 2 to 4:
in the morning in that way will
represent the eye of your highest
activity point of energy and 2 to 4: in
the afternoon your
lowest many of you force yourselves to
be awake during your lowest and force
yourselves to be asleep during your
highest as you begin the blending into
fourth density you may simply find that
many of you will reverse the pattern
regardless of what jobs you think you
have to
maintain why is 2 to 4 in the afternoon
a low period that is simply the way you
have created the cycle of the energy of
your planet the whole planet basically
why do you think so many cultures have
what you call siesta
briefly um I just I was also curious I
heard about um these like let's say the
light from a quazars is uh being you
know gravitationally pull so we see two
quazars but it's really one and they
said the mass that was pulling the light
apart was so great they couldn't really
identify it
yeah within the entirety of the idea of
the universe everything will fall function
universe everything will fall function
around the idea that you call a black
hole which is a doorway every level of
existence from what you call Atomic to
Universal will always go around a
doorway in the center what you have now
begun to perceive is the doorway of this
universe itself around which the
entirety of all the physical matter of
your Universe
orbits that doorway leads to other
universes and directly into the idea that it is
and directly into the idea that it is
one of the valves that leads directly
into all that is that connects all
universes where is this in the
sky in a sense
everywhere in this way
basically in what
you would refer to as 60° North
inclination above what you call the
plane of the
ecliptic research further into your
own terminologies for in this way we do
not have the terminology within the
physical channel to draw upon as to what
your astronomer would use to describe
that
idea sure sure guys thank you I just
wanted to this is Lori and I
was and I just want the one exploring
flexibility yes yes I wanted to thank
you for the energy that you sent me last
week and I thank you for reflecting it
to yourself and being willing to open up
your own valves
yes thank you thank you
guys guys I can't see you I don't need
to I am not
[Laughter] here I would like to know if you would
here I would like to know if you would
help me pleas with some physical things
that um I know from talking to you a
number of times to a point and yet
there's still confusion
one is you are assuming that confusion
is negative uh neither negative nor
positive I would just it can be
positive the idea as we have said is
that you are cusing cusing fusing with
more of yourself yes okay one is the the
um uh hot spashes I seem to occasionally
get real cold and occasion get and sweat
this is typical fourth density symptom
okay thank you that was good and the
second is um I did a I also I listened
to what you said before about the lady
with the migraines what I do is I get
bone shifting in my skull and uh this
has been going on for nearly eight years
and I've been healing during that entire
time oh right and yet it still seems to
persist in fact it was doing it just
today and it still is in me and I was
wondering is there something that you
can perception now this may seem to be a
bit
obtuse is that you can discover much
about the idea should you carry on some
conversations with what you call your
geologists for in a way you are
reflecting the shifting of your
place allow there to be an analogy drawn
and information received in the
exploration of the information of what
the ship shifting of your plates
represents to the Earth as a
modification of the crystallin form that
it
is and allow yourself to partake of the
green emerald Ray that represents the
transformation of your planet into
fourth density stat and allow yourself
to
become already a perfect
Crystal so that you will not have to
deviate from that
formation that is what you are heading
towards anyway H hand
hand
that do you have an emerald no can you
acquire one oh yes I
one oh yes I
will I love emeralds but I never had one
go get
one and you will have a tool and a
companion through which you can Channel
some of the energy in this way to act as
a balancing for the shifting of the
plates that you have allowed yourself to
be so that it will equalize the energy
within you all right wonderful thank you
there will now be a short
break each and every one of you tonight
if your time is you create time to exist
perect in this way will be the allowance
of the idea of the exercise the going
into the imagination in this way the
forming of the crystal Consciousness
within each and every one of you and col
together the idea of the forming of the
Matrix of the idea of the Crystal and
Consciousness so that each and every one
of you May participate in the idea of
forming together a matrix that will
allow you to stick in the idea of
togetherness within the idea of the
transparence that will allow you to go
within your Consciousness in this way we
will decide and discover the idea that
the idea of dimensionality in of itself
will be something that you ATT to the
idea of mathematics and the idea of
height width and depth you will now
explore the idea of the dimensionality
of your own existence in this way and
utilize the idea of the structure of the
Matrix to be able to go within 90° out
of phase of the idea of your
Consciousness regarding the dimension of
your imagination is simply another
differentiation another perspective
another idea of out of faas the idea 90°
out of face to the reality you
understand to be the dimension of your
imagination are you all following along yeah
no will this represent a spe at which
you can fathom the
idea in this way allow us to illuminate
the idea that there will be a dimension
of imagination as has been expressed to
you in this way you can regard the idea
of your physical reality as an
expression of 90° phase differentiation
phase conjugation from the idea of your
second density representing the idea
that you are in your third we will start
at the beginning represent the idea by
closing your eyes in this way and
manifesting the idea of the relaxation
through three deep
breaths as you partake of the idea of
the 3D bth recognize that you are
breathing in the idea of the atmosphere
of the electromagnetic connection that
connects each and every being together
within the civilization you call your
own recognizing this way that as you
breathe together the idea of the
atmosphere you are linking within
yourself the identification of your very
cre creativity the very origin of your
own individual identity the very origin
of your Collective identity is a mass
Consciousness in this way you are
allowing yourself to fundamental feeling
of the creation of the vibration of the
atmosphere and the thickening round and
about you of that which will represent
the fluid in which you exist the fluid
out of which you create the reality you
know to be yourselves in this way the
idea that is the vibration of
unconditional love with which you are
surrounded which immerses you in this
way which fills you in this way which
you breathe in and out every moment of
time that you create to exist out of the
same fluid out of which the identity
that you know be yourselves also exists
you are one in the same idea one in one
part and parcel of the idea of the
creation of the fluid being the
identification of your own Consciousness
out of the fluid the identification of
any idea you call reality out of the
same fluid the projection of this
reality in front of your senses as you
create the illusion to exist but all is
created out of the same fundamental
fluid the electromagnetic alium of the
idea of the creation of the vibration of
the fundamental Primal energy that is
the creation of the homogeneous energy
that is the Primal energy itself of
Creation in this way allow yourself the
opportunity as you have breathed in in
and out this idea of the fluid to Simply
recognize that you are just as
homogeneous as the fluid you are
breathing in and allow there to be in
your imagination for now no separation
between the idea of the outside reality
the inside reality and the being you
know yourself to be allow yourself the
opportunity to feel that you are made
out of the same substance in this way
that you're simply a solidified
vibration of the idea a little bit more
coherent in terms of the vibration that
represents the idea of your identity
being where you are in Diamond space but
in this way now begin to allow yourself
to recognize that you are starting from
this zero point identity no Dimension at
all imagine yourselves to be a point
within a void and in the void there is
nothingness in this way you exist within
this point in one single point in
stretching away from you in Infinity
Direction in every 360° is nothing to
Eternity in this way that you understand
to be any kind of reality whatsoever you
are simply at the center of a void allow
yourselves to let this sink and soak
into the idea of the fabric of creation
as you know your energy to be focused in
this single point for now with three
deep breaths again allow yourself to
identify and simply that the entire
universe as you know it exists totally
within this single point and you are the
single point you are everything in the
universe but you are all within this
single
point now allow yourselves in this way
to recognize that you know yourself to
be a single point in this sense
contained within the idea of everything
that exists within this single point and
now you have the recognition that you
can realize an idea of of being outside
yourself now that you have recognized
the void the first Direction and The
First Dimension in which you will
realize yourself will be the idea and
the expression from the single point
outward One Direction in front of you
One Direction in back of you with the
forming of the idea of a single line you
will now upon this Revelation upon this
realization explode into a single line stretching to
explode into a single line stretching to
Infinity before stretching to Infinity
after in this way becoming a single line
of vibratory energy in this way straight
as a laser beam in that way as you call
that terminology upon your planet before
and after you now exist infinitely in a
single Dimension and recognize that all
that you had contained within the idea
that you were as a single point is now
also contained within the idea of the
line any point along the line is one of
the many infinite Eternal points that
exist between the idea of any other two
points upon the place of the line in
this way you can recognize that any
space upon the line is infinite unto
itself contains all the infinite
realities that you will understand
yourself to be and understood yourself
to be within the point now you allow
yourself to recognize that you have
phased out 90° from the idea in two
directions of the idea of the point that
you were and now that you are a line
stretching to Infinity there is another
Direction 90° in this way that you can
allow yourself to be you can recognize
the idea of the Ascension and descension
of the idea in lateral movement of the
idea spreading outward in what you call
to be a plane 90° in Phase to the idea
of the line perpendicular to it in this
way and allow yourselves simultaneously
in this way as you receive this
Revelation within yourselves to explode
into a plane that stretches into
Infinity in this way in every direction
according to the flat idea of the
representation of the line the many
lines infinite number of lines you now
find yourselves to be 90° in One
Direction 90° in another direction of
the idea of the line that you used to be
which was only a 90° extension of the
idea of the point that you used to be in
this way and now you can recognize that
within this infinite plane you are an
infinite plane in this way stretching to
Infinity eternally in this way and
contains the totality of all the number
of infinite lines that represent all the
different universes in line and linear
reality that have ever been are now and
shall ever be in this way and you
recognize you begin to recognize that as
you recognize the idea of the time frame
within the present the past and the
future in this way you begin to
recognize that as you are now a plane
you also exist in this way as a plain
reality in all Infinities and contain
the entire idea of many different
Infinities of lines in this way in all
time modes all frames of reference 90°
to what you have been now you begin to
recognize that much more readily that
much more rapidly the idea that this 90°
phase can conjugate in this way can
continue in a spiral pattern in this way
always perpendicular to itself and you
begin to realize that you can in this
way become an infinite series of planes
filling the idea of the previous void to
be a volume which you can contain within
yourself in this way and you find that
as you allow yourself the revelation of
the experience in the 90°
perpendicularity of the idea to the
plane that you were you now allow
yourself to explode to the idea of an
infinite series of planes above you an
infinite series of planes below you in
this way and begin to be the third
density vibrational reality that allows
you to fill the void in its spiral
fashion infinitely in every direction
you are now the solidness filling the
void that was previously there when you
existed in the IDE of a point when you
existed in the IDE of a line when you
existed in the idea of a plane there was
void above you void below you in this
way now there is no void in the idea you
feel the idea of the internal void in in
this way you search around for you
recognize that you have filled the void
90° in every direction you can fill the
void in the idea of your understanding
is now that there is no more directions
to go but in this way you recognize
there is one there is the idea in this
way of recognizing that you have
expanded outward and in this way you now
create the reflection and reverberation
of the idea of expanding inward to be
the 90° phase that stretches into your
imagination and as you find yourself expanding
and as you find yourself expanding
inward you realize you are not covering
territory you have covered you are not
retracing your steps in this way but you
are actually breaking into 90°
parallelity in this way into a new
dimension as you recognize this
Revelation you will explode inward in
this way 90° in Phase to the idea that
you previously were in filling the
physical dimensional void you recognize
now that you have taken upon yourself
the idea of mimicking and reflecting the
idea of a parallel alternate Crystal
which exists within the crystal you have
become there is a universe that exists within
there is a universe that exists within
the universe that you were a void that
exists within the void that you have
filled and in this way you recognize
that you have now with this breakthrough
90° within yourself you recognize it to
be the dimension that you call
imagination in this third density void
you have called this idea the
imagination now you recognize that as
you go 90° inward into yourself there is
now the recognition and the Revelation
that there is an infinite number of 90°
phase conjugations that allow you to
Forever and eternally go go further and
further inward into yourself in an
infinite series of 90° directions that
allows you to know you are a constant
spiral of energy always manifesting 90°
perpendicular to the previous dimension
in which you existed allowing yourself
to recognize that there is an infinite
amount of dimensions and density
vibrations and variations into which you
will always find yourself
instantaneously exploding now
exploding now
howow yourself to recognize in this way
that you have become an infinite series
an infinite number of facets an infinite
number of crystals an infinite number of
Dimensions an infinite number of
realities an infinite number of
probabilities and in this way you can
recognize that each and every being
within any reality you experience is
only a projection of the number of
infinite crystals that exist within any
given reality that means that you are
every being in every reality and every
being in every reality is you in this
way and as you project the idea of an
infinite number of facets an infinite
number of Reflections an infinite number
of mirrors recently recognize that all
that you are seeing are only you
reflected in different 90° phase
variable conjugations being Reflections
back to yourself through different
points of view your energy having taking
different routes through the infinite
all that is and coming back to you
through the representations of the
different Windows of the infinite which
is all all the beings that surround you
are they are the windows of the infinite
that reflect all the different ideas
that you have become in all the infinite
universes coming back through the
spiraling motion to the center of your
being to the phase point the Primal
point you started out as being what you
always find yourself to be you have sent
yourself out spiraling through the idea
of yourself and find yourself always
returning back to yourself forming upon
yourself the closed idea of the infinite
multifaceted spiritual Crystal that you
find yourself to
be now eternally eternally
within and
without now recognize what we have done
in this way has allowed you to explore a
certain facet of your imagination that
will allow you to form what is necessary
for the trip to come in this way that
Bashar will assist you within for now
you have formed within you a
subconscious and unconscious and a
conscious linking to each and every
identity within your Crystal and fabric
in this way of the particular universe
that you exist within and you will allow
yourself to partake and parcel of the
idea of the transformation to any level
of density vibration in this way and you
will always link yourself together and
transport yourselves as a mass unit in
this way while still maintaining the
individuality that allows you to mark
yourself as one individual facet of the
multi-dimensional crystal you have now
discovered yourselves to be recognize
first and foremost that every single
journey into your imagination is just as
real as any other reality you have ever
experienced and ever will experience in
this way and now we will turn back the
idea of the idea to the transportation
of
the Endeavor into the spacecraft as you
call the projection of that you call a
space bre back to the idea identity you
call Bashar in this way we will thank
you for the sharing and the allowing of
the idea to us to turn on the
illumination of the idea of the 90°
phase conjugation that was your reality
in this way the crystallization of your
imagination which shall now and forever
more eternally in the now present moment
always be reflecting to you all the
probabilities you can become and all the
probabilities you are in any given
moment of time we thank you for the
sharing you have allowed us to partake
this evening of your time and we now in
this way instill within you our
projection for an enjoyable experience
within your imagination in this way we
thank you and B you a fond good night
good how are you all doing
wonderful now before we
now before we
begin as we have called it our little
field trip
allow me to remind you of something each
and every one of you is your own
being each and every one of you creates
the symbols in your reality to fit the
idea that you hold yourself to be so
recognize this many of you when you find
yourselves aboard our
spacecraft may be perceiving it in ways
that will allow you to experience it
comfortably many of you may think you
are in an ordinary building upon your
own Planet but simply go along with it
it may transform it may transmute do not
judge that you are not there you will be
there there is at this
time no way unless you make the
conscious choice not to there is no way
that a portion of of your Consciousness
will not be aboard that craft because at
this time your reality and your
imagination are linked and malleable
enough that you will through your desire
through your excitement whether you
think you are or not take yourself where
you truly desire to be in that
truly desire to be in that
way in this sense therefore do not judge
any interpretation any idea any
visualization that comes into your
imagination regardless of what you see
you will be on the craft there will be
an opportunity after the journey to
share what you have seen and we will in
this way illuminate and interpret the
experiences that you have had in
specific portions of the
crowd now allow yourselves to close your
eyes and go within your imagination and
remember that what your pop has shared
with you is you are now a single Crystal
you have individuality in your own
component but in this way as you will be
a single Crystal you will all wind up on
the craft
together once you are on the craft in
this way being that it is cylindrical
and many deck a tube within a tube
within a tube within a tube within a
tube the center of all the tubes will be
to Any Given deck the direction of up
and in this way you will find that you
have the ability to walk walk anywhere
you will or to
instantaneously transport yourself to
any deck any chamber any room any
encounter allow yourselves now in your
imagination to
to
surround yourselves all of yourselves
the entire gathering tonight of your
time with a blue white energy bubble and
in this way as you know you are within
the house you are within allow yourself
to begin to recognize as chop has shown
you that now that you are in this bubble
you are in an isolation black hole
Singularity that allows you to be in
touch with any probable reality any
probable Universe any probable location
in time and space in this way allow
yourselves now to visualize in your
imagination in any way shape and form
that your imagination allows it to be
comfortable to see through the
transparent blue bubble house you are in
and see it in your imagination begin to
dissolve into a whitish gray fog of
immateriality the homogeneous Primal
energy out of which any reality can be
formed see the Gathering floating in
this fog in your blue energy
bubble breathe easily breathe deeply for
you know that a portion of your
Consciousness is now other than the
physical reality you have inhabited for
so very long in your terms of time allow
yourself to begin to perceive that the
idea of the gray white fog that
surrounds the bubble in this way is now
the malleable clay and energy out of
which you may now allow your imagination
to form whatever picture it will have of
your materialization upon the
materialization upon the
crow in this way allow yourselves the
opportunity you simply experience that
each and every one of you are aboard
this craft exactly where you imagine
yourselves to be partake of the Ecstasy
of the thickening of the atmosphere you
may perceive there will be beings but
many of them may seem to be very etheric
or astral or ghostlike to you popping in
and out of solidity in this way do not
fear you are more than welcomed with
unconditional love allow your curiosity
to to let you explore the very depths
and dimensions of the craft in this way
and recognize that at the same time each
and every one of you will be aware in an
energy empathic sensation of where
exactly every other member of your group
that came with you happens to be if you
so desire to find anyone you may link up
with them in an instant you cannot
become lost within the craft no matter
how large it may seem to you in this way
while you are exploring what you are
exploring and perceiving in the manner
you are perceiving allow yourself to
trust that whether it seems so or not
you are now in the energy surrounded
within our mentality and are sharing an
experience aboard our spacecraft in this
way allow yourself to know that this
experience will blend and bleed into
your oric field and you will take this
back with you when you return to your
planet in this way always knowing that a
new portion of yourself has done
unlocked in this sense and a new
identification with the association and
all that is has been constructed for you
in the identification and the definition
you will now from this point forward
hold yourselves to be feel free to
participate and enjoy in any Endeavor in
this way and drink deeply of the
experiences that you may find aboard the
ship now recognize in this way that many
of the smaller craft that we may pilot
that are contained within the mother C
will usually not be given the
identification of names but the mother
crafts have vibrations that may
translate as names in your language the
identification of the name of this
mothercraft that you are on may be
translated freely into your language as
the solar wind allow yourself to explore
the solar wind freely and in this way
joyfully sharing and blending the
identification of those that are
surrounding you and sharing and
bequeathing to you their energy so that
you may partake in an ecstatic childlike
manner of all that you will find upon
the craft in this way feel free to go
into and through any Chambers in that
you find before you that you find within
your imagination and simply partake of
the experience as you shall we shall
give you a moment to explore freely
within your imagination and remind you
to breathe deeply and joyfully and with
the ease of creation
you may understand again that no matter
what you are getting whether you are in
this way feeling like you are receiving
anything or not you are above this craft
and allowing yourself to
absorb the information and
absorb the energy in whatever manner you
so deem to be what you will allow
yourself to be best served by and
willing to allow yourself to serve
others with when you partake and bring
back this experience with you now at
this time allow yourselves to form a
connection in your identification and
your imagination to every single member
of the group that came with you in this
way and allow yourselves to reather and
form the manifestation of the sharing of
the UNC conditional love and the idea of
your farewell in a farewell that is
never sharing broken that continues
eternally in this way to surround
yourselves with the energy bubble and
allow the idea that you have within your
dimension of imagination of the craft to
dissolve back into the gray blue white
fog and in this way allow yourselves to
form in this limbo State while you are
surrounded with your own spacecraft
which is a projection of your
Consciousness allow yourself to form an
identif vacation with your own Planet as
you see it hovering below you in this
way the loving idea of your planet that
reaches out to you nurturing you in this
way and see the green emerald crystal
Clarity of the vibration in your planet
that is equal in unconditional love to
anything you ever experienced upon any
spacecraft or in any dream state or in
any dimension of existence and know that
here is love personified upon your
planet and know that you have chosen to
belong you have chosen to exist upon
your Planet because it is that you are
sharing the idea of unconditional love
personified in the service you are
providing in this way allow
yourselves in the integration and the
solidification of
your physical reality the room that you
entered this night of your time to
reform round and vow you to become
comfortable within your surroundings and
allow yourselves to know that even as
you solidify the room around you and
dissolve the energy Shield that you
still maintain with Crystal Clarity
within you always the identification
that you and your doorway of imagination
is always linked to all realities that
you may go anywhere any when anytime you
wish you may breathe deeply of the
vibrations of your Earth welcome
yourselves to this home and in this way
you may partake
of sharing your experience who will be
first yes yes
I I first went in the ship it was
like it was kind of like inate panels
but tremendous big thing I didn't quite
oh and then later I wanted to go up to
another deck so I went up there I
teleported myself up there Greenery like
some kind of green plants growing uh
some kind of green there are Gardens
aboard the ship yes and then I transport
myself on up further and there was a big
dome it was like a a rounding kind of
Dome and it looked like beautiful
brilliant colored crystals that area and
uh then when I finished that when you
started to bring us back down I didn't
want to come down but I did but I felt
the most tremendous love there the most
beautiful love it was just so pure so
beautiful thank you for participating in
that matter who
else uh The Impressions I I had were a
black and white checkerboard pattern oh
right not literal but go ahead um
individual or individuals wearing green
um costumes you are sensing
our vibration of the idea that is the
mimicry of our vibration of our star
light in that way which is a green star
and the vibration of the shifting in
that way that is green blue within us
not so much the actual identification of
the actual material of the
costume continue um a large screen or
screens translucent in quality yes um
railings of some some kind of catwalk or
railing in a sense
as um and pl form areas
ni emotionally a lot of um a lot of
energy within me a wonderful feelings of
of love and Oneness sharing
um uh gentleness uh
gentleness uh
Delight for your participation in this
manner who
else guys
um how many of your people are there on
the ship share your experience you sure
ship share your experience you sure
well
um okay I experienced many different
decks and seeing the whole cylindrical
thing and I felt the
real my perception was that there were a
large number of people there are
thousands right that's what I got
thousands or sometime somewhere between
1 and th000 more more okay and that
while I could perceive them they have
separate bodies but the perception that
they are all aware of their
interconnectedness and collectively good
and collectively although without
distracting themselves physiologically
if you will from their tasks and
everyone seemed to have a task
correct it was clear that they could
expand their awareness to offer us a we
welcome as we appear yes thank you for
your participation in this man yes um I
was experiencing also a tremendous
amount of beings and some some seem to
be very dark eyed and very light colored
yes quite a few the majority yes that is
our species right that's what I felt and
there was also some very different kinds
of being coming and going kinding of you
know they weren't real solid like you
were saying ni in this way they were
simply out of phas slightly with the
phase you were in and I had a feeling of
long round hallways of like hallways yes
um oh such a feeling of um Joy there to
and peace yes balance yes was wonderful
thank you for your participation
El when I first got there uh talking
about different beings I had a strong
feeling of what I would have interpreted
as being as elves playing children yes
ah and they were having a
wonderful and I continued and saw some
Gardens also plants and and
um as I was leaving I seemed to embrace
someone guys and it it was it was
wonderful thank you thank you
thanks back there
um I experienced a it's like all of a
sudden I woke up and I was in a seemed
like a clear plastic or crystallin round
um tunnel that seemed to be in the
center of the sh yes continue and there
was a spiral staircase yes and so as a
group there were a number of us going
down the staircase and then it was like
we were sliding yes very good there was
an individual last night of your time
who have the same experience in the same
area of the craft okay and faster and
faster towards on the bottom there seem
to be a
rotating I don't know what the fans or
rotating in a sense is it a generator
or I wasn't anyway it is more of a
amplifier and then there were little I
had round little doorways that opened up
and it's kind of like I kept just
popping my head out on different levels
at one point I got out and this was I
don't really understand this either but
I was
holding a a a rectangular piece but
seemed like metal and it had a circuit
boards on it or crystals very good and
there was another person that came to
meet me that also had a circuit board
yes and it was like we were doing this
little dance of the circuit boards were
sparking back for yes what was that you
simply have picked up upon piece of
equipment that lets you recognize that
many of the ideas of our circuitry are
embedded within thin plates of Crystal
and metal in that way and may perform
many different functions and when you
form an identification from one to the
other then that one being basically
blank or neutral to begin with will take
on the function it has been given from
the other that was the idea of what you
call programming to form an identical
circuit system
one other experience I had was when you
asked us to make contact with the rest
of the
group my experience was that became very
dark and it became like a solar system
and I experienced everyone else as stars
or planets all right very good you
simply expanded your idea of contacting
the rest of the group a little bit
beyond the boundaries of the
ship for in this way you also identified
with the association
thank you thank you
guys I experienced um what I felt with
children nice um they were gray and
white and they were just they seemed
delighted to see me and oh yes they have
been so for the last three nights of
your time to see all of you they and
they were reaching out their hands and
touching me and I was touching them and
it was just sort of a feeling
of playfulness and delight and Discovery
yes and the only other thing I sensed
was a was falling down or sliding down
along tube and also coming up out of
this tube to where these children were
yes it thear yes is the number of people
12,000 in that
magnitude it is
wow thank you thank you that's
I experienced myself in a room that
seemed to the word gy came to mind and
there were a a piece of equipment that I
um would say was maybe about 20 ft long
and about 10 layers high in each layer
there was something cooking and the
bottom layer opened was open and in it
there were there was food that was kind
of sizzling and the uh dimensions of the
food were like about 3 in wide and about
6 in long and they were right next to
each other and I thought I ought to eat
one of them but it was too hot all right
now you did not literally see
food but in this way you interpret it as
sustenance sustenance energy in that way
for you will find that those are
individualized chambers that allow there
to be identification with any
individual's vibrational Matrix and
there to be in a sense a resupplying of
energy it is not literally food the heat
comes from the intensity of what you
felt to be the
energy and you manifested the idea and
recognizing it to be in a sense
sustenance but it is not solid
frood was there some reason that I
should not have eaten it or it would not
have hard
you simply you did not allow yourself to
recognize that you also burn that
brightly and it would have truly been
quite comfortable to the touch thank you I
you I
experienced a expansion of the mind
which was funny because it expanded
beyond the skull to and yet it was
contained in the skull all in the same
time and on the ship I experienced
levels up and down to me up and down the
lower I went the darker dark blues and
not black but dark blues and the weight
got heavier I and I saw different beings
that were I actually almost beca I
became round circular beings in the
heavier gravity and then going up in the
middle of the ship was a greenness and
going up to me to the top of the ship
was a yellow red colors there a lot of as I
a yellow red colors there a lot of as I
went through it's almost like different
people of different races were living
there in a sense now what you are
experiencing is also something that
another individual of your species
experienced another night of your time
in doing this and it's not so much that
they are all exactly reflective of
different races although to some degree
that is true but it's the idea that on
each deck there are many specific
purposes going on and you are sensing
the overall energy as they assimilate
and acclimate in that way to the overall
purposes on each deck you are picking it
up as if they are a different species
unto themselves because they so greatly
identify with each other in their
specific purposes on each deck it seems
to be different civilizations it is not
it is simply different
intentions I see and then coming back it
was the connection with others was not
as I would have predicted icted it would
be it was a new type of
connection to
where I got the concept yes of being
able to change my reality and then
reform it yes which was interesting
thank you I have viewed your ship as a
you I have viewed your ship as a
transparency yes and I I floated it
seemed like I was floating through the
mass consciousness of the ship ni but
still with the ability to recognize each
individual yes and feeling how it would
be to to be there and feel recognize
individual
and how did it feel well it felt they
were reflecting my wholeness yes there was no
reflecting my wholeness yes there was no
judgment it was all a pure reflection of
the being without the physiological
personality thank you very
much yes um first I got the Sensation
that well inside the craft seemed like
it was a lot larger than it appeared on
the outside as if there was more space
than what that appear also um the idea
had come to me while I was there is oh
well they they they probably don't sleep
much so so I um like entered a room
where it wasn't like sleeping quarters
but it was kind of a
a space for quietness or something space
just did you see the palace uh no all
right what pets the flat white
pallets what you might take to be
resting
Chambers and then but are what allows us
to amplify the connection through the
computers of the ship to allow us to
channel to you oh really so so you are
in that room
that's very interesting cuz that's where
I I felt like what I wanted was to have
face to face contact with you well you
were close next room over so um I was with I
close next room over so um I was with I
felt then what I wanted to do was being
communication with the people rather
than go around the ship and or the
entities and uh what I felt was like you
said the childlike and they were really
interested in what I had to say good
does that surprise you no it was just no
it was really it was just a fun
experience and um and it felt so much
the love felt kind of like honey you
know yes and thickening
luxuous yeah I enjoy thank you very
much yes then you um I
experience standing on the outside of
the ship oh very creative
oh and then um I experienced walking
through I guess would be it seemed like
a deck yes and it seemed to be like
pipes or like corrugated slightly yes to
some degree coration would be more
appropriate rather than pipes and um so
pipes in a sense in that they do Channel
energy through
them um
I sense that they looked more
three-dimensional than they were
threedimensional yes and um I also um experienced looking
yes and um I also um experienced looking
out some kind of window I don't know
whether it was a window into other areas
of the ship or outside or what did you
see Blackness did you see
Blackness did you see
stars I don't recall seeing
Stars was it a small chamber that you
were in yes it felt like a small chamber
was there a crystal in the middle of the
room I don't recall seeing it this how
did it feel being in the room like you
were in touch with more than
yourself yes there was the quality of
being in touch with more than
myself how did it feel to look out
through the window very peaceful very
all right peaceful you are then in the
three nights have done this the third
person to find what can be colloquially
referred to as a chapel but not really
it is a chamber in which an individual
can form a direct Association and
identification with all that
is you simply did not activate it to its
fullest potential and while I was in that
potential and while I was in that
chamber um I thought about you but not
like the physical you ni and um I was
feeling very shy so all right that is
why the chamber was not activated uhhuh
and um but I did experience an enormous
amount of love it was like even my
shyness was accepted oh of course and it
was really nice thank you very much guys
one moment um then you well my initial
experience was I was trying to see
things as you had described them but I
realized that wasn't really my path so
um my I
met a group of individuals and I felt
like I was there in physical form and
all right we sort of more or less bowed
to each other in a recognition of the
beauty of self and the beauty of each
other but my greatest Fascination Bard
was with the computer all right sh that
I felt um I felt very crystalline and
multifaceted and I felt like this I know
was like I'm just trying to use words as
a feeling but tentacles all throughout
the ship and I felt like I had the that
was my greatest way of being of service
to all these individuals because I felt
very connected to them and that I could
serve them very well and that was really
neat experience thank you very much
guys I
uh saw like hands uh touching
fingertips and between them was a
tremendous amount of light yes and I was
like bathed in that and welcomed yes
called into that light and I was very
felt very loved and secure and allowed
myself to feel that and I felt as if I
was a child again those children
I was laughing ecstatically I did a lot
of laughing and then I was like I was
told the message that I this is within
me and I can take that with me and be
that thank you for accepting the gift
and uh and tears started flowing when we
were I was coming back I had like lots
of tears coming releasing centering
acknowledging your ecstasy yeah and it
was like like a release right
thank you very much for your
sharing anyone else sure yes you said
that your the name we call you means
Commander does that mean that you are
the commander of that entire ship
no Bashar yes um I fell for a good deal
of the experience that I was in some
kind of a rec room Recreation room all
right what did you see well it seemed
almost like a theater to me it felt like
in a sense it is yes it felt like a
theater anyway there were lots of people
around it was very loving and most
enjoyable I mean I was having a very
good time and I was disappointed when I
had to come back but realizing I why why
why well you're right so I realized that
I was able to be there and be
here and I also realized that I was
connected to everybody all of our group
here and in some way connected to all of
the beings on the ship as well at all
times and I was almost playing in the
act that was going on and also
reflecting all the people doing what
they were doing at the same time like
this glorious giant stage and production
it was great it was
wonderful and it turned around and I
mean it was it was wonderful move oh
thank you very much for participating in
that way oh it was a great time I
enjoyed it thank you for providing
it you you uh yeah when you mentioned
about Recreation room I I saw thought I
was in a room like this too and I
perceiv what I interpreted to be you
were seeing
seeing
equipment that has to do with in a
sense the toning of forms the
identification of forms but it is not
the idea of exercis in that way it is
not the idea of needing to maintain
Health in that way yes I realize that
but it is the idea of forming different
identifications on a cellular
level and many beings wish to
participate in that area in identifying
and being able to feel what it is like
to feel like another
being wonderful
wonderful
guys i s such a tremendous amount of
people and there didn't seem to be ining
of
Separation The One guys and the shark um
iess such a tremendous amount of people
and there didn't seem to be a feeling of
separation and I was wondering is there
a governing body on a ship or a
commander there is the idea of what you
would call a commander but in this way
no one governs in our
civilization there is on every mother
ship a forum of the
association thousands of Consciousness
is always eternally in a sense
exchanging aspects of their Consciousness to allow
aspects of their Consciousness to allow
there to be the blending that continues
forever that forms the allowance of
communication to flow in the association
of all civilizations that partake of the
Gatherings it is not as you understand
it a government it is a
service it is more of an
exchange and the association refers to
all the
civilizations that go into making the
association you would term it a
confederation but that is in our
perspective a governmental
term thank you very much
guys I would like before you uh before
pop left sh pop left uh I
saw it was as though I were on the ship
prior to or some place El because there
were small children did I guys you are
having a Flash Forward I see
thank you
you
yes um I I saw I was invited to see and
feel something felt with my
hand um I don't even know what it was it
like a giant well first of all look like
a center of a really really really big
tunnel nice uh it was farther than I
could see and there were two
two within my vision large white things
almost look like lit crystals all did
you also see some sort of
a what you might call a woven
structure or an
intertwining or a radial pattern yes all
right like rain yes all right you were
in the middle of one of the engines
[Laughter] [Music] [Music]
in the
middle inside one of the Eng I put my
hand on I did yes how did you feel
wonderful yes for it operates upon the principle
yes for it operates upon the principle
of the fundamental energy that powers
the
universe there will be
a few moments remaining for this
interaction this evening of your time
sure yes um then you while on the ship
where I said that I felt like I want to
have face to face communication with you
but I did have an experience that I did
yes but you said almost well in the
sense that I did not break from my
communication you did in this way my
occupi nature allowed you to communicate
with an aspect but not the totality in
that I am linked up this way and back oh
but I also had visual like saw you
visually okay yeah no I I didn't yeah I
felt that you can different aspects of
yourself that you
can still be in one
place understand that the spacecraft is
very much in our point of view a
definite projection of our Consciousness
and within it can be a veritable
Wonderland of impossible Miracles so
what you're channeling through Bashar
there's still I beg your pardon I mean
while you're channeling through
darl there could be um you still be
doing whatever you're doing to some
degree an aspect of myself in that way
for the purpose of making a greeting
that is requested yes normally no right
I mean I felt like you you when I
visualized you you were very kind of
quiet I mean you weren't really doing
anything physically um
now can you Channel through more than
one person at one time or do you yes so
do you do that yes I mean simultaneously
yes okay good good like you yes
um I I have a question there was one
item that I saw when I was in the the
chamber that you called the chapel or
like the chapel guys it was it seemed
marinik to me um it looked sort of like
very irregular and large maybe six to 7
ft tall and it had like what looked like
Barnacles on it your
it your
interpretation of the crystal oh okay so
but that is not a literal interpretation
okay so then I did see yes the Crystal
and then I was extremely aware of your
voice changing when I was on the ship
the energy shifted the okay and um also
I could feel it vibrating in my ears
yes you were
closer oh okay you were within the
atmosphere in which I
exist and thus in this way
simultaneously was a deeper connection
and also in a sense a more remote one to
be able to function as your overall died
dispersing my Consciousness throughout
the ship simultaneous L while also
remaining focused in the channeling to
guide you through this end I was at both
ends at
once well you did a splendid job
you yes uh one last little note um at
the ending point or whenever we were you
were telling us to come back to the
surrounding area and describing the
planet and such I that was actually to
me the most exciting part of it it was I
felt such an incredible sort of
realization of the magnitude of the
civilization that we are and the beauty
and the um the essence that it really is
and of which I'm a part and I was
extremely happy about that thank you now
may I let you in on a little secret
sure are you sure yes sure yes all
right a few
individuals upon your planet who allow
their senses to be specifically tuned to
the vibration of what was
occurring saw your leaving and return as
a
UFO I felt that that's interesting I
felt that by the way the title for tonight is
that by the way the title for tonight is
field trip thank
you thank you
break as I was outside we saw two um
brilliant ruby red lights moving and
flashing moving in a formation across
the
sky is that a question no it's a shering
all right they were your own C yes thank
you um it was a wonderful experience
going to the ship and and being able to
join but I found that there was fear
that was connected to it yes that is why
many of the inhabitants remain slightly
out of your perception for in this way
they did not want to broach the idea of
whatever level of allowance you would
create for yourself not wanting to force
you to face all of the different
portions of your personality that you
have not yet been willing to face for in
this way you will find that when you get
into the vibration of an accelerated
nature in that way it will have a tendy
to overwhelm your vibration and bring to
the surface perhaps against your will
all of those portions you have not yet
been ready to face so you may have been
a little bit jittery anxiety is the same
energy as excitement you were simply
putting a little bit of judgment upon it
you follow me yes I
do yeah you communicate for people
plant planted you give give
message
catac you give today I yeah
welcome and then
I love to
you thank you for your sh
thanks I know what was going on could
you not feel
it not exactly did it pass right through
you between my
ears all right understand you have
already made your own understandings of
connections of that nature and allowing
the energy to go around you you knew
what you were doing for you would have
instantaneously accelerated where you do
not want to go right now had you
received the energy directly you know
whereof I am speaking
okay and what the
language it was an emotional imagination
compilation of language in this way it
was no specific language except the
language of the soul in that way
translated into the vibrations of your
language of your Earth language of the
idea of your archetypal language in that
sense it was in a sense what you might
also call Angelic or
Celestial thank you
guys um what Consciousness was coming
through that other physical
person that will be a sharing and a
blending for another
time and also because for now this is
personal unless that person wishes to
share at a later
date thank you partake of the energy in
whatever manner you wish to partake on
whatever level you have received it and
allow yourselves simply to know that the
idea of the sharing of love and
emotionality May at times seem in this
way to be remote from your day-to-day
experience but that the experience you
have just co-created and shared with all
of you together is a result of the
opening up and the acceleration of your
own emotionality and getting in touch
with all of the facets of all that you
are in the present now we will extend
this time of your time our unconditional
love to you once again and the opening
of the many doorways that you may now
found to be open in your dream realities
this night of your time from this point
forward according to the essence in your
oric field that you have allowed this
experience to maintain within the
crystallization of your existence in the
Eternal now moment we thank you for the
gift of your sharing in this way and we
bid you all exciting dream lives and a
fond and loving good
[Music] evening everything
evening everything
go you had you had a bit of our yes
[Applause]