all right how are you all this evening
of your time as you create time to
exist allow me to begin in the following
Manner and this also will be the title
of tonight's interaction are you
ready happy
an for in this way you will find that
this very night of your timing of your
counting precisely three of your years
ago was our first communication with you
through this
travel in this way therefore recognize
that this represents the idea of a new
phase a new passage a new doorway a new
Direction acceleration of momentum
blending of ideas and
energy and with regard to this idea with
respect to this particular point of view
allow us to share a few ideas with
you that will be the time for the
sharing that in this way allow us to
share with
you first that there will now be because of
first that there will now be because of
the representative timing more
acceleration in what you call the days
to come relatively quickly you will now
find that as you approach your year of
counting 1 bound
987 in this way there will be more and
more opportunity to recognize the
solidification of your desires the
solidification of your dreams into
physical materiality and you are now going to
materiality and you are now going to
begin to see that energy of accelerated
knowingness that is represented by your
Collective willingness to expand and explore more
willingness to expand and explore more
of yourself now come to fruition in your
physical world more and more more events
more and more opportunities more and
more blatant
representations of the manifestation of
change and
opportunity that can point in the dire
direction of unity and peace will now
begin to appear in your society as you
accelerate towards the
doorway of the springtime of your coming
new year which represents a gate an
energy gate through which you will be
nothing this energy gate as we have said
will involve more conscious
recognition more direct interaction from
many facets of your Society more impact
from many facets of your Society upon
the whole civilization in which you
exist with regard to what type of a
world you actually can create there will
be more expression of willingness to
share boldly
blatantly overtly
from many individuals and many groups
within your
civilization about the things that you
do desire to experience in your world no
longer within the next year of your time
will you find it necessary to keep back
to keep hidden the things that represent
your desire your energy your
acceleration your
knowingness your willingness your
convictions the
idea of the creation of a physiological
Harmony peace and ecstasy upon your
planet are now being anchored in solid
foundations of physiological
experience you will see more and more
opportunity to recognize this in your
Society in the coming months of your
time and therefore will create and
attract to yourselves more and more
opportunities to express that idea
yourselves as your lives become more
blatant representations of the
synchronicity of all
B now at this time therefore allow us to
as you say recapitulate some ideas that
we have been sharing with you for the
past 3 years of your time not so much
that we will repeat it but that we will
now explain the foundation that has been
laid down through the sharing of all the
ideas we have interacted with you
as in this way therefore do recognize
that we have always and still do know that
we have always and still do know that
you are in a world that involves
processes and at no time in our
discussion our sharing with
you was there ever intended to be the
idea that your processes are not valid
or that you should attempt to get rid of
them they are reflective of your world
and they are the very essence of the
courses of the lives you have chosen to
live but what we have been laying down
with you as a foundation is that the
idea of knowing that the processes are
your Creations your Illusions so to speak
Creations your Illusions so to speak
will create the ability to create your
processes in fluid flowing effortless
struggl manner that will allow it to be
perceived in your life as if you are not
going through
a process but simply enjoying another
ecstatic opportunity to experience more
and more life more and more joy more and
more happiness we simply sought to
happiness we simply sought to
disassociate your old definition of
processes so that the processes you
would continue to create as long as you
are physically real would not seem like
the struggle your processes of old have
been
in this way from time to time we have
shared certain ideas of
technique that may be representative of
an overall Collective Mass Consciousness
ability to tap into different levels of
itself at the same time we have
discussed that of course you are quite
capable of creating your own techniques
by tapping into this Collective
Consciousness your sense and that your
imagination is the doorway and the key
to which you have access access to all
that you need any tool any ritual any
method any process that you require in
life from time to time we have assisted
we have nudged we have
suggested different methodologies that
may be representative of what will
generally function or work for the
majority of you at the same time
reminding you that any general process
that we share with you any general
technique that we suggest is still
always going to be slightly altered to
fit the vibration the signature
vibration of the unique being that you
are so it is still your unique process
your unique creation and you are still
funneling or channeling our suggestions
through the dimension of your
imagination in order to allow it to make
sense in the reality you have created
yourself you all follow me
along thus in this
way we will after your break tonight of
your time share with you a
technique which in this way may allow
you to recognize the true expansiveness
that has grown within each and every one
of you through not only the interactions
you have had with us but through the
interactions you have had with
yourselves during the past several of
your years and in quite an acceleration
State during the past several of your
months regardless of whether you have
interacted with us before is not
important you have interacted with
exactly the information you have needed
to interact with and if you simply find
yourself exploring any of the ideas we
are sharing with you this evening of
your time at all then simply take it for
granted you are exactly precisely the
right place in the right time to
understand everything you need to
understand and you will understand it on
whatever level of your Consciousness is
required for you to understand it do not
worry that some things may seem foreign
in the technique you will understand it
and you will apply it in whatever way is
necessary for you to do so within your
own degree of willingness your own
degree of Readiness and your own degree
of comfort in applying these ideas
follow thir no one need feel to be a
stranger to the idea of the expiration
of the Ecstasy within themselves it is
not that you have missed out that you
are late that you need to catch up to
any particular techniques that have been
shared or anything like that simply
finding yourself interacting with the
individuals you are interacting with at
this time is indication that you are
exactly at the right place and the right
time or you would not be where you are
you will understand it in the way you
need to understand
it at this time allow us also because
you are now going to find that as you
expand your sensory awareness your
sensory apparatus there will be more of
an understanding of some of the ideas
you call psychic functioning and
telepathy in your
civilization we have shared some of
these ideas with you of recent and we
will share more this idea again
now in a sense allow us therefore to lay
down a foundation and an analogy and an
example some of the ways your Society has
some of the ways your Society has
represented the idea of psychic
functioning of telepathy for now we find
that this Foundation is necessary in
your Consciousness so that you can
recognize these things when and where
you see them in your Society so that you
will have a perspective and be able to
recognize that there is no need for
negative confusion about these ideas it
is all quite simply arranged within a
matrix of understanding it all quite
fits in
in
recognize that as
what you call your scientific approach
has been held to be
responsible has been given the job of
explaining your reality to
you thus having accepted that position
many individuals who are pursuing the
idea of scientific technique have
therefore sought to also explain the
idea of psychic phenomena of telepathy
in this way even though many of them do
not believe that such a thing is
possible they are still accepting the
job application of of explaining the
phenomena of something that do not
believe in now recognize in this
in now recognize in this
way it is simply that a
mythology so to speak has been created
about this idea and he will find it that
from our point of view it is quite
paradoxical that an
individual who purports to think of
themselves as scientific would a comment
on something they do not believe in to
begin with in that way thus forming a
conclusion that quote unquote in their
point of view should set the standards
for the rest of the society about what
that idea is all about to begin with and
be that they should find that because
they do not believe that they are
capable of designing an explanation of
it to begin
with in this way simply recognize their
point of view is valid for their own
understanding and their own approach of
themselves but at this time allow us to
give an analogy for why many individuals
that think that certain ideas or all
ideas should fit into pre-arranged and
preconceived structures simply do not
fit and why they think that if those
ideas do not fit then it represents the
idea that those ideas do not
exist may I remind you that the usual
form in general that this takes by
example is the following let us say
there is an individual who is
relatively in touch with the fact that
they are so to speak psychically
sensitive telepathically sensitive as
each and every individual actually is
but there is varying degrees of
awareness of this ability varying
degrees of willingness to share this
ability to express this
ability recognize of course as we have
shared with you many times the idea of
telepathy and psychic functioning is not
so much a mental activation it is
perhaps a mental expression so to speak
or it is contained within the idea you
call mental
but it is an emotional activation it is
activated by Desire by
emotion therefore in this way many times
first of all recognize that many of the
scenarios that are set up to explore and
examine psychic functioning an telepathy
are the most sterile of environments in
which there is no spontaneous
emotionality involved it is being
measured as if it were something to pick
apart and prod in a very seemingly
objectified way and by definition
definition it is not an objective
phenomenon thus that is why primarily it
has eluded many of the so-called
attempts at laboratory ising the
idea now you will find again that many
of these individuals that think they
know what the definition of psychic
functioning is even though they may not
believe it exists they have taken upon
themselves to believe that a definition
implies that if I ask you ex psychic
person to tell me something that you
have no basic access to and you tell me this
no basic access to and you tell me this
then I will believe that such a thing
exists if you do not I will not believe
that such a thing exists I will set the
standards and by those standards that I
set even though I do not believe that
such a thing exists I will determine
whether or not such a thing exists by
the standards that I set based upon my
understanding of this idea regardless of
what it may act be thus in this way it
usually takes the form of scientists
requesting of psychic oh well let us see
tell me what I have for breakfast tell
me who is going to win tomorrow's Gang
Tell me what I have hidden in my upper
shelf closet on the third floor in the
left hand corner of my house if you can
do that I will believe that such things
are possible tell me what I am thinking
tell me what my favorite fellow is all
of these ideas are usually in your
Society used as parameters to determine
even the basic reality of psychic
functioning or
the now let us turn this analogy around
and perhaps it will be clearer as to why
this is so to speak let us say to use
your terminology a
naive approach may I have a volunteer to
approach may I have a volunteer to
represent the planet
Earth all right you thinky now we will
suppose that I am the type of
extraterrestrial Consciousness that only
knows about your civilization through
the most remote hearsay and rumor my
impression of your civilization is
rather sketchy I have heard certain
things but I have not had the time to
put two and two together and really
explore the idea in total so I come to
you at this time mind with this
understanding hello hello how are you
I'm great how are you oh fine say you
know I have heard that there is this
device perhaps you can tell me the truth
of this matter if such a device exists
upon your planet I have heard you have a
technological device that enables you
gives you the technical capability of
speaking to anyone on your planet
within moments do you have such a device
yes we do oh what do you call it we call
it uh the telephone is all right number
ways to do it oh thank you this is very
exciting to discover that this is in
fact a
reality now therefore allow me to
request a demonstration oh may I oh well
thank you I will be most excited to set
up the parameters of this demonstration
which when fulfilled will excite me no
end to see the mar marvelous functioning
of this device therefore since you say
this device exists I will now set up a
demonstration so that you may have the
pleasure of demonstrating this device to
me let's see now we also have a rumor of
some individuals upon your planet we
have heard some names leaking through so
I will pick one of these names at random
and allow you to demonstrate your device
by communicating with this individual
let us see the name
ayat stands
out now therefore would you please
within the next 30 of your seconds place
a phone call to this individual and have
a communication with them so that I may
observe well can you do it can you take
me any long in 30 seconds but you said
the device is capable of talking to
anyone on your planet within that time
frame are you now implying that there is
no such capability well it it may be
possible though maybe you don't know you
said you had such a device why are you
hedging it depends on their person's
being available at at the other L Al so
what you are telling me is that my
particular request in a sense is naive
because I am unaware of all of the
variables that go into allowing the
process to actually be fulfilled is that
what you are saying well no it's not na
at all no yes it
is for I do not have an awareness of
what those variables are so my
assumption that it is in your terms
within your system of
reality simply a matter of picking up
the device at your end and placing the
call at the other end is not presenting
a cognizance of the fact that there is
upon the part of the individual at the
other end also a need to express the
willingness to communicate well I mean I
can make a phone call and it will ring
on the other end and somebody May pick
it up but it may not be the all right
but in this way are you understanding
the point we are making yes of course
all right then the idea simply can be
reversed to be understood that when an
individual suggests of another that they
function psychically or telepathically
in the way they think represents psychic
functioning or telepathy it does not
necessarily take into account all of the
factors
involved therefore in this way there are
three basic factors that allow for the
functioning of this idea in a clear and
concise manner just as there are certain
factors that allow for a clear
connection and communication through
your telephonic
device the first one is to recognize
psychic functioning and
telepathy will manifest along the line
of least
resistance now what this means is very
simply that if the information that is
being requested is accessible without
going to another level then you
generally won't go to another level to
get it so if an individual says to you
what did I have for breakfast they
already know so why should the psychic
not that it is not possible for the
psychic to do so if that is another
circumstance but why should that ability
open up when the answer already exists
in the individual asking the question it
is easily accessible through that
individual and let us
say the quickest response the quickest
the quickest response the quickest
manifestation of that answer would be
simply for the psychic to reply don't
you know what you have Professor you
tell me therefore you will also understand
me therefore you will also understand
that another way to express the path of
least resistance may be in the following
manner that again the information may be
directly accessible on the level in
which you exist in the conscious state
so let us say an individual asks you all
right you tell me what time did I get up
this morning now you may find that
nothing comes to you in your normal
psychic manner but as you are pondering
this you look around and over there for
some reason stands out a sign that has
the number seven on it so you simply say
well all right it's a
seven but you recognize that the ID is
even so much that you did not have to go
to another level to get it so to speak
but it was right there for you and the
synchronicity of the event played itself
out so it still took the path of least
resistance you follow it yes item
two will be there must be a
need very strong need or a very strong
desire or a very strong trust for the
information to be
there without one at least one of those
factors there is no need for the
activation and no ability for the
emotional activation of that information if
activation of that information if
somebody says well what did I have for
breakfast this morning who
cares it may be very important to the
person who had the breakfast if it is
important to the person to know that
they can know that if they simply have a
great need to know it they can know it
if they have a great desire to know it
they can know it if they have a great
trust they can know it they can know
generally speaking however that type of
a question does not usually evoke a
great need desire or trust since again
it is easily accessible information and
generally speaking it is being used to
create the idea of a test which
generally as you say turns people off
rather than excites them emotionally you
follow me the
idea in this way
therefore will be the second phase of
psychic functioning the
functioning the
third will be the IDE you call
preconceived notions these preconceived notions fall
notions these preconceived notions fall
into the category of the test in this
way because an
individual who is testing you for your
ability to access information within
them is in a sense actually holding that
information information from you they
are consciously putting a block around
it and not willing to interact with you
on an emotional level they are hiding
the information so that in creating a
preconceived notion that you should be
able to be able to dig after it root it
out tear them apart and pull it from
their midsection implies that you have
the capability of doing that that is a
preconceived notion about what the whole
idea is all about and thus does not
allow for the actual mechanism to
function another manifestation of what you call
another manifestation of what you call
preconceived notion can be in the
following example let it say you are utilizing the
example let it say you are utilizing the
device on your planet you call playing
cards and one individual holds up in
front of themselves the idea you call
the ace of spade they say to the psychic
all right guess what card I'm
holding the psychic says I get an
impression of free of heart no the
tester says you are wrong long you have
failed I do not believe in telepathy or
psychic functioning however it is a
preconceived notion that the idea has to
be transmitted in the way the
transmitter thinks it should to
represent what you call an actual
transmission the idea for what appears
to be the discrepancy can be for many
reasons one of which is as follows let
us say the individual holding the Ace of
space implies or puts into a certain
meaning to the Ace of Spades perhaps
that was something that carries great
importance for the
tester in this way what the psychic May
first pick up on is the feeling the card
gives the tester let us say it is a card
that won a game for the tester at some
point in their life so the psychic in
picking up the feeling may make a
relative preconceived notion of a
familiar Association and what they may
pick up on is the idea this is a card
that won a game for me at some point in
my life and allowed me to be very
excited what that may translate into is
the card that allowed the psychic to win
a game at some time in their life and
become very excited perhaps that card
was the three of Hearts so the idea may
be that the psychic was picking up on
what the card means rather than what it
physiologically is and the tester may
not be in touch with that
consciously you follow
me all of these
ideas many
times obfuscate the fact that psychic
obfuscate the fact that psychic
functioning and telepathy occurs
constantly in your civilization but many
times you do not allow yourself to
recognize that there are many
invalidations on the part of your society that allow
on the part of your society that allow
it to seem as if no such interchange
exists therefore from this point forward you
therefore from this point forward you
can be sensitive to the ideas as they
are being expressed and recognized that
feelings are what is usually exchanged
as telepathy or psychic functioning not
so much that it has to be literal
representational symbols though it can
be so the more sensitive you become to
the understanding that the
feeling is probably on the mark the more
confidence you will build within
yourselves that will allow you more
recognition of what another individual
symbols are that represent the feeling
you get and then you may be able to hone
in more precisely on the symbols
themselves but first you must allow the
feeling to devalidate
itself we all follow
along therefore along with the exercise
the technique we will
provide on the other side of your break
we will also this evening of your time
have a message for you at the end of the
session at this time share [Music]
[Music]
i' enjoy this evening very much did I
understand you to say on a previous tape
just a few weeks ago that uh the
transformation will extend into about 27
years from now approximately in
generalized terms each and every
individual within this overall bubble of
con will accelerate after their own pace
individually but the general average
crosssection of the combined rate at
which you are all progressing will take
up approximately the next 27 to 30 of
your years that sounds like a reduction
from the 30
were're doing doing good as we have said
the IDE as it still stands from our
point of view is that every single day
of your time time now brings with it as
many connections to different levels of
your Consciousness as it took one to
three years to make 10 years
ago that is the rate of which you are
accelerating okay um there's a fellow on
this planet named pron who calls himself
a
mentalist and he puts on some very
fascinating demonstrations of psychic
functioning I for one believe that he's
being honest and I believe that he's
doing in fact what he says he's doing
and what it appears to
be what he appears to be doing would you
give me your P perception and your from
your perspective of whether he's doing
that allow us to Simply say that we
perceive that that individual at times
will be conscious of the fact that they
are doing it that way and at times will
be conscious of the fact that they are
employing the idea you call illusion
although they consciously recognize and
state this to be so uhuh but the idea of
the creation of those Illusions many
times still relies on the same abilities
they utilize in psychic
functioning right whether they may be
consciously aware of this or
not thank you thank
you uh I also was very excited by your
introduction I think it's wonderful I
assume uh that's one of the reasons is
speeding up that uh some of us have been
very spaced out lately yes the limbo
state is in full force the
transition the shifting of Gears is
taking place that is why many of you now
find that you are coasting along with
your clutches
out our clutches out yes you are not
engaged oh right exactly uh now over the
weekend I slept a lot and Steve
mentioned that he and his family slept a
lot a lot of people connections onto
other levels that you now find necessary
to create the certain types of buffers
that you need to re-engage smoothly
that's what I assumed there was one if
it was that or if it was simply getting
ready to be speeded up what is the
difference exactly that was my next qu
next question if there was a difference
at all okay it's the same that was your
next answer oh my next answer right
right for you are in touch with what
these ideas mean for you and you do not
need to put them in the form of a
question right you can therefore allow
me to thank you for your sharing it's
been very it is very exciting very
intense thank you
definitely present relax relax
thany
yes sure there's been a few things that i'
sure there's been a few things that i'
I'd like to share with you and um go
righte okay I really also enjoyed very much
okay I really also enjoyed very much
your talk um this evening
and as I had shared uh previously about
my own experiences um with some psychic
um
phenomena uh mine didn't my experiences didn't
uh mine didn't my experiences didn't
seem to fit
into anything that in in the way that
you described describe drud it um
Define okay well like the the example of
the the neighbor that had passed away
and I knew um who it was and where it
happened guys how who was who where was
the emotional connection I didn't I
didn't really know these you you have a
need to be connected to that event so
that it can teach you things that you
are learning so that it can teach you to
expand the ideas you have a very strong
desire to fulfill within yourself so you
connected yourself to the event out of
Desire out of need to learn what you
need to learn because that event has
propelled you in the direction that
represents the path you want to
be these connections can be unconscious
we are not saying they are always
con I I don't know what a connection is
but I it does not have to be that
I it does not have to be that
complicated the idea of the connection
simply is to be event itself the fact
that it was in your
proximity not that you have to say well
what is my specific connection to that
specific individual
specifically it is simply that that
circumstance was available to you and
you took them up on it because you
needed to okay
um last night I had um
I wanted to go see you um at in North
Hollywood last night with a u a
girlfriend and another friend and I had
made a prior
commitment with um with a man I had met
on Friday night guys I didn't really
want to go with him and I don't know why
I had accepted but I was saying okay
there must be something for me to do
with this but he had was supposed to
have cold by 6:00 and I hadn't heard
from him so I just said I was going to
be felt said to myself and my friend I
was going to go to see you
and um my roommate was going to be
watching my son and I when the phone
rang I my psychic sense was saying I
wasn't going to I wouldn't have picked
it up CU I didn't want to hear from him
but I thought that it was her waiting
wondering why I wasn't there to pick her
up yet and I picked up the phone and it
was it was not her it was him guys and I
was like where was my psychic ability
when I wanted it to be I had exactly
where it needed to be again understand
you are confusing certain ideas you are
mixing them up the idea is that you
psychically functioned exactly as you
needed to based upon what you believed
to be true or necessary in your life you
simply Drew yourself into the perfect
action the perfect reaction to represent
what you knew you were picking up on the
exemplification of what you had chosen
to
do many ideas may seem to be reversed
but are still complete and full
fruitions of psychic ability in fact
there actually is a type of psychic
manifestation called
opposition in that many individuals will
find that exactly precisely the opposite
of what they think is going to happen
happens exactly the opposite not just
something else exactly the opposite it
shows them that they are in touch but
what it may show them is that they are
attempting to force their psychic
functioning through their
expectations rather than simply allowing
themselves to be naturally and in a
relaxed state in touch with what they
truly desire for their lives so they
cross their circuits so to speak you
follow me yes yes and that makes total
sense of what happened last
night then simply relax and recognize
back to square one that the idea of
everything that occurs in your life is
there for a reason and you can learn
from it in a positive way no need to
feel that you have stopped functioning
that you have
fail that you are out of touch that you
are not not psychically sensitive and
all of these other wonderful
ideas was just that when I wanted it to
be there it was like where is it when I
need it you know kind of thing what you
get is what you think you
need what you want has nothing to do
with what you believe you
need you gave yourself the situation you
needed so that you would examine the
very things you are examining now and
decide whether or not you are going to
have faith in yourself or
not you follow me yes you give yourself
an opportunity to experience the buttons
within you that can still be
pushed there is no need to examine the
ones you are already sure
of you follow me yes very much so relax
you are doing just
fine thank
you all right
were the Pyramids built by
extraterrestrials who came here in St
there was some assistance with what you
call some of the very early ones most of
which do not exist on the surface of
your world anymore or have as of yet
still been not discovered some of the
very oldest of those that you are aware of
oldest of those that you are aware of
were remnants of a shared
technology but not
directly let us
say constructed nor did it have direct
involvement as the older ones used to
then how were they built some of them
the older ones were built along similar
ideas but built by members of your own
civilization that had not yet forgotten
the techniques the later ones were
generally constructed
through manners of what you would call
clever variations of mechanical leverage
some of which your modern society since
it no longer needs to know them simply
has forgotten about some of them the
older ones were constructed through
means of Sonic nullification of gravity
this is a technique which still does
exist upon your planet in very remote
areas primarily some of this
understanding still exists in the areas
you call India and
Tibet there's been some news recently
that a another chamber has been found in
the yes it is timing there are a few
Chambers yet to discover as well and as
was already
sensed each of these Chambers will be
discovered at an appropriate timing that
represents a new Gateway a new doorway a
new level of Consciousness that your
Society evolves into so now is one of
those timings time to
celebrate thank you thank you b bash yes
yes are you familiar with a system or a
planet or a star called ethos or
Enos not in that
terminology there may be other
terminologies by which we would
recognize the
vibration can you define further no
thank you sry one
moment what we will find right now at
least in the perception we have access
to at this time is that right
now from our point of view unless there
is more reason for
solidification the idea as you are
expressing it is more representative of
a particular
relationship that certain individuals
upon your planet may have to other
fragments of other lives in other
systems that they have as a collective
representational symbolic idea than God
thank you thank you ni um last week was
the first time that I heard you speak
and it was really exciting for me um I
went home that night and I had some very
vivid dreams in one of them I dreamt
that I was communicating with you
telepathically and I wanted to know our energy in
and I wanted to know our energy in
general the energy of our civilization
is available constantly to you all and
in your dream realities many of you home
in on that Beacon and visit our
civilization yes great um I also the in
the same
dream was um a little bit nervous
because I felt that I was losing touch
with my husband because of exploring
my exploring psychic phenomenon but you
are gaining touch with
yourself you cannot really lose touch
with anything again simply recognize
that whatever the relationships that you
form in your life are there are there to
allow you to be in touch with yourself
and therefore by being fully in touch
with yourself to share with the others
in your lives the being you know
yourself to be if another individual
does not wish to share the being that
you are then in that way simply
recognize that the situation may change
by definition but always you will create
a relationship that does represent your
ability to express what you know to be
true for you this does not invalidate
what they are going through but simply
their timing may be slightly different
mhm uh yeah I think I realized that um
now one methodology to allow that
individual to become more synchronized
with you is to simply be fully
representative of the person you are
thus you give them an honest reflection
to deal with MH you follow me yeah if
you hide things because you are afraid
of offending them then they are not
dealing with you and you are not being
fair to them yes I see I see being fair
to them by being who you are then allows
them opportunity to truly decide whether
they feel like they belong in the
reality with you or not mhm um I also
wanted to know I felt a very instant
rapport with my husband when I first met
him as though I had known him before yes
you have can you tell me anything about
that yes but at this time we find that
the specifics may not be
necessary okay first begin toow allow
yourself to be who you need to be in the
present and then you will have access to
all you need to know about any idea you
have ever been in the past you follow me
yeah your willingness to do that also
grants us more ability and accessibility
to the idea of what you have been in the
past because in all reality no pun
intended the idea of sharing your
so-called past with with you is more
easily accomplished when there is not a
great need to do so based upon a belief
that you think you have to know that in
order to be able to live your present
life you follow me yeah not that
understanding cannot be gleamed from
those cognitions but simply recognize that
cognitions but simply recognize that
many individuals that you are now close
to in this life you have been close to
many times
yeah whatever idea you are being in this
life brings with it enough information
to totally understand this
life then with that point of view you
can explore what you
real all right yeah thank you
thaning sharing
yay I'm having a relationship with my
right as of uh last uh Christmas Eve
we've basically been on almost
nonspeaking terms and I I find it quite fascinating
terms and I I find it quite fascinating
the changes uh but I'm interested in
knowing not a need but I'm interested in
knowing uh what who this is being mostly
of service to I don't feel that these
changes are so much of service to me but
rather to uh them particularly my mother
now of course it is all way to vote of
course and in this way again if you find
that you are relaxed about the
situation then you can simply recognize
it may be an indication that all the
exploration in that sense may be on
their behalf and that's that pretty much
describes the situation
than uh can you tell me in what way it's
being of service to my mother what's she
getting out of
it ask
her then you may instigate some of this
communication that is how you can be of
service well see it doesn't feel I'm not
excited to um to do that because then
don't ask okay that's what I'm saying
I'm not I'm not going to ask I mean
don't ask me
well that I am excited about
to then that is only a replacement
symbol for the fact that you may truly
be more excited about asking her than
you think but may be afraid to do no
it's not then go
ask you see asking will change the
experiment asking is a part of the whole
idea it will not change anything
you already have a direct conduit to
them you are a part of the interaction
you are not
objective right
okay okay well um if you are curious to
find out then act as if you are part of
the experiment and you will be able to
find out through your own
resources okay just just that it's more
exciting to me not to ask and just allow
to allow it to um
progress as it as it is all right and
then I thought well if you were willing
to give me some information that would
be great if not that's fine I have given
you the information that I can okay it
is our perception that any further
information must come from an
interaction between you okay and so what
excites me is not to interact in that
way but just to allow her to continue
with her progress where she that may
change within the next three of your
months good thank
you yes um are you with an energy by the
name of do some negre okay A friend of
mine um called me today
and told me a very strange story and I
would like if um if you could give me
any
idea it was very strange to me maybe
because I have never involved myself in
in these types of things before all
right okay so she says that last night
in La that this entity called
maku said that in 3 weeks time in Santa
Barbara there was going to be an
earthquake and that there were a group
of
beings called the ples
pleadians okay thank you that were going
to surface at this point in time and
blend with to some degree there is going
to be pleadian interaction in that area
with that energy at that time yes now
recognize that the idea is not so much
let us say a prediction of catastrophe
it is the idea of the recognition that
that area contains individuals in your
own civilization that are willing to
express and exemplify an equal
interaction with the idea of the
pleadian energy and thus find that they
are co-creating a balance of that energy
so that it does not have to be released
catastrophically but can be
retransformed in a positive way
channeled through the beings in your
civilization as they form recognizable
identification with their own pleadian
energy
connections of Isel mother sh is that
only over the white energy is that the
only place it's able to be view are you
speaking of The Craft that centers over
the area you call your Middle East over
the four
corners in your United States
right there are many craft of associated
with different energy points upon your
world is this in the the linear grid
system between ID wild and Hilo
connecting through the white hole
of in Four Corners what you are
referring to as a white hole we will
assume you mean to be a free zone an
energy Vortex it is associated in that general
Vortex it is associated in that general
area it is also associated with other
areas Shasta is one of those
areas other areas in your Arizona New
Mexico area are also involved as energy
vortices and for the same craft an area
in what you would call the heart or dead
center of the area you call Colorado
also one in
Montana and a few in the area you call
Canada all are associated with the same
craft what is an energy Vortex an energy
Vortex is a door way an energy conduit
that allows there to be a linking
between one level of reality and all
other levels of
reality it is a flow a flux of energy
Exchange between the different
levels a conduit of exchange and
information and
energy what do
tornadoes
hurricanes what's their function what do
they will allow you to extrapolate
certain ideas by simply laying down the
foundation that all of your weather is a
general representation of the emotional
Mass consciousness of Your World
i i s dust devil one time in my
perception it was quite almost as though
practicing it was like a it was like an
individual yes in a sense it can be
represented as a fragment of the
emotional Consciousness in that
way interesting life for guys what
craft in a sense now recognize that the
idea of the craft being referred to this
is not our connotation o Isel in this
way that is a specific vibration that in
a sense now again not in a derogatory
way do we mean this in a sense that
vibration is slightly
outdated but the idea is that there are
representational crafts that do scan
identify and Connect into various energy
points of your
planet there is one associated with that
entire area we have already described
there is one associated with the area
you call your Middle
East and surrounding an area also
connected to what you call your Egypt in
that way and several areas in EUR
Asia there is one associated with your
North Polar area one associated with
your South polar
area there are variations of this idea
associated with specific points your
South American
continent and to some degree variations
of this idea yet again associated with
what you call your African
continent all from the same civilization
no what civilizations are they from
no some of them are pleadian H for now
that will
suffice some of them thousands of
years now we understand how that sounds
translated into your linear time frame
so do not put a linear application on it
but that is how it would translate into
linear time hey um you said that
time hey um you said that
Earth
and serious or one Consciousness a Triad
Consciousness and that uh it seems like
many of people of people on this planet
are from different different plants also
guys no one is native ultimately to any
place we see we see a connection and a
sense well will everyone see a
connection too as SNY and serious they
may see their connections in various
ways they do not have to utilize the
symbology precisely in that way because
we exist in a slightly different
dimensionality than you do we are
assisting in an unobtrusive way the
majority of the connections that are
recognized although there are some that
are recognizable and traceable to our
energies will be too serious to the
pleades as well and some to
Arcturus these will be the primary
connections that will occur firstly what
is for now the idea you call pades is
representative of a group of Stellar
systems associated with that
constellation you call ples in that way
that represents in a very literal sense
your let us say brothers sisters and
cousins you are both offshoots of a
primary race which ten would be more um limited
race which ten would be more um limited
the uh human version or is there those
limitations existing in the cles too not
to any great extent
mostly the human version is the
limitated one they have you're saying
the uh the humans there are pretty much
equivalent to the humans here in many
ways but they are not limited as much
yeah one question I have about uh
Scientologist Ron hover made many
references over the years about A
Confederacy called marad Confederacy
would that be U it is an old Orion
connotation there it go yeah I thought
was or hey uh is that an extinct um so
to speak in what you would call your
present day
awareness what he was describing uh at
that time was pretty much an extinct uh
view so to speak yes okay an old reality
uh are the Orion involved much on what's
going on here at this time to some
degree yes because now there has been
the ability for the blending of light in
the Orion systems for quite some time so
there is involvement with many of them
as well um correct me if I'm sensing it
not quite right but is the U Orion
Energy U have a strong orientation to
grow through negativity is that uh that
was the old idea was was the uh was
Humber was Humber um what's the word uh
running off of momentum or was he
actually getting active in interaction
with both recognize in this way the idea
of running off the momentum was simply
fulfilling one of the ideas that many
Orion incarnated on your Earth plane for
to begin with the idea of the direct
interaction is representative of setting
up real time scenarios that would allow
the reincarnated Orion to get in touch
with the old momentum and begin to
explore phases of it that would allow
them to begin to blend it you follow
me the idea of the older systems
basically represented in the old Orion
methodologies were to explore the Realms
of negativity that had been Paramount in
those systems long ago the idea now in
being born within your Earth system is
to let us say regurgitate all of that
bring it up to the surface so that you
can now balance it with the
understanding that all of that no longer
need apply and that many changes have
occurred within the original Ryan system
there is much that is of the light in
the Orion systems at this time and now
you can recognize that you have both
sent that energy to them through all the
reincarnational Cycles you have
experienced on this planet as Orion
Consciousness and now you can also
receive from them what you have allowed
them to become in their Blended polarity
idea uh was do you see H as a uh at that
time a fairly well I two questions
actually as a missionary or a commander
or so to speak um as a
catalyst yeah but was he on specific
order only his own only yeah I sense
that he was very independent that way
everyone is only on their own specific
orders how specific are the orders for
each being as specific as you create
them to be
um what is money for money is one
representational exchange tool to
represent symbolically the idea you call
abundance which is a natural state of
being and does not always have to be
represented by money though in your
Society often is and can be there is
nothing wrong with that manifestation in
that way simply that many of you assume
that is the only way you can manifest
abundance and it is not
thank you you follow me thank
you a couple minutes ago you said that
no one is actually NE to any planet or
whatever to anyone could you expand on
that a little bit please well you simply
are inherently
nonphysical all the physical universe is
pure creation mhm Collective creation it
thus in that way you are at the same
time native to them all but do not
really come from any one of
them good so we we the only thing we're
native to is our signature vibration is
that would that be a fair statement to
in a sense yes you are native to
existence and you are native to the
vibrational representation you are of
existence and that's it not a riot or
this or that everything else is a part
of the
dance and we make up the music yes you
do
you uh last month uh August I SP in GRE
and I was picking up energies and
vibrations like I have never felt before
and intensity all right you were
reconnecting with other ideas some past
life ideas I felt that I went through a great
ideas I felt that I went through a great
cleansing and a burial and a reboot yes
and I feel that also happening uh with
my business yes and was why should it be
any different since it is a part of
you and and with my body as well yes
everything is
connected I was wondering if you had any
Visions or Notions about what I should
do should that are no shoulds what do
you want to do what excites
you that's what we were talking about it
yes well excitement that is what you can
trust always 100%
follow your excitement that's what it is
there for your excitement is there to
let you know that whatever it is that
excites you represents the path you
chose to be it is your arrow it is your
barometer follow it trust it it will
always lead you into situations that
will support you automatically
effortlessly I find that excitement can
sometimes be nervousness and fear that
is only the invalidation of the
excitement that is not willing to
believe that you can trust
it it is the same
energy but you are not believing in it
you are not believing in
you you follow me yes trust it trusted
trusted it has no choice but to work it
is the mechanism of
creation all right thank you you you
thank you and happy anniversary un to
you thank you um I would like to
acknowledge and thank you very much for
your assistance and co-creating with my
painting as I have invited you to do
last week I'm yours I I thank you I had
a very exciting ride home in which a an
appar well I it's it was more solid than
an apparition but there were actually a
gossamer Wing that attached itself to my
right view my right miror mirr on the
side of my car I know you know this
because this is a form of an
acknowledgement and I was I just caught
it out of my peripheral vision when I
was driving at first and during the hour
and a half drive home I became more and
more excited at these wings of a
butterfly or however I chose to
translate it I thought it was very
interesting that it was on the mirror as
a reflection of myself very good I
enjoyed many possibilities of the
symbolism involved um when I slowed down
the car I became a little anxious that
if it were actually a piece of physical
Universe material it might fall off and
then the whole bubble would burst but as
it turns out it did not fall off the car
if indeed it was a real piece of
physical Universe material and I played
games with myself all the way home and
you have a good time and with you yes
thank you I had a wonderful time and I'm
still exploring the possibilities of how
that might be utilized in a painting
because there's so many potential symb
symbolisms between right so that's very exciting i'
between right so that's very exciting i'
like to thank you I also have a question
which is in a little more serious nature
but maybe we can keep it
light all right I'm
ready I prefer to keep it light so I'm
sure between the two of us can do that
okay as you undoubtedly know we are
currently experiencing epidemics of AIDS
and herpes on this planet my first
question is why and the second question
is considering that these diseases are
spread by geometric progression and that
they can lie dormant for years how can a
single person ensure that his or her
prospective partner is
clean thank
you first of all to answer the second
one first you can simply recognize that
if you know you don't need that symbol
in your life then you will not attract
that symbol in your life
perfect firstly
secondly we have shared the idea of the
reasons for the creation of that idea
many times so we will be brief in the
recapitulation since you do have access
to this information in the recordings
and the transcripts that already exist
thank you I'm the new kid on the Block
that is right but
briefly it is a result generally of a
longstanding habitual ritual of your
Society fearing to face and integrate
the male and female energies within each
individual thus it became necessary for certain
thus it became necessary for certain
individuals to be born into your society
that would reflect a
preponderance of more more one side than
the other in what you call an opposite
effect male expressing
femininity female expressing
masculin so that you would see so that
the mainstream of your Society would see
that each individual contain the
potential of
both but since your Society chose to
continue to be locked into in validation
in that way it still judged these
individuals and refused to take
responsibility for the blending of those
energies as more and more
invalidation became imbued with the
energy of the momentum of your Society
then it simply reached the point where
your Society could not create any other way
Society could not create any other way
other than to force itself to lower its
barriers before it would be willing to
incorporate all beings and all phases of
energy into its Society begin to blend
blend harmoniously with these energies
these polarities within yourself and so
you have created a symbolic
representation of the lowering of your
immunity because now you are exposed to
everything and you must deal with
it wherein if we had chosen to rather
than resist uh the situation that was
resist uh the situation that was
developing if we had recognized that and
in a sense let it flow through us you
would not have this
on your world at all no form of
it thank you very much thank you hey we
started this new chapter you're opening
this is this going to be another
threeyear program hey what would be some
of the differences or some of the
highlights that we could anticipate with
respect to the idea of the physiological
Channel there will be more blending in
that way so that the ideas that the
physiological Channel wishes to express
upon your planet will be able to be
expressed in a manner that will allow
the physiological channel to know that
they can consciously create their
version of the blending of our energy
and express it in your world in that way
so that they can recognize they will
always be channeling the same goes for
all of
you the idea one of the exemplifications
of the next phase is that you will all
put into action the ideas you desire to
be
so there will be more
Equalization apparent in your reality of
these interactions more opportunity to
actually physicalize the manifestations
of the things you all desire to
experience in your reality therefore
there will be more direct
interactiveness it will occur less often
however you follow me yeah more more
direct contact on a meditative level
with in sense we will now become more
actively involved with you and thus
experience these types of interactions
less and less often because you will be
putting into actual activation in other
words you will be going out in the world
and doing more so you need to talk about
it
less talking in that way is all well and
good doing it is the actual
representation of equal communication
with us so everyone will begin to
do more and talk less thank you and
you've referred yourself uh twice now I
I first time I've heard it you heard
yourself in the singular tonight I uh
does that u mean any represent any
change or what's that mean it does
represent some degree of that ability to
begin to recognize
that each and every individual does make
a difference to the whole and at the
same time it is I and we and they do not
cancel each other out now you are strong
enough to understand that becoming a we
does not cancel out the ey but in fact
strengthens it good picture or something of course
it good picture or something of course
um uh I uh had I had contained some um
an aspect I wanted to share about the
idea of pictures of
reality and there's a there's a lot of
preaching and stuff going on the idea
that one has to have faith but behind
that is a picture of reality that if one
doesn't have this one
thing their world is going to fall apart
now recognize something you are
always using your faith always ways it
is not a mechanism you don't
use what is being shared is that the
idea now can be that you can use your
faith to create negativity or you can
use it to create
positivity but you are always using
Faith to create that because your
physical reality is the result of what
you truly Faithfully believe it will be
yeah also what I'm saying is that
there's a an idea there that if one
doesn't Focus on the positive Faith than
the unconscious socaled uh negative
things that one is is uh could could
emerge yes um in other words using Faith
to hold out so-called garbage and and
that sort of things that's what I'm
talking about there are aspects of
talking about faith that may seem to be
positive aspects that can still be
negative but it's motivated out of fear
yes that is why is a Nega
aspect faith without
fear in that way is a relaxed State not
a have to
State it is automatic and
self-perpetuating yeah thank you
yeah thank you
me go
ahead do not be
sorry um I I was just curious as to the
um people who consider themselves po
devil worshippers um which they see as a
worshippers um which they see as a
religion in a sense let us say to give a
definition in a colloquial term they are
supporters of
segregation and
limitation very much
so what I guess I'm I'm getting at is is
there a very strong connection with them
and the Iranian energies some of the old
Orion energies yes for they may still be
individuals who are understanding their
connection to everything only from the
point of view that in order to be
connected to everything you have to
dominate it you follow me the idea of an
it you follow me the idea of an
individual coming from negativity coming
from separation coming from limitation
is that they will still on a fun mental
level know they are connected to
everything but will not give themselves
conscious recognition of this as long as
they continue to believe that their
power lies in separation so the only way
they will be able to feel as if they are
fulfilling their let us say heartfelt
recognition their subconscious
recognition of their connection to
everything will be to express it through
the attempt to dominate all that they
see in their reality to control know it
rather than simply recognize that every
individual is as powerful as they need
to be to have anything they desire in
life without having to hurt anyone else
or themselves in order to get it because
they know they are connected to
everything you follow me yes I do
therefore the idea you call satanic
worship is simply a belief that you are
not truly actually connected to
everything and therefore you must try to
control it in order to get it to do what
you want if
want if
only yes it do you um if I may
um I had an experience um today in
dealing with um the bureaucracy of my of
the school system I were yes in and oh
how very exciting yes it very exting
Very exting
Yes um this is teaching you many things
how ecstatic please continue yes it
taught me a lot of things today still is
it still is still working on
integrating um they had made an error um in our uh
um they had made an error um in our uh
check uh two weeks ago and it was kicked
out of the computer so we didn't get the
proper pay and we were told that it was
going to be corrected by today and it
had not been that is because this is no
error it is a completely perfect
representation of the collective beliefs
of the individuals participating in this
reality well you know those
bureaucracies this is what always
happens when you have to deal with a
bureaucracy everyone knows
everyone knows
that therefore you are rewarded with an
example therefore it is no error it is a
perfect reflection of the combined
beliefs about what the situation is
needed for because it may be putting
individuals in touch with their own
capability to become involved in the
situation to a greater degree and
recognize that the individuals involved
are the bureaucracy they are
experiencing okay I um no separation
okay integration right my my
um my feeling of being a rebel um gets
get that button that button gets pushed
in situations like this you can be a
nice level that's what I worked on today
level that's what I worked on today
which was real different for me I came
very good I came off in a much lighter
way very good than I have in the past
with situations like this have come to
yes because you are learning that you
are powerful enough to get what you need
without having to accost anyone or
accuse anyone in order to get it I
worked with um affirming the payroll
clerk uh for her for her efforts and and
trying to get this resolved and bringing
her into the solution instead of staying
in the problem and I kept affirming
throughout the whole thing that for
every problem there is a solution and
that I will P persist and persevere
until the solution of the money all
right comes to be but your perseverance
does not have to create a
struggle that's what what it was it was
today all right that is simply only
because you are still in the habit of
thinking that it has to be you are
learning it will become easier and
easier the more you are willing to allow
it to be more and more effortless the
more you are willing to recognize that
you are in touch with whatever aspects
of the situation you need to be and that
communication is quite clear on these
levels the last thing about this
situation was that when it it resolved
itself with the Su with the head
supervisor who I went to um writing me a
personal check um in faith of the
situation and I somehow that was not
what I wanted but yet I had created the
need that that I that I did need this
money and I do
um but I didn't feel any satisfaction in
having received it it was like it didn't
feel like a win even though I got the
money and it was resolved it because it
was not not resolved the payroll gave it
to me and it had to come out of his Che
out of his check I felt um
yeah what to attach on a personal
level no it wasn't a person it wasn't
the attachment it was just like it
didn't feel like a victory it felt like
why should it feel like a victory this
is not a war
sheist yeah it was like I wanted to beat
that was the thing I think I wanted to
beat the system I wanted to you see that
is the whole idea as long as you think
you have to beat the system then you are
going to constantly be being beaten
up you are the system if you're going to
beat the system you're only beating
yourself relax so I manipulated this it
felt like I ended up even if my
conscious you allowed the system to
change you allow the definition to flow
into something
else that is overcoming the
system if you think you have to fight it
on its own terms and win that way then
you have not one you have only created
another system that is similar and
reinforces the first
one you follow
me quite other
words if you think you have to beat
someone at their own game so to speak
all you do is create the game to
continue on a larger scale because now
you are playing their
game what would you have suggested that
I have done differently you did what you
needed to do you allowed the system to
change and allow them to begin to play
your game you follow me you allow them to
game you follow me you allow them to
come through in another way other than
what is generally represented by the
bureaucracies as you think of them you
are finding that there are other
conduits that there are loopholes so to
speak in the definition of anything that
You' create to be a bureaucracy or a
government or a structure on your planet
and that they can transform that they
can be malleable that they can be
flexible and therefore not so rigid so
then there is not so much rigidity to
feel like you have have to
fight you follow me
yes this does not seem to be settling
into you are you saying that you would prefer
you are you saying that you would prefer
to fight no no I I then why do you feel
that you should have done something
differently so that I would feel better
about the resolution than I do what is
the basic definition without emotion of
the
resolution the basic resolution would be
one moment what was the basic resolution you
moment what was the basic resolution you
were seeking was it not to be paid yes
did you not get paid yes well
then why is it so important that it has
to happen in a certain manner as long as
the effect is the same and does not
invalidate anyone else's
Integrity is that not a
win I will say something about
winning later
on all right all right relax and at this
time each and every one of you enjoy a
brief
break all right I'll say
technique each and every one of you that
wishes to participate at this time in
any way shape or form that you decide to
participate now get on relax
on relax
is that
comfortable take three I'm going to keep
now allow yourselves to recognize as you
are relaxing that there is no right way and
relaxing that there is no right way and
there is no wrong way to do this
technique the way your
Consciousness the way your imagination
interprets it in terms of the
visualizations that you have will be
sufficient allow yourself to recog I
that visualization specifically is not even
visualization specifically is not even
necessary the feelings will do trust
your imagination trust that you will give
imagination trust that you will give
yourself the symbols you require and
that in
fact you can for the period of the
exercise you can
implicitly trust at least for the
following few moments
that regardless of whether or not you
think you are doing it the way you need
to do it you are in fact doing it the
way you need to do it and you will get
out of it what you need to get out of
it so set aside all
preconceived notions of how it should be
done or how it should feel or what you
should good
sleep you will have a tendency to see or
feel what we will
describe but if it
changes let the change be a part of the
exercise not an interruption in it do
you all follow
along thank you then first and foremost
your primary requirement in in this exercise
primary requirement in in this exercise
is to simply enjoy it all right now what
we will be
doing is what we can refer to as
synchronization of the mental field the
electromagnetic field of your planet
that allows you to create awareness of
each other that allows you to telepathic
to communicate your shared reality and
reinforce it or deviate from
it
therefore you will be getting in touch
with the
patterns of
energy that communicate the idea between
you of your Collective reality and
represent your individual reality within
it this is also what we refer to as
identification or at least one aspect of
it three more
de let everything now that drifts into
your awareness also become a part of and not
awareness also become a part of and not
an interruption in overall process in
this technique for everything you have
ever done and anything you can
imagine is a part of you a valid part of
the integration you are now performing
within this exercise
more breaths and as you take these
breaths imagine that your
physical your mental and your spiritual
selves are
aligning merging
blending in whatever way you visualize
it this is the correct way for
you enjoy the merger enjoy the blending
enjoy the merger enjoy the blending
enjoy the
overlap allow yourself to
experience the happiness of the joining
in that way and the cognition of the
alignment it allows you
feel trust that you are feeling that
alignment Trust that regardless of how
you choose to feel that alignment you
will experience the effect of that
alignment regardless of what portions of your
regardless of what portions of your
mentality may think
otherwise regardless of what portions of
your mentality decide to cloak it in
ways you may not used to have thought
represented an alignment trust that it
is is your way of doing it right now it
is the perfect way you need to do
it now allow yourself do not take the
deep breaths yet but in the next series
of three breaths you will with your
imagination again in whatever way shape
or form it occurs form around your
entire physical body a transparent
Crystal blue bubble that you can see
blue bubble that you can see
through three deep breaths and allow
this bubble to form no it is there
whether you can perceive it or not three
rep
allow yourself at this time to Simply
for a moment immerse yourself in the
experience of that bubble you are
immersed within it you can imagine it to
be in a sense Hollow you can imagine it
to be filled with the same type of
energy that represents itself in the
Shell of the bubble you can imagine
yourself if you wish to actually be a
manifestation of that energy at the
center of the bubble in much the same
way that when you drop pebbles in a pond
and you see the wave forms interacting
with each other from two different
Pebbles those waveforms as you see them
overlap can be what represents the
solidified form you think of as your
body allow yourself to recognize that
your body is simply a solidified form of
the same blue crystalling
electromagnetic energy of which the
sphere is composed allow yourselves to
dwell within that for a brief moment
feel it out try it are wiggle around in
in your imagination
breathe know that you are very
comfortable breathing
that fluid that electromagnetic fluid in
and out in and
out you can even imagine that every Poe
every cell is breathing that fluid in
and out allowing you to feel at once
invigorated and yet
relaxed excited
and at peace
smooth and yet containing an infinite
number of
potential directions activations and energy feel
directions activations and energy feel
the energy coruscating scintillating
tingling in every atom of your being as
you breathe it in and out feel its
coolness feel the war form it may
generate within you feel feel
feel the feelings that you create with
regard to being
immersed within this energy fluid within
this Matrix feel the expansion of your
awareness you can allow yourself now to
imagine that you actually
are this bubble of energy become in your
imagination the bubble of
energy continue to assume that it still
has a skin that is slightly different
from the rest of the energy in the
bubble it can
be fluid it can be crystallin it can be
gelatinous it can be light it can be any
way you choose to think of the skin but
allow it to have a slightly different
consistency on the surface of the sphere
that you are but throughout the interior
allow that to be a homogeneous fluid a
homogeneous electric fluid or magnetism
or energy or light or water or anything
you desire it to be allow it to be
homogenous and simply trust that no
matter what you're imagination comes up
with in terms of images it is homogenous
at this
time free more relaxing and
enjoyable deep
breath now while you are doing that and
while you are simply
enjoying floating as that being as the
energy bubble
allow yourself to
recall the individuals the other
individuals that are in the room with
you at this time that you arrived at
this interaction but now you do not have
to be specific just know they are
there now that you are
aware of the other
bubbles be aware of one more
thing the surface the skin the outer
layer of each and every
bubble vibrates in a
slightly slightly different subtle pattern even
slightly different subtle pattern even
though they may all vibrate in accord in
a synchronous pattern
throughout allow yourself to perceive
the subtleties of the
differences when you have done this just
as a General
recognition allow yourself then to look
at the pattern of your own Crystal
surface recognize its vibratory
rate make a comparison see the
differences in the different vibratory
RS see that you can in fact
recognize distinct individuals simply by
the differences in the pattern of the
vibratory rate of the surface of the
SE
now do
this pick out another sphere's vibratory
pattern something that attracts you for
whatever reason you do not have to know
the individual
c simply pick it out and begin to
attempt to make your surface membrane
vibrate to that pattern mimic it copy it
play around play a game of Follow the
Leader feel within yourself the changes
that take place within the idea that you
are when you
allow the surface pattern you have now
changed your surface into feel the
surface pattern creating ripples within
the homogeneous fluid throughout the
sphere that you are see how it creates
differences of approach differences of
feelings nuances that represent what you
perceive to
be another
individual's representational pattern of
Life their beat of the heart their beat
of the
drum now allow your pattern to Simply go
back to the pattern you had before your
zero rest State natural pattern trust
for now that whether it seems to
completely go back to what you had
before it is back to your natural
pattern we are not saying it has to be
the old pattern but it is your natural
pattern the one that represents the you
you now are after having
identified with the other individual's
pattern as
well now you know you have become more
you have shared in a way that allows you
to know you will always be your own
individual at the same time you have the
capability of identifying with the
patterns of other individuals and
creating a model for yourself so that
you can sense your
version of how the vibration plays
through your fluid so that you can see
how their pattern their point of
view can be
acclimatized to your point of view to
allow you to have an
understanding of what their point of
view can show you about
yourself by trying on their clothes by
walking in their shoes temporarily You
Now understand what it means to be that
version of
yourself this increases the opportunity
to recognize that you can be a
multidimensional idea identifying with
an infinite number of patterns
and at the same time you will always be
your own
individual you will not lose your
identity but you will become the
collective result of all the
identities that you
identify with and therefore
sharing opening exchanging patterns to try them
opening exchanging patterns to try them
on to try them out can become something
that does not have to create fear loss
of
identification loss of
individuality or any of the Notions of
separation is that
way allow yourself to know that at any
given moment as you create and recreate
this technique for
yourself you
are are quite
are quite
capable of
knowing primarily because you are in
this state quite willing to be loving of all
state quite willing to be loving of all
other individuals and therefore you are
quite capable of
knowing what another individual may be
thinking maybe
feeling this is
telepathy this is psychic functioning it
is for forming your own identificational
pattern representing another's
pattern this is so you can recognize
that you have the capability of
expressing your version of everyone else
and by being in synchronous harmony with
their pattern you can
pattern you can
see their point of
view identically as identically as being the
identically as identically as being the
individual idual you are is necessary
for you to proceed you
proceed you
can do this
exercise when you are in relaxed state
or when you wish to become in a relaxed
State and it can give you great
insight into the individuals around you
that you play with that you work with so
that you can come out of this technique
with a greater understanding of their
point of view and
thus arm yourself with the appropriate
tools to create a flow of communication
between you rather than struggle to
understand each
other three deep breaths and re-enter
the surroundings of your
room always know knowing always trusting
that this
technique will place you squarely in
touch firmly
grounded and in connection with the
entire electromagnetic understanding not
only of your own civilization but also
where appropriate with the feeling the
generalized electromagnetic feeling of
any other level of Consciousness that
you so desire to be in touch with it
will come through in whatever format is
necessary for you to be able to express
that energy in your own
reality we thank you for this
opportunity of sharing in this
way there will now be a
brief time frame for sharing yes [Music]
oh what I've
already I won't all that but anyway uh
many many years ago he was involved uh
he had an intis and during this time he
was in a coma off about for 3 months um
and also during this time he felt that
his energy was being used in betet for
some reason and uh when he came out of
it he not only lived and was not
paralyzed he had renewed perceptions
guys um I think I know the answer to
this but uh perh even like to say
something about that for
him what is your answer my answer is
that he was doing some work on
another on another level of himself and
uh perhaps it involve some friends of
his in in sense he is a very strong
integrator and there was aspects of
bilocation in that
even at times there actually was another
physiological representation of himself
elsewhere in your
world yes he's a very very powerful
person as we all are but this person is
very much serving others and has done so
yes this individual knows what they are
doing and in this way knows that they
have the energy they
desire yes one thing he did say uh as a
form of uh well anyway what he said was
that he didn't feel he was trying to get
off this planet and I said oh really and
he goes yeah well I just feel that my
energies are not being utilized properly
and that is up to him yeah I we got into
that all right um the other thing I
would like to say uh I would like to
share with you is that um so fantastic
that we're talking about this idea of of
um sharing another's
Viewpoint this week what I've
experienced you know I told you that I
had this bird and the bird grew up and I
let her go on my birthday and that was
all a very
lovelyy um this week I met a person who
flies private jet airplanes I'm going to
go in one of those guys but this person
um there's a wonderful uh friendship
there but this person also is opposed to
all of this stuff but but I what I'm
finding fascinating about it is that I'm
enjoying that yes um it's actually fun
and there's no what a surprise Lely
there's no bite in it Y and so what I'm
seeing yes uh is that I don't know what this uh
yes uh is that I don't know what this uh
what I'm seeing is that the two can
exist very harmoniously how about that
is that me yes and so um the idea of
going going up in jet ples to me is it's
just more of the acceleration of that
idea into the fourth density very good
you have now become the bird
yeah and another thing I would like to
say to you that I never get to say and
that we all feel and I always forget
that I wanted to say it when you close
you always say there is one thing that
we will never ever be able to do and it
always just kills me when you say and
that is to express how much we love you
and I want you to know that every time
you say that it is reflected back to you
by all of
[Music] us you us you
thank
you sure
you the idea of rings upon rings of
reality Rings upon rings of reality
remember yes of course how could I
forget such a stimulating
conversation uh an idea of I wouldn't to
align this that um there would be a
larger ring which would allow uh more
containing uh of reality which whereby
individuals would be engaged in um
energy theft and that's I've heard I've
heard um you mean in the idea that energy
um you mean in the idea that energy
theft is possible yeah well that's why I
was trying I was containing that as
being a an optional reality that's not a
a universal type truth my universal
truth would would contain an idea that
um that's that's just an optional idea
that's something one could engage in but
it's not it's not a a very necessarily a
universal activity
no the idea is as you have only restated
that the truth is composed of all truths
and likewise
I haven't ever heard you discuss the
idea of uh or you may you discussed it
but I haven't been there of um um the
effects of disembodied U uh in
co-inhabitants of the body you know
disembodied spirits and that's so
inhabitant well there is that reality
which which uh says that the clusters of
individuals living simultaneously with
someone you mean in the same
body so to speak yeah so to speak
right all right but I would just
defining that as that's another optional
reality not necessarily yes it does not
as we perceive
it truly manifest in your level of
reality what you is it an astral type
activity let us say from our perspective
it is more of an alternate reality type
activity but one could very easily uh
get on off that wavelength and those
things would not be pertinent realities
you can in your reality create the
illusion of that idea but it would not
be as literal as it is in some other
realities simply because of the
definition of your reality yeah but in
in in Worlds where it is on a spiritual
perhaps an astral uh non physical level
or whatever um where it is more gerine
all right um yes is it uh something one
could still move off that wavelength of
course of those are not influences yes
just by choice yes thank you thank you
thank you B one moment
uh uh earlier this evening you mentioned
about uh weather changes in regards to
mass Consciousness and which reminded me
mass conscious emotionality thank you m
Mass conscious emotionality reminded me
of a a gentleman that I met about a year
ago who had basically given me the same
data and he also mentioned a group
called The Golden ones his name is Steve
Groves and I was wondering if you could
tell me any any more about this uh life
form or this energy form he says he's a
messenger and he was here to help the
planet planet Earth so are you that's
true but I was wondering if you could
give me any more about this golden ones
and the concept that he was thank you
all we can share at this time because we
do not wish to label it any further okay
is that it is representative to some
degree of what you may call a
higher Realm Of Consciousness that may
be mostly
non-physiological entity Consciousness
is that are connected through assistance
to your planet Earth and
function as what you might refer to as a
quote unquote
hierarchy but not really okay they do
represent larger
rings but in this
way the idea is simply that they are of
assistance as co-creators of the
realities you are
experiencing with regard to what you now
desire for your own expansion and
awareness of yourself also existing on
that level okay uh something else that
he was putting across was
that it was up to this group that it
could either be positive or negative
circumstances for the planet yes um it
is not up to them in terms of control
uhhuh how is it up to them it is up to
them to assist in the co-creation of
whatever you choose so
choose so
they will support the idea this specific
level will support whatever idea of the
transformation you are willing to
believe is
necessary how much Interac do they
actually have how much as much as you
desire but only to the point where you
are taking responsibility for the
reality you are
creating thank
you hey um the drill that
you oh Dr all right Sergeant
B very helpful Rel ask question about
but I like to get a little Enlightenment
in this area my husband is pursuing his
spirituality in a is it running away
from
him he's Jo a different Direction than I
am by definition he's a different
individual well it's more than that um
if you say
so if you are willing to make more of
it well he has quite a resistance
on that has to do with channeling or
things well that's no problem all I'm
pointing is maybe your perception of
where he's at what direction he's going
and how this difference is going to
affect where he needs to
be how do you think it will affect your
relationship I can tell you this it will
obviously be that your relationship will
transform into whatever the definition
of the individuals within it care to
create themselves to be
period if you need to continue to
interact physically you will if you
don't you won't well I I think that's
definitely going to continue I just
there's things there I wish I could
understand little more I thought perhaps
your perception in what way do you wish
to understand them and why do you think
you need to understand them in that way
in order to Simply continue to be the
person you know yourself to
be I don't think I need it for that
reason why do you think we need it so
that I may just understand him better
and create a better relationship because
of all right well if you wish to
understand him better why don't you ask
him to
explain that's very touy for
me you mean it is touchy when you ask
somebody to explain themselves relative
to the way you think they should explain
themselves but if you make it understood
that what you are asking is simply for
them to explain themselves on their own
terms of validation why would that be
touching you are willing to accept their
terms as valid yes I am well
then then that is his explanation
all right well I have another
are I cannot shed any light on anything
you are the one that controls the
switch way of asking or saying something
it helps me all
right um I've being very successful in
not being able to create inflence I
believe that I would like to have oh and
I'm I'm doing it very well I'm not able
to create that so I put a lot of stops
there and uh for
now let us be very compact about this
and we will refer you to someone
else there already exists quite a lovely
technique through the entity you call
Lazarus for the idea of getting in touch
with what it is
that you desire and
manifesting approach the idea of
accessing the causal
plan do that see if that assists you if
it does not we will speak again but I
think it
will this goes for all of
you sure
yes could you give any more information
on the causal plane as we have said
access the information for now that
already exists in your Society
right yes yes from your perspective would you
yes yes from your perspective would you
comment on the idea known as Divine will
divine will all right it can be now
will all right it can be now
have you already been present when we
spoke about the idea of the Free Will of
the higher self and the Free Will of the
physical self no all right we will be
brief the idea is that there is two
types of Free Will Free Will of higher
self which you may refer to as at least
by proxy Divine will and Free Will of
the physical self the Free Will of the
higher self may be interpreted by the
physical self to be what you call fate
Destiny predestination Divine will and
these ideas but this is only expressed
in your physical life in the most
generalized of themes the most
generalized of
terms let us say for example that the
higher Consciousness in physical life
wishes to send a fragment of itself into
physicality to explore a certain theme
which we will call a general
hallway well all right well the Divine
will that the physical entity the
physical fragment will perceive will be
that the physical fragment
must walk down that hallway in that
sense the physical fragment will usually
have no choice however how the physical
fragment walks down that hallway that
has been chosen by the higher self is
completely under the opes of the Free
Will of the physical Consciousness so
how you do it whether you run whether
you walk whether you crawl whether you
fly whether you go backwards whether you
go in the light whether you go in the
dark whether you go alone whether you go
friends whether you swim whether you go
upside down whether you go fast whether
you go
slow is up to you whether it is positive
whether it is negative or variations
thereof is up to you as a physical being
but walk down that Hall you
will now but that is only in the most
generalized of ideas it is not that the
higher consciousness specifically says
in order to learn this you must stub
your toe no it says you will create whatever
toe no it says you will create whatever
type positive or negative of situations
you as my physical representative in
physical reality decide to create for
yourself to represent the idea of your
connection to let us say physicality in
that way that is the perhaps General
theme explore the idea of physical
action and reaction all right bang
ouch that is one way or simply I move
from here to there because of friction
Action Reaction all right both of those
are valid I understand the principle
thank you physical self that will do you
follow me yes does that assist you yes
one more question hey yes when standing
confronting several hallways in front of
you what's the best way to
choose all right first first of all
recognize that it is not a
confrontation and that a decision does
not have to be a difficult thing you can
allow allow allow allow allow
allow whichever one needs to stand out
to do so if you find that they are equal
then obviously it doesn't matter which
one you
take your excitement which ever
represents your level of excitement take
that one if you find
that both or several are represented by
the same degree of
excitement then allow whichever one
comes into timing first to be the one
you take you follow me
take you follow me
yeah generally speaking one of them
because of what your linear time reality
is one of them will manifest
sooner than another take that
one all right yes thank than you yes did
you please Identify some of the general
themes that you refer to as uh what the
higher Consciousness is going for
exploration of the polarities
exploration of abundance exploration of
deserv ability exploration of
relationships these kinds of things
okay find you you than
you um two things one is you have you've
put you've said a few times that
all life or our life lives and I'm not
sure which one that is is all one event
yes all everything okay is that in a
general sense or in an individual sense
everything both both all of it okay any way you can
both both all of it okay any way you can
mean it okay all right right okay so if
if all there all that is is all one
event yes and if my this lifetime is all
one event right and if I think I've
spotted that one event what do I do with
it you spotted it spotted it realized
what one event that is you live it
oh then I must not have it oh you yes
you do you are it you are it yes you are
it right let me put it this way let me
put it this way perhaps you are simply
confused by the
terminology everything is the same one
thing manifesting in multitudinous
multi-dimensional simultaneous
aspects so each and every one of those
aspects in and of itself is also valid
as your
version this time of the whole
event so live the life you are that is
what your event
is you follow me okay so if I think that
I have spotted a particular repeating
situation that is not it that is simply
one aspect of the whole event
right okay fre you I the not really okay
thank you really can't be okay right
right right right okay secondly um last
week I mentioned to you that I had this
de friend that had come across my cast
and bed in and then bed out
again and I and we just we were
exploring that idea a little bit and
this the BR bed back into into my space
b
[Laughter]
you are in the midst of your life you
will find out what you need to know
right you don't want me to unwrap all
the presents and spoil Christmas for you
no but I always love to open one on
Christmas morning all right then open it
right and discover what you will perhaps
the read bopping is the present itself
oh you might like know that Victoria
still has a Christmas tree up by the
way I wasn't
lying then Merry
Christmas guys um I have a couple
questions that I don't understand um
basically about reincarnation all right
when somebody reincarnates are they the
only one that decides what they want to
come back as or do they have other make
a agreement with others you cocreate the
situation but in terms of your part in
the scenario yes you are the only one
that makes the final decision and
there's no there's no it is not forced
no okay the other question I have is um
well who are the other people that you
make the agreement with are they the
ones that are in your life with
you parents your parents first of all
all since they give birth to you okay
and then any of the friends that you
meet any of the associations that you
meet relationships so on so forth this
also includes the idea that some of your
friends in other lives don't always
physicalize with you in this one but
sometimes act as
guides okay the other question I have
is why why would somebody come into a
life and then commit suicide is that
correct is suicide suicide conscious
suicide is let us say the only
loophole that exists within the contract
you make with your higher
self it is
a more or less negation of the Divine
will of the higher Consciousness as free
will however once you extract yourself
from physical reality usually because as
an individual you have not been taught
that you have control over your reality
so you do not believe that you can
change the events in your life so you
run away from them through the idea of
physical death but once you extract
yourself from the physical reality you
are once again the higher self that made
the original decision and
99.9% of the times you will re-inject
yourself back into a similar life
immediately because you know you did not
want to leave it you want to learn all
the way to the contractual end of that
life what it is you want to learn what
about abortion is that the same why
would why why would a person want to
reincarnate into a woman there are
entities levels of consciousness whose
experience of physical reality is let us
say the first time around they wish to
slowly get their feet wet
idea you call abortion so that they will
know they do not have to exist for a
very long period of time in physical
reality before they will be released
once again isn't that very painful
no the total sole Consciousness does not
enter a physical body until exactly just
prior to physical
burden and since there is still that
much control from the other side there
is no real pain
today you follow me yes thank you
briefly is that the same then as a Mis
can be yes that can simply be an
automatically induced idea recognizing
the timing recognizing there is no need
for what you call the fruition of the
bir physically and it is also to some
degree what is represented by what you
call cride because up to approximately 3
years of age The Entity still has the
choice of staying or
leaving so that is where the
solidifications of the combined
telepathic structuring of your Society
begin to take a very rigidized and solid
hold and the individual at that point
may not believe they have the ability to
leave so the the child the pregnancy is
that the child had made an agreement
with the parents to be born yes and then
changes its mind three or four months
into the it is not so much that it
changed let us say the potential for it
to leave at that time always existed
strongly in many cases it can be looked
at as a change of mind so to speak which
can be done also the idea can be that it
is a change of mind if the individual
stays alive follow me thank you at this
alive follow me thank you at this
timing allow us to remind you once again
with regard to all the lives you have
lived within the cycle of incarnation on
your planet in a sense this is the one you
planet in a sense this is the one you
have been waiting
for this one is the transformational
light that allows you to use the
experience you have gained in all the
other lives now is why you are
integrating now is why you are exploring
this idea trust
idea trust
therefore that this life is the life you
have been waiting for is the life in
which you can remember your deserv
ability in which you can recall your
ecstasy in which you can create your
physiological reality to be
a synchronous harmonious event this is
the one here it is all the waiting all
the practicing is
over go and live it trust it do it be it
you will be
supported we
can guarantee
it 100%
this is it the transformational age the
beginning of a completely new
perspective of yourselves
so feel free and do not fear because you
will not have to go and live your lives
so that you can win you can go and live
your lives because you cannot lose
our unconditional love to you all
exciting dream life and life dreams we
are the sharing that continues forever
we will see you in your dreams which is
becoming your physical world we thank
you for your sharing fond and
unconditionally loving full moon good
evening thank you good everything go happy
anniversary thanks for being here
tonight everyone thank
youl Danielle's birthday oh
yes Daniel's birth stand up Daniel it's
his birthday today
too happy birthday to you happy birthday
to you happy birthday dear
Danel happy birthday to
[Music] you
you
birthday channeling chaning happy
birthday happy anniversary happyn
okay what that time it's uh
10:4 5 49 thank you all for
coming anyone who would like a tape up
tonight we can have it ready for you
tonight we got a high speed tape
duplicator can we just sit here for
about a half hour you can just here as
long as you want your phone operating in
the
kit thank you all thank you all
no