All right. I will say how are you all
this evening of time as you create time
to
exist. Before we begin this evening of
your time with the ideal sharing,
sharing,
mood to illuminate for
you as we have for other
individuals so
far to exemplify the idea that you have
created that which you call your new.
Yeah. which is a reflection of the ideas
that you are willing to be as a new idea
of yourself, a new consciousness, a new
you, a new
reality. As any new idea that you have
of yourself will create a new reality.
Now therefore the idea that you have given
therefore the idea that you have given
as we have discussed with your year
1,986 will be the
idea of activation,
participation, conviction, the acting out of what you
conviction, the acting out of what you
are willing to be. And thus in this way
recognize you are now in this idea
allowing yourselves to
become more of the idea of fourth
density than
previously. And as
such we will allow ourselves to begin to
address you in this
way in the
cocreation of this
idea. this density, this
acceleration, this conglomeration in a
collection of
yourself. We will
then simply say
this questions you may ask for anything
that you have to say, whether a
statement or a question will always be
considered a sharing and something that
can be a teaching and a learning for you
and for
us. In this way, however,
recognize that if you are now willing to
have the conviction to
share what it is,
you see yourself as
being, what you are willing to perform,
to act out as service, to play out as
the idea of yourself within the
agreement that you made to be within
this transformational life with everyone
else in which you are in it. Then we can
with you explore the ideas that you
bring to the
surface and in this
way can
endeavor to create a more equal basis
for activity upon your planet, upon
ours, upon many others.
Therefore, once again, questions you may
ask, but recognize in this way, we will
cocreate a
situation where we will walk down the
path together to discover that which
exists within you as the answer before
you have asked the
question. In this way also each and
every one of you who is willing to
simply discuss what you have chosen to
allow yourself to be to represent the
idea of yourself in this life the
service you are willing to perform. We
will also be very joyful and
appreciative of that sharing of your
idea of yourself as this will be a
statement, a vocalization of
conviction that you have in this way
shared with the rest of the people that
you have co-created to be with you this
night of your time and will accelerate
the vibration of your own being to allow
that lifestyle, that idea of yourself
you have chosen to be to Bring to
it all the situations, relationships,
and opportunities that you require to
continue being what you are willing to
be. Are you all following along? Yes. Yes. Now, your
Now, your
acceleration into fourth
density will allow for us as well
certain ideas which have only begun to
blend to blend little further as they
have the past week of your time.
The consciousness of the physical
channel, the consciousness of myself, of
my own future self, and the conglomerate
consciousness of your entire
civilization can now begin to
participate within a blending and ease
of creation, a sharing of energy as you
find yourself accelerating into fourth
density. Then as you make that step up, so to
Then as you make that step up, so to
speak, it is in so many words quote
unquote easier for us to meet you
halfway. Therefore, recognize that the
Therefore, recognize that the
idea of the fluidity of our conversation
and our ability to be in a sense more
with you will thus be our symbol and our
offering and our gift of our
participation with you in the formation
of the fourth density reality in which
you now begin to find yourselves and
feel free to participate within. Are you
all following along? Yes. Yes,
Yes,
you uh happy new year Bashar. Uh I'd
like to share a few things. First is
that uh the explosion of coincidence
that is my life. Yes, that has always
been my life actually. It is more and
more ecstatic as I go through. Thank
you. And it is uh it is fabulous. It's
very very exciting. Nice. One of the
things that I noticed is a reflection in
our automobiles of what I see as a
transformation. Nice. Up to 1985,
automobiles had two tail lights, one on
the right, one on the left, in the
position of eyes. Now we're starting to
add a third tail light above in between
in the third eye position. Oh, very
creative of you to create and notice
that idea. Thank you. Yes, it's quite
quite fun. Uh, another thing, um,
Let me see. I have a question here that
I wanted to ask uh or say. Uh the term
live and learn in the past has been used
by many people almost in a negative
sense in that somebody makes a quote
mistake unquote and they say well live
and learn. Nice. But in fact live and
learn is a statement of the very fabric
of our existence here. Nice. That's kind
of a a nice way to put it into a
positive can also be viewed positively
as the idea really that there are no
mistakes and that the idea that you
created is something you can learn from.
Right. Right. I did some thinking on the
terms remorse and guilt and um what uh
there seems to be a feeling that
occurs when when somebody has allowed
his integrity to drop. Uh we talked
about this one time before where a
person might do that and they look let's
say that they I'm going to say hurt
somebody else as a result of their job
in integrity. Yes. Of course it's
planned and it's it's in agreement but
uh the other person is being uncert and
allowing themselves to let's say be
hurt. Okay. Oh my. And there's a feeling
that comes when the person who has
allowed their integrity to drop views
the other person from their viewpoint.
Goes, "Oh my god, I've hurt this other
person." Nice. And I would say that that
feeling would be called remorse. And I
distinguish that distinguish that from
guilt in that guilt is a judgment on you
know somehow right or wrong good or bad
that doesn't necessarily relate to a
drop in integrity. All right. I just
wanted to know if you um had any
comments on that. Uh I would say that
um that that emotion that I'm calling
remorse is a uh is the emotional prod to
uh get us to reinstate our integrity.
Yes. Very good. It is as simple as that.
The idea is that there is really no
reason as we have said and as you have
just said to be sorry so to speak.
Simply the idea that you recognize the
idea of the shift out of your integrity
and the idea that you are calling the
remorse. Yes, the ability to recognize
how you can reintegrate yourself and
then create the scenario that does with
that other individual then co-create the
type of relationship that will allow you
to offer them another option, a more
positive option in terms of how they can
see themselves reflected in you.
I have one last question here for now.
Um, when I was in Scientology, we had
what we called charge, which was an
uncomfortable feeling for me anyway of
sort of anxiety,
um, would be one way of describing it.
And, uh, it could be accompanied by
increased heartbeat, um, gnawing in the
stomach, something like that. And uh I
found that I had charge occur in the
midst of a relationship with a female
when things that I judged would come up
and I create this charge for myself. Now
I'm looking at a relationship with a
female in which these same feelings are
coming up. However, I have a new
viewpoint to view them through since uh
coming and chatting with you since uh
last July. And it's very very
interesting in that first I removed the
judgment from whatever it is that I had
been judging before. Nice. So now
whatever it was that I was judging is
okay. I'm left with a feeling and then I
look at the feeling and I remove the
judgment from the feeling. Said said
judgment being that the feeling is
uncomfortable. Now I have I'm left with kind of an
Now I have I'm left with kind of an
excitation. It's not exactly excitement
of oh yes I'm going to go do something.
It's like that. Very good. But you are
sensing the zero rest point vibration of
excitation which in polarity expressed
becomes excitement or anxiety positive
or negative same energy. Uhhuh. Uh now
it does feel different from the
excitement of of I'm going to go do
something that I enjoy. But I'm
wondering is it but it is definitely an
excitation. Would you say it's an
excitation of integration that that's
what's yes it is your awareness of as we
just said the zero rest point the
natural background vibration of activity
of existence of your very being the idea
of all the pieces of yourself
integrating and how they create the
vibration of the temporal manifestation
of your physical existence. You are on
idol so to speak but not idol in the
negative sense. Yeah. Okay. Got it. You
are feeling the potential of your
expandability. Uhhuh. Kind of tapping into the fabric
Uhhuh. Kind of tapping into the fabric
vibration of my existence. Nice. Thank
you very much. Thank you very much. And
to return I not only happy new year but
happy new year you.
Thank you. For you. Yes. Yes. Vash uh I
am willing I'd like to share what I'm
willing to be this year. By all means.
But before I do that, I would like to
ask you a quick question about the u out
of body experience. I related to you.
Nice. Uh you that really surprised me
that the man with a cardboard face with
a gray cardboard face. Nice. On the hill
that was killed, you said that was my
father. Was that my father in his life?
Nice. And um Okay. My father actually
died the year before that experience. Uh
I'm not I wasn't real close to him. I
wondered why my father was in that
experience and why the cardboard face.
Simply in this way understand that what
you recognized in the symbology you saw
in the out of body experience took on
the blankness in a sense the
two-dimensionality that you had felt
with regard to the experience of that
relationship with the being here in this
life. And in that way because they had
already removed themselves from the
physical life, they were no longer to
you in this way solid. But you recognize
the same spirit and the same ideas that
that individual was experiencing from
many different lives to many other
different lives. And as you witness that
individual create the scenario that took
their life in what you call the
avalanche, you can find that there is
much to relate to that incident with
many incidents that took place.
simultaneously within your present
father's life. This life before he
allowed himself to move on. Now
understand in this way that it was a
simultaneous experience. What you were
perceiving in that other reality was an
alternate version an alternate self of
the same soul. And because it was
simultaneous then they died about the
same time. You follow me? Yeah. So it
was his choice to be in that experience
for me. Of course it is all choice.
Right. Well, I I always assumed it was
um I I I never thought what it Well, I
did have some ideas, but uh I didn't
know what it was. I never thought it was
my father. Oh, right. So, okay. Now, um
you've been telling us to
um I can I hope I hope I
can. I think that I have the potential
for opportunities to talk to the army
and I would like before I tell you
exactly what I think how that I think
this can happen um and I'd like your
help with it. We'll see. Uh understand I
think you do not need help but go ahead.
All right. Um well let me tell you
briefly the kind of work I do. I work
for a place called Likon and we have
government contracts and um right now I
don't work on a project. All right. I
need a project to be able to talk to the
army. May I suggest something? Uh-huh.
Understand that the methodology of how
you arrive at what you are willing to do
is of no concern to us, though we care
that you are creating something that you
enjoy. Recognize it will suffice to
simply state what you are willing to do.
Okay, if I assuming I have the
opportunity to to talk to people, which
we will assume, okay, continue to talk
to people, there are probably people
that represent various intelligence
agencies and uh
my typical
uh way of dealing when I go to business
meetings is to keep it a business and
not not to be very social. Except May I
suggest something else? You have still
not answered my question. What I plan to
do? Yes. Uh well, you know, the paramble
does not matter. The parameters do not
matter to me right now. Okay. What are
you willing to do? I am willing to do my
part in communicating the ideas that
need to be communicated in order to
bring about the blending of our
civilization. And what ideas do you feel
bizarre? Okay, that's what I need to
talk to you about. You do not know.
Well, I don't know how to go about it
because even though you say the
methodology doesn't matter, it it does
matter because these people I the way I
would start would be to to sort of fraud
them and find out if they're willing to
listen to different kinds of ideas. All
right. Well, have you done this? I have
not had any opportunities and I haven't
thought about it. I do it with people
that I meet on everyday basis. Do you
not believe that you will create the
opportunities? Yes. exactly when and where you need
Yes. exactly when and where you need
them. Uh yes, then all you need to do is
allow yourself the idea of knowing what
you want to say and when you know what
you want to say, the individuals and the
opportunities and the situations will be
there. I think what I in in order to
know what I want to say, I would like to
know from you. You've said that there
has been contact with various uh
representatives of our government and of
the armed forces. guys. Um, and they
declined. Um, now I would like to know a little
Um, now I would like to know a little
more what that contact consisted of.
Why? Uh, because I think give me a
better framework for talking to these
people because they have a lot invested
in their careers. Now, I know of a of a
general I think it's a general styine.
Does that mean anything to you? No.
Okay. who is who was very open to to
outlandish ideas. Let's say outlandish
and I don't think he's with the
Department of Defense anymore because I
and from what I heard I don't know much
about it from what I heard is that he
tried to do some things to open people's
minds and he really got sort of pushed
on the side. So if I know are you afraid
that will happen to you? No, because
that can't happen to me. I mean I don't
have that kind of career in in my
background. All right. But also why do
you need to assume what you will
encounter in terms of the type of
individual you will attract to tell what
you want to tell? Why do you assume that
you will have to find an individual with
whom you will have to struggle to tell
your story because they may not want to
hear it? Why would you want to attract
someone who would not want to hear it?
Oh, I don't. But it's it's possible it
could happen. And I like Is it
Is it
Why is it possible that it could happen?
If that is not your reality, why is it
possible that it could happen? Okay,
maybe now we realize you are only
attempting to be fair.
I mean, I do have, you know, I do have a
certain amount of experience talking to
these people. I know what they're like.
All right, but understand this. Much of
what you feel you cannot change in your
life you blame upon the experience that
you have previously had which keeps you
exactly where you don't want to
be. Now if you know you are creating
your past and your future from the
present. So what about all that previous
experience? The you that you are now is
not the you that experienced what you
experienced then. Mhm. That's very true.
Then understand you are creating your
reality in the moment and you will
attract if you are willing to be the
vibration of an individual who can
attract only the individual who will be
able to listen and be able to do
something about what you say. Okay?
experience, not withstanding. Because
the idea of
experience only has to do with the idea
you had of yourself when you were
creating those relationships with those
individuals. You are now creating a new
idea of yourself and a new relationship
with new individuals who will vibrate on
the same frequency that you are willing
to be. Okay. So in what is your purpose
in in asking us to share? You said you
would be of of help in in what way would
you be of help in this case? Simply the
idea of discussing with you what you are
willing to do and assisting you to
clarify as I am the idea that you truly
are willing to do what you want to do.
All right. Let's say that consciously my
out of consciousness I'm I know I'm
willing to do it. I think it's it's very
exciting and I think that then define
it. What do you want to say?
Uh-huh. I haven't I thought well when
when the time comes I'll know what to
say. That's what I thought in a sense.
Yes. Therefore you are telling me that
since you do not know now the time is
not now. No the time is not now. I know
that it may be sometime in a few months.
All right. Now, do you think you would
like it to be sooner?
Sure. Why? Because I'm very excited over
it. All right. But I really don't know
what to say because I I heard a tape in
which you discussed your contact or was
it was it you personally or was it other
people from Erasan? No, it was you.
Understand in this way our civilization
has not physically contacted yours. So
who physically contacted these people?
Many other civilizations that have been
plleaden that have been reticulum who
actually become then take on human shape
human form not so much. They how do they
how do they meet these people? There
have been face to face. Uhhuh.
And what what kinds of things do they
offer to do? They discuss
mostly the ideas of what degree of
willingness may exist within your
society at this time for them to allow
the information to be released. There
has been some exchange of what you call
scientific information but in a very
limited sense.
There have been discussions of some of
the ideas of what you call politics and
economics but very limited again for the
most part any interactions we are
describing are very limited and very
rare but they have happened. Okay. So
you think simply releasing the
information would be enough? Uh what I'm
trying to figure out is is it'd be nice
if somebody me or anybody else could
actually suggest ways of bringing about
this blending or Why don't you? Because
I don't know how to do it. Why not? Uh
if you do not know how to do it, how do
you know that is what you want to do?
You must have something when you say
this is what you want to do. You must
have some feeling or idea or picture
about how you think you might go about
doing it. Otherwise, you would have
nothing to view that you think well that
would be exciting to do. That's very
true. I thought that's why. Then what is
your picture? What is the picture you
have created? about how
about how
you will go about doing this idea if
that is what you want to do. What if you
had a person right now in front of you
that you knew? Mhm. Was someone who
would listen to you? What would be the
first thing you would say to them? Well,
I I think I would at least find out
where they stand. let's say okay they're
interested and uh I would simply ask
them how they would view the
possibilities because they know more
about the the organization that they
they deal with than I do right so I
would ask them how do you think this
could be done then do you not assume
that if you attract such an individual
and initiate the conversation that the
reply you will get will allow the
conversation to continue and you will
know what to say because you will be
playing off of them right That's that's
why I stopped thinking at that point.
Then simply know that you have all you
need within your atlas time right now to
attract such an individual and allow
yourself to know that you can and that
you will know what to say when you do.
Keep it simple. All right. Thank you.
Thank you. Sure. Uh last week I had an
experience that was uh never happened to
me before. Um, and it was a ball of
energy sort of appearing in my brain and
uh, it expanded and glowed and then kind
of flowed out towards my girlfriend that
was in the same room and she was able to
observe it. And how did you feel? Oh, I
felt wonderful. How did she feel? I felt
good. All right. So, I want to know if you
All right. So, I want to know if you
could give me some um, advice on what it
may have been. I've been thinking I have
my own ideas. All right. Well, your own
ideas will be paramount to mine because
it is your life and your experience.
What does your imagination tell you?
This is what we will assist you with the
recognition that your imagination is a
dimension of reality that you can rely
on to be giving you valid information
for what it is you are wishing to
explore about yourself. So trust what
you give yourself through your
imagination. What did your imagination
tell you was the meaning of the
experience for you at this time? It told
me that it was a cleaning out of u a
channel for energy information complex.
All right. Then how does that feel? It
feels wonderful. All right. Is that
sufficient for you? Uh yes. Well,
then okay. There's no need to complicate
the issue.
Was it not simple to understand? Yes,
actually was. Uh I've been wondering in
relation to that where it begins to get
complex is um how to go about um you
mentioned in one of your tapes that the
the physical channeling that is set up
as an agreement arrange prior to this
lifetime with the medium. Usually um yes
that's right usually. So I had the idea
of well
um where would I go to to further
increase any latent skills? All right.
You're saying where do I go from here
now that I've had this experience? Is
this what you are saying? Yes. Well,
allow me to ask you this. What did you
do to get to the point where you did
what you did? Well,
Well,
I think you've answered my question.
Understand that you as a physical being
will experience every single idea that
you chose to experience when you chose
to become physical. You will not miss
one of them. So all you need to do is
keep living to experience all that you
have chosen to experience in
life. Act upon your intuition. Be
willing to have the conviction to give
validity and reality to your imagination
by acting it out. Acting upon it as if
it is real to you. as if it does
represent the reality you wish to be to
you and then you will be consciously
creating your imagination to be that
reality and you will live your dreams.
Simple. Yes. Thank you.
Michelle, you okay? I want to um first
share an experience I had over the
holidays and then have your comment on
it. Okay. Uh I went to New Jersey and I
saw a person named Sandy Stein. Now this
is a person that 18 about 18 years ago
I'd gone out with a few times and um I
didn't like him much then. And this time
I liked him better except I still had uh
I didn't trust him totally. But there
were times where I felt like we had a
really nice time together. He taught he
told me he was glad we were friends and
he wanted to remain friends and and he
enjoyed my openness and um he said some
really you know nice friendly things to
me in our last conversation before I
came back um to California from New
Jersey. Nice. It's okay. So I felt
really good about that and I also was
building up ideas in my mind
romantically that have since um aren't
quite there anymore like that. It was
like kind of like when you're initially
with in that fantasy thing for maybe
about a week and then reality sets in.
But um another reality sets in. Another
reality comes in. Okay.
So I went and asked another um another
entity who's channelneled through
someone called the agent and I asked him
about the relationship and I told him
that I I you know like this person yet
felt like he was dishonest and he
assured me he was very dishonest and he
assured me that he didn't care well he
said at that point that he said this
person Sandy doesn't care as much about
you as you think he does and that he
doesn't it's not that he's lying to you
but he doesn't tell you kind of
everything um that and I said well is it
true that he really wants to be friends
with me and he said well yes you know
and there's just other things that he
doesn't tell you and uh I felt
tremendously sad why well I felt sad
because I felt like it was important for
me um to the time that I spent with him
was really nice and and I felt like the
things that he said he really meant but
when I was sharing with this other
entity I wasn't so sure at that time.
All right. Well, understand this as
well. The idea of the things that he
said felt nice because you created them
to be nice because your vibration and
your reality will always create the idea
of the positive manifestation now that
you are moving in the idea of yourself
in that manner. Again, you can form
relationships with any type of
individual. recognize that no matter
what they are in the relationship for,
you will always benefit in a positive
way if that is the type of reality you
have set up for yourself. So while they
may be being in your terminology
dishonest, the idea still will allow you
to utilize whatever information comes
from them for yourself in a positive
way. Okay? And then for you, you can
recognize that what is honest about the
information is that it is a valid symbol
that you have chosen to co-create with
them for you.
Well, okay. But I'm a real Yes, I
understand everything you're saying. And
yet it it feels important to me to know
how another person really feels. And
what you're saying is we actually create
what they're feeling, too. I mean, in a
sense, yes. I mean, how would you know
for sure then how a person feels about
you? I mean, if someone says they care
about me,
understand that the idea, so to speak,
is not so much that an individual that
is collected within total integration
and self-love. It is not so much that that
self-love. It is not so much that that
individual needs to know how other
people feel.
They will simply be able to perceive all
the ideas for which they have attracted
any particular relationship. They may
know how another person feels. They may
not know exactly how another person
feels. But the idea is this.
You in your integrated
self-love do not need to differentiate
the idea of how they feel precisely to
simply recognize what you are allowing
the relationship to exist for. Well, I
Yes. And I think that's very well put
and I I
um and I have made that an important
part of my life. how other people feel
about me has been yes has been important
to me. Um all right but understand again
even that idea as you are now describing
it still does involve little bit of the
idea of judgment even though it is not
so much that you are concerned about how
they feel about you but just to know how
they feel is still a judgment of
differentiation. There's not so much the need to really
There's not so much the need to really
pick that out and diversify that from
all the other ways in which they might
feel if you are simply willing to allow
the interaction to be known to you for
the reasons that you have co-created it.
Because you see, when you are in a
knowing state, you do not necessarily
have to go through the panorama of
feelings to know what it is about. Okay.
Well, that's that's a different reality
for me that I'm learning about now that
I'm it's like I'm in the midst I'm in
the middle some it's I'm making the
switch but I haven't quite but that is
why you attracted that type of an
opportunity to show you that you are no
matter what another individual is
offering to you going to translate it
into positive effect for yourself. And
so it is not so much that you have to
know what they are really feeling per se
because you simply do know that no
matter what they are in the reality for
they are still being of service to you
and you can feel that and only the
service that they are doing. Okay. Okay.
Now and then I just have one more thing
and that is that I I have a feeling that
this person um has sexual relations with
a lot of people. He's a very sexual
person and I because I distrust him. I I
feel like at one hand I don't feel like
I've picked up like any any disease or
anything from him. I don't I don't
really feel that. But but there's a part
of me that the part that doesn't trust
him thinks like that would be something
he would do. You know what I mean? Like
they wouldn't tell me or something. Oh,
right. But you know that is not what you
need. Okay. All right. Yeah. You're right. All
Okay. All right. Yeah. You're right. All
right. I But I do have a fear that okay,
I could create something like that out
of my own fears of sex, my own things
that I have going on about sex. Like,
oh, that would be convenient way out,
you know. Then all you need to do is get
in touch with the fact that you love
yourself unconditionally. And when you are
unconditionally. And when you are
integrated in loving yourself
unconditionally, you will always be
consciously knowledgeable of the fact
that you will never need to do that to
yourself. So even if I have that fear,
it doesn't mean that that fear is going
to cause it to happen. You can
understand that you can recognize
something that might be a probability
without instilling energy behind it.
Okay? So I don't have to be like afraid
that certain fears I have are absolutely
going to manifest in my life. I can just
recognize that they're fears and that
not you know once again the library. You
may read every book on the shelf. The
ones that are frightening, the ones that
are joyous, the only ones that will
become your reality are the ones you
check out.
Thank you. All right. Thank you. Nice.
Hello. Hello. Um, we got back Sunday
from our trip. Nice. Have a good time.
Yes, I had a wonderful time.
Um, I'm I don't know how to even express
I'm I don't know how to even express
myself. Um, of course you do. Well, I
have creative problem with that. Oh, no
you don't.
For instance, I perfectly understood you
to now say, "I do not know how to
express myself." And you express that
idea perfectly.
Thank you, Michelle. Oh, thank you.
Well, we got to New Hampshire and um I
was first four days I wasn't all that I
wasn't thinking too much about, oh, the
contact's going to happen. what's it
going to be?
Um, but as the days went along, I
started thinking, well, gee, one day
less, one day less. When's it going to
happen? I I was centered. I wasn't
driving myself crazy. All right.
Remember what we said to you before you
left about expectation? Yes, I
remembered that. All right. I really I I
was proud of myself. All right. Um,
before we got to New Hampshire, when we
were in New York, I had some dreams that
I think are related. All right. I'd like
to mention them briefly and maybe go
right ahead. I think I had uh contact a
lot of contacts on the trip with the
leaves. Um one of the dreams I had was
three three contacts. Yes. Dream. Yes.
three contacts. Yes. Dream. Yes.
That that's perfect. That's exactly what
I have written down. Um the first one
was it was in an office
environment and I'm sure that's symbol I
created, right? Um, and there were many
employees in this office, but there were
certain ones that wore these pink robes
and it was understood that the people
wearing the pink this secret club
membership and it was almost like we
were having a large convention or a
conference and I don't remember a lot of
the details. I just remember that my
friend Butch was in the dream and he was
one of the
people and I got a a pleadian plleadian
and I got a a pleadian plleadian
feeling. There was a lot of people from
that area. All right. Um but as far as
dad's concerned I just felt I woke up
and I felt like it was a very large
meeting of you. Am I correct? Yes. Do
you want to love it? Simply the idea
that you were recalling, recreating in
the present the idea
of in your terms a
past visitation in astral state that you
had made with regard to the idea of
learning what you needed to learn to set
up the type of system you want to set up
on your planet. Now
thus it was formed the idea of conclave
to illuminate to you all the
methodologies that had been undertaken
to that point so that you could pick
from among them all the ways that you
wish to implement upon your planet this
time. Yes, that sounds good coming out of your
Yes, that sounds good coming out of your
mouth. I couldn't verbalize that but
that's not how it helped. Um the other
one was I believe I I categorized it as
a memory um of my early studies with
black when in their early days. This is
also in a sense when the meeting took
place. I see. Okay. This uh was really
interesting because I Yes. And I would physically go
because I Yes. And I would physically go
to and from wherever they were holding
the teaching. Nice. By myself in the
physical. And I remember leaving one of
the the learning days and I was going
home to where I was residing and
um I I remember feeling that I did not
really quote unquote like these people
that were teaching me. I didn't agree
with a lot of their methodologies, but
there was a reason why I wanted to be
taught this. Understand that ultimately
they also did not agree with their own
methodologies. Yeah. That is why many of
them are upon your planet again now
because they have realized the idea that
in
attempting to meet the opposition on their own
to meet the opposition on their own
level, they only drew the opposition to
themselves so that they could be wiped
out.
Yes. Um anyway, I was going home and I
just knew I had this terrible purpose.
Oh, terrible. Well, I'm sorry. asked
from a book and I just take it off all
of a sudden.
Um, where I came from. Anyway, I was
standing at the shore. There's a river.
This is this is really beautiful. I've
never experienced anything like this
before in a dream. And I had to wait to
cross the river. And it's much like when
the tides would go out on Earth.
However, the tides here went out like a
10-minute interval. And what they do is
it was almost like the splitting of the
Red Sea. Certain
pieces across the river would just split
and there would be a walkway and you
would walk through and I was just
sitting there waiting for the tide to
split that and that's what I was
thinking that I was unhappy. I didn't
really like the people that I had to
learn this stuff. So I was wondering if
I vision if I imag whatever imagined
that correctly if that was in a sense it
was also symbolic for you in the idea
that you attracted yourself to that
particular symbol to represent the idea
of the split that would have to take
place the idea of the creativity flowing
in both directions. one realizing that
it could no longer use the methodology
that it had already chosen and the other
realizing that the so-called
rectification of that previous
methodology would take place in the
other direction you were performing the
idea of beginning to set up to co-create
with many other individuals the 180°ree
opposite direction quote unquote in case
the original idea failed so to speak. So
you were in this way willing to
institute in this time frame this
transformational frame the idea of the
type of network that would allow them in
your terminology to have something to
fall back on later.
Yes.
As you said, I'm not quote unquote a
member of the Black Lead. I'm like a
Yes. Yes. Okay. Um and now you said
there were three and I had two others
that are worth mentioning. They're very
brief. One was um a friend of mine for
Christmas gave me um I call it a crystal
crystal. It's it's two quartz crystals and fused
It's it's two quartz crystals and fused
together in a way where you can hold it
and it's just like a a pistol, a laser
gun. Yes. And I didn't bring it with me
on the trip, but when I got to New York,
I um had a dream that some being or
being were teaching me how to use it and
that it was a tool for me. Nice. And the
alarm went off and it jolted me so much
I couldn't bring up that that conscious
I couldn't bring the memory in my
consciousness. You will when you allow
yourself a little more freedom in play
time.
Thank you. Um the other dream, if this
was it, I don't know. Entity appeared in
the bedroom I was sleeping in New York
when I and um it was a man with dark
hair and a mustache. He had three quartz
crystal balls in his hand. They were
they were small. He held me towards take
these. If you learn to scry into them
with patience, you will begin to have
visions. And that was it. Very good. Yes,
Yes,
you have given yourself all that you
need and you have consciously brought
forth contact. I really
I really
you are becoming more so. Yes, that is
the idea. [Music]
[Music]
Does that do I think that mean okay if I
start scrying that or or is it more I
don't know I really am I'm having
sto [Music]
would you in this way proceed physically
to walk before the channel's body
standing in front. Facing. Yeah, he's
facing
the three fingers with your
own with your imagination. At this
point, can you allow yourself the
freedom to scry into those
spheres to know that you can create for
yourself if you wish the idea of
attracting yourself to physiological
representations of those spheres if you
wish. You may have them physically with
you. You may find your own versions of
those ideas so that you may utilize them
in that way. You may also simply keep
them in your imagination if you wish. In
this way, all that you need to do is
endeavor to perform the act that you
perceived was being suggested to you in
any way, shape, or form, whether you
have the physical spheres with you or
not. And you will allow yourself in
relaxing into the idea of that type of
meditation. to be able to see through
them as doorways and to contact in that
way all the information that you need
with regard to the fundamental triad
foundation you will form within the
particular network that you are forming
upon your planet at this time and you
will understand how you can build a
basis that will always support itself
flawlessly as the tetrahedrin the
pyramid the three-sided pyramid will
allow you to recognize that it is the
most stable form And the simplest form
of solid you can have your
three-dimensional density. Two sides
always supporting the one. The one never
letting the two come apart in this way.
You will understand as you begin to
scribe further into the idea of
yourself, your own triad partnerships,
your own unity in this way that you can
simply take it for granted that you are
a being of play and allow yourself the
freedom to roam in your imagination.
Allow yourself the freedom to love
yourself in this way. Cherish yourself.
Take care of yourself in this way. Play
and endeavor to love unconditionally all
that you are. For then you will find
that in unconditionally loving what you
are, you will be able to share that
unconditional love with all those that
you will attract to yourself as you have
chosen this exemplification of the hub
of the network, the nexus that you will
perform this service with this
transformational life in this particular
civilization. Understand you are
surrounded by these ideas. You are
surrounded by friends. Each and every
one of you all know each other on some
level in this way. You are all part of
the same network. You are not special.
No one is special. But you are all
unique. Allow yourself the freedom to
express your uniqueness with conviction
and the shortity that it can seem as
simple as simply following your
intuition, playing in your imagination,
and allowing yourself the freedom to
know that that is how you can unfold the
entirety of your life. Nothing needs to
be complex. You can allow yourself not
to become childish, but childlike as you
already are in that way. Allow yourself
to know that as you make the sweet
sounds of childhood, those will be the
tonalities and the harmonies and the
bells that will be ringing in other
individuals ears for they have heard
them themselves in their own lives and
it will strike a chord. You will attract
yourself to them. They will attract
themselves to you. Collect, if you wish,
three crystal spheres to represent the
idea that was suggested to you in the
astral contact that you had. But you do
not need them. It is up to you. It is up
to you to determine the nature of your
toys, the nature of your symbols as you
create them in this reality. Understand,
my human friend, understand, my dear
child, understand in this way that you
are God. God is all that is. That you
are crystallin in nature. You are the
spheres. You are 360° outward in
yourself and at the center of yourself
simultaneously. You are a projection and
you are real. You are everything you
want to be right now. Allow yourself
only the idea of the unconditional love.
Feel yourself, love yourself, and go
into the depths of yourself and explode
outward in this way in any way, shape,
or form your imagination tells you is
valid for you. Are you following along?
I'm following you very closely. Uh-huh.
Now understand that there are messages
of appreciation from the league in
allowing you to allow them to play with
you in this way and for cocreating the
idea that they now understand the idea
simply of offering freedom of choice
equally between positive and negative
reality. So that in this way all things
being equal, then all beings can choose.
And that this is the way. This is the
way they were seeking. The way they were
seeking to circumvent the negativity
that they were creating in their own
systems. And in this way, you are a part
of the illumination. You are a part of
the overall idea that they now
understand within themselves. Now
understand they have been a very serious
allowing themselves to come upon your
plan. In this transformational life,
they will only love you all the more for
simply allowing yourself to completely
be who and what you are for. In that
way, you will be illuminating brightly
the path that you are and they will
enjoy seeing you very much.
Thank you. Thank you.
If I could, I'd kiss now. You already
have.
I feel really wonderful. I don't
Thank you. I hope you can feel the
appreciation. There is no need to hope.
Understand that the degree of
appreciation that we have for your
entire civilization is infinite.
Um, I'd like I'd like to relate the
visual Same. You may a little bit later. Okay.
Same. You may a little bit later. Okay.
For right now, allow me to underline the
idea that what we were just doing with
you is something that you can do with
anyone in your society. You have given
yourself an entire playground and it is
full of children.
Thank you very much. Y have time for a
question always. Okay. Would you
consider politics or the political
system in this country of a positive
polarity or negative polarity?
Understand that the idea of politics in
and of
itself as you have created it generally
upon your
civilization has come out of the
negative manifestation of the separation
of yourself from the all that is that
you are. But this is not a judgment.
It is an observation simply that the
need for which you have created politics
has allowed your politics to be
negatively manifested. How could that be
switched? Change yourself.
And then the rest of the people too. You
talking domino effect or they got Yes.
Yeah. Understand it is not even so much
that idea. It is that every individual
already exists on every level of
existence that there is to exist upon.
As you change yourself, you are looking
out of new eyes. And those new eyes only
can see upon the level in which they
exist. So you will only see the other
portions of those individuals that only
exist on the level you have been willing
to change yourself to. They will seem to
have changed, but it is you that have
changed. Now understand
simply, you are your governments. You
are your governments. You are every idea
in your civilization.
When you act the way you want to act,
the way you would act if you were the
idea of a government in peace, in love,
then you will be radiating to other
individuals the opportunity to think of
themselves that way as well. For you
will be an example of the possibility to
see yourself in that way. Then if they
choose to, they also can understand and
share and cocreate that idea of seeing
themselves unseparated from their
government, which is what you have done
with it. Taken your responsibility and
pushed it away from yourself, given it
over to someone else, given your power
away, take care of my life for me. I
have many fears, but you will protect
me. In creating your government out of
your fear, you have created a being a
consciousness that born out of fear must
generate fear to sustain its
existence. You follow me? Yeah. What
good would it do to join? How can you
change from joining? You join I mean
change it from the inside. I'm talking
you know like on a bigger sense
understand again immediate sense. You
are your government.
You are your
government. Change yourself and act like
you have changed. Act like you exist in
a world where there is
peace. But not from the idea of judging
what you have, simply preferring what
you want. As I have said, you do not get
want. As I have said, you do not get
peace by hating war. You get peace by
loving peace.
So do not hate your government or you
will only be the hateful government that
you perceive. Be the loving idea of sharing
perceive. Be the loving idea of sharing
equally. Take back your responsibility
for everything that occurs to you. Take
back your power. Take back your fear.
And in this way, you will act like the
type of individual that other
individuals within your civilization can
look at and say that person is showing
me that I also am my economics, my
government, my religions, my everything,
my life, my reality. Therefore, the idea
of responsibility is not blame but
freedom to choose what I prefer. I am
completely responsible for everything in
my reality. Which is the same thing as
saying I can choose whatever I want in
my reality. You cannot in this way
change anyone else if they do not wish
to change. But you can change yourself
and not perceive nor experience them
anymore if they do not want to change.
For you will be in another idea, another
reality, and you will create for
yourself the existence on that level in
which exists all the other types of
individuals of the same nature that will
cocreate with you the type of idea
reality that you want to experience. You
will think it is the same reality
changed. It is not the same reality
changed. It is a completely different
universe. Do you follow me?
Do you follow me?
Yeah. Are you sure? Well, yeah. For the
most part, I'm going to get the tape
after. All right. Could you tell me something
All right. Could you tell me something
personal about business? Are you allowed
to give up? Can you like prognosticate
commodity markets?
Understand the idea that we call
prediction. Yeah, I remember that part.
I'm just wondering if you could give
like definite possibilities of the
parameters or give me a formula for
computing them on a on a I don't know
the most efficient system for doing
that. The most efficient system is to
simply know
the second most
[Laughter] guess. Thank you.
Thank you.
For sure. Nice. I have um four months
now. My right shoulder, my right arm has
just been hurting so tremendously like I
can hardly lift something up and a lot
of physical things
lately. And what do you do with your
right arm?
I work I lift I what I've been
trying to do is to do more with my left
arm and my left side as opposed to my
right it out. Why?
Because I felt that maybe I was doing
too much with I was too right sided or
something. He and besides it hurt so
much he couldn't do anything. All right.
So I had to work with my or you know do
anything with my left. All right. Can
you simply
imagine? Can it be sufficient reason for
you that you may have chosen the idea to
incapacitate your right side so that you
could learn to use the other side to
integrate the hemispheres of your brain?
That had crossed my mind. But understand
that if you know that that is the
reason, if you can allow yourself to
feel that that may be valid, then you
know you do not necessarily have to
create it in such an unconscious fashion
and you do not need the pain in order to
simply allow yourself to know that you
will continue to
integrate. Do you follow me? Yes, I I
do. I follow you. I wanted validation on
the Put both of your hands up in the air.
Now, as you do
this, feel both hemispheres of your
brain. Feel the left hemisphere
connected to the right hand and the
right hemisphere connected to the left.
Feel the analytical
you that you may feel tired of
controlling the right hand and the
creative you that you may wish more
experience with controlling the
left. But allow the left and the right
to both be equally valid in the
functions they have performed. You may
relax. Allow both sides to be valid equally in
Allow both sides to be valid equally in
the functions they perform and allow the
symbol you have given yourself to be a
valid symbol. Do not judge it. Do not
try to get rid of it in trying to get
rid of it. You reinforce
it. Allow it to be valid in the way you
have created it. for it has served the
purpose of reminding you that you want
to integrate and balance both sides of
yourself. Now that you can know that is
what you give yourself the symbol for.
It has served its purpose and has
delivered its message to your
consciousness and you can let it
dissolve into something else knowing
that you will continue to balance
yourself and do not need to nag yourself
to remind yourself that you will
continue to do so. You do not need to
drive yourself
to make the integration. You do not need
to whip
yourself to move
forward. You do not need to pull
yourself agonizingly, straining
agonizingly, straining
yourself. You may simply
flow. Do you follow me?
Yes. Um, my body feels like it's been hit by
Um, my body feels like it's been hit by
an lasting months. Nice.
And it's very sore and it's very tired.
It feels like it can sleep for five
years straight. Go right ahead.
Why? Why? Uh why is that? What?
Understand simply that you are, as is
your nature, giving yourself a crash
course in acceleration. You are
impacting yourself very rapidly into the
new idea of yourself. And so you are
creating many ideas of friction between
the idea of an old you and a new you
with such rapidity that you are
basically beating yourself up.
How do your ribs feel? My ribs? Yes.
Under your arms? They feel fine.
I've had muscular pain up my chest and
my back. Nice.
Can you take slowly
slowly three deep gentle and loving
breaths in and
out. As you do
so, close your eyes and float and
describe whether it is what you call a
physiological sensation or not. Describe
in your
imagination what you feel as a sensation
in any portion of your chest area as you
do so.
I feel a tingling. Any temperature
change? Yes.
Yes.
Very good. It is cool. Yes.
Can you allow this idea, this sensation
to extend itself into all your
extremities? Can you then feel the air
rushing through you?
Can you feel that? Yes.
Can you allow this feeling of atmosphere
of coolness of mint to exude from your
pores and fill your oric field so that
you breathe the atmosphere in creating a
cycle? Yes.
Take your right hand and follow what I
do. Now
Now
relax and tonight at your time as you
sleep know that you are talking to
yourself and you are talking yourself
from your higher consciousness to your
physical consciousness into a state of
relaxation. And when you arise, the idea
of the symbol of yourself will be more
and more with every breath of your oric
field, more
assimilated, more centered and more
present. Understand that when you reach
for things in the future, you are always
going to strain yourself because the
future is not something you have to
reach for. You will be reaching for
infinity. It is all within you. It is
all right in the present. Do not strain
your reach because simply you already
know that your reach as all that is
already contains everything that you
need. Do you follow me? Yes.
Thank you. For sure. Yes. Then you
Hi. This is the first evening that I've come
This is the first evening that I've come
to um see you. I've been listening to
tapes for quite a while now for my
husband and I'm really enjoying you. We
are enjoying you all as well. Thank you.
I have a question about our concept of
death. All right. When we leave our
physical body and we go wherever we go,
right? It has been for a while now that I've
It has been for a while now that I've
been very bothered by the thought. Yes.
I'm having a hard time trying to sort in
my own mind and
understand what it's all about. All
right. But understand every time you
try, you will have a hard time. Yes.
Okay. Now, what do you feel it is quote
unquote all about?
Um, what do I feel?
Okay, I feel that. Well, I I it's I
can't explain it. That's the problem. I
I'm trying to understand exactly what I
feel. Okay. Excuse me. No, I feel fear.
All right. Very good. Okay. Very good.
Now, why? because I don't know what it's
about. So,
so what are you trying to tell me? I'm
not trying to tell you anything. I
simply said so.
Okay. Now, is it that my
All right. All right. All right. Use
your imagination. What do you think will
happen when you die?
I'm going to go somewhere. I don't know.
Where? At this point in time, I don't
know. I choose to go. Okay. Very good.
Okay. All right. Now, what I want to
understand too, my feeling, my One
moment. What? Do you believe what you
just said? Yes, I do. You will choose to
go wherever you want. Yes. All right.
Now, if you believe that you will choose
to go wherever you want, what are you
afraid of? Good question.
Good question.
uh trying to understand where I'm going.
Uh no, that's not it. Well, thank you.
The fear I understand that yes, I will
be going somewhere wherever I choose to
go when that time comes that I leave my
physical body. Are you afraid of death
or are you afraid of pain?
I'm sorry, that's hard to answer.
Probably both.
Maybe I'm trying to think that is there
somebody close to me that I'm having
this feeling that maybe they're going to
die and that's what's frightening me.
Are you telling me that your feeling
about your fear of death is specific
rather than general? Right or no? Well,
yes. I've got myself confused. All
right. Elaborate on that. Spec is
specific or general. Do you
feel that the idea of death is a
separation, a loss?
Uh, if it was me, no. Somebody else.
Yes. All right. Now, why not if it was
you?
Cuz I didn't go anywhere.
All right. Very good.
Now then, do you not know that when they
die, they don't go anywhere either?
Well, yeah, true. But they're not there.
Oh, yes, they are. You can physically
see them. Okay. Well, you can sense
them. Yes. You can know that you are
still connected to them as you always
have been.
Okay. So what you're saying or what you
are trying to show me is that if someone
close to me does die, then I should be
able to accept it as that and still be
able to feel their vibration or sense
that they're still there. All right? In
a sense. Now, there is no should about
it. You do not have to should anything.
But recognize in this way it may be that
if such an individual were to choose to
offer you the gift of transforming from
physical to
non-physicality for you it would be
something that would be a gift for you
to reflect within yourself your belief
systems about those ideas and perhaps
that is what you chose it for. Recognize
also that in this way you can form the
analogy that if you have a friend that
you are talking with one day and then
you see them the next day wearing a
different set of clothes. Well, do you
tremble in fear because they have
changed their clothes? No. You still
recognize them as your friend. The idea
that they have left their physical body
is simply a change of clothes, so to
speak. Why fear the idea that you have
lost them simply because they have
changed their
clothes? You can still
sense the idea of the relationship. You
can sense the
consciousness. Now, understand this.
Everything occurs within perfect timing.
And therefore, if someone that you know
should physically die, it serves a
purpose in the co-arrangement, the
co-aggreement that you all made.
Therefore, understand that what is
happening is in accord with what you
agreed to experience. It is up to you
whether to make a negative or a positive
experience out of
it. But agree to experience it you did.
And if you know you agreed to experience
it, then you can. You do have the right
to assume that you chose to experience
it for a positive reason.
Yes. To try to understand. To
understand. Okay. To understand in
whatever way you as the being that you
are, as the personality that you are,
chose to understand
it. Therefore, do not be hard on
yourself when you think you do not get
the whole picture right away. that I
guess you're reading my mind. That's
that's it. You know, it I I can't get
the whole picture. It does frighten me.
If it could be maybe my husband uh
dying, God forbid, that it would happen
right now, like you say, that we may not
this moment right in this time right
here, but in what we call the future.
Let me ask you
something. Do you understand that you
have many physical lives?
I'm beginning to understand that. All
right. Do you
understand that when you choose to have
a physical life while you are still
non-physical as you would say in between
lives so to speak? Now we are speaking
linearly because you are in a linear
time track. Although all your lives are
actually simultaneous because there is
only here and now. But as we are talking
linearly while you are in non-physical
state choosing your next physical
life understand that there are certain
ideas about that life in that life that
you wish to experience to fulfill
another idea of yourself as a total
being. Now in choosing those ideas that
you will
experience, understand this. You will
experience every single one that you
chose to experience. You will experience
nothing extra, nor will you miss any of
the things that you chose to
experience. By living your life, you
will live through and live out and
experience every idea that you chose to
experience and create this life for the
purpose of experiencing it.
Therefore, since there is no extra
time, since you are going to experience
everything you chose to experience, you
have set aside the idea of a certain
number of events that we call
timings. Now, the amount of time in
which you can have the experience of
your timings can vary depending upon how
you choose to go through the experience
of the timings. If you choose to negate
it, to judge it, to separate yourself
from the event, you will create that
much more
time that is needed to get through the
experience. Things will drag as you say,
you will get stuck in a rut and you will
become frustrated and tired. If you
choose to go through the event to
experience the timing from a positive
point of view, then it will be very
highly accelerated because you are
willing to integrate and less time will
be required to experience all the
timings, all the events you chose to
experience in this life. But when you
create your timings with the other
individuals, when you create yourself to
have a life with other individuals, you
are co-creating your timings to merge
and blend and always fulfill each
other's timings at exactly the right
moment. Therefore, no one is ever ahead
of anyone else. No one is ever behind
anyone else. And when someone in a sense
finishes what they have chosen to do in
a physical life and moves on, they are
not leaving you prematurely. You are not
leaving them prematurely. They are
leaving in exactly the right time and
timing that they chose to and that you
agreed to. Therefore, understand that if
you have agreed to stay physical longer,
then their leaving first provides for
you one of the experiences you chose to
have while still physical. So that you
can learn from it. Okay? You are going
to quote unquote catch up to them
eventually. I hope so. You do not have to. Oh, okay.
I hope so. You do not have to. Oh, okay.
I will. Yes. Okay. Okay. One more
question. Now, one more thing before
your question. Yes. For sure. The
recognition that every event in your
life serves a purpose can be the
choosing of the positive way for you to
learn the idea that you are thinking
about cocreating that event for perhaps
in a negative way. And by assuming that
it serves a positive purpose and
learning what that idea might be about
before you need to experience it in a
negative way means that it doesn't
necessarily have to happen in a negative
way for you to get the
message. You follow me? Yes. Then you
have the situation wherein you have the
so-called prediction of the oh horrible
catastrophe coming up. But the idea that
you now are aware of the prediction
itself lets you understand the reasons
for why you attracted that idea. And if
you understand the reasons, then you may
say, well, now I understand the purpose
of why I would have created a
catastrophe. So I no longer need to
experience it as a catastrophe. I can
now move ahead to the next thing. Okay.
Thank you very much. Thank you. My
second question regarding health. Yes.
Uh just like the young lady was about
pain. Uh I have been experiencing
excruciating I determine excruciating
headaches pains starting from the crown
of the head in the front of the forehead
past the ears down to the base of my
neck. All right. I also have experienced
infection in the nose and in the upper
part of my stomach. Now I have
decided that So you have what is
called post-nasal drip. Uh yes I do.
Thank you. Okay. Now I was told that
well no excuse me I decided to go to the
doctors. I have tried for uh two weeks
maybe two and a half weeks to try and
meditate concentrate with my power rods
my crystals everything to try and try
try try. Yes. Excuse
me. Uh distribute or
Uh distribute or
eliminate the pain that I am feeling. I
couldn't succeed in this. So I went to
the doctors. He ended up putting me on
medication. All right. Okay. I did. What
do you think about yourself for having
created the idea of pain? I don't like
it. You don't like yourself? No, I don't
like creating the idea of pain. All
right. But what do you think about
yourself for having created the idea of
pain? What do I think about myself? Yes.
Well, do you love yourself? When I
create pain, no. Why not? Because it
hurts. So,
well, why am I going to love myself if
I'm creating pain? Perhaps so that the
pain will go away.
Okay. You see, if you put conditions
upon your love, then you will always be
creating a doorway through which one of
those conditions can remind you that
they are there.
You follow me? I follow you. Okay. How
about the medication? Okay. The
medication has helped me. All right. I
have not been a my tool as you say, our
different tools that we need to help
assist us in whatever the situation may
be. It has helped you. Yes, it has
helped me. All right. Is that okay by
you? Why not?
Do you feel that I could concentrate on
myself alone without the drugs to be
able to eliminate? I feel you have that
potential. Yes.
I just have to find it. You do not have
to find it. You simply have to be it.
You have to live like it.
I don't understand. It's just like right
now I'm experiencing the pain in the
upper part of my stomach. Now, you made
the comment of the post-nasal drip. Are
you telling me that the post-nasal drip
is causing the pain in the upper part of
my stomach? No. What was the the
connection to your future self is the
connection to my future self? Understand
that the majority of the idea of energy
distribution in connecting to your
future self, to your higher self, to the
idea of the you you think you are
becoming usually occurs through the
solar plexus. And this is why as you
plexus. And this is why as you
understood in this way as I have said
myself in a sense to be the future self
of the physical channel you see before
you. Why we usually and used to in the
idea of the frequency as we were
acclimating the physical channel to the
connection with us used to regulate the
idea being in front of the solar plexus
of the hands of the physical channel to
form a link and a bridge so that there
would be an easing of the idea of the
blending of the two frequencies so there
would not be pain.
Recognize in this way the idea is simply
that as you create the idea of a future
self that you think to be so much better
than you at a higher frequency than you,
then you are creating a friction between
the frequency you think yourself to be
now and the frequency you think you are
becoming because you are putting the two
together by comparison and a slower
vibration and a faster vibration creates
friction and that friction is felt in
your physical form as pain and
disease. When you allow yourself to be
the future you now, then you form an
automatic blending that alleviates all
need for the symbol that reminds you
that you are still separating yourself
in the present from the idea of your
future self. All pain and disease is the
self. All pain and disease is the
product of your
separation from other portions of
yourself.
Therefore, it is a reminder or can be
viewed as a reminder that you are still
separating what it is you are seeking to
become because you are seeking it rather
than simply acting like you already are
it. And the more you seek, the more you
may double over.
It hurts. So maybe I should like now as
you breathe in a relaxed manner,
recognize that as you breathe
in, if you wish an analogy, if you wish
a symbol, as you breathe
in, then draw to yourself the future you
with every breath in.
And as you breathe out, you are taking
what you have drawn in as the future you
and gently placed it into position
around you as your reality.
In this way, you can ease through the
rhythmic vibration of the centering of
your being, through the energy of the
breathing, the centering of yourself,
the identification of your present self
with the future self to make them one
thing. And you can ease all of your
pains and
separations. Now to some degree the
intensity that you have been feeling in
this area is representative of the idea
of your third eye crown and channeling
chakras opening up to accept the you
have said you are on your way to meet.
But they're standing wide open waiting
for you to be that person. And you are
still walking with them wide open
waiting to get there.
So allow them to
relax. You are holding everything open
under tension and you are making them
hold open under tension for a very long
time because you are creating the idea
of being your future self in the present
as a very long journey that you need to accomplish. Relax.
accomplish. Relax.
Okay, one more thing and then I'm done.
What I'm experiencing right now, I have
in my hand here is a crystal. Okay. A
raw crystal which I meditate with and I
feel things with. Yes. As I'm talking to
you. Yes. Experiencing. I'm sitting here
and my body is shivering. Yes. My
temperature is warm. Yes. What is Can
What is your Is your whole body warm or
are there portions that are cold?
My toes. All right. What about your
hands? My hands are sweating. All
right. What about the crystal itself?
It's very warm. All right.
Now, that
vibration right
now, does it feel like something that
has great potential in it?