say how are you all this evening of your
time as you create time to
exist we will begin the idea of
interaction this evening of your time by
Illuminating a little bit further the
idea you have been exploring many of you
this time of your time the idea of your
own abundance recognize in this way there
abundance recognize in this way there
are many ideas that exist within the
society you have created yourself to be
about the idea of abundance which in
this way are part and parcel of the
structure that that you have created
your Society to be and not intrinsically
definitions of
abundance you many of you attach the
idea of abundance to the specific symbol
of what you call your Monetary
Exchange now it is not that your
Monetary Exchange cannot represent the
idea of abundance but abundance is far
more than that idea though many of you
will not allow yourself to perceive
abundance as being such and in this way
many of you limit the idea that you are
already very abundant in exactly the way
you need to be because you assume that
you are not abundant because you do not
have the monetary symbolic
representation of this
idea recognize that the basic primal
definition of abundance in a sense in
your terms more closely is simply being
able to do what you want to do when you
want to do it this does not always and
I'm sure your imagination is able to
come up with many examples it does not
always mean that you must have money in
order to fulfill that definition for
recognize there are many ways many
connections that can be formed many
doorways many opportunities many
interactions many relationships many
situations that can bring you the
opportunity to do what you want when you
want to without money ever changing your
hands from one to the
other in this way as you restrict
yourself into the assumption
that it is only through money that you
can allow yourself to achieve abundance
than you are closing all the doors
through which many opportunities that
will allow you to express your abundance
May manifest recognize many of you feel in
manifest recognize many of you feel in
this way that because you do not have
enough money more money than you have
you cannot do some of the things you
would like to do things that excite you
in that way things that you know are the
vibration are reflections of the
vibration that represent the things you
most desire in your life but as you say
who is you you do not have enough money
now recognize many of you make the
assumption that individuals in your
society that you call
Rich have
more than enough money to do anything
they want they do
not an individual you see as Rich has
exact L just enough money but they have
just enough money to fulfill the idea of
themselves that they
have you if you will stop and think
about it usually always have just enough
money to do what you want to do one way
or another I always have just enough but
I never seem to have more than just
enough but simply recognize an
individual who is also Rich always only
has just enough to do what it is they
have allowed themselves to realize they
are capable of doing therefore recognize
the idea of the scope of the symbol of
abundance is directly proportional to
the degree to which you believe you are
capable of expressing the being that you
are the idea that you are being willing
to be fully the idea that you would like
to think you are will expand you to the
point where you will then attract
automatically to yourself all of the
individuals opportunities and situations
and relationships that will provide for you
relationships that will provide for you
a directly
proportional means of expressing the
degree of the idea you are willing to be
nature Works automatically in that way
functions quite automatically will
always Supply you with exactly the
degree of the tool that will go into
allowing you to express the degree of
the idea you are willing to be are you
all following along this idea yes
also many of you feel in this way that
being rich is to hoard the symbol of
money recognize again that why it is not
in your terms impossible to do this idea
all then that has been done is the
compilation of the symbol money and in
this way it is not the fundamental
activity of abundance it is simply a
pile of money in this way recognize that
again if you will look at it many of the
individuals upon your planet who are
truly let us say functionally abundant
functionally Rich are not prone to be
able to say come to this room I will
show you all my
money as you say their money is doing
things for them recognize therefore that
another idea another aspect of abundance
is not that it sits is that it flows
when you create a flow when you put out
the idea of yourself in this way and are
willing to be equal to know to trust
without fear Beyond shadow of a doubt
that the idea of of putting out an idea
of abundance will allow there to be a
vacuum and allow there to be the vacuum
filled to create a flow in that way then
the idea will be understood that those
that are expressing abundance are not
stockpiling they are allowing abundance
to flow through them to do things in
that way therefore
recognize that is why many individuals
upon your planet coming from the
assumptions from the beliefs that
abundance is holding onto the riches in
this way when they come from those
beliefs and are about to experience the
idea of abundance many times they will
because they are not willing to do it
willingly they will in a sense attract a
situation that will force them to
release a part of what they now know to
be their so-called abundance to allow a
greater abundance to come in because of
the flow that will be created by the
release many of you will create this
release through your relu
by having something stolen from you that
is why many individuals who are very
very accelerated in the exploration of
abundance will automatically find that
many times they will have objects stolen
from them because they will attract an
individual in that sense who is
powerless in their own right and willing
to be attracted by those in that sense
who are exploring the abundance but not
willing to release they will attract
that individual to uncork the plug for
them in that sense and allow there to be
now the recognition if you are willing
to look at the situation in a positive
light and not a self-pitying negative
light you will then recognize that that
has been a release that now allows the
Waters of abundance to flow through you
for a gap created will be a gap filled
there can be no Vacuums in Creation in
that way you follow me there are many
manifestations of different ideas of how
individuals may allow their own
abundance to become Paramount and
recognizable in their lives but also as
we have said recognize abundance is not
just your monetary symbol any any
situation any opportunity that allows
you to Simply function as the being you
know yourself to be is an expression of
your abundance and many times you can
create a situation whereas you
previously thought you required money
for the manifestation of that situation
but now that you are functioning within
trust in your abundance you can
recognize that many times you will
attract situations that will
automatically Grant you the same
circumstance es that will allow you to
function in the way you wish to function
regardless of the definition for example
many of you will say well I am looking
for a place to live therefore I need
money for a place to live but recognize
as long as you focus on the idea that
you may only get a place to live if you
have the money then you may not allow
the ecstatic explosion of coincidence to
occur where a friend comes up to you and
says I happen to know someone who is
going out of town for 5 years and want
somebody to watch their house will you
do that free of charge in that way and
have a place to live
these things can happen and do happen
all the time when you allow them to
happen you will find yourself walking
exactly into the right place the right
time interacting with exactly who you
need to be interacting with because they
are providing a service to you and you
are providing a service to them and you
are trusting that the Universe when you
let it works that way and works that
simply all the time you follow
me
sh yes
there was a news broadcast this
afternoon that talked about a massive
body the scientists have just discover
this could you talk about that for now
briefly it is simply an exemplification
that you recognize that there are
doorways at the center of all
physicalized realized manifestations you
refer to them usually as black holes you
will recognize therefore that this is
true not only on a cellular Atomic level
in the center of every idea that you
call an atom is a black hole in that way
in the center of every cell in this way
is a black hole in the center of every
idea of a stellar system is a black hole
in that way in the center of the star in
the center of many Stellar systems are
black holes around which the entire
group of systems revolve there are black
holes around which entire Gatherings of
galaxies revolve and there is in a sense
a doorway in a black hole around which
the entire universe revolves in that
sense you follow me yes this is the
possession that allows you to understand
that it is out of the center of all that
is that all proceeds in that way when it
creates the spherical shell of the 360°
infinite unlimited Universe you are
seeing the idea of the bending and the
reflection of your Universe on the other
side because you are recognizing in this
way that you are infinite in either
direction around this Central doorway
which in a sense is a doorway into many
different universes many different
dimensions of experience and it is one
of the direct doorways through which all
that is expresses itself in this
particular unit the letters follow me
yes that and that mean that the mass
Consciousness is coming to a kind of
doorway and we've symbolically projected
it out into our universe yes you are
about to have passage into another
density of experience and so all the
symbols in your astronomical universe
and many other aspects of your universe
will begin to reflect the idea of
finding the central doorway around which
all revolves for it is always always
whether you perceive it to be or not in
that Express local it is always in a
sense through the one Central doorway
from which all was created that all
transitions pass through you follow me
yes does that mean that there will have
to be a whole new Theory now manifested
of course INE that so it's a whole new
idea yes and it is the beginnings once
again of the recognition one more step
that will allow what you call your
scientists to begin to realize that they
will have the unific ation of their
understandings of what they are calling
forces which do not really exist but
they will have that understanding when
they begin to allow Consciousness into
their equations they're already doing that
equations they're already doing that
this
much equations mathematical systems
doorways that is all based on the
mathematical theories in which the
scientists step by step grope towards
the answers right
yes they are coming to much the same
conclusions as many other individuals
who have gone within they are simply
doing it in their own unique
way
sure um last night you asked me um if I
received a gift I was on spaceship and I
said No and then afterwards I had an
idea of what that gift might be so I
meditated this no yeah I think this
morning last night this morning um I'm
going back there and looking into this
male's eyes and and oh it was this
morning and I received the gift that I
had imagined it was last night which was
um a hatched egg or a baby chick all
right and um I just wanted to tell you
that thank you for your own recognition
of the birth of many new ideas within
your uhhuh
uhhuh
Shing M I'm going to be faing illegal
situation this Friday do you have any
advice for me have a good time
for again recognize every situation is
fundamentally neutral you give it the
meaning positive or negative and
according to what meaning you give it
that will be the effect that you get you
follow me I do thank you very
much sh Bashar
sh Bashar
yes could you tell me something about
the constellation the Big Dipper and
perhaps uh energies that are there
or in those
areas our perception at this time
since in a sense this is a new Focus for
us is that there are seven different
levels of understanding seven different
levels of consciousness connected to
that area seven different levels of
communication that can begin to be
perceived upon your planet by many
individuals some of it will take the
idea symbolically of of crystallin
form some of it will take the idea
symbolically a vegetable
life plant kingdom in that way as you
call it do not take me literally this is
symbolic but it is expressing itself
into your realm in these
ways it is no
accident that some of the ideas that you
connected to what you call Early
navigation we're connected to this way
for some of the Consciousness and
communication coming from that area has
to do with navigation in a different
form through the energy waves that you
call SpaceTime energy waves the
electromagnetic Vortex flux medium in
that way some of this information can be
perceived from conscious
in that direction at this
time there are a few ideas of what you
may call guides from that area at this
time there is also a type of
self-recognition of
self-empowerment a way of meditation
that involves recognizing one's
self-empowerment particularly in nature
connections coming from that emanation
at this
time and it is unto itself a type of
spectrum in the representation of the
seven different levels coming from it
all the way from what you call
physicalized vibrations to
spiritualized vibrations it is its own band its own
vibrations it is its own band its own
range of
frequencies but it is connected to the
overall Association to what you may
refer to as the overall Confederation
though we prefer the term
Association this is our perception at
this time we would therefore request that if
time we would therefore request that if
you wish to proceed further the next
step is up to
you thank you do you wish to share
anything further at this time about what
you feel your connections to be
I have always felt a
connection many many
years always looked for that
constellation in the
sky and some of it in out of perception
has to do with the idea of having relied
upon it as we said for navigation in
past lives and there are many aspects that
lives and there are many aspects that
you have just spoken that enter into my
personal learning my my
learning my my
search
um there are many many levels there that
speak to me personally very
much then we will now at this time
express our gratitude and appreciation
in allowing yourself to be a valve for
that particular energy at this time so
that it can be included in the overall
makeup of all the Consciousness that is
blending within your Earth Society now
for the assistance and the aid of the
transformation from third to Fourth
density we will fight
you sure good guys um the throat chakra that
sure good guys um the throat chakra that
of communication is associated with the
color blue and I was wondering if the
idea of communication has anything to do
with the fact that the sky is
BL you can make an association in that
way you can recognize that the sky can
be a reflective symbolic idea of the
electromagnetic field round your planet
in this way that expresses the mentality
through which you are all connected
telepathically you can allow yourself to
exemplify that you are creating the
vibration of the spirituality in your
skies by recognizing it represents the
idea of Heavens to you in that way and
having chosen to represent it in a blue
tinge or a hue will allow you to know
that the access to each and every being
upon your planet is inherent within the
electromagnetic atmosphere that you
breathe that permeates the entire
atmosphere of your planet and can be
representative symbolically of the idea
of allowing there to be a heaven upon
your Earth it can be reflected in that
way from our point of view it is only an
arbitrary symbol in that sense there is
no basic fundamental
what you would call mechanical reason in
that way for why there should be that
Association but you can draw an
association from it and rely upon it
within your imagination in that way it
is a
vibration which will reflect the idea of
the spectral graphic breakdown of your
spectral graphic breakdown of your
moisture content Your Dust content and
in this way will reflect the idea of the
striving in your terms as you have been
striving toward the crystal clarity of
your own Consciousness it will be a
reflection of Consciousness in that
way okay thank you why is it been so
stormy and cloudy in the last few days
it's been very very windy is there are
there a lot more ships than usual it is
not so much the product of the
ships in this way recognize that what
you call your weather is a direct result
of your mass conscious
emotionality you follow me yes I do
all transformations and transitions that
will allow there to be a release of
energy in a mass conscious way will
exude into your atmosphere and cause
manifestations that you call
weather what do you mean by mass
conscious the combined consciousness of
your entire civilization creates your
weather through its emotional
bias sure yes could you comment in on
the um the all the emotions and
Consciousness that led to the earthquake
in
[Music] Mexico again we have discussed this idea
Mexico again we have discussed this idea
to some degree that localized phenomena
in terms of earthquake in that area is
specifically linked to a mass conscious
a mini Mass conscious miniature group of
mass consciousnesses reflecting upon
themselves the belief that they have
taken themselves far away from their own
nature and have jolted themselves back
to a primal level of existence because
they felt they had removed themselves
too far in their technology and polluted
themselves to such a degree that the
only way they could reverse the process
would be to wipe out the entire idea you
follow me
sure sh sure nice uh couple of weeks ago
or so you talked about the shift of the
electromagnetic field of the earth is
that the same electromagnetic
electromagnetic field that affects a
compass because of the magnetic compass
to work ni okay then would the variation
that is Shifting annually would that be
shifting at a more accelerated rate at
this time that to some degree although
you may find it may allow itself to be
slight shifts and proceed toward a
buildup of a major shift all at once so
then the charts that are used for
navigation would become obsolete nice
okay electromagnetically they don't use that
electromagnetically they don't use that
much of course anymore thank thank you
sh him I'd just like to share that
speaking of electromagnetic shifts that
one can really tune into what the mass
Consciousness is feeling at any time the
day of the U meltdown in Russia I didn't
listen to the news and in the morning I
was driving along and and I and I
thought well I'll tune into the mass
Consciousness today and see what's going
on and um I really felt a very strong
sense of sadness and of
that negative almost
energy and I thought that's interesting
there's a lot going on today and I don't
know what it is and then I found out
later on that that's what it was thank
you for your sharing and your
willingness to express that you are in
touch with the entirety of the mass
Consciousness allow me to remind each
and every one of you that you all have
that capability for you are all always
in touch with the totality of all that
is particularly of your own Society now
each and every one of you will try
translated through in different ways
different symbolic interpretations but
you all have the ability to understand
the emotional shiftings that are going
on and taking place and the interactions
that can result from all of those
interactions that take place on that
level that can manifest into your
physical reality you are all sensitive
to this idea and you are all becoming
more sensitive to that idea as you
become more sensitive in this way this
is why as we have said you will find for
now many individuals are beginning to
feel more of this sensitivity physically
in what you call your sinus area and in
what you call your heart area and your
solar plexus for these are here the
sensitivity to the vibrations in the
electromagnetic field and here the
sensitivity to the actual
electromagnetic manifestation itself
because of the collection of what you
call magnetite in your sinuses that Aid
to the idea of navigation in many
animals and in you
sharing yes uh you said that you and
your own Planet recognize people through
vibration ni you recognize people on
this planet by vibration yes uh can we
develop that
capability you already have that
capability develop to the point where we
can yes you simply do not pay attention
to it do you not already have within
what you call your linguistic the idea
of good or bad
vibes then recognize again it is part
and parcel of your subconscious
awareness of your ability to sniff out
the vibration of an individual and
understand their
intentions then all we have to do is be
aware of it yes you can find tun it for
in a sense s and again that is why you
call it a gut feeling yes
solar plexus in that
way the chakra of
intention yes yesterday on the news
although I didn't see it it told me
second one of the the major terrorist
leaders of the world um came on and ass
Su time very calmly and said that you
know they were going to Target Americans
specifically United States and in Europe
and U from your perspective
the way that be suggested way to
approach an individual like this now you
can understand that our perspective will
always be one of unconditional love and
as we have said you can suggest as we
dictated in this
way sometime ago the idea that you can
express to them that you
know they have killed that you have
killed that you have both discovered
together how easy it is for you to
kill ask that individual and and ask
yourselves if you have the strength to
love each other and in this way allow
yourselves to recognize that it is only
a
belief in your innate
powerlessness that says You must force
your opinion on someone else an
individual who believes in what they
believe in believes in the idea the
in believes in the idea the
philosophy then recognizes that if they
have true belief in their philosophy
they do not need to force that
philosophy on anyone for their innate
recognition is that the philosophy
stands for itself speaks for itself and
if you find any individual or any
country or any group of individuals
finding that they must force their
philosophy on someone else they
obviously do not believe in that
philosophy themselves for anyone who
believes in something in that way will
simply know that it will always stand on
its own Merit this is not naive
you follow me yes you can discuss with
this individual the idea of taking back
their power you taking back your power
and recognizing that you already are as
powerful as you need to be to have
anything you desire without having to
hurt anyone else to get it otherwise you
are saying you are in fact dependent
upon everyone else for your
reality you follow me yes and but that's
a conscious recognition that they're
going to accept that they in fact do
recognize the idea that that individuals
need to conform to a specific if you
wish to be more quote unquote pragmatic
about it you can allow them the analogy
that they are the sole and single
strongest support for what they are
fighting against for when they feel they are
against for when they feel they are
being
oppressed and they retaliate in a
violent manner against a so-called
oppressor they only give the so-called
oppressor that much more reason to
become that much more
oppressive you follow me sure they are
attempting to fight in their Viewpoint a
raging forest fire of Oppression out of
control but they are fighting it by
throwing sticks at it feeding it you
follow me sure in this way they can then
simply recognize that they
recognize that they
paradoxically are the single most strong
foundational support for any oppressive
regime for it gives the oppressive
regime an excuse to tighten its grip you
follow me totally
you yes um I've had a very difficult
relationship with my father and he
represents the idea of an alcoholic
right and um not having been very loving
and supportive understandably um
therefore I have been working on
building my own strength and my own love
all right through meditation but I was
wondering if you could help me help me
to understand the purpose of this
relationship can be as simple as you
have just stated to allow you to build
your own strength and unconditional love
at least on your end once you have
allowed that individual to reflect to
you your opportunity to be
self-empowered and know that you are
complete in this way you can then
reflect back to them their own
self-empowerment which can allow them to
take responsibility for their life back
into their control and not put
responsibility on a symbolic tool the
drug you follow me you are serving each
other allow what that individual is
doing to be of service to you and then
once you allow yourself to know that you
have gotten the idea that you are
self-empowered in that way and can
express unconditional love for all the
different ways that any individual may
choose to live their life being that all
ways are equal then you can take upon
yourself the opportunity to continue
your own recognition of your
self-empowerment without needing them to
be something against which you are
pushing to develop that ability within
yourself you can then say I am under my
own steam thank you for your reflection
thank you for your barrier thank you for
your wall that I pushed against to
arrive at where I am now I am under my
own power and I will reflect the
knowledge back to you that you also are
under your own power that I have
unlimited unconditional faith and love
in you that whatever you choose is
exactly what you need to choose to learn
what you have decided to learn therefore
by offering you the opportunity to be
able to learn what you are learning in
another way you give them the
opportunity to choose another way rather
than what you perceive to be a
destructive negative way you follow me
yes thank you
will that have served you um yes I had
one more question right while I'm
working on on this empowerment to the
fullest potential um now may I remind
you of something it is at its fullest
potential right now and always will be
you are only allowing yourself to
remember this that is what you mean by
working at it but you do not have to
struggle okay it is simply
remembering relax you know that when you
are trying to remember something it is
when you relax that you remember it
right so relax that's correct and you
will be at your full
potential can I still ask my question of
course as I relax um my uh my dilemma
has been your
what uh oh my situation yes your
fundamentally neutral
situation let see has uh been
deciding how uh to approach the
relationship and how to deal with him
unconditional love okay if you are unconditionally
love okay if you are unconditionally
loving then you are granting support
support
understanding to the
relationship and you will allow to
bolster itself upon that support and
reach the understanding you require you
follow me yes thank you thank you allow
yourself to know that it is serving you
it is not an interruption in your path
it is how you chose to interact let it
serve you then you can allow him to let
himself let it serve him as
well through your example of allowing
the situation to serve you you can show
him how it can serve him and he can
choose another way to learn whatever it
is he is learning you follow me yeah
thank you thank you sure so her
situation just to expand on it a little
bit um then the individual that's
abusing call it abuse alcohol or drugs
or whatever guys they're they're at a
point that they need to go through that
to learn a certain lesson they obviously
believe they need to go through that it
is not that they really need to go
through that it is that they believe
they need to go through that there is no
need for anyone to go through anything
unless they believe they need
to does that clarify the
idea yes than thank you
sharing yes you talked from the
beginning until now on one subject
abundance magnetic fields doorways
galaxies problems one thing is just
acceptance allowance well whatever word
acceptance nice
okay and you talk about accepting and
that we accept our powers and our lives
and our universe and our lessons and our
problems situations guys um all right
these are this is fine but what do you
do what would you suggest as the
possibility when you don't look at it as
a situation but you look at as a problem
how do you go inside of yourself to
learn that this is just an accepted
lesson or this is just an accepted in
whatever way your imagination tells you
to how do you see
this what is a way of seeing it what is
a
suggestion how to handle you want me to
give you a specific exercise something
that would help you me go down inside of
myself and see that this is all right
may I ask you a question yes for now
before I share something with you how do
you imagine you could do that pretend
well I I've tried it in different
spheres different times levels yes and
there are problems situations that uh
you come against that you know that you
haven't been given a larger problem than
you can handle all right okay but you
but but you can't seem to get past the
point of Letting Go perhaps because you
are judging what you are getting do not
be a part of the process mhm how about
that stepping back from allowing
yourself to know that whatever it is
that is
happening is a part of the
process that you feel to be a
problematic situation a block something
that lets you feel you are not going
where you need to go to solve your
problem but understand what you are
being given is always the exact thing
you need to be given
many times you will judge that what you
are being given is not what you need to
be given and then it will take the form
of a seeming block simply because what
you are being given is a direction you
did not expect and therefore you do not
think the direction is valid according
to how your ego thinks you should
discover the answer to your
question it is a matter of trust it is
all trust and it all comes down to that
one concept trust trust is all there is
that is the only thing you need to allow
yourself in this way to recognize and
realize any answer to any question
trust are you following the law yes sir
sir sir all
right ma'am in this
ma'am in this
way you may simply recognize that many
individuals when they come upon a
so-called block are simply not allowing
themselves to recognize it is actually a
brightly lit sign saying now is the time
to go left to go right but many
individuals allowing their ego to be in
the driver's seat say no no no I must go
straight ahead exactly at that moment because
ahead exactly at that moment because
your higher self knows that the way to
go is not straight ahead but to the left
or to the right and that is why the sign
is there at that moment that you become
stubborn the sign changes into a brick
wall now you can stand there as long as
you like and beat your head into it if
you enjoy that sort of thing or you can
allow yourself to say all right this is
an unexpected
Direction what you will allow yourself
to do by moving in that unexpected
direction is to recognize that at that
moment going left or going right is
exactly the way to go straight
ahead expectation is what says it's got
to be like this or
nothing allowance is what says it can be
this way it can
way it can
be and that is what paradoxically gives
you the Sensation that all of this is
actually this when you assume that the way you
this when you assume that the way you
want to go through your ego
gratification says it must be this or
nothing that is when this becomes
this because you are not going with the
flow of what may be an unexpected
Direction but it is the direction
nonetheless that you need to go in it is
Trust that
whatever whatever and I mean whatever
your imagination comes up with at that
moment is exactly what you need to
here's the word act
upon to allow yourself to continue that
journey and understand the idea of
yourself is any of this making sense yes
is uh what you're saying then is in this
trust We Trust in
ourselves you trust that the Universe
has provided you with all the
ingredients necessary to be completely
at any given moment any idea you desire
to be and you trust that being a part of
the universe you are able to function as
all of the activation principles in the
universe in that way utilizing them
allowing them to flow through you so
that you flow through life
life is the only process you need to
live more
life when you allow yourself to know
that nothing that occurs in your life is
an interruption in your path but allow
yourself to trust that no matter what is
occurring it is a part of the path you
chose to be then you will allow yourself
to gain and gather the actual experience
of seeing how the situation is a part of
the path you chose to be you may look at
it as we have said many times like this
a path is not what you are on a path is
what you are you can't be off of
yourself everything that occurs in your
life is a part of your path by
definition you cannot have anything in
your life that is not a part of your
your path by
definition there are no extraneous
events in
creation you follow me does this act as
some sort of assistance to you thank you
thank you very much for the willingness
to express your unique methodology and
the path that you are for in your
sharing many individuals will allow
themselves to glean for themselves
their own approach to a similar idea for
recognize if you are present in the
asking of a question or the sharing of a
statement there is a reason why you are
present nothing is extraneous if you are
there to hear it you can use it you can
ask yourself the same question that is
being asked by someone else apply it to
your own path or you can share and state
to yourself the same statement being
made by someone else and apply it to
your own path and you will have your own
unique manifestation of how that idea
applies to you in that way nothing that
anyone asks and nothing that anyone
shares will ever be
boring for everything that you are
present to perceive applies to you or
you wouldn't perceive
it thank you
sharing yes back to the electromagnetic
energy Shi all right that you spoke of I
have suffered from headaches
periodically through my all of my adult
life and I just when I think I
understand what causes them uh I find
out that that's not the case the second
time oh right and you mentioned that the
stresses that build up in the
electromagnetic atmosphere are perceived
by some of us as headaches is that one
is that one of the causes of my
headaches and that's have you also been
sensitive to the idea of visual or
auditory manifestations which most
individuals are not privy
to I have expected that always but it
but no I I can't say that I enjoy that
but I perceive
that what do you imagine would happen
should you allow yourself to do
so I think I would grow in my sensy why because
because
I I would love to because why would you
grow from perceiving something which in
your terminology your colloquial
terminology is outside the normal realm
of experience of life as you know it why
would you imagine that you would grow
from something like that do
share because I
would see beyond the camouflage or the
the uh all
right may I ask you another
question yes oh thank
you if you were able to as you say
See Beyond the
camouflage would you be interested in
staying in the
camouflage well for a
time I guess I mean I guess I would all
right how are you being of C us within
the
camouflage I'm trying to be as loving as
I can I'm trying to be trying I am being
as loving as I all right in what
ways practicing unconditional love
practicing when are you going to do it
loving unconditionally all right okay in
what ways will you apply physically or
have you applied physically this
unconditional loving service
what is it you
do resect myself as much as I can I keep
my for a living oh for a
living I'm an art director all right do
you enjoy it I love it all right I love
my oh very good very good now may I ask
you another question by all means oh
thank you very
much have you
found that your so-called
headaches have assisted in any way with
your
work I think sometimes I relieve
stresses around me through them I think
that happen do you feel that that is the
only way you can relieve stress around
you and why do you have stress around
you if you love your
work that's a good question well
sometimes there are like sometimes when
put new things into the show that I work
on yes there are stresses that why reach
very high levels why do they need to
reach you because I have to release them I
you because I have to release them I
have you do yeah why why is that your
job because I'm concerned with the look
of the show and that's what everyone is
stressful about at that moment everyone
else being stressful does not mean you
have to
be true
you do not have to pass those energies
through you in a negative
way can you not let them wash over and
around you and
Beyond being the bubble of Serenity in
it
all pulling all things together by
allowing yourself to be an energy
exchange system through which things can
pass by allowing yourself to be
transparent parent allowing all things
to blend but allow them to pass through
you
unobstructed you do not need
to in a sense manipulate them on the way
through you can allow them to flow
through you
unimpeded and you will glean what you
need to glean from them without trying
to glean from them what you need to
glean these energies that come to you
you don't not have to wrestle with them
allow them to flow allow yourself to
channel them
in Channel them through and out in ways
that reflect the harmonious synchronous
vibration that is a reflection of the
unconditional love you experience in
doing your work you do not need to
express or experience that energy in a
stressful way you do not need to process
it in that way everyone else's stress is
their choice it does not have to be
yours thank you very much no thank
you for expressing your
creativity understand that
creation is an act of Joy Of Love of
ease it is a natural
expression it is like
breathing so take it in
let it out and recognize that like
breathing the only thing it does while
it is within you is refresh
you not cause you
stress you follow me
yes thank
you thank you you are
welcome sharing
you sure ni uh there's a family in Wales
the Sunderland family and they have a
few children and there's a little
daughter that was about 10 back I think
it happened about
1977 and she had a face Toof face
encounter um with some uh space brothers
and sisters who she described as being
very tall and angular looking and uh so
did a few of her family it seemed almost
accidental she just sort of of that auto
accident yes but the parency was
accidental of uh for discovering them
taking soil samples and later they began
coming to her in her dream state and uh
are you going to ask me for a label next question one
question one
label i' had never heard of that type uh
for and I wanted to know I I'm in
communication with the author who wrote
a book on it and uh I was looking into
um putting it together for a film and I
the author had told me they were back in
communication with her the girl is now
about 18 years old uh in the dream state
here and uh I haven't been able to place
I'd like to you know say well this
sounds like play and this sounds like R
you would like to be able to say that
why I don't know just makes me yes
comfortable yes
why um why makes me feel that I I know
them better
why there certain characteristics of why
does needing a label be the only thing
that allows you to feel you know
them when are you going to trust your
feelings Oh you mean instead of the the
uh intellectual mental s yes
um that's what seems to trigger off the
feeling though I do feel a feeling and
an emotion towards them all right then
there seems to be some kind of balancing
of the mental wanting to have some kind
of information on it then go and ask
look at
her well she's a
lot oh mean
oh mean
like I'm going to wh give me her
address right
good this is only an
exercise in allowing you to utilize what
synchronicity is available to you rather
than running to me all the time for
labels all right thank
you understand also this is a part of
that child's
process and and it is something that if
you have the desire to interact with her
within will be part of the joy of
Discovery for all concerned good we do
not give away what is inside your
presence okay
okay
now understand also in this way as we
have begun to say now to us the idea of
labeling is what causes separation and
actually keeps you from interacting in
the event
itself go and find out what you need to
find out in any manner that you
can then the idea is that you will tell
me okay then you will know that your
ability to ascertain this information is
equal to mine MH and in many ways when
it concerns specifically the process of
taking place in your own civilization in
your terms better than mine for your
process is yours and not mine to
illuminate you follow me yes I do thank
you very much we can discuss this later
okay could you tell us a bit about your
Society What
specifically oh let's see are you I
presume you're not the only member of
your Society no so tell us about um are
there any social habits that people have
their they're different than ours like
we have the habit of shaking hands as a
greeting our society in that way is what
you would call
telepathic empathic more
precisely for all telepathy is actually
empathy do you have any physical needs
like we need food for our very
sustenance little our sustenance at this
time though we have a fourth density
bodily form that you would recognize as
a physical form sustains itself mostly
upon energy at this time though there is
a symbolic representational organic
substance that you would recognize as a
vegetable very small very much like what
you would call your Li of beine in this
way that symbolically represents all of
the intake of substenance in the
physical form that we require it is not
taken often and it is taken ever so much
less than it used used to be what do you
do for recreation what do you consider
many things what I am doing right now is
fun this is one of my
Recreations you believe do you have
competition between other members of
your species not even for purely uh
Amusement it is not looked at as
competition for each individual is
recognized for their own merits
separately in that way as the individual
and is not compared to any other
individual all May partake in what you
may call a game in that way to some
degree but it will not be us versus them
it will simply be individuals
interacting there is music there is Art
there is
exploration there is sharing of
Consciousness in many different forms
and expressions what about
schools no not in terms of what you say
to be the structure that you have made
them to be our children in that way will
draw themselves exactly to where they
need to be drawn and will learn as you
will say on the job for any adult they
will encounter will be willing to
recognize that it is no accident the
child is there and they will teach them
for all adults are the parents and all
children are the children of all for all
in our civilization are married to
everyone's no
exus no there are the biological parents
and they are recognized as such but that
is not something that prohibits the idea
of the child from forming their
relationships with all the other parents
that they have in the
society we always know where they are
anyway got do you have the same senses that we
got do you have the same senses that we
have are you limited by the body that
you're currently inhabiting to some
degree but in this way we also have the
ability to blend our Consciousness to
extend our senses beyond what you would
call the physical
for this idea is what is allowing my
ability to communicate with you to go on
right now my conscious recognition that I have
now my conscious recognition that I have
this
ability you have this ability as
well is your growth process then similar
to ours as far as
relaxing we are always in a state of
ecstasy you is the idea of growth
recognized or in a sense yes but we have
a very different reference of what you
would call a time frame in that sense to
us the idea is simply that we are living
in the moment and everything is an
eternal now we are enjoying what we are
creating ourselves to be and in this way
again we can recognize the idea of
additional expansion but not through the
process of comparison in the sense that
we are quote unquote better than we used
to be or worse than than someone else
you follow me yeah our recognition of
the idea of growth in that sense is to
Simply become all the different types of
perfect now manifestations that we can
imagine you are not going to achieve
Perfection you are perfect right now
everything that you do is a perfect
manifestation of the thing you are doing
it is no better or worse than anything
else you have ever done it is simply
different complete unto itself and equal
to anything else in its potential to
allow you to
grow and to
choose do you have what we what we call
emotions do you still exibit emotions
yes most of them are
Joy what do you learn you think like we
are of average 5 ft of your height white
whitish gray skin coloration wide set
eyes in this way the eyes are mostly
white but you would perceive them to be
black because the pupils engulf the
majority of the circumference in that
way of the eye the males will have no
hair females will usually have hair
usually be whitish though there are
exceptions in that way you will find it
to be relatively slender and Akin to the
idea of what you would call a cross
between American Indian and Mongolian
aspect though not exactly
either what is your art like there are
many different forms of the idea the
majority of it would not be what you
call painting but would be what you call
sculpting or the manifestation of energy
forms also tonalities music as you would
call it to some
degree will be the basic forms of what
you would recognize as our art although
again to us everything that we do is Art
life is
Art do you have what we term like
theater or media to some degree yes
although it is again mostly
spontaneous not what you would call to
be pre-planned to any
extent individuals will come together
and interact perhaps for the enjoyment
and the amusement of others who also
coincidentally just happen to be
gathered in that spot at that time do
you have books no not what you would
recognize as a book you don't sell
tickets either no we do not have a
monetary system
we are mostly now the idea again of
telepathy we do have a Remnant language
that we have shared aspects of use from
time to time that is from the time when
we more use the idea of vocabulary but
it is now in Remnant form and is usually
only used as an
accent you follow me yes can I give go
specific for me yes okay an example
uh let's say if you were to have a
telephone and you wanted someone to call
you and you were to give them that
message tell uh using tath would you why
would I need a
telephone all right would you need to to
telepathy give the idea of a person
picking up a telephone or would the
words be what would be transmitted pick
up or whatever it is other was any
thought it's the actual idea of seeing
an individual doing something or seeing
an object or is the telepathy
transmitted through the symbology of
words no not words no it is feeling and
image mostly emotions in a sense emotion
is what activates the idea that is how
we use them you have the idea to be
praic of a picture you apply the feeling
the emotion to it and that is what
allows the picture to be transmitted and
received motion energy
motion energy
motion are there objects on your planet
as like we have streets that the number
of people use that government we are
able to create those streets and
maintain them and so forth no we don't
not have need of streets I know but I
mean are there objects that have common
use yes buildings but they are in this
way created by associations of
individuals who find joy in the
manufacturer of those structures
did your Society does that answer your
question yes um is there a oh yes okay
it does thank you guys did your Society
evolve through the fear levels that we
are experimenting with no that has not
been our definition from the
beginning has our society done something
yours hasn't done oh many
[Music] things yes of course positive and
things yes of course positive and
negative in this way the idea is that
you are your own expression you will
always be doing things in your own way
even if you should have something
similar it will not be
exact your fourth density it's an
identification and it's assisting Us in
in Remembering if I'm clear about this
there will be people who will remain in
third density and will not make a move
to Fourth density you once made a
comment and please correct me if I'm
mistaken about this about once you get
to Fourth density that there will be no
remembrance or no you will not be able
to move back to third death oh you can
if you want to but you would probably
not want to I would imagine um there may
be reasons for it reasons for it will
include those that have in your terms
ascended accelerated and wish to be of
service to those in what you would turn
to be lower densities and so will
manifest themselves to be beacons of
light and in this way illuminate the
path that all may
choose okay um um not have you you have
not always been forth density you've
come from have you come through the same
gradual in a sense yes processes through
what through the first density to Fourth
density yes and are there people then
who are moving from fourth density to
fifth density yes we are as you are
moving from third to Fourth we are
moving from fourth to fifth so then does
the density unto itself uh only withhold
a certain number a certain amount of
energy as as if as certain amount of
beings can move with into fourth density
and then there will those density will
create the vacuum for those to move
into in a sense that can take place
within what you call a linear
progression perspective but not really
every density is infinite unto it
settled see all right what I want to
know though is is can can um you and and
the people you share asny with do is
there a remembrance of of where you came
from is there we can create that
Remembrance in the present yes you can
so you can see the lives through your
higher self you can almost look through
to everything that you have already
experienced of course that is open to
every being in the
universe yes I understand and so that is
what you're helping us to remember yes
is that ability to do that ourselves
yes thank you for
remembering you remembered what you just
said that's that's
[Music]
true uh we create our reality through
our beliefs our emotion and our thoughts
what do you create your reality with
knowing this just one facet knowing this
trust trust and noise and to some degree
we are creating our reality through our
beliefs as well but it is more our
connection and our trust to our
knowingness that allows us to experience
always the positive synchronicity of our
beliefs is your Anatomy the same and do
you live off your glanding system more
off the glands yes you will find the
idea of our organs to be in your terms
quite atrophied mhm and is your Anatomy the
atrophied mhm and is your Anatomy the
same your physical exterior exterior
yeah similar there are some differences again
similar there are some differences again
you would notice the first idea not only
in the coloration of the skin but also
in the idea of the texture in that way
it may to you seem to be a little bit
more silica
like a little more
pliable more clay like I believe he
would call it in a way like Su and
rubber not exactly but it will
do is this you the yes you yourselves
are becoming more silica like and will
increase in that way into your fourth
density as you recognize that the idea
of the crystal in form within you as it
increases will allow you to become a
more sensitive receiver of the energy
that will allow you to partake more
fully in Awareness in fourth density
manifestation for fourth density simply
means that you are conscious of more of
your energy you are more dense but
because more of your energy is there you
are more highly accelerated and
paradoxically feel less dense in a solid
way we this change our outer appearance
to some degree in time yes so slowly
aging process it will eliminate it
eliminate there will be an idea of
maturation but it will not be from the
same idea as aging you will reach a
certain point that represents the idea
of your Peak vibration and you will stay
there until you choose to leave the body
conscious ler mhm we have a a our
density is becoming more in energy and
less in Mass
yes once remembrance is whole and
complete is it possible to forget again
the idea again paradoxically is that you
will begin now that you are entering
forth density to forget your path
because you will simply recognize that
anything you need to know you can know
in the
present you are creating your your past
and your future from your present
anywhere the present is not a result of
the past until you make the connection
in your beliefs you can begin to
seemingly forget past events as you
restructure the idea of yourself in the
present and in this way simply allow
yourself to know that whatever you need
to know you will know it when you need
to know
it you may all take a short break if you
desire there can be for those who
experienced last night of your time a
repeat for those who did not for the
first time the sojourn onto the
spacecraft great for in this way it will
get you used to the idea you may take
your break