H how are you all this is of your time
that you create time to
exist so be each and every one of you
this night of your time
synchronicity now may I also take this
opportunity to applaud you on the
creation of the acceleration of your
fourth density
awareness the recognition of the
blending the co- forming the co-creation
of the
idea of the physical
experiencing of the continuing state of
ecstasy that your world can
become for each and every one of you
that has allowed yourself to create the
idea with any other being and even
within yourselves of the idea of your
blending of your own levels of
consciousness will as an individual make
a difference in the entire
of your
civilization do you follow
me no you have for several thousand of
your years given yourselves many
symbols many situations many forms of
experience and expression and
relationship by which you could
experience yourselves separated from the
idea of your own Creator hood and in
this way allow allow yourself to
recognize that none of these events
needs to be expunged from you they have
all served you each and every one of
these situations have gotten you where
you are today and in this sense you know
that it is all part of the understanding
of your willingness to explore every
single corner of creation that you can
explore because you want the totality of
the understanding of all that is within
you so that you will know that when you
make the shift within yourself to forth
vty to more awareness of more of
yourself you will then experience an
unparalleled feeling of
expression and activity upon your planet
that will allow you to know in no
uncertain terms that you have ended the
cycle of separation and begun the cycle
of
integration and that you can have upon
your planet what you have for so
long embodied in your mythologies
embodied in your music embodied in your
poetry the idea of living your
dreams truly and literally living your
dream reality upon your planet for you
have now each and every one of you and
collectively begun to understand that
the idea of your imagination is real as
real as what you have long considered to
be physical reality and that what you
consider to be physical reality is
nothing but the product of your
imagination but simply the one you have
agreed to share have agreed to call the
only real reality for the purposes you
are serving of yourself to experience
the limitation and separation of
yourself from your own godhood now you
have reached the ending of the cycle of
needing to experience the separation in
that way and you can give yourself the
opportunity for the blending and the
allowance of your own easy and ease of
creation you exist you always have you
always will you do not have to do anything to
will you do not have to do anything to
continue to exist you do not have to do
anything to deserve to exist for exist
you do and that is all there is to
it understand in this way therefore you
can begin to Grant
yourself the
same feeling of
birth of selfawareness of unconditional
love that gave rise to the idea of the
creation you are all each and every one
of you beginning to realize that you are
the creator of your universe that in
fact each and every one of you is your
own universe and that what you experience
universe and that what you experience
within the universe of yourself is
completely and totally a product of what
you choose to experience for your own
sense of growth your own sense of
awareness of the all that is that you
are are individually and collectively
collectively
now in this
creation of limitation for several
thousands of your
years once again allow me to applaud you
on the creativity with which you have
manifested the
scenario all of the reflections you have
given yourself to always remind yourself
in uncounted
ways the god that you are
in this way recognize you have
chosen the design of your solar system
to reflect the ideas and identities you
would be working out in the injection of
your soul into material
reality and in this way allow me to say
you have performed a brilliant L for you
will recognize that all the symbols of
the way your system is laid out and
particularly the relationship you have
created with what you call your
moon allows you to always recognize that
there is something deeper within you now
you have ascribed it and assigned it in
your separation in the various levels of
your Consciousness to what you call your
un or sub Consciousness but it is a part
of your overall Consciousness
nonetheless and it has always been there
for you so that you could see reflected
in that face your own god goddess all
that is energy
and so you would reach
out beyond the idea of your
limitations reach out and hold
contain nurture the idea of a relationship to
nurture the idea of a relationship to
the
Stars not only from where you came but
that you yourselves actually created
created
understand all that is in your
vernacular did not create the universe
all that is is the
universe all that is created you and us
and all
Consciousness within the
universe but in this way recognize that
you and all
Consciousness that was created by all
that is that Consciousness has created the
is that Consciousness has created the
universe for the universe is but an
expression an expression of all that is reflecting
an expression of all that is reflecting
upon
itself which is what you and we and all
civilizations and densities of
Consciousness and parallel and Alternate
realities represent the reflection of
all that is to itself all the different
ways that all that is has of looking at
itself allow yourself to feel the
expressiveness that you are of creation
for you are like un do all that is
unlimited beings and the reality you experience is
beings and the reality you experience is
only a reflection of what you believe it
can be you are now moving out of the
idea of the limitation you have imposed
upon yourself and creating new beliefs
new ways of perspective new points of
view recognize that everything you are
seeing change in your world at this time
is a reflection of a change within you
for you cannot perceive what you do not
contain do you follow
me
Shing sir yes you mentioned uh in
January the April event uh there would
be something said in February as the
second the elements for the second
Factor were coming into play and there
was something that was mentioned last
week to Morin regarding the event um and
wondering if that is all that can be
said in it for now or there anything El
you can tell us before the end of the
month in this way for the most part
recognize there have been some changes
recognize this in this case as in many
cases at this time there are
probabilities up to the point of when
the choice is made and so in that sense
it is unknown what the final choice will
be the probabilities that are
fluctuating that still exist in this way
are although this one has altered to
some extent relationships of the idea of
allowing your entire civilization to
make choices based upon interactions
with other what you call governments
upon your planet now I have said in this
way that what you have been
calling the Libyan government will
continue to add some momentum to the
idea of what you will be experiencing
but in this way it has diminished
somewhat there will still be and to some
degree it has already begun the idea of
some new interaction between what you
call your own country and that you call
Soviet Union in the March time of your
year in this way all these things will
come together all the probabilities will
reinforce each other so that with the
idea of the
sociological understanding you will
create for yourselves the reflections
and the symbols you will create for El
in your April month there can be a
recognition and realization that each
and every one of you have a
choice and can begin to exercise that
choice as to what type of reality you
truly do wish to experience upon your
planet not that you have to force your
choices upon anyone but simply that you
can begin living the life you choose to
live regardless of what anyone else
judges you should or should not do and
that this change within yourselves will
allow you to experience the the fourth
density reality that you have begun to
experience upon your planet
physiologically with the increase in
what you call coincidence
synchronicity and the experiences of the
simultaneous nature of all that
is now in this way what you call the
April event will in one way shape or
form involve the idea of what you call
extraterrestrial energy in this way it
may or may not be as obvious as you
think it might be but it will be there
and in this way it is only because it is
a co-
agreement with your Consciousness to
create that reality according to your
own timing of when you think you are
ready and so we
await and so we assist and so when you
choose to act so will we we follow me
yes I do thank you
Shing I have a sense that part of the uh
event that's going to occur in March
will be a reaction the Soviet Union has
to the Fallout from the spacecraft the
space all right understand they are in
that way matching you and you have
perceived in that sense somewhat the
idea of polarity for one of their own
spacecraft is now tumbling and will
enter the atmosphere in your March month
and it also contains
nuclear you follow me
um I'd like to talk about the idea of
separation with you before you mentioned
that the reason that Daryl is all of the
lifetimes he served out on the planet
Earth is because of one lifetime he had
175,000 years ago and it seems um from
information that I've understood from
you speaking about that Souls come here
to experience the idea of separation is
that a major reason or is that just one
of
many it is an overall understanding but
it is one of many in that sense that the
way in which you choose to experience
the idea of separation will go according
to the purpose that you have chosen to
experience it for you follow me in this
sense with regard to the physiological
Channel it was the need to experience
your methodologies of Separation that would
methodologies of Separation that would
enable there to be the offering of the
service in this way with us to all of
the beings in that Civilization your
civilization at this time of your time
so as to offer a choice between
the idea of positive or negative reality
if only
me yes what what I'm wondering is how
this idea interrelates with the
transformational age because it seems
like there's some kind of direct
connection with it and I was
wondering everyone is going to be able
to have the choice of of choosing Unity
or diversity in the transformation ages
there will be diversity and unity in for
density diversity as we have said is not
a negative phenomenon you follow me you
will have unity and diversity you will
have Unity because you will grant
equality to diversity you follow me you
will have positive manifestation of
unity and
diversity well as the transformational
age going to uh align the planet or the
balance of it in more of a different
polarity in a sense you will understand that the
in a sense you will understand that the
agreement to experience forth Dent
reality will simply allow you to begin
to see the Illusions you have created
and reabsorb what has been experienced
for so long as dichotomy into a type of
polarity that can be contained in the
center of your being at the same
time not this or that but this and that
you follow me
well this is the idea
of it is one way to express it yes my
understanding of that is
that people I think took the an analogy
literally of Christ coming back in this
age and arising from the dead but in
that time frame of your civilization
that was the only way they could
understand it but it's actually the
interational aring of Consciousness and
information self the recognition of what
you call the Christ Consciousness within
each and every one of you that is your
second coming okay and so that is in one sense
coming okay and so that is in one sense
the
dissipation or elimination of the idea
of separation in it is the integration
not elimination you will in your terms so to
elimination you will in your terms so to
speak eliminate the
effect of
Separation but that effect will be not
because you will be integrated within
the totality of your being you follow me
because you will not be focusing so
strongly on only one
aspect that is what causes the
exerience of
limitation but limitation the idea of
limitation in of itself will never
vanish from the universe you will simply
integrated within you equal to all other
ideas that you can be and because you
allow every idea including limitation to
be equal because it has served you then
once all ideas in your reality are equal
you will be able to choose from among
them of which you prefer without judging
the ones you do not prefer you follow me
yes I
do thank you
Ching guys you here to comment on the uh
craft over West Los Angeles last
night special allow me simply to
special allow me simply to
say that it was one of the
manifestations of the acceleration we
have been speaking of in this way that
will go towards the idea of your apro
you follow me simply
recognize let us say the idea is that
there is
almost almost now too much
recognition too much information to be
controlled you follow me
yes sh was it your civiliz was your
civilization participating in that very
briefly yes a majority of the civilizations were
yes a majority of the civilizations were
very
briefly is that the same group that was
in oh yes they're doing a little Global
and a few weeks ago as well
can you say the next city that
they up it will
up it will
increase and there will begin to be
simultaneous occurrence in many of your
city and when will the media finally
accept and that is up to you that's up
to us of course you are your government
you are your
media talk openly share of yourselves
share of your heart share of your
intention do not attack do not accuse
share and then once you open the lines
of communication within
yourselves your symbolic lines of
communication upon your planet will open
to reflect that idea follow
me thank you very much sir yeah um say
that you opened with the synchronicity
funny and talking about the separation
because uh today more than more than I felt in a
uh today more than more than I felt in a
long time it's been like a frustration
like in my heart I feel I want to do
something pretty you know strongly but
then everything on the outside says it's
like being uh hurdles or challenges or
whatever outside outside outside outside
I'm going two different directions and I
don't know you are going in One
Direction One
Direction seems like I'm working against
myself then because I want to do one
thing but everything else piles up so is
it you w to do well for instance tonight
I wanted to come here we get the seat my
heart one my car broke down and I was
having trouble getting a ride I was like
should I go shouldn't I go so I just
like I could have got my carfix tonight
but I said the heck with it last time
you said don't sh something so I said I
want to come here whether I should fix
my car or not then understand you have
given yourself not because you came here
but simply because you allowed yourself
to act without
making it necessary that other incidents
in a sense all perform the way you
expect they should before being willing
to act because you have allowed yourself
to do that you are beginning to change
your own
habits and you can continue to do so
yeah I was thinking it would be good
maybe is there any way I could give it a
shot in the arm when I decide which way
I should go
like I don't know just uh understand
understand understand there is no which
way you should go any way you go is your
right direction because you are going
there do you follow me yeah you are not
on a path you are a path you cannot be
off yourself so wherever you are you are on
yourself so wherever you are you are on
your path as soon as you choose to stop
judging all the different ways you can
be a path you will not need to create
the need to make a
decision do you follow me you are
creating need to make decision instead
of allowing yourself to be where you
are and trust that where you are
reflects where you want to be that you
have already made the decision to be
there or there is no way in the universe
you would would be there you cannot be
somewhere you have not chosen to be it
is not
possible you follow me well I find
myself in situations that I really don't
think I chose to be and that is not
possible you may not like it
there but you chose to be there because
of the way you choose to think of
yourself do you follow me yeah if you
are choosing to think of yourself as
someone who can be battered back and
forth by the tithes of whim in the
universe then that belief about yourself
will throw you into the tide pools and
you will swirl around wondering what you
are doing there not thinking you would
ever possibly choose this I could never
have made this Choice it has nothing to
do with what I think my life should be
about you are judging judging and
judging at every step every corner and
those are the dead ends you are finding
you are running into your own
judgment if you would release the idea
of judging yourself wherever and
whenever you find yourself to be then
you will find that those paths that you
become are not in and of themselves dead
ends you will walk through the illusion
of the wall and on the other side you
will find that you are right back where
you started can you follow me yeah thank you
started can you follow me yeah thank you
um one moment
simply simply simply
simply lighten up on your T do not take
yourself too seriously well you
had you told me to trust and I thought
it was another one of those trust things
but it feel like I was fighting myself
all right but you can also trust that
you know what you are doing even when
you are fighting with I wer you always
win understand that all right you always
win and in a sense more than that you simply
and in a sense more than that you simply
always
are you're don't to have to make it a
win when you make things a win you are
assuming you can lose and it is the fear
that if you do not win that there is an
alternative that creates it for you
because your fear is stronger is the
strongest overriding belief more than
the idea of simply just being
you follow me why is that you tell me oh
okay why why should you choose that
idea why should you choose to believe
you have to win thereby creating the
idea that you might
lose well hard to say no it is
not how has it served you I guess I must
been uh training myself with that or
something all right how has it served
you to do
that how has it served you to feel like
you can lose I get to the point where I
don't have to win or lose very good
thank you then allow it to have served
you and you will be done with it good oh
right thank you yes okay um I I had a
real interesting conversation with some
friends of mine on this very subject and
I was sharing my idea of of but may I
interrupt you for one moment thank you
now this will be a very good synchronous
example of simultaneous experience and
expression of and within the different
beings in your civilization many of
which are very close around you that you
if you are willing to share as you have
done can allow others to share and you
can see the overall pattern only because
your lines of communication are limited
by your judgment
have you not allowed yourself to
recognize that if you simply share who
you are if there is anything that you do
in fact need it will automatically be
provided by someone else who was also
willing to share please continue okay I
don't know if this is going to what you
just said but oh judgement
judgment um so this person was we got
into the idea of the best choice being
the best and I was Pro presenting the
idea that there is no best that you're
always choosing the right path and you
can't pick a wrong path
and they were this guy said well let me
give you an example me and my wife were
driving along and she said well let's
and we wanted to go home and she said
well let's take this way home and so he
said okay and they wound up on the top
of a mountain nice and he said now you
tell me that was not the best our goal
was to go home and that was not the best
way to go home because it didn't get us
home and so I presented the idea that
well you got something out of that
interaction whatever it was and he said
well then what you're saying is you can
gain thing from it but you can't prove
to me that that was the best that it had
validity in terms of learning something
about your life on an overall view but
it did not get you home so so I had no I
understanding it way that simply what is
being done is what you call on your
civilization mixing apples and oranges
Ah that's what he would be kissing me of
no other way around recognize this in
your terminology allow me to use your
terminology for a moment all right I
will use the term best for now that
happen may not have been the best way to
achieve what he had in mind but that is
not the point simply what is being done
by that individual is a judgment and a
comparison that that path should have
been connected to his goal the simple
living in the moment recognition would
have been this path is what this path
is it may not have anything to do with
getting home but that is why it is is not
home but that is why it is is not
connected to that idea it is its own
idea being on that path is simply being
on that path the idea of making a
connection that this path is not the
best path to get home really has nothing
to do and is beside the point the idea
is is that for them there are many paths
so to speak to have gotten home that
simply was not one of them and because
it is not one of them it has no business
being compared to one of them for it is
its own path and if that individual was
willing to live in the moment instead of
in the future wanting to get home and
only seeing validity if the path
achieved that for him if he would have
preferred to live in the moment then the
path for what it was could have served
him but it was not allowed to serve for
what it was but only was compared for
what it was not you follow me that is
the idea of living in the moment then
you will not make a judgment if you
simply find yourself on a path you will
accept the path for what it is and then
you will allow yourself to learn the
lesson of that
idea instead of judging it against what
you thought you may or may not have
wanted yes
simply it is not best or worst it is
simply different it may not be the path
to that individual's house
but so what that is not the
point now the idea is not to insist that
it is the path to his house or a bad
path to his house it simply has nothing
to do with the concept of a path to his
house in the overall direct sense you
follow me MH what have answered your
question yeah I I would like very much
to remember all this I will remember all
this thank it simply comes down to being
in the moment okay I would have asked
him what he saw when he got to the top
of the mountain oh that would
work maybe you know that's
3 now you can understand that a way that
path may be connected to the idea he was
exploring is to discover that that path
is not a way to his home and therefore
he will not take it
again and in that sense it is still on
the path toward his house because he
know that that's not and therefore in
that sense it is connected to the
original idea
bipolarity so it is still connected in
that way but aside from that it is a
completely separate idea and there is no
need to judge that it is a worse path
than any other it simply needs to be
appreciated for the path that it is you
follow me mhm thank you
sure um I am I'm experiencing a time in
my life where I feel very open to the
future but for my entire life I felt an
immense tie toward things past and I
don't see them clearly even in my own
lifetime now I don't understand what the
the continuity has been thank you first
of all recognize that only in your
present mentality are you creating the
concept of continuity you follow me yeah
there really is no time in that sense
except as you created to be you follow
me yeah you are living experientially in
the present you follow that is the only
time in which you experience existence
do you follow me you are creating your
past and your future from your present
therefore do you follow me yeah
therefore simply recognize in that way
that if you simply allow yourself to
recognize who and what you are in the
moment in the present and do not extend
the idea of needing to discover yourself
in the future or in the past then
everything you need to know about
yourself will be here and now instead of
out there and then and the fuzziness
will dissipate you and the clarity will
come in now this is not to say that your
creation of the search in the past the
search in the future is not valid for
you and not appropriate for you because
again it has gotten you where you are
and it has served you and you have
created it and it is a loving equal
creation to anything else you could do
and is not to be judged in that way but
simply recognize if you have come to the
recognition that you are here and now
and would prefer that all understandings
of yourself be with you now then simply
allow yourself to realize that your
present is not a result of your past
because you are creating your past from
the present you follow me yes how does
that feel um it feels like I'm a lot
closer to being certain I understand who
I am right now all right who are you
right
now well all right I'll give you a as
you say break all
right all right now before you answer
before you answer allow me not to tell
you but to remind you of something all
right before you answer who you are
right now allow me to remind you that
you are not attempting to achieve
Perfection you already are perfect as a
manifestation of exactly whatever you
are you are a perfect manifestation of
whatever manifestation you are and so
every moment of time you are that
perfect representation of that idea in
that moment of time you are perfect now
you always will be Perfection is not
something you will ever reach because
that is where you are now therefore do
not fear to State what you are now
because what you are now for now is
perfect and in the next moment it will
be different and then the moment after
that and the moment after that and the
moment after that it will be different
different different and always perfect
perfect perfect so take the weight off
of having to believe you need to give a
answer reflective of some future
Perfection you think you are not rather
simply be the you you are perfectly you
now all right so who are you well even
before you gave me that explanation
something in my mind I feel I I'm a baby
I mean it's like everything is very new
every good thank
you because you are in a very literal
sense every moment of time that you
exist constantly
reor so you are in that sense always new
yes very
good is that not exciting it's great
thank you I'm happy oh yes maybe to
thank you very much for your sharing has
this been of service to you if yes very
much so you then we will extend our
appreciation to you for your willingness
to be bold about the conviction of the
idea that you are thank you for your
gift yes um the question following up on
that realizing that you are perfect in
the moment yeah if you want to change
something that you are in the
moment is seeing yourself as that and
and as that as perfect is that uh
valid everything is valid
uh now simp we recognize that the moment
you see another idea of yourself it is
another moment and in that moment you
are that new you still perfect but
different you follow me yeah understand
that in one moment you did not have the
conception the next moment you were the
conception you follow me so in that
brief interlude between the moment you
became a new you the VI that is being
expressed as this conception now there
is no need to separate yourself from it
and assume that what you are imagining
is unreal and that you have to do
something to create a process to achieve
what you are Imagining the moment you
imagine it you are it you are that
vibration or you would not have the
thought you follow me
yes than I'm you remember me I talked about
than I'm you remember me I talked about
having an enemy oh yes and you told me
only unconditional love will change the
situation if you are willing to act as
unconditional love yes I
Tred there is a difference between being
it and trying to be it I agree with you
all right but I'm very imperfect oh no
you are not I feel un blessed when
learns to feel unconditional love when
is imperfect
why because it's the goal there is no
goal you are making the path long you
are making the path hard you are making
the path difficult because you assume
you will reach a goal and that will be
it learning and expressing yourself as
the unconditional love that you always
are never
ends in this physical life in
non-physical life it never ends you are
always becoming yet another facet of the
Unconditional Love of All That is and
expressing yourself in whatever way
perfectly that you choose to no it is
your choice to use your unconditional
loving Creative Energy to assume that
you are not unconditionally
loving change your
idea the longer you continue to judge
yourself the longer you will be judged
by others for they are only reflections
of your own self
judgment if you follow me yes love
yourself love yourself how do I do that
doing it acting like it use your
imagination all right let's do this you
have an imagination yes all right now
let us use your example of the so-called
goal for a moment
just as an
example how would you describe that you
would be if you reached that goal and
became an unconditionally loving being
how would you act how would you
appear I want to ask I can love a dog
and cat
uncond I love all
animal do I know what it feels like love
un yes but men are Jud more probably
like myself all right but that is not
what I asked you it's
true in this way for now play a game
with me right simply use your
imagination and imagine what you would
be like if you unconditionally loved
everything now since you have said that
you have an example you can use simply
for a moment if it makes it easier for
you allow me to remind you we're only
playing if you wish in the next moment
you can go back to judging but for now
lay along there only a game will not
hurt you to be unconditionally loving
for a second or
two it is all right it won't stick if
you don't want it
to you are in control and nothing will
force you to become unconditionally
loving of
yourself therefore do not worry we're
only playing a game therefore for a
moment allow yourself simply to relax
and have fun with the idea of what it
would feel like to be unconditionally
loving with everything and everyone all
right
I oh very
good then you have your clue but
understand that in the moment you can
imagine that you are it you are it right
now right now now you do not have to
continue to be it it is up to you but
you can continue to be it it is up to
you it is all based upon the
degree to which you are
willing to prefer that reality over any
other so allow me simply to say simply
being obvious about it that if that is
not the reality you are
experiencing then in a sense let me just
say based upon your point of view you
are simply not well tired of the other
realities yet learn that is all right right does
yet learn that is all right right does
not need to be a judgment that is your
path that is your way it is just as
valid as any other way and in this sense
recognize that your soul body your
higher self value your process your
choice of how you wish to learn still as
just as much of an enriching experience
to its whole soul self as any other path
you could have chosen as a personality
your higher self does not judge you for
the path you have taken for it is
enriched by anything that you do for you
are the product of unconditional love
you are made of love love is what you
are made of therefore Every Act you do
is an act of love and that is how your
higher self sees it therefore since we
know your higher self is enriched you as
a personality can choose to share the
belief that your higher self knows is
true you do not have to continue to
judge it's up to you if you continue to
judge then do not judge yourself for
judging and enjoying your
judgment and that will at least allow
you to relax into the unconditionally
loving way you have chosen to explore
the idea of
judgment what does eny try to
teach that you yes of course that is the
point right there you have got it all in
a nutshell the idea that enemies are
created in your mind as long as you
continue to label that idea it will
function as an enemy enemies like anyone
else are teachers and if you choose to
begin to look at it as a teacher it can
become a friendly teacher as well as an
unfriendly one and last time you told me to to
one and last time you told me to to
receive her and to put all kinds of
things on the table I did all that she
did come in when I wasn't there she
could not let let on that she was there
and now she has gone back to Israel all
right and I have decided to go to isra
lady right and try to hunt her up and
there is no trying I must talk to her if
you say so I must make peace with her
make peace with
yourselves but I think I must find her
and also make peace with her all right
then trust your feeling if that is the
way you wish to act out making peace
with yourself do it do you feel I am
successful anding her and making peace
with her would you know this there is no
way to know it is your decision decision
it can go
anyway now allow me to ask you do you
feel strongly that you are at peace with
that idea yes then you will
found if that is what you needan I need
it very much one
moment understand this
though and I realize that in your own
terminology You may wish to make it
difficult to understand but understand
this is our suggestion to you go and
seek her
out but there is no need to make it a
need to find her that is when you will
find her that is when you will allow her
to find you exactly in the moment at
which you can both be at
peace sessions earlier we were talking
about Karma and the idea of uh
experiencing the polarity of of
something uh If you experience a great
deal of what you consider to be positive
does that mean you will also experience
the negative no not manifestly in your
physical reality you contain while you
are physical always the positive and
negative energy the probabilities mhm
the idea of what you prefer if you allow
everything to be equal will simply
result in positive
manifestation you follow me yes so
you'll experience what you need to
experience but you'll experience with in
a positive manner as you perceive it yes
so there is no the concept sort of been
banging around somewhat at least the way
I'm understood is If you experience
negative then you'll I mean sort of like
a it had to happen karma is completely
self-imposed right now recognize in this
way as we have said that the idea of
playing Karma out from life to life is
not always literal the idea that if you
kill someone you have to be killed no
you can simply in this way let us say if
you feel the need to experience the
balance it can still be in this way
positive in another sense not negatively
played out by having your own life taken
although that has happened for each and
every one of you many times but you can
choose in this way perhaps to assist and
Aid the emotionality of someone who
knows someone who has been killed in
your next life and that will be your
working out of the
balance you follow me yes I also had
another question about your life on
esani uh when your civilization was in
third density did you have a character
like we have our our Jesus or our Buddha
that that type of of
Personality there was not that form
exactly of
symbology there were more the idea of
the archetypal energies in a sense
embodying themselves when we came to
recognize eventually as our own
subconscious and unconscious projections
the world Spirit of our World in that
way the idea however in this way was
understood when it appeared and it is
what allowed us to begin to integrate
ourselves when it
occurred we did not follow we acted like
following yes the the archetype concept
eved me though uh simply the idea that
you as a world Consciousness because you
have created your individual
Consciousness as to have levels
conscious sub conscious unconsciousness
you also instill that reality into the
overall Mass Consciousness there is a
mass un and sub Consciousness and it is
out of those that many of the archetypal
mythologies that present themselves upon
your world that cloak themselves in the
aspect of your own godhood to reflect
your own godhood to you use that energy
to embody themselves upon your planet
with you follow me yes they come out of
your subconscious realization and
recognition of who and what you are the
creator of all that is thank you thank
you yes recently um I've been getting
feeling like I've been infused with
information having sometimes a lot of
twitching going on in my upper and lower
lid and oh what I feel information
coming through and one of the sources
seems to be I'm getting the words ra as
in the Egyptian son God yes and I don't
personally have any you know conscious
knowledge of of what that is there is a
body of material upon your planet
already in literature form that you may
explore there are individuals here who
can guide you to that material after
allowing yourself to absorb that
material we will speak again so that you
can see what portions of that material
are reflected within you and how it may
delineate the path you have chosen to be
all
right um also in terms of polarity I'm
involved in a relationship that seems to
be when when it's on the loving end it's
very very loving and when it's on the um
conflicted end very very conflict right
and I as a preference I would much
prefer to sit in the middle and sit
Center and keep finding myself reacting
and I do a lot of visualization and
imagining of what it would be like not
to react right I'm I'm still it seems
like I keep playing the same pattern
over and over and over again it is never
the same over and over and over again
because you are never the same you you
think we may be giving yourself an
opportunity with each and every new you
you become to observe similar ideas from
different perspectives different points
of view so that you can round out the
totality of your sample if you follow
me all right the idea simply is that if
you wish to stop reacting then start
acting start acting like the being you
wish to
be Do not sit and think about it be it
act like it respond like it talk like it
think like it love like it share like it
be it do it become it all right follow
me yes you can recognize that there
still may be many things in your
habitual patterns that reflect lack of
willingness to truly take the step to be
the being you wish to be if you are
using your imagination allow it to show
you methodologies ways to act like that
being all right
sh I was meditating the other day and I
this voice kept repeating in my ear
Bernard Star
yes on well simply we have told you
about the idea of the Barnard system
yes now in this way therefore you can
begin to recognize that as you begin to
go into fourth density reality you are
are going to begin to form the network
of connections that you will have with
that planet in the same way we have
connections with you so that as the
serious civilization goes on to another
idea and we in a sense take their place
and you take ours they will take yours
and you will interact with them as we
interact with you you simply beginning
to recognize that these connections are
beginning to form even as your own
connections to Fourth density are
beginning to congeal
okay I was vaguely seeing pictures of it
what did you
see there was a star in the planet out
there couple around there and and is
there anything on those planets yet oh
yes the civilization you will be
interacting with is loose analogy
approximately in what you call your
Renaissance phase of
existence can you see them I I didn't at
the time well go ahead
I see an IM what do you
see relax go inward use your imagination
relax focus
in touch them with love touch them with
compassion and you will have the
pictures that represent the ideas of
their civilization what do you see do not
civilization what do you see do not
think about it say what you see images
of say the way London and England used
to look in the period you just mentioned
what I was
go through your own archetypes and see
theirs see through the eyes of their
subconscious reality for that is how we
approached your
civilization I don't see anything real
clear just more all right what do you
see all right describe them in any way
that you
can more like clouds
and some color some of them had colors
in nothing real real clear though what
is the
feeling
um soft feeling all right let me make a
suggestion randomly pick an individual
in that Civilization right now and focus
upon him or her what do you see uh man
with a deer all right what is he doing
he walking down a street
and like an app Street
carry something under his arm and
there's some people in the street around
him all right kind of like carriages all
right like a busy City street all right
what does this individual feel
like uh touch his mentality taste his
mind on his way to to do something but
it's definitely walking in a direction to to
definitely walking in a direction to to
meet
seems purposeful yes yeah all
right now see the individual in whatever
now see the individual in whatever
setting even though the image May pop
into another setting see the individual
looking Skyward do you see this what setting is
Skyward do you see this what setting is
this individual in now that they are
looking Skyward Hill all right very good all
Skyward Hill all right very good all
right where are you suppose
he's looking looking towards
uh this word whatever constellation we
yes yes
yes now do me a favor send love and light
now do me a favor send love and light
compassion and creativity to that
individual all right now break the
connection all right do you know what
you have just done yes
yes yes now
recognize that in the process of time
and timing that will be another connection
timing that will be another connection
that you will eventually explore all
right thank
you you may all take a short break
okay now the
idea of some
acceleration of
energy will begin to commence this time
of your time and as we spoke to you what
you call all last year of your time
about this doorway you are approaching
that you went through before and are
going through again it is
representational of a cycle a pattern of
repetition that you create in your mass
Consciousness to allow yourself to open
up to many portions of your
subconsciousness your
unconsciousness now whereas in Past
Times you have created this to be a
symbol of the idea of things that can
come out that are negative in nature and
attack you surprise you from within and
destroy you in This Way You Now
understand that for the past several of
your years you have been utilizing this
doorway in a positive nature to step
through to a new idea of yourself this
time is coming up round and about again
as you create time to exist in your
orbit around your Central
Star allow me in this way to remind you
it is what you call the eyeses of
March there will be on that date you
call the 15th of that
month some increase and acceleration in
what you call
sightings all right
great Anica
yeah recognize that you and those with
you in this way sharing the idea of your
exploration of your own channeling will
conduct one of your sessions on that day
being it that it is what you call your
Saturday in this way recognize that it
will be an open door for the opportunity
to recognize that energy will be sent
and you will now begin starting the
first of the month of the same name
march to feel an acceleration in this
way that will lead you to that opening
that doorway and you will upon that day
be able if you wish in any way that you
wish to express through yourself more
solidity of
contact recognize it is an opening a
time of opening a doorway into the
internal you a doorway into all levels
of your
Consciousness a doorway that you can
step within and meet
within and meet
yourselves when you do this introduce
yourselves to the selves that you have
supressed to the selves that you have
feared to the selves and the portions of
yourself that you can now love and
extend an opportunity to share in the
blending of the rest of your
Consciousness so that there need not be
any further in your life the idea of the
different levels of your Consciousness
that you can function as one homogenous
conscious being in this
way in what you call your day-to-day
experiential reality you can begin then since you
reality you can begin then since you
will no longer be creating the division
of being awake and being asleep you can
be begin to live your dream lives live
your dreams and you can form
disconnections in that sense from what
you have long considered to be the
continuity of your
past you may
find that in the forming of that
disconnection there may be what you call
loss of memory do not fear you are
simply breaking the continuity of the
idea that you can only know what you
need to know in the present as a result
of what you have done in the
past now you can begin to
realize as we have said your present is
not a result of the past and you can
simply recognize that even if you do not
continue to create the idea of memory
which you are still creating in the
present even when you
created but even if you do not continue
to create that idea you can simply allow
yourself to know that you can know
whatever you need to know in the present
at any given moment in any given
situation in which you find yourselves
in which you have created for yourselves
to
experience you all follow
along sh yes last week we spoke about
the fourth chakra um opening having to
do with compassion and third chakra with
intention and them coming together in
transition heart chakra solar plexus
chakra yes to be compassionate
yes and I moved um I created a positive
manifestation of that blending and Al
once before that and since then and
especially right now I'm physiologically
experiencing um tremendous like fever
burning and um idea that the organs are
actually moving and um a chiropractor
said the idea of a diaphragmatic Heria
which is
it's like the third area moving up into
the four
um and I I'm wondering about the pain
associated with it how I could
experience this all right simply ease
off a little bit on yourself in that way
relax into the idea of your timing dise
one final
reminder that with compassion not only
outwardly but for
yourself then those transitions can
occur within the ease of creation no
need to punch yourself through the
doorway can you I'm not aware of where
which personality doing which
personality the totality of you is doing
it that is the idea but when you say
lighten up oh in that sense simply the
idea still the habit of the comparison
between the idea of an old and a new
you allow the blending to be
spontaneous and in this way also allow
it to let you know that even when it is
spontaneous you still have enough time
to recognize what is occurring so that
you can ease into
it you follow me yeah could you say
something about the nature of the
physiological I also have other
different yes well simply in this way
any idea of fever friction or pain is
still little bit of what you call the
remnants of the habits of considering
there to be a difference between the
slower vibration of third density and
the higher vibration or faster vibration
of fourth it'll all even itself
out it will all
mesh all the gears will be to turn at
the same rate as you say simply you are
going through this transformation with
little bumps and jars in this way
because you are finding that there are
little blocks little habits and they are being
blocks little habits and they are being
kicked out of the way this is why we say
ease up you can move them aside accept
them within you let them
melt within the liquid
of your being become fluid in your
integration become fluid so that when
you encounter a block it will be as if a
encounter a block it will be as if a
block of ice and you will be the water
which through your warmth of compassion
will eventually while it flows around
and engulf the ice melt and integrate
with it so it will flow with you as well
carry that imagery with you apply that
to yourself and feel yourself to be the
essence of fluid
action let that fluid wash through your
system and ease the pain that you have
created in this way all right are there
any specific Suggs for I just gave you
one I
was why do you need more how many do you
want 257
you will never get around to using them
all anyway how many do you think you need I
anyway how many do you think you need I
don't have number good because there is
no number that you need you do not need
any you are your own process and what I
have suggested to you is simply one way
in which you can if you wish see
yourself if you wish to create any other
methodologies rely on your imagination
that is what its job is it is tuned to
the vibration of your own being and your
imagination will always only create
rituals and methodologies and
suggestions that are in syn with you so
use your imagination if you do not
prefer what I have suggested create your
own for you it will be right you follow
me yes thank you for thank you for
yours will you be willing to
reflect
creating this will be very pragmatic a
question in your how do
you no matter what in a sense physically
you are doing how do
you see what is your attitude about yourself
see what is your attitude about yourself
in terms of what you do for a living
loock I have a sense of see like
BL pushing against
a wall that
is what do you think you will find on
the other side of that wall when it
mes flow flow what is
FL the willingness to allow
problem problem all right can you sum it up in
problem all right can you sum it up in
one
word allowance all right which
means what is the basis for
allowance in a
sense start with a te te
yes Trust now the
now the
idea is simply that you come from a
place and in
your terminology you have made
connections to a past life idea even
though that is only still in the present
as a connection the idea of rejecting
portions of your own
naturalness understanding this way way
that when
you go through that
wall much of what is in the
flow will be
atmosphere that you in a sense will find
now in your mentality many foreign
objects within the more familiar you allow
within the more familiar you allow
yourself to become with the ideas that
are foreign the easier you will allow and
foreign the easier you will allow and
accept that you can survive in any
atmosphere that you do not have to
reject those
ideas that you do not have to create
such a
rarified atmosphere for yourself to
exist within do you follow me so
far now you also do not have to
push through that
wall I will also not tell you but
suggest this idea for
you imagine yourself standing in front
of the
wall it is solid before
you but you are solid before
it
slowly
gently allow your
face to come close closer to the
wall Closer Closer allow your face to
touch the
wall allow the sensations to transmit
themselves to your
skin warm cold hard
soft rough
smooth and then in your
imagination recognize that you are
breathing easily
deeply and as you continue to breathe
easily deeply joyfully
expansively slowly slowly
slowly push your face into and through
the material of the wall let it sink
into the
ball and bit by bit
allow yourself to begin to
breathe the wall into you so that the
more you breathe of the wall the less
solid it
becomes now do not worry it will not
dissolve all at once it will not let a
flood of what is on the other side indul
you take deep breath in and let it out
do this twice more
more
now at this time slowly back out of the
wall back out all the way out now as you
look at the wall notice the difference
in its
resonance notice it is made of
little bit more immaterial
material just a little bit less
Fair on your
side now with this idea with this
exercise allow yourself at any time you
wish and augmenting it with whatever
comes into your imagination however you
wish you may if you choose utilize this
suggestion go back into the wall and out
in and out until you are used to
breathing the idea of what the wall is
made of then when you are ready allow
yourself to poke through and breathe a
little bit of what the atmosphere on the
other side is you may step
back and go further any time you wish
and allow yourself to know that with
each breath that you take of the
substance on the other side of the wall
the atmosphere you will incorporate within
atmosphere you will incorporate within
yourself a willingness and an allowance
and a trust that within you is one more
recognition of another portion of
yourself that is no longer forign to you
and bit by bit you can begin to
explore the naturalness of every portion
of your
being every atmosphere every idea every
path every facet
every Spore of an idea that you are that can
Spore of an idea that you are that can
now grow Within
You Without
Fear of destroying all other
ideas before me thank you very
much yes Saturday of
CRA our understanding at this time is
that the majority of the connection you
will be witnessing will be
creating there are other connections
specifically because of that area at
this time and for right
now we cannot say
there may be opportunity to
explode within some of the other
individuals that you are sharing this
evening with some of that idea of
experiences in that area as well feel
free after this discussion to do
so all
right Sher sh yes you mention crash in 1947
Sher sh yes you mention crash in 1947
yes can you tell me um what civilization
they were promis little more about the
how many people are in there CRA the
idea basically would be being you would
recognize as what you call from
reticulum in this
way there were in
that three
beings what else do you wish to know uh
I think I'd like to write to the
government and request some more
information and I just thought it might
be say if I had they had more
recognition that we were more aware of
what that was may help them to share the
information it is not in that way what
you call
data that will open them up it will be
compassion of the way you feel about the
idea again not
again not
accusing but simply the recognition of
your willingness to let them know that you
willingness to let them know that you
know that allowance of that
communication to be
shared will allow
them along with you to be equally
self-empowered for now in that
way until you your
civilization can allow itself further
progress in communication with itself on
this matter details cannot be
allowed you will find that that craft
has been moved many times
anyway they still oh
yes and there have been more than one
there have been more than one crash yes
well was it the crash because of
conscious crash because it was part of
agreement in a sense but in the overall
sense in this way the scenario that was
created was an interference of the
guidance system of The Craft by what you
call your radar at the
time in a sense in your terminology it
was a seeming
accident some of the ones since then
were not
not
cons conscious attempt to use the radar
to cause the
crashes now recognize that since that
time in your terms precautions have been
taken and your device can no longer
affect those
craft but you do have
several sh yes there was a lot of uh
sightings in there one
moment the idea also that we have
already spoken of is that you will that
there that being your scientist's
dissection of the bodies will have
revealed few internal
organs you follow me yeah you said that
theyve toar on their yes do they have
like a they have a heart in a
sense uh that period of the late 40s and
the early 50s there was a lot of
sighting world that particular time and
then there seemed to be
about a 10 or 15 year period where there
wasn't a lot um can you tell me why that
was so there something most simply the
idea at first of your creation of the
idea you call Atomic
power then in that way there was a
creation in this way that was more an
involvement with you in the
manifestation of
emotional mental spiritual ideas that
were being played out so that you could
get used to that idea you follow me sure
that what you call the beginning of the
idea that you do desire peace rather
than W what you call your peace
movements oh yeah therefore our
interaction with you at that time was
more on the level of the idea of mental
interaction rather than
physiological you follow me yes I do
thank you nice Seth at one time said
that there was a possibility that our
government might put those aliens that
they have on
is that still a possibility it is a
possibility for they will want to In
This Way redeem themselves however they
can and take the attention off what they
have done by diverting attention onto
the existence of that idea now you can allow
existence of that idea now you can allow
yourself if you
wish to suggest other
methodologies rather than in that idea
what you would find to be in that way
disrespectful all right
right
sh yes the entities from how do they
feel about having their uhri his
uhri his
life now understand that they do
recognize what all of this is going
towards and they are willing to allow in
this way that to continue for they know
that it will be one of the things that
will form a fulcrum point
for the release of that
information you follow me they know it
will perform a positive service so they
are willing in this way to recognize how
it functions as
so you follow
me thank thank you then live ones right
now do you mean in your
custody yeah the government have any
live no why were you
laughing simply the sensation in this
way that very recently of your time in
that sense while there
sense while there
were they have in this way evacuated
their bodies on purpose because they
knew what was coming they have served
their purpose
purpose
no it was a Europe country
yes within the last 7 to 10 of your
yearses one within the last
five sh many government that would be
more spiritually receptive and
embarrassed embarrassed embarrass you
are your government I'm embar for myself
then that I would do not be
embarrassed I'm
sick you know what I mean you know what
I'm trying to say so stupid to take
communication yeah stupid to take a
communication from another civilization
and to surrounded in guns and feel they
have to the only way they can
communicate with it is with a scalp some
kind of objective out we don't have
enough courage to
communicate live communication are there
any my my initial interest was was is
there any other government on Earth that
you feel would be more spiritually
receptive there will never be only
one that is the
point the blending of the ideas of every
government will be what is spiritually
receptive there is never going to be an
isolated one toally yes is the idea of of
one toally yes is the idea of of
entities from other planets helping to
unify the idea of us as a race yes from
our plan yes yes but still we will not
meet in the overall sense with any one
government until you are all equal with
yourselves and then you will be equal to
the idea of any other planetary
civilization follow
me what is it that the governments are
afraid of that they would not share this
information which is very simple
recognize that you have created your
governments to be operating on the idea
that they are taking control of your
fears for you they are protecting you
when you create an institution from the
prospect that you fear that you will be
attacked that you need protection they
are both born of fear and so must
generate fear to survive and continue in
the way that they are thus it is in
their mentality that the only way they
will be in power is to continue to
generate the removal of power from
everyone else not realizing that if they
allow you to take back your power and
make them equal to you then they will be
completely self owered but your
government because of the structure you
have created it to be does not
understand self-empowerment as power
you follow me that is why when you take
back responsibility for your fears and
do not need a shield to protect you then
any organization that would be akin to
what you call a government can perform
its true function to serve you does the
government think that we will we would
be terrified by to some degree yes but
understand that that is their stock in
trade how else would you expect them to
think you have told them that you are
you have told them that you are
terrified of
everything protect us from our
enemies Keep Us Safe Keep Us
sound I do not want that responsibility
it is up to you you
say you follow me yes therefore of
course they think he will be terrified
they are
terrified I I am personally confused on
how it's possible for the IND idual not
speaking as the government but the
individuals who actually encounter the a
to not go home and tell their neighbors
or their many of them
do and they're not the be
well when you have created a type of
structure that says seeing is believing
instead of believing is seeing of course
they are not believed because the
individual to whom they are telling this
did not see for
themselves you have created the idea of
distrust therefore why should you expect
someone to believe you if you operate
from the idea that you could be
consciously deceiving
them that is the pattern and the Habit
you have created now you will find
however that there is one aspect of your
society that is allowing this idea to
change and simply that you use usually
do understand that if many individuals
are saying they are seeing the same
thing sooner or later even if it is
grudgingly many of you will give in and
say well all right there must be
something to it but perhaps it is
well swamp
[Laughter] gask gask
when individuals
allow themselves to take responsibility for
themselves to take responsibility for
what they create in their
lives then they will allow themselves to
know that anyone who would come to
them expressing The Compassion of such an
expressing The Compassion of such an
encounter or a situation in that way you
will be able to
sense the reality of that idea and you
will know that it means something to you
for thank
you what you were talking about the
Consciousness Mass Consciousness
government yes reminds me of the impression I've
yes reminds me of the impression I've
been getting this former government has
stabilized anyway on a down spiral
different on a spiral two similar yes
and I'm feeling that we will be so to
speak forced to be self-empowered within
only a few years yes because this for no
longer already it requires more and more
taxes to and services
right yes you will understand of course
in this way that what you have now so to
speak as a governmental structure is not
the way it was intended to be
anyway follow me you are not designed so
to speak to have what you call a
democracy you desire to have what you
call a
republic follow
me well what do you mean
by In This Way the idea of each
individual being responsible for
themselves and for their actions and
interacting with Integrity with all
other individuals I have a picture of small
individuals I have a picture of small
communities perhaps tribes and perhaps
villes town all right that is the way
you conceived of it then but now as you
say you are in your own terms a global
village you can function like one all it
takes is trust and then you will
experience what we call the ecstatic
explosion of synchronicity and
coincidence that will allow each and
every one of you to function of service
to every other being on your planet
always being exactly when and where you
need to be to provide the service that
is required by those you interact with
and only being able to interact with
those beings that the service is is
provided for and that can provide
similar services to you that you require
always interacting with only whom you
need to interact to have the services
exchanged in a synchronous Manner and
that is why on our civilization we do
not need the idea you call Monetary
Exchange politics or any other
institutions of that nature for all
takes care of itself in synchronous
movement as we are willing to be
serviced and attract only those
individuals with whom we can be of
service to and who can be of service to
us it is automatically functioning and
that in a sense is the
idea basically of the so-called Republic
of the so-called communistic Society
they are both one and the
same you are experiencing the two
polarities the two negative polarities
of those ideas within yourself and
allowing yourselves to represent in each
other with the idea you call your United
States your Soviet Union the expression
and experience of in each other what you
fear in
yourselves you follow
me that is why you have those
polarities what you fear in yourselves
they express what they fear in
themselves you express but you are both
doing it in negative ways du two your
TS this is
changing you are beginning to
communicate more openly more
willingly and in this way you will
understand that at this time
symbolically you have formed even if you
must at this time maintain the so-called
structure of the governments that you
are used to you have formed individuals
at the Pinnacles of each that already
know each
other you follow
me therefore they are working together
from a sense of
familiarity and this can be utilized by
each and every one of you to recognize
that in your idea of having so to speak
put them there you are your own
government and you have decided together
that you will allow yourselves all to be
representatives of your own realities they
realities they
know I did not understand that they have
connections other than the sa men of yes
did you stand
no now if you wish to think of it this
way let us say it will not hurt to say
they have interacted in what you call
pathwise but that will not exactly
explain the whole essence of the idea
and for now simply allow yourself to
feel that Essence and express it and
then you will know what the connections
are
CH uh someone change the topic um change
the topic have we been speaking of one topic
topic have we been speaking of one topic
the direction oh why um you spoke a few
weeks [Music]
[Music]
ago1 and uh and I've been thinking about
itous specifically whether it's involved
with uh part of Cl or or is it Fusion
driver or is it not Fusion as you
understand it at all or is it
part it is a part of the
dispersion shell that allows there to be
the channeling of the stepped up light
energy and the creation of the field
round and about it is a sense what is
used as the
lens now this is why you understand that
the majority of spacecraft that you
encounter in this way are dis form and
it is the hole that is made of this
magnesium for it is that whole lens
shape that allows there to be the
dispersion of the energy round about the
craft in a lenslike manner so that the
field is stable what level of energy is
actually required to to activate the
shell in what you call the idea of
microwave energy
G 10 to the 14th
power now this does not mean you cannot
achieve to some degree this effect on
smaller scale but this is simply the
average of the expression being
channeled through the majority of what
you call
scoutcraft the terminology is not within
the physiological Channel memory allow
me to express in this [Music]
way what you perceive to be an
output what you call your highest
setting in what you
call your microwave device your oven
[Music] yes times [Music]
no
[Music] no
that to the 14th yes all right um right um
[Music]
now do not concern yourself with the
achievement of that level of energy it
is not necessary for operation at
first you can simply allow
yourself to experiment with the idea of
the rotational
masses as we have described
them or any idea of the creation of
crystallin matrices as have discussed them for now
matrices as have discussed them for now
and the
exploration of the latent etheric energy
in the substance you call
Gold along with your magnesium and
crystalling B simply explore along these Avenues and
B simply explore along these Avenues and
what you call quasy crystallin plastic
Metals see how they absorb and
contain different kinds of
electromagnetic energy and when
stimulated in certain ways perhaps by
light perhaps by electricity can
release that energy from their
crystallin structures altering their
crystallin structures back and forth
back and forth back and
forth to become matter energy matter
energy matter energy and exist
continually in a quasy material plasma
state so to speak but it is not in that
way hot as you would understand it it is
cold
it is in that sense cold fusion but not
Fusion as you understand
Fusion it is the
fusion of templates of
[Music] matri the form upon which something else
matri the form upon which something else
takes its
shape the idea of the underlying energy
pattern that gives substance and shape
to your threedimensional
Universe the interaction and
interception of 90° out of phase
portions of the template will allow
there to be a quasi planar
existence to an object at the focal
point in which it does not have to exist
in one particular reality or another and
can in that way slip through all
realities you follow me
that will do for now
sh I'm s uh I found it interesting I
read the paper the other day that
garbach had had uh bypassed our usual
governmental channels and had rented a
or bought a full page ad in New York
Times saying that uh he was willing to
have Russia the nuclear free by the year
2000 and would allow on-site inspection
nice thank you
howal how we get the we how do you get
to the point all right go
ahead uh how how how how all right go
ahead
who what where when why how live now
that's how
ni it does not make sense to you does it
no because you think it is too
simple I don't even understand I mean
I've never experienced living now oh yes
you have yes you have yes you have have
you ever been ecstatic
yes well in that moment of ecstasy were you
well in that moment of ecstasy were you
not completely focused on the idea that
was happening to you right then and
there no concerns for the past who cares
what's coming up tomorrow right now I am
ecstatic do you follow me yeah that
how living that way is the
expression of
trust follow
me yes no maybe yeah yeah but all
right first of
all there is no need to judge the path
you are on you are as you are expressing
yourself now first of
now first of
all second of
all what in your
terminology in your definition what does
it mean to be in the
moment exactly what you're doing as well
as you do without wor about tomorrow
right and all do you do that
occasionally all right would you like to
do it more often yes all right go
ahead now recognize recognize the little
way that went in there into your
mentality really if you will allow
yourself to stop and look at it what
really prevents you from doing it as
often as you wish
nothing if you have done it once you can
do it again anytime you
wish your present is not the result of
your past so at any moment you choose to
be ecstatic in the moment you do not
have to create uh-oh connections to the
past that block
me it is up to you you do not have to do
that maybe you like
to do you like to that's what I'm afraid
of
afraid why should you be
afraid you think you are not controlling
that to say you are afraid of that means
you think there is a portion of your
Consciousness that is not under your
control and that is not so well it may
seem so but you are in control of
creating the outof control
feeling you are creating a feeling of
being out of control do you know that I
know that then if you know that you know
you are really in control and you are
simply playing a game with yourself the
game of being out of control oh very
much fun
sometimes very
exciting so sometimes you allow yourself
to create the game of being out of
control because when you create that
kind of panic that also is one way to be
in the
moment when you are
panicking oh you are in the
moment you follow me therefore ecstasy
Panic which
way positive negative manifestation same
energy ecstasy panic
choose which way you wish to channel the
idea as the being that you are you are
using the same energy anyway might as
well be
positive so in other words when you feel
anxious it can be
excitement is the same
energy anxiety is simply looked at
through negative eyes
all right how about
this you have a choice of having a
negative or a positive attitude about
anything you
experience now why not choose the positive attitude
now why not choose the positive attitude
if it is in your terminology that the
situation is not going to change anyway
well why not at least enjoy it while
you're doing it I guess there's always
this fear that maybe if I had at I would
change it all right why is that a
fear well if I stay with this attitude
then I don't to experience what I would
get with that at how do you know what
you are missing if you do not contain
it if you do not feel it when you talk
about it you are obviously sensing
something that you are talking about to
me the moment you conceive of that idea
that you are making the comparison with
you are that
idea you follow
me you are saying I am the idea of
ecstasy and I choose not to think that I
am the idea simply is that if you can
perceive an idea you are the idea if you
can even think of the concept of ecstasy
then in that moment of the conception
you are
ecstatic why change it
good that implies
despair do you follow me
now to need to Hope means you are
fearful that your trust is not
enough but trust is all there is
that is all that creates your entire
reality trust everything you experience even
trust everything you experience even
your negative reality is the product of
your trust you elaborate on
trust you elaborate on
trust there is really not much to
elaborate on it is very simple it is
your willingness to
express the fundamental right that you
have to
exist you follow me
uh you do not have to do anything to
deserve to exist you exist therefore you
do not have to prove yourself to
continue to exist in any way that you
choose to trust that since you are here now you
to trust that since you are here now you
always will be you have all the time in
the universe because you're creating
it so where are you rushing to relax
enjoy yourself Trust that you know what you
yourself Trust that you know what you
are
doing the only reason that you create
Panic is because you don't think you
know what you're
doing but you do or that you don't trust
same
thing you follow me yes you have created
the idea of separating yourself from
your knowing self trusting yourself is
simply knowing that you are responsible
for everything in your reality that you
experience responsibility does not mean
blame it means you have free choice if
you have created everything that you
have experienced then that means you can
create anything you follow
anything you follow
me well trust that it has always worked
yes it is working right now and it will
never stop
working even when you create the idea
that you are not creating your reality
you are still creating
that it always comes back to you always
you are the
Creator period oh yes oh yes no yes no
yes no yes I
know thank you thank
you yeah I have a friend brought here
and she back
she oh all
right then be bold in your fear ask the
question very fearfully all
right I I've been in a relationship that
has involved a lot of affection and a
lot of anger and I have pulled away from
it because I feel that bring out a lot
of a lot of negative things and things I
don't myself so and my my question is I
I figure either this is just the wrong
person for wrong or it has brought out
ideas in you that you have refused to
look at so it has served its purpose
hasn't it it has shown me that I have been un
it it has shown me that I have been un
willing to be inally Ling all right and
I question how I can I'm willing be
unconditionally Ling to a
mate to a mate yeah to a man with woman
simply allow yourself first of all to
know that you are unconditionally the
product of unconditional love you are
made of unconditional love and you have
maleness and you have femaleness within
you allow your unconditional lovingness
to extend to the maleness and femaleness
within you and marry them within you
then you will
attract if you need to a representative
symbol in the form of another
individual into a relationship in which
you can share your already acknowledged
completness you follow
me if you create relationship because
you think you need a relationship in
order to Feel Complete then the
relationship you have created will only
reflect to you your belief in your own
incomp complete
completeness so they will seem
incomplete and will bring up within you
all the portions of yourself that you
have refused to look at that is keeping
you from being aware that you are
complete so it has served its loving
purpose by showing you all these things
now simply allow yourself to integrate
them to accept them as valid to see how
they have served you marry all those
ideas equally within you allow them all
to be valid and you will attract a
situation that that will reflect that
idea it may or may not be the same
individual but it will not matter if it
is or not for if they choose to change
to reflect the new idea of yourself that
you are creating then everything will be
in your terms just fine if they choose
not to they will go on their way and you
will attract someone else who will
reflect that to you and you will still
fill all of those needs you follow
me recognize in this way that the idea
is akin to what we have spoken before or
that you call soulmates many individuals
feel that if only I could find my
soulmate oh everything would be
wonderful but the idea is if you know
everything is wonderful then you are
vibrating on the level that attracts the
soulmate that is a reflection of your
sense of
completeness you follow me will that
have been of some
assistance thank you very much for the
willingness to explore and
share all that you are for everything
you do is an act of love and a
gift what density is
time in this way it is usually the
product more or less of third density
reality though to some extent it can
extend into
forth in a different way but it is is
mostly the idea of third
density you follow
me in terms of the actual sensation of
the separated moments there is a fourth
density time but it is more synchronous
more simultaneous more motion
simultaneous more motion
oriented more
active acceleration but more the
acceleration but more the
let us say lack of sensing of things
taking much time to occur it is less the
experience of time and more the
experience of
timing you follow me timing being the
events the
interactions that you chose to be in
physical time more the
time more the
simultaneous synchronous sharing of
events rather than the actual experiencing of
rather than the actual experiencing of
the passage of time except in the most
General overall feeling follow
[Music] me will that have answer good
me will that have answer good
question are you
sure fun sh Sean yes
um uh just recently I I went over to
Chris Morin for the meditation evening
and I had a very strong intuitive sense
that I need to bring a female friend of
mine because she needed to meet chis and
I just knew that this was necessary
right okay so anyways I brought her over
and I didn't say anything to either one
of them and right when she walked up to
the door and Chris opened it she said
she looked up at the stars and she said
I feel like I'm from the
FES how do you feel and Chris Chris said
I was just feeling like that is where
I've been from the whole day what a
coincidence okay so anyway they they hit
it off real
well what I'm wondering is okay is is my
higher self first of all was did it
already experience that and that's how
it knew it or is it communic in a sense
yes okay and then is it also that I have
communicated with their higher cells
same thing okay can you can you explain a
thing okay can you can you explain a
little bit to me nope you are asking for
separation and it is all one thing you
know and understand the event exactly as
you need to you understand it through
the actual experience there is no need
to scatter it into its components again
you put it together in order to create
it why break it
apart you follow me it is all the
blending of the Consciousness that you
are here the Consciousness that you are
there their Consciousness your
Consciousness it is all all an action
and a creation of the overall event that
you are all
together thank
you it is motion
motion thank you yes can you talk a
little bit about the effect of Hal's
comet is happening right now today
just's not so much the effect of H's
Comet it is the idea of you creating the
effect for yourself and creating a
symbol to reflect the idea that you are
stepping through into another cycle the
idea of comets represent that type of
periodicity of
cyclic and in this way you are giving
yourself with this symbol many ideas it
will be Paramount in the April month
that will reflect a change
sociologically upon your planet in this
way the beginning of the movement into
fourth density also understand at this
time it is a reflection of the idea of
your average lifespan in its period of
76 years in this way this will now
change from this point forward it is our
perception at this time that your
civilization will not experience that
Comet again for it will have served all of its
again for it will have served all of its
purposes
told it is a doorway it is a gateway a
reflection of you willing to step into a
higher idea of
yourselves follow me
thank [Music]
you guys is there any particular uh area
that uh you would recommend to see some
of these sighting for the March [Music]
[Music]
only if you do not take me
[Music] literally all right all right and if you
literally all right all right and if you
follow your own Instinct and your own
imagination all right thank you
[Music] Malibu Malibu
son
Diego is that too far [Music]
[Music]
There Will Be Few over your own
[Music] City what about oh
the our perception is that while not
improbable more the area you call
[Music]
Baker the other even you were telling
maren about bringing three of certain
different um herbs and Etc and what what
I got from that was you were saying by
her putting out certain energy she could
attract fighting did I get that
correctly in a sense so can can we like
put out a certain energy to be able to
attract the science to where we are you
can use your imagination as long as you
do not put expectation upon it for what
you create will attract what you need
whether it is a sighting or not well
what I'm wondering is is that
communication reive oh yes it is
received but it is returned in the way
your higher self says it needs to be
returned not the way your physiological
ego structure expects it to be return
follow thank you there will be in your
terms a few more minutes
remaining sh I just wanted to say that your
sh I just wanted to say that your
being so generous with your time and
your M my
time I have no
need I have no need for patience I enjoy
every moment with all of you I do not
need to be generous in that way I am
expressing the essence of my
being well I appreciate you all very
much thank you for your your willingness
to cocreate this
interaction for it is very exotically
loving experience to
us this is my no my no
matter
I'm all right although there is no such
thing as objectivity [\h__\h] go
ahead I just wanted to well thank you
you of course
realize that nothing that I am saying
needs to be accepted by you that is the
whole idea I in your terminology am
successful in my job when you do not
need me the idea is simply to remind each and
me the idea is simply to remind each and
every one of you that you have all the
answers and you are self-empowered in
your own free will to create the lives
you wish you have co-created this idea
with us and with many other energies in
this way simply as one more way you have
of experiencing and expressing different
ideas of the relationship of yourself to
yourself and in this way we enjoy the
interaction with you in this way but it
is not something that you need to do to
Simply something you have chosen to need
to do and you can simply choose to
interact in other ways and recognize
that you always attract yourself to any
Endeavor for your own reasons and in no
way shape or form are your reasons in
any any any stretch of the
imagination they do not need in this way
to be the same reasons as anyone else's
reasons we thank you for your
willingness to interact to share of the
being that you are for any expression as
we have that you have to share is a gift
an act of love and a revelation of one
more facet of all that is one more way
that all that is can look at itself is
there something else that you would wish
to
share um I don't
right all right the idea of dentity can
be explained by analogy in this way are
you familiar with the idea of what you
call your visible spectrum of
light do you recognize that there are
let us say vibrational patterns of light
that are invisible to
you what you call ultraviolet you
following you do not perceive it
directly with your eyes yes all right
this is a rough analogy of the idea of
density vibration in other words whole
reality what you consider to be your
physical Universe reality vibrates at a
certain level let to say frequency or
pitch out of the homogeneous one energy
of creation all realities are created
out of that one vibration by varying the
different vibrational pitches and these
variances become whole universes
everything is simply a matter of
different vibrations of one homogenous
Primal energy you follow me so far
therefore the idea of different
densities is simply different levels or
planes or different frequencies Each of
which are invisible to the other but
when you accelerate the idea of yourself
yourself also only being a collection of
the idea of frequencies in that way or
in other words the reality of yourself
that you experience as a physical
reality being an extension of your
Consciousness that expresses itself
along a certain wavelength when you
change the idea of yourself it is like
tuning yourself to a different frequency
and so you experience the reality that
is representative of that frequency
fourth density represents the
acceleration of your awareness of
yourself so that you become more aware
of more of yourself more of yourself as
all that is in that way your
relationship to the idea of the Creator
in that sense the all that isness of
yourself it is the ability now that you
have third density which is the
representation of existing in space
existing in time existing with polarity
third density being the ability to in a
sense look at yourself as you said so to
speak objectively but that is only an
illusion everything is subjective but
the ability to create the illusion of
objectivity is one of the ideas of third
density that you can stand outside
yourself and look back or look upon a
situation seemingly outside of yourself
all of this is from you all of your
reality that you experience is from you
it is you it is a part of you fourth
density reality will allow you to
experience your reality as a part of you
because you are more aware of more of
yourself and are actually able to
physically perceive what you have for so
long considered to be outside yourself
as actually a part of you in this way
because fourth density is not only the
idea or the ability to stand apart and
look at yourself or back at yourself it
is the ability to look through yourself
and see all the reasons and all the
illusions that you have created to
experience this sense of objectivity or
separation am I making myself C
yes I understand what you're saying
therefore what is second what is thank
you the idea of first second third
fourth fifth sixth and seventh density
are Akin again to the seven color
vibration the seven planes of existence
each is more expanded and more rarified
in that way first density will be the
idea so to speak of what you call the
energy mineral vibration the single idea
of the line linear motion in that way
and and the expression of linear
Consciousness in the sense that you
would understand there to be the natural
state of mineral the existence of
Crystal and form in that way second
density will be the idea most often
expressed by what you ter to be the
vegetable Kingdom in this way the idea
of growing life in that way expanded in
another dimension above the mineral in
that sense and will contain some aspects
of animal Nest although that also
extends into third density as well in
this way it is the expression of only
the linear motion and the planer motion
but the volumetric motion as well for
therefore understand that in third
density that is why you can for the
first time step up and out and look back
at yourself because there is now an up
and a down relationship to your
Consciousness and you expand yourself in
the idea of time in space fourth density
will be the progression of the idea of
time in a timing sense the ability to
you see through the illusion of the
first three volumetric XYZ coordinates
in this way recognizing them simply to
be a structure an illusion a skeleton
that you have expressed your reality
within and in this way it will be an
extension of the sense of time in the
idea of motion now fifth density will be
the recognition of the idea
experientially of simultaneousness of
your existence so you will perceive
yourself not only as volume not only as
motion but also as the idea of
simultaneous Motion in many different
alternate realities and parallel density
experiences sixth density in this way
will be like the idea of two is to one
volumetric again in the sense of planer
again in the sense from fifth density
not only the idea of simultaneous motion
but simultaneous existence in many
different alternate realities in this
way the actual sensing of yourself as
the dimensions in which you exist in
this sense seventh dentity will be the
experience of what you call the idea of
the god plane the god Soul the actual
existence of yourself as all that is in
that way you will be then completely
volumetrically existent in
multi-dimensional senses experiencing
yourself in alternate realities parallel
realities different civilizations the
totality of Consciousness up and down
and sideways in all the spectrums you
will actually be the dimension of that
existence itself and experience yourself
as not being in a dimension but being
the dimension of existence itself you
follow I think probably one
I think probably one
of of course there are moments that you
call Revelation in which you are let us
say in communication with every level of
your being that you exist upon you
follow me saying you're that level why not yes
not yes
well that is all right you are exactly
where you have chosen to be and it
serves your purposes recognize that this
is the transformational life on this
planet and if you have agreed to be here
now you have done so and made this
contract with all the other beings that
are here you are going to therefore
proceed at your own rate but you are
going to stay within a basic fundamental
rate that serves everyone you have made
the agreement with otherwise what is the
point you do not need to be
here you follow me
thank you very much and in this way
allow me once again to express to each
and every one of you our appreciation of
the gift of your sharing for in this way
we also as our civilization learn more
ways that all that is has of expressing
itself within creation and we will thank
you for that gift we bid you exciting
dream lives we than you good night