All right, I'll say how are you all this
dream time?
Allow us to begin once again with the
reaffirmation and reinforcement of the
ideal we have called the awakening. In
this way allowing there to be through
this repetition of this particular as
you say exercise the alignment
synchronous harmonization of all of your
physical, mental and energy body and
your cohesiveness with the physical, mental
cohesiveness with the physical, mental
and energy bodies of all individuals in
the civilization in which you live.
allowing yourselves to begin to realize
that as a group, as a gathering, as you
so direct your energy in this linear
fashion to the exercise we are about to
do once again for what you call the
third time of your caling, you will be
placing yourself more in tune, more in
alignment with all the different levels
of energy that represent the realities
you choose to be. And you will be able
to see in individuals around you in your
world. More of those individuals also
attuning to the synchronicity in their
lives. Individuals attracting themselves
to you. You attracting yourselves to
them. So that you can more consciously
perceive the interactions between each
and every one of you as an
orchestration of beautiful and explicit complexity.
of beautiful and explicit complexity.
and simplicity at the same
time. This technique, this exercise will
not invade anyone who does not wish to
be open to this
idea. Therefore, do not feel that in
your radiation of the energy that you
are to the rest of your world that you
will be forcing yourselves upon anyone
that does not wish to remain open to the
idea of receiving the gift of that
energy. It will simply allow you to
align with those that choose to be
aligned with you and allow you to
coalesce, become cohesive and attractive
to each other. So that no matter how far
apart your physical local, you can begin
to function as if you are working in, as
you say, concert with respect to the
creation of the synchronistic and
harmonious realities you desire to
experience upon your world. Are you all
following along so far?
In this way, therefore, allow yourself
to begin with to relax and center
yourselves in whatever way you find
comfortable. Your eyes may be open, your
eyes may be closed. And once again allow
us to remind you that even though we
will be directing the idea of the
imagery, your imagination will always
alter this idea according to what way
will represent the vibration that you
will best be able to utilize this energy
in radiating this energy to the rest of
your world to allow all to link up
together so that you can see the effects
around you in physical
reality. Three deep breaths. Now the Now the
first
scenario which will begin when we begin
the count of one will be for you to
visualize, imagine, feel whatever way it
comes to you the easiest the idea
that you are
radiating bright emotional orange
energy, orange light, and that you will
radiate this orange
light around your earth, through your
earth, to every single being upon your
earth, nondiscriminately, unconditionally.
nondiscriminately, unconditionally.
Every single being, every single
consciousness, be it plant, mineral,
animal, human form, citation, anything
you desire, all upon your world, allow
it to receive this energy. And when we
begin the count of one, we will proceed
to your count of
33. With each increasing
number, allow yourself in your
imagination to increase the energy that
you are radiating this light
at 10fold, 20fold, 100fold with each
number until you think you can stand it
no longer, until you think you can
contain this energy no longer. And then
just when you think you will explode if
you allow it to become greater than it
is, create it to be greater still.
For if you can conceive of the idea of a
limit, there is always something beyond.
Always. When we arrive at the count of
30, allow it to go a thousand times
greater, a million times greater by
whatever factor again your imagination
will allow. By the time we reach 33,
allow it to be at the pinnacle of the
expression of the radiant
energy. When we say
cut, allow it to
absolutely cut. Do not fade it out. We
will assist you by supplying alternate
imagery that you can focus on to allow
you to immediately cut the radiation.
You all follow
along. Three mode. Deep breath. Relaxing
breath. Easy breath. centering
breath. Begin to imagine the bright
orange light building up, twipping,
about to be released in a spontaneous
explosion over the entire Earth.
Beginning now. 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11
12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24
25 26 27 28 29 30 31 32 33 Cut right
blue sky. Birds calling to one another.
Clouds in the background. Rain on the
mountains in the distance. Fields of
grass blowing in the wind. The trees
trickling down through the rocks of the
forest. Allow this energy also to shake
itself within you.
Allow it to settle within
you. Feel the
afterblow. Allow yourself now to gather
together for the same type of
scenario. A brilliant and crystallum
blue light. A more highly accelerated light.
light. A more highly accelerated light.
The gathering together as a whirlpool of
your entire electro and a steromagnetic
energy which you will allow to radiate
from you, burst from you in a shock wave
of brilliant energy through and around
the planet, touching every single
individual, passing through the cellular
structure of every single individual and
allowing them to choose what vibration
ations are correct for
them. Begin to radiate this brilliant
blue light
light
starting now. 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12
13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24 25
26 27 28 28 29 30 31 32 33 Cut the
bottom of the ocean. Deep still
creatures stirring across the bottom
between the rocks.
Coolness, death,
darkness, calm. Three deep breaths.
In the final
scenario, you will allow yourself, your
body, your energy body, every cell,
every atom to become absolutely crystal
clear so that you may allow to pass
through every cell through your skin A
brilliant photonic white
flash that will
instantaneously envelop the entire
planet Earth in that white
flash. Blinding yet loving light. In no
way painful, but absolutely
penetrating, absolutely
permeating, allowing everything to be
rendered with crystal clarity so that no
shadows on earth
remain. All becomes a transparent
crystal in the light of that
knowingness, of that brilliance, of that
clarity, of that purity.
Not a shadow of a doubt
remains. Allow it once again by the
counting to increase in intensity beyond
anything you imagine your body capable
of
tolerating. And then always expand by a
factor of at least three when you think
you can expand no more. between the
count of 30 to
33. Allow
every individual corporeal object upon
the planet earth to
become one with that light for those
three seconds. There will be no
seconds. There will be no
differentiation of any one thing as
different from any other thing. All will
be made of the same white light and all
will be immersed in that same white
light. It will be one homogeneous sea.
The entire planet will have no solid
form to the very limits of the
atmosphere above. One brilliant
incandescent flash
flash
beginning now. 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11
12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20
26 23 24 25 26 27 28 29 30 31 32 33 C
dark space empty void black star
brilliant taste of light in the voice
forever infinity coolness clarity
brilliant vibrations through your body patterns of
vibrations through your body patterns of
energy crystallizing and aligning
themselves
Free loving automonious breath.
As you now
relax and
recreate what you may call the typical
pattern of energy that represents your
day-to-day existence. Recognize you are
not recreating it to be the same as it
was before you began this
exercise. It is now being rewoven in a
new matrix. One that is now
indicative. One that is now
definitive according to the
desire, the
love that
you will express, the willingness, the
certainty, the knowingness that you are.
Your life will now
life will now
exponentially begin to manifest more and
more synchronicity. And you have now through
synchronicity. And you have now through
this act of love allowed all other
individuals upon your planet to be able
to also choose if they so
desire to involve themselves in
synchronous harmony with you.
in the direction of the creation of
harmonious peace and joy. Ecstasy upon
your world, within your world, from your
world, to your
world, for a final time in what you
call this your year
1,986 of your counting.
Next week of your time once again we
will perform this awakening.
These four times including next week of
your time that we will have done so will
have been one
each for all that you consider to be the
four directions and all the polarities
within the being that you are with that
alignment and thus beginning in what you
call your new
year. Added dimension will be brought
into play. This exercise will expand in
play. This exercise will expand in
different ways, different levels and
incorporate more dimensionality aspects
of your
being. Upon the creation of the fourth
manifestation of this
exercise, you will have the laying down
of the foundations of all the energy you
require to take with you through the
gate that will be your year of
manifestation 1,987.
We at this time extend our
appreciation for your willingness to
experience the depth of the
energy and the expansiveness of the
consciousness that each and every one of
you individually and together
collectively are. We thank you for your sharing in
are. We thank you for your sharing in
this dream. Sharing
dream. Sharing
you and venue.
I had a very exciting experience today
that I'd like to share with you in the
group. You share and speak up. Okay. So
that all may share, right? Um I came
home from a party to my house, unlocked
my door, walked in and found out my
computer was gone and my printer and my
tape deck and my answering machine. And
I was so stunned with amazement. And I
first of all, I compared it with how I
felt a couple years ago when I had a
robbery, as they say. Oh, what? And I
was so angry. I was really I felt that I
could easily kill someone years ago.
Yeah. In another lifetime. And I
thought, this is wonderful. I've come so
far since then.
And I thought, what does this mean? And
I I was listening to the tape yesterday
and something you said really stressed
me with and that is nothing happens to
you. Everything happens from you. you
made such an impression. I thought,
well, of course, this is something I've
created. And perhaps it has to do with
the fact that I don't need to be so
cerebral and more intuitive
and more intuitive
because on my front porch, as I had come
in to the door and I had my hands full,
I noticed there was a box. So, I went
back to the front porch and I brought it
in and I opened it up. And in the box is
a gift from a friend of mine in Florida.
And it's a sculpture of two bronze
dolls.
And I don't know what to say about this
except that it was totally exciting. We
would simply at this time recommend that
you take the combined feeling of the
polarity of the two events. Let the
feelings balance out in a positive
direction. Let yourself continue with
your life. Let yourself still follow
what excites you. And in a very short
order, you will begin to see how these
events will play into the setting up of
circumstances that will lead you in
directions you truly desire to go. You
will have your analytical understanding
in the moment you need to have it. You
are still in the middle of the
experiential momentum. Let it play
itself out. you will have analytical
understanding why you had arranged the
scenario in that manner in relatively
short order. Thank you. I feel that's
exactly right and that's a perfect
reflection of my own feelings. I love
you. Thank you so much. We love you as
well for being so bold in your creation.
[Music] You will also recognize
You will also recognize
paradoxically that as soon as you allow
these ideas to blend and utilize the
momentum that you can glean from them,
then you will begin to emerge
into a time wherein you no longer need
the removal of physiological objects
from your life to teach you what it is
you are learning about this particular
scenario. Very good. Good point.
Very good. Good point.
Hey, I have a very elderly aunt who has
been very ill for more than a year and
um her life is physically very
uncomfortable and she is emotionally
afraid of uh dying which I think is
going on
and can you suggest or advise me how I
can be of what can I say to help this
individual through this? will depend on
what the individual's belief systems
are. Do you have in your terms any
inkling as to what they would accept
about the idea that they are infinite
and eternal and that death is only a
transformation and not an end? Well, uh
this this particular woman has uh for
her entire life been uh involved in the
I call the the established church and uh
you know they think that heaven and hell
or that's the the routine they go
through and and I'm sure that there's
some element of disbelief and now that
has come to face the real issue I sense
that uh that this the person is now very
doubtful and confused very worried and I
don't know quite what to say which might
be helpful or I might say something
which is even more shocking. Oh, I do
not worry. Do not worry. First of all,
before we continue with her, what are
you learning from this from this
situation? Well, um, one of one of the
main things, uh, for me is that, uh,
it's, uh, it's an opportunity for me to
really get to grips with how I really
feel. All right. And what I And also,
it's a good opportunity to to learn
something about how you can be of
service to people situations. All right.
And that there really are no difficult
situations at all. Okay. Except as you
label them. The label here. find it.
Now, with regard to her, a little bit of
background. First, recognize that
strongly held belief in physical life
will usually result upon physical death
in the experience of a scenario to
represent those strongly held beliefs at
least temporarily. So, you will find that if
temporarily. So, you will find that if
an individual had a particular scenario
in mind that they were most likely to
experience upon physical death, they
will experience that scenario.
Now that will simply be the product of
their own projections of consciousness
because they will be a thought form in a
world of thought form and what they
think there is instantaneously what they
experience as seemingly solidly real.
You follow me? Yes. Bit by bit this
individual will learn that this scenario
they perceive is utterly under the
control of what they think it to be. And
as soon as they change their mind, a bit
here, a bit there, they will see these
changes take place in the scenario
around them, which will let them know
that it is completely and utterly the
product of what they imagine it to be.
Bit by bit, as they get used to this
idea, they will then be more free and
more able and willing to realize that
they are totally in control of this idea
and always have been and that many of
the belief systems they bought into in
the physical plane you call your Earth
were simply nothing more than that,
belief systems. and not necessarily
directly indicative of any one set
reality that is more real than any other
reality they could experience in the
non-physical world of what we call the
afterlife. Now, without necessarily
having to go into all of this, what you
can always be certain of in terms of
reassuring this individual is the
following. Whatever in her
Whatever in her
mind is the best and most joyous
representation of what she thinks she
can or will
experience after she has physically died
will be what she experiences experiences
100%
guaranteed. Now it will change in time
and she will have assistants all around
her all the time who will assist her in
recognizing that she is creating that
scenario. But they will wean her out of
it
gently when she can handle as you say
the understanding that the scenario has
always been the product of her belief.
But you may always reassure her that
whatever in her imagination, in her
heart, is the most joyous scenario she
imagines to be true, that she will
experience after her death is what she
will experience. Absolutely
100%. And she will not be alone. Far
from it. She will be more lovingly supported
it. She will be more lovingly supported
than she has ever thought could be
possible. All she needs to do is
remember that and then radiate that
love. There will be beings, many beings
of light around her, some of whom she
will know. Thank
Thank
you. I shall see this individual over
the Christmas period. All right. You may
also if you
wish allow this individual to understand
that this is a time of joy, a time of
preparation for
transformation and that she has always
had and has now the capability in
opening her heart to communicate
directly with the totality of the
consciousness of the love that is always
being sent to your world from all levels
of infinite creation. This is her time
to be aware that she can be in touch
with this infinite love and that this
infinite love will support her through
the transformation. She will hardly know
it has happened.
[Music] You follow me?
You follow me?
We thank you.
you does that exercise with the orange and
does that exercise with the orange and
the blue and the white on our own in the
house. Does that uh I don't know. I have
a good time doing it. So then do it
anytime you feel so inclined. It will
have of course an effect like little
tremors of what we do in there tonight.
It does not have to be so little.
Now if you are willing to recognize that
you as an individual are equal to what
all of these individuals together have
done this evening of your time. Then
every time you yourself do it, it will
be on the same level as all of these
individuals together having done it
because you are equal with that idea.
Thank you. Oh, thank you. I have nothing
to do
with another question. All right. the two
another question. All right. the two
stars in the sky that just like lately I
keep seeing these two stars. One is
really bright and one's a little smaller
and I planet. Okay. Planets. Um Mars.
Yes. Are they closer together tonight
than they were? Only by what you call
your line of sight. They are not
physiologically closer in their orbits
per se to any great degree, but in terms
of your line of sight, they appear to be
very close.
They surprise me because I'm always
looking up in the sky. Just lately I
noticed those two really standing out.
Hey, they are very bright because they
are physically much closer than any of
the stars. All of them. Yeah. Okay. The last
stars. All of them. Yeah. Okay. The last
thing is just a sharing about the the
quickness of everything being an
opportunity and that the part I caught
last week. I think you said about uh
assuming that there's some more coming
that'll uh explain what's happening
right now and of course for the positive
cards. Of course, I have a item removed
from my house too
that the person told me they asked me
but I have no recollection because I was
sleeping or not but they said they
didn't. I just had uh my usual faith and
creative imagination of all the
opportunities that would bring me and it
all worked out and uh I got I knew that
was one of the things I could be of
service and a reflection to my other
family members that were thinking that
they should lynch the
person that uh uh did something. So I
just wanted to share that everything
being an opportunity it's just like
knowing that it's right short order as
we call it. Yes. Everything's right
there. Well, thank you for your
explosion of awareness
and sharing.
You the new.
Okay. Um the first time I came here some
weeks ago, I mentioned a um problem I
was having. A what?
[Music] I mentioned a situation in my life very
I mentioned a situation in my life very
negative and uh at least that was the
way I perceived it, right? And uh so I
am now uh in the process of removing
myself from that dwelling and I will be
moving into what looks like a much more
positive situation. All right. So at
that time I made the judgment that I was
going to be leaving my brother behind
and now and now uh it seems that the
film studio that I work for, one of our
customers is making a film of all things
about dolphins. Oh, what a good
And it's and it's not just about
dolphins. It's about the Bay of Dolphins
on the island of Fernando D Nanha. And
uh this man is making the film in order
to show it to the um government of
Brazil and other people that will help
him make it into a park so that the
dolphins won't be driven away by hordes
of uh hotel dwellers and etc. So my
roommate that I am moving out with or
moving out from is now going to do the
narration on that
film. So I thought that was pretty
wonderful. Oh, thank you very much. May
I do something we rarely do? Oh, yes, of
course. To allow all individuals
connected to this event on what you
would call both sides to be able to
utilize their imagination to the fullest
and blend together in a harmonious way.
May we suggest one of your hotels spread
out on the water so that each and every
room has a pit leading to the ocean up
through which a dolphin can emerge.
[Music] Oh, everybody would be happy. Yay.
Oh, everybody would be happy. Yay.
That's the whole idea.
You would be happy. They would be happy.
The dolphins would be happy. Everybody
would be happy.
Oh my goodness. What a terrific idea.
Well, my energy for that. All right.
Thank you very much. I have another
question on a more personal level. I I
have the things that I'm dealing with
now are that I
have trouble moving through. That's a
good way to put it. Go away. Okay. Uh
are procrastination and feeling left out and
procrastination and feeling left out and
addiction especially to you have someone
who agrees. Yes, I know. Especially to
sugar. And I have some feeling that this
procrastination and feeling left out in
this addiction to sugar are somehow tied
together. And I'd like particularly the
idea of procrastination and the sugar
really. But in this way, you will find
that many individuals who do feel
themselves to be accelerating many times
will simply rely upon a physiological
way to represent that by ingesting a
substance that will make them feel
accelerated. At the same time, the
reliance on that, let us say the forcing
of that substance into the system in
that way will come also from a
reluctance to allow yourself to flow
along natural lines, the
procrastination. Now, both of these
ideas in a sense are the polarities that
are hinged upon the central theme of
being left out, which is the fulcrum
point of both sides of this issue.
Left out of what? Oh, just uh you know
I'm not going to have enough money to
come to Bashar. I'm not going. You don't
move to but that's beside the point.
Look at it this way. In the center you
have the idea of being left out which is
another way of saying I am not in touch
with the perfect timing of my life.
And on either side of this issue of
perfect timing is going too slow, going
too fast.
Oh, you follow me? Yes, I do. It is your
little seessaw.
Now, when you recognize once again that
you create your own destiny and that the
dates with destiny are always on time,
then you will allow the idea of this
fulcrum point to be that which balances
both sides of the seessaw so that
everything will be seen by you to occur
in perfect timing exactly when it needs
to, exactly where it needs to. You
cannot be left out of your own
creation. Oh, your planet is so very
creative to have come up with that
concept. I must admit I have never
thought of that
[Music] myself. A wonderful work of art.
myself. A wonderful work of art.
However, we will suggest at this time
that if you find it causes
consternation that we will remind you
and allow yourself to be reminded that
everything occurs in perfect timing. You
will be left out of
nothing. Relax. Go with your flow. Enjoy
where you are at any given moment. And
that is what will paradoxically
accelerate you beyond your wildest
dreams as you say.
All right. Thank you.
You are very welcome. So are you. So are
you. Thank you.
Thank you.
Yay. Um for the past three weeks I've
had trouble with my left knee and I have
trouble walking. I can't dance anymore
and uh do anything. And nothing at all.
How did you get here? Well, today's
better and Oh.
But it still doesn't feel comfortable.
All right. Last night, uh, before
falling asleep, I was kind of thinking,
wishing for a teaching in my dreams. And
and, uh, this one part of my dream
stands out about a carriage, a man in a
carriage with two horses harnessed to
it. One, a black one in front and a
white one behind him. Nothing about
polarity in this.
[Music]
And uh look like like my old
and uh all the very sweet and the white
horse was very young and full of energy
and quite beautiful and fatter. Uh and
the uh driver of the carriage tried to
jump over ahead with the carriage and
the two horses and uh the white horse
got very impatient. It had more energy
than the black horse in front of it. and
hit the black horse in the legs in the
left leg. Oh yeah. Around the area of
the knee and I tried to break the leg
and um when I woke up I was just like
sinking. The dream was with me. Yes. And
um very good very creative but there is
a very good teaching. I don't quite
understand but my leg feels much better.
Very good. It will continue to become,
as you say, better and better now that
you recognize that it represents the old
way of walking as opposed to the new
way. There is no need for the
impatience. You have enough energy to
balance both sides. But the old way
simply represents a lot of old negative
beliefs that supported you in their
time, and so you consider them to be an
old friend. Very sweet for the time you
used them, very sweet for the time you
rode upon them. They brought you to
where you needed to be. But now it is
time to mount the younger horse. But
there is no need for impatience. You do
not have to feel as if you are dragging
a heavy weight or have to have
impossible demands put upon
you, leaping over hedges and
such. Allow yourself to simply recognize
that you have taken your body and split
it down the middle with one half
representing the old negativity and one
half representing the new positivity.
Now that you have allowed yourself to
begin to blend and balance these ideas,
very shortly you will be able to run
with the wind once again.
Well, thank you. I have another
question. Oh, all right. Because uh I
went to I was going to an acupuncturist
and he told me that I may be getting
arthritis. Uh and the idea of arthritis
is only that you lose your idea of
flexibility.
Mhm. Let yourself realize that you are
becoming more subtle. The only reason
that the idea of our Christ would
manifest at this time within you as we
perceive your energy is if you did
become too demanding upon the idea of
the energy that you are. You do not need
impatience. It is the impatience that
will cause the rigidity you call
arthritis. You do not need to experience that
You do not need to experience that
rigidity because you do not need
impatience because you do not need
patience. Again, when you are enjoying
the energy that you are in the moment,
every moment you are not waiting for
something better to come along. So you
are not in need of patience which create
impatience which creates rigidity which
can create arthritis or many other
diseased manifestations.
Allow yourself to simply recognize that
this is your opportunity to send energy
to that area. Balance it out and you
will then by definition homogenize the
electromagnetic field that you are. And
in such a balanced definition, there is
no room for the variable in that
equation that represents disease in any
form. Be supple, be fluid,
slow. All right. Uh yes. Uh in the
meantime uh if if if you have if if if
if
well if if impatience persists I is the
realization impatience does not persist
you insist on continuing to chew it.
Okay. Is the realization of all that
sufficient or should they also somehow
change their diet or or do some
physical? Would you like it to be
sufficient? Yes. Do you believe that it can be that
Yes. Do you believe that it can be that
simple? Be honest. Yes. Are you sure?
Absolutely. Absolutely. Then it's
sufficient. Now, if you have any other sensings with
Now, if you have any other sensings with
regard to your communications with what
you might call your body consciousness
about what alterations in diet might go
along with this idea, then simply go
with your
flow. Recognize that the idea is that
you will simply lose the urge for
something when you accelerate into a new
level of energy. You will lose the urge
for those substances which no longer
represent the new level you have taken
yourself to. If you feel there is something you
to. If you feel there is something you
wish to do to clarify and purify your
system, then trust your imagination and
trust your instincts because those
imaginations and those instincts now
come from the new level of trust that
you are willing to allow to be all that
you require in simplicity. Feeling that
I need to drink a lot of water. Do
it. Understand there is as
Understand there is as
yet by many of you an untapped energy in
water that when you evoke that energy
with your
imagination by many different
methodology. One can simply be doing a
meditation as you say with the water for
approximately 10 of your minutes.
feeding that water, feeding into that
water, your blue
electromagnetic energy from your head,
from your hand, from your heart, from
your polar plexus does not much matter.
Energizing that purified water and then
drinking it will allow that crystallin
energy to be unlocked from the water and
it will infuse every single cell in your
body. They will come alive. So by all
means drink that water and realize what
you are using that water for. All right.
Thank you very much. We thank you for
your clarity and insight. You Yes.
You Yes.
I've I've been finding myself getting
more and more fatigued and waking
up earlier
uh even even though I would like to uh
find periods to rest more. And I'm What
type of a quote unquote schedule do you
force yourself to
have rather than a schedule you can
allow yourself to reflect in a more
natural biological pattern? For do
recognize that in general terms, a more
natural biological pattern for your form
of life and for many forms of life that
still regard themselves as a
physiological being is to be very awake,
very energetic, and very alert at what
you call the very wee hours of the
morning and asleep in what you call your
afternoon. Now, do you find that you have a
Now, do you find that you have a
structured schedule that might be at
odds with your ability to sleep when you
truly are tired and be awake when you
truly are awake?
Once you tell me, uh, yes, that's very
possible. I have I have a tendency to
want to be a awake in the daylight
hours, all of the daylight hours. Uh, why? because
why? because
uh the enterprises I've chosen the the
world seems to be focused on uh being
awake during those hours. Some, not
all. There are many many many streams
running through every culture that do
not follow what is usually thought to be
the typical pattern and therefore the
pattern is not as typical as you think.
Now understand that if you truly are
allowing yourself to blend in a more
harmonious way with a natural cycle of
your being, then everything you as a
being are interested in doing will also
be able to be tailored to that cycle.
Otherwise, there would be no point in
you as a being interested in those
things. Yes. Then trust that if you are flowing
Yes. Then trust that if you are flowing
into a natural cycle, everything that
you truly need to do and that truly
excites you and truly is a
representation of the being you are will
be able to flow in the same
cycle. What are your own inclinations?
My inclination is to believe that
uh that I took on more positions of
power than I am
uh in the life I'm living now. And what
did you do with my power?
Well, I'm not I'm not sure. I pro I I
suspect I used it uh cruy
at times. that time. If you felt that
you had access to the same power levels
now, what would you do with it? I I
would use it more
lovingly as for instance.
Oh, if I Well, if I had a position where
I was
uh I with what's called the elite and
and having a lot the elite having a lot
having a lot of uh one
moment that nomenclature comes from your
past life.
All is one. If you continue to think in
terms of the fact that there is an
elite, then you are only recreating the
same use of the power that you used
to. You are powerful now, as powerful as
you need to be to create anything you
desire in your life without having to
hurt anyone else or yourself in order to
create it. You are all of the
it. You are all of the
elite. You are all unique. You are all
expressions of the
infinite. There is no longer any need to
think in terms of better, worse, or any
such labeling. That let us say
labeling. That let us say
inclination is what created what you now
perceive to be the so-called trouble in
your last
life. Thinking in terms of levels rather
than thinking in terms of wholeness.
You have the same power in a sense. You
may actually find that you are able to
express more power than you had when you
begin to think in terms of wholeness
rather than thinking in terms of part.
Yes, I do. Rather than thinking also in
terms of
hemisphere, think in terms of
wholeness. Feel the energy of your brain
to be one
idea. There is no longer any need for a
battle of two
sides to be taking place within
you. No
conflict, no dichotomy.
All polarity stems from a single
source. Become that single source and
you are completely
self-empowered to create what excites
you the most.
Are you truly doing what excites you the
most in [Music]
[Music]
life as far as well depend on the
definition of excitement there's I see
as different levels of satisfaction
again different levels
[Music] very good
very good
you are becoming more
homogeneous you
lack. You do not need so many
definitions in order to be able to live
the life you are. You will understand
whatever you need to understand in
whatever terms you need to understand
it. There is nothing wrong with your
approach, but it is something that may
continue to allow since you think of
yourself as a collection of portions.
This approach may allow therefore some
of those self-created portions to remain
out of touch with other
portions. Blend, homogenize, become
whole, become
one, become the cause and the effect in
a single
event. We will
suggest for now that you sleep on this.
We bid you pleasant dreams. There will
be much
assistance. Look for it. Acknowledge it.
But also acknowledge that you will do
your own
part and that you are in this present
life to learn how to blend and not
segregate any
longer. All right. Thank you. We thank
you for your
willingness and the boldness to
experience the life you have experienced
in the way you have chosen to experience
it. Much acceleration will be the
result. Thank
you. Our energy and our love to you. Your
you. Your
desires will make a difference.
Let it be a
difference. Let your imagination be
real. Live your
dream. We thank you. Drink
you. Drink
deeply from the cup of
life. It will always refresh you and
there will always be more.
It is never ending. It is infinite. It
is eternal.
Point of view, guys.
Could you share a title uh with us for
last week, please? How about awakening
part two? I thought about that. Okay.
How about part three for tonight? All
right. And part four for next week.
uh since it is one cohesive idea.
Okay. Thank you. Uh another thing is at
least for myself it's going to be the
last time I hear you in 1986 and you
called 1987 the year of manifestation
and I know you have shared some thoughts
with us about 1987 before but I was
wondering if you could add to it at this
time. Not at this time. Again, there
will be, as we have said, other levels
coming into it beginning
in your year 1,987.
Well, could you be a little more
specific about something? Maybe
[Music] maybe
anything in particular?
Well, my site, yes. is about about um
UFOs quote uh civilizations other
civilizations quote the uh the uh the
kinds of things that we can expect most
people to become aware of. I think you
said something about that in the form.
Yes, I have.
Well, could you be a little more
specific about what you what you said or
saying it again?
simply that beginning within what you
call your springtime and moving in
through the summer, passing through the
date 7787, there will be more opportunity for
7787, there will be more opportunity for
individuals a to recognize that you have
the technology to create what you
typically regard to be our type of
spacecraft to some degree. B that your
planet has been in contact with other
civilizations for quite some time. C
that you'll begin to equalize
communication between yourselves and
your government so that they can share
this information or at least some of it
with you. D that there can be more and more
you. D that there can be more and more
interactions between our civilizations
and your civilization during that summer
time. There will be many more contacts
taking place as more and more
individuals find themselves
spontaneously in regions that would be
most often called your desert
regions throughout the summer and into
the fall. Now I know that uh a lot of
people have seen um
spacecraft and it's been reported
locally at times but not in the national
I've never seen it reported in except
you know from time to time it has been
but recognized this is all part and
parcel of the connection of the idea of
what you call a ban of information
imposed by your government. Right. Do
you think it's going to be lifted at in
the ban? That's up to you. But we
perceive that as a highly probable
situation so that people will be more
open to all these ideas which will make
it then possible for us to become
but directly proportional to your
involvement in opening up dialogues with
these individuals to allow them to know
that you are interested in hearing about
these things.
What other kinds of manifestations um in
terms of force density phenomena would
you expect to occur in 1987?
Primarily again
more contact physically between your
species and the dolphin species highly
accelerated. Highly accelerated. You may
even begin to see changes in what you
call your social laws because of it.
In other words, who is regarded as human
and who is not?
You follow me? Yeah. Again, this will be
up to you, but we sense that is highly
likely. Wonderful. Thank you very much. We thank
Wonderful. Thank you very much. We thank
you. It is your world.
[Music] Okay.
Okay.
Um, I have a question concerning anger.
Anger? All right. Um, I'm wondering if
um there are ways to to examine an angle
to diffuse it and I'm also absolutely
and I was also wondering if uh color and
working with color it can be of
assistance as a tool in that way yes
first of all once again recognize that
what you typically call anger is simply
the process of complete and total
alignment with what you believe to be
true for yourself compared to a scenario
that you are presented with in your life
that is offering you an opportunity to
decide whether that scenario is also
true for you or not. Now the only reason
that the so-called anger becomes a
negative manifestation is when you go
beyond the idea of the alignment and
begin to invalidate or judge that
scenario as something not worthy of
being in your life. Obviously it is in
your life for a reason. Obviously you
are experiencing it for a reason. So
allow yourself to use it in a positive
way by simply allowing the situation to
offer you a set of circumstances that
can cause different actions or reactions
within you and determine for yourself by
aligning with what you know to be true
for you which of those responses is
apropo in your life. Then by centering
yourself in that way, you can interact
with that scenario coming from a
complete place of centeredness and
interact with any individuals in that
scenario by letting them see within you.
An example, a reflection of that
centeredness of that loving light that
you can then share, reflect back to them
to let them know once again one of the
many variations of the main theme that
usually comes about causing what you
call anger. And that is once again
simply teach every individual that they
are as powerful as they need to be to
have anything they desire in life
without having to hurt anyone else or
themselves in order to create
it. And that if you witness something
being forced upon someone else or on
yourself, anyone who needs to force an
idea on someone else obviously does not
believe in the power of that idea
themselves. The forcing of an idea is an
expression of their inherent belief in
their own
powerlessness, not power. see that,
align with that, reflect that back,
teach them that. And you can use any
scenario as a learning experience, as a
centering experience, as an aligning
experience. That rush of energy that you
feel that you most often think of simply
under the lump sum of anger is simply
the adrenaline rush that comes with
alignment. For anxiety and excitement is
the vibration of your alignment. One
that is not judged, not invalidated, and
one that is. It is the same energy. So
in other words, when you So in other
words, when you feel the rush, recognize
it. That rush that that is anger that I
often times try to deny. Recognize that
as an alignment. Yeah. You see, if you
attempt to deny it, then you are
refusing to acknowledge a portion of
your own consciousness. You are not
willing to use it in a positive way
because you have been taught to believe
that there could be something about that
scenario inherently built in that will
not be positive. But no situation has
built-in meaning. You give it the
meaning and the meaning you give it
utterly determines the effect you get
out of
it. So if you give it a positive
meaning, you will only get a positive
effect. If you believe it has negative
meaning built in, you will get a
negative effect. And that will lead to
what goes beyond the alignment, which is
invalidation, resentment, hate,
frustration, rage, guilt, and all of
those wonderfully creative scenarios.
[Music] Yes, I do. Does that assist you? Yes.
Yes, I do. Does that assist you? Yes.
Um, how how would one uh use color in an
instance of somehow I'm trying to think
of some way using the the feeling
instead of frustration. Again, first of
all, recognize that if you know you are
using the scenario in a positive way,
then there will be nothing to
diffuse. You follow me? You will absorb
the entire energy and it will all for
you be positive. There will be nothing
to diffuse.
[Music]
But does that assist you? Yes, it does.
Thank you very much.
Yes. Have a problem about Oh, what?
Have a problem about Oh, what?
I have a a question.
All right.
Uh there's a there seems to be a million
ways that people tell other people how
to reach for money prosperity. Yes. Um
there are a million different ways. Or
actually well let us see what is the
approximate population of your plan.
I got it. Thank you. I need to know what
to do about that. I'm having a problem.
I'm having a You are exploring the idea
of abundance.
Yes. Just money abundance. Why just
money abundance? Well, I have I think
the other the other things are okay for
me. I don't feel that. Why are you
segregating this idea? It seems to be
abundance is one concept. Why are you
making money stand out as something more
important than any other form of
abundance? Be the most difficult one for
me to to grab onto. Maybe that's because
you don't need it as much as you think
you do. So that's the one you go chasing
after. So that's the one that eludes you
because you are not willing to let it
occur when it occurs as an indication of
when it needs to occur and allow it to
be equal to any other way that abundance
in your life could
occur. Understand you will never have
more than you need anyways. You will
always have exactly just enough. When
you expand the idea of yourself, then
perhaps the symbols that go along with
abundance will expand accordingly. It
may seem as if an individual you think
of as rich has more than they need, but
they don't. They have exactly just
enough to be the expanded idea that they
are being relative to someone else. But
the someone else, if they are still able
to do what they need to do when they
need to do it, they are just as rich on
their own terms. Abundance is simply the
ability to do what you need to do when
you need to do it. Period. no matter how
it comes to you. Now, many times you
will find that what you call money will
be the way that will represent the path
of least resistance. But many times it
won't. Now, let me simply ask you
straight out. If you knew that money
would actually take longer in certain
cases to bring you the abundance you
require, would you still insist upon it?
Oh, yes. No. Maybe.
I don't know. You don't know? If there
is something in your life, if there is
something in your life that you desire
above and beyond anything else and you
were told point blank, well, there are a
few ways this can come to you. The
easiest way will be to use your trust
and allow someone to walk up to you and
simply give it to you. What will take
the longest is if you think you need
money in order to get it. Which way do
you choose?
Will you still insist on the money? Even
though you know you can have it quicker,
easier if you allow someone to give it
to you. You knew beyond a shadow of a
doubt that that would be quicker than
the money. You would still insist on the
money.
I don't understand. All right. I realize
that I'm being resented, but I because I
don't understand what
what you perhaps do not understand is
that life can work as a series of
coincidences. You are always in the
right place at the right time
interacting with exactly the right
individuals to attract into your life
the things that you need and you attract
the individuals into your life that
require what they need from you. You are
always sharing with the individuals and
only the individuals that need your
services and that you need the services
of. Period. You cannot by definition
interact with anyone else. There are
many many ways that a certain idea could
manifest in your life. There are some
that represent processes that may take a
long time. And there are some ways, some
paths to the same goal, so to speak,
that could represent a very short period
of time. You follow me? There are more
than one way to arrive at the same goal.
You understand? Yes. Now, if somebody
told you when you told them what your
goal was that there was a short path and
a long path, are you saying that you
would insist on the longer path?
No. All right. Then all we are saying to
you is that
sometimes even though you think with
your analytical aware physical ego that
money is what will get you this thing
quickest, that is not always true. And
many times therefore if you insist that
money is the only way you will accept as
the way to have what you desire, then
your focus on the longer path is what
will make it take a longer and b
probably not even allow you to recognize
that there is a shorter path. So you
will avoid the shorter path altogether
because your focus is on what might
potentially be the longer harder
path. You follow me? That is why when
you allow money to simply be one of the
tools of abundance absolutely in every
way, shape and form equal to all the
other ways that you can create abundance
in your life, then it will simply be one
tool in your box of tools and you will
not have to elevate it to a special
place. Therefore, it will not be so hard
to reach.
because you are putting it on a pedestal
above all the other tools in your
toolbox. When you allow it to be just as
valid as all the tools, then when you
need that tool, it will be easily at
hand. It will be there. The right tool
for the right job as you
say. So when money is not there, when
that does not come the quickest, it is
not the right tool for the right job.
another tool is more appropriate. Let
the other tool be more appropriate. Do
not insist on using a tool that does not
fit the piece you are working on. Use
the one that fits. Let the one that will
manifest most quickly in your life
manifest. And trust that when you see
indications in your life of situations
that attract you, that excite you, that
interest you, whether the situation
seems to be connected to what you find
exciting in your life or not. If the
situation itself comes with excitement,
it is the excitement that lets you know
it is connected and that that will allow
you to experience the manifestation you
desire. perhaps much more quickly than
the way you thought was the necessary
way to experience that manifestation or
bring it
about. If only. And again, when you let
all of these tools be equal,
paradoxically, you usually wind up with
an abundance of all of
them. the money, the
giftgiving, the trading, and all the
different ways you can experience
abundance. You follow
me? Relax. You are
Relax. You are
abundant. Let yourself be abundant in
whatever way is the path of least
resistance. You will find as a general principle as
You will find as a general principle as
we perceive your society's energy that
the tool of money will not remain around
for too much longer
anyway. So the idea is is that you will
learn how to be abundant in many ways
that in a sense are quicker. That is why
our society has absolutely no monetary
system of economics.
We are always sharing with the
individuals we need to be sharing with
who will provide for us what we need in
turn. So why do you need a middle ground
symbol to represent something that can
occur more directly one to one?
You follow me? Now we understand the way
your society is at this time but it is
changing. You will still be able to
create in your life by whatever
methodologies you require as much
abundance in whatever form as you need
to be the idea you are most excited
about being. If you are acting upon the
opportunities that present themsel in
your life that are reflective of the
idea you are most excited about being.
If you ignore those opportunities then
do not be surprised that abundance does
not come to you.
All right. Thank you. Thank you very
much. Oh my. [Music]
[Music]
You then you I'd like to ask a question
about uh ch in regards to children. Um
the thing about you say that well you
can't lose like let them uh figure
things out. How you said if your police
were right then other people come around
to it. When you have to tell a child to
do something and they don't do it and
they or they keep doing exactly what you
don't want them to do, can you reflect?
It's it's not my child, but I live with
a child and I can help. Yes, you can
reflect an understanding. Now, also at
this time, again, do understand that
many of the children upon your planet
will still be playing out reflections of
past agreements from past lives with
many of the individuals and many of the
families that they are enscconced
within. So in this way you may find that
any degree of stubbornness that exceeds
what you would term to be common sense
may be an indication of an agreement
that is yet not worked out.
Also allow the entire experience to be a
whole event. Not just what the child is
doing but what are the parents
reflecting to that
child. Many times you will find that all
the child is doing is reflecting the
beliefs they are receiving right back to
the parents.
You follow me? The parents are a quite
uh they don't you know after they tell
the child to do something they don't
enforce it. They just like will keep
telling her but she won't you know keep
doing it. So it's like she knows that
she doesn't have to do what she's told
to do. We understand that. But what we
are saying is that it may take some
self-examination on the part of the
parents to understand why they have
co-created this particular reflection in
their lives. Why I co-created them in my
lives. Yes. There will be varying
degrees of significance according to how
you chose to be connected to this event.
So you don't have any specific
uh specific general
[Music] reflections on the child's life. Yes.
reflections on the child's life. Yes.
Ask the child why it does what it does
and then listen.
Okay. Thank you. Thank you. Yes.
Did you fall
asleep? No. Do you still have a sharing?
Yes, I do. All right. Do share. Uh, when
you were talking about abundance, it
occurred to me that one of the facets of
abundance is being able to give freely.
Absolutely. Therefore, having something
quote taken from you is just another way
of giving. Sometimes it is one way to
get the abundance flowing. Sometimes.
Sometimes. Yes. Well, today when I was
reflecting the things that were stolen,
I thought, well, this is this is really
interesting because I I know that I am
totally abundant all the time. And it's
it was interesting how little it really
mattered to me, okay, to have these
things taken. I thought, you know, I can
always replace this. It's no big deal.
And somebody else is probably feeling
very abundant right now to some degree.
Maybe, maybe not. Maybe not. They're
doing whatever they're doing. But I am
able to let go of that without a strain
because I realize it's part of the
abundance. And by having that
taken then something else can come in
and fill and also it is your opportunity
to realize that in an overall sense
nothing can really be taken from you.
Yes. It is all part of the same world.
It hasn't left the earth. That's right.
And coincidentally enough, I was just
saying to uh someone probably about the
time this happened, as a matter of fact,
that um the things we have in the world
are not really our possessions. We just
kind of use them while we're here. And
we never really own them. They are your
creations. They are your reflections.
And they are here uh for us to create
and enjoy. But in the ultimate sense, we
don't really own them. It's it's
something um that we use while we're here and it
um that we use while we're here and it
doesn't matter. I mean in although you
both use them temporarily and you do in
an ultimate sense completely and utterly
own them because they are extensions of
you. Yes, that's true. also recognize
that again not that this particular
methodology is one that needs to remain
nor are we condoning it as a
representation of integrity because
obviously it is not. But even those
individuals who function outside of
their integrity still can play their
part in getting integrity going in your
world. Because those that may shuffle
objects around out of the home of one
individual into the home of another
individual are still doing their part
whether they realize it or not to extend
the idea of your earth as a global
community. for the
idea. The idea used to be that well if
it was out of your immediate sight then
it was actually gone from your sphere of
influence. But now you are realizing
that this object could wind up anywhere
in the world and you could run into it
again and sometimes do and sometimes do
because this shuffling around allows you
to recognize the fluidity with which you
are connected to the entire earth.
Nothing is beyond your sphere of
influence. You follow me? I sure do. So,
it has not truly in that sense been
taken from you. It has simply been
placed in another room in the large
house you now live in. Exactly. And
that's a wonderful
example that just that shuffling around
of the the law of abundance which is
inflow and outflow. And again, and
shuffling. This methodology will change.
No need to use this idea from the point
of view of lack of integrity as these
individuals are doing. But again, when
each and every individual blends into
the understanding that nothing is really
taken, it is still there and still
accessible, then is when they will allow
these individuals also to regain their
own power when they know they can't take
anything from anyone because the
individuals will always have access to
it no matter how far physically it goes
from the original quote unquote owner.
Yes, I remember hearing you say Bashar
that uh nothing can be taken from you
that you need to be the expression of
the idea that you are. Okay. And that
was one of the things I thought of today
and I I realized well great. And in this
sense you even have an example of the
polarity quote unquote in your terms of
having something been taken quote
unquote from you in order to aid and
assist in the idea that you are excited
about becoming because it has forced you
to expand your senses to include a wider
range of what you will call your
immediate influencable surroundings.
Yes. And the gift that was given back
dolphins. What could be better? Yes. for
they range far and wide. And may I
remind each and every one of you, there
are no countries in the ocean.
There are no borders in the sea.
Oh, thank you very much.
You I have a question. Uh speak up. Okay.
I have a question. Uh speak up. Okay.
Well, thank you.
I have been listening to a couple of
your tapes and what I get from them is
the bottom line is trust. Uh live for
what excites you. Okay guys, um right
now I am experiencing that there is
nothing that is as exciting to me that
I'm doing in my life except reading
death material or except listening to
you or finding out these answers to
questions that I've had for as long as I
can remember. All right, but what can
you do with this information? I can
share it. All right, then that is an
active doing. Okay. Um,
is that not exciting? That's marvelously
exciting. All right. Okay. Thank you.
Then shake by all means and you will be
doing putting into action what it is you
are learning to be as an example as a
reflection. Then you will be doing your
part. Okay. So basically working at
some job let's say what we call an
occupation that I'm doing is not really
exciting to me. It takes up a lot of my
day. But within the midst of that, I can
be creating other people or having them
in my creation as as as picking up
certain things or or or I can share what
I know with them in that atmosphere. And
when you are then willing to put out
what you take in, you may find that that
action in and of itself may simply
effortlessly and before you know it turn
into its own occupation. Great. Thank
you. Oh, thank you very much. For sure.
Hey, um I'm in a creative field where
sometimes I need to create when I'm not
feeling creative or when the materials
or fabrics I'm dealing with don't excite
me. And then always simply trust at that
moment that whatever does excite you is
what will put you back in touch with the
perspective, the point of view, the
angle of approach necessary for you to
recreate excitement to allow you to
continue to complete that particular
idea or project. So if you find at any
given moment that your creative flow is
not in that particular direction you
think it should be in, but it is in this
direction, even though that definition
of that direction may not immediately
seem to be connected to the job at hand,
trust that it is. As long as you are
honest with yourself that you are truly
not running away from something, then
understand that you are running to
something. Allow yourself to become a
spontaneous generator of excitement in
all probable directions. So that when
the excitement seems to vanish from this
particular line, you pick it up on this
line. Whether it seems connected to the
other line or not, always you will know
that whatever you find on this line will
be applicable to this line as well since
this originally did represent what
excited you. But why so many times am I
creative like on a whim almost? I have I
seem to have no control over it. It
comes, it goes. I never know when to
expect it. And that is all right. I
mean, is that being spontaneous or is
that just being out of control? It can
be being both. But recognize again, it
devolves the idea of what we have said
of being honest with yourself as to
whether you really truly want to do what
you are doing or whether you would
really rather be doing something
else. First of all, determine that.
Now understand again that wide degrees
of
spontaneity may to some individuals at
first seem like you are
scattered. But that spontaneous change
in and of itself is a very stabilizing
phenomena because change is the only
constant. You follow me? Yeah. When you
are honest with yourself about what it
is you truly in an overall sense do
desire to be doing, then you will
understand that all the changes and the
seemingly scattered approaches that take
place within that overall idea must
therefore by definition all be a part of
the manifestation of that overall idea
and not a diversion from
it. So if at one moment you are working
on this and say well it seems that right
now this has run dry. I need to come up
let us say for example with a pattern
for this particular idea I find my
imagination gives me nothing right now
what my imagination does find exciting
all let's say is a walk on the beach off
I go see you later as you are walking
along that beach and mesmerized by the
ocean appearing on the shore lo and
behold you look down and washed up to
your feet is the most beautiful little
shell with the exquisite and perfect
pattern you need to complete your job.
You follow me? Yeah. Life does work that
way when you let it. And there is no
such thing as something that is too good
to be true.
You follow me? Yeah. Let it work for
you. I I kept thinking when I would get a
I I kept thinking when I would get a
block, I could work through the block
instead of But a block is not something
to avoid. A block is something to
experience. If you find you have what you used to
If you find you have what you used to
call a block, simply treat it as a sign
that points in an unexpected direction.
It only becomes a block when you insist
that you still want to go straight ahead
and keep banging your head into the
wall. Following the unexpected
direction, left or right, is the way to
actually go most quickly straight ahead.
But you will create it in an unexpected
way so that along the way you will have
the insights and the new knowledge that
you wish to
learn. So that by the time you do get to
where you thought you were going all
along, you will have taken a route that
will bring you a greater appreciation of
the scenario when you arrive there. You
follow it? Yes. Thank you. Enjoy life in
the moment. It is all orchestrated for a
reason. Your
reason. Enjoy it.
Sure. Thank you. Thank you. Hey
There's a big difference between want
and need. There can be. There's not have
to be, but there can be. Well, if
somebody wants something but doesn't
necessarily need it and they desire,
will they will they get what they want
even though they don't need it? Let me
put it this way. If you really want it,
but do not need it to get what it is you
really want, then you won't get what you first
want, then you won't get what you first
wanted, but will get what you need
because you are saying that what you
need is what will help you get what you
really want.
However, always, always, always you have
the opportunity to explore that what you
truly find yourself most compassionately
desirous of is usually in synchronous
alignment with what you need. Therefore,
at no time hesitate or stop yourself
from opening up to allow the situations
and opportunity in your life that will
bring you what you want. Simply be very
honest with yourself as to whether what
you want truly is what you want. Because
many times many individuals will think
they want something and the only reason
they want that is because they are
avoiding something else that they really
do want that they think will be an
effort to get.
They are not giving themselves perhaps
an opportunity to realize that what they
truly do need, what they truly do
desire is able to be manifested in your life
is able to be manifested in your life
just as effortlessly as what it may
appear on the surface that you want.
Simply be very honest with yourself as
to whether what you think you want is
truly what you want in your
life. There are many ways to go about
finding this out.
You may at any given moment simply ask
yourself, well, all right, here is
something I truly truly
want. Now, what do I imagine would happen if I
Now, what do I imagine would happen if I
got
it? What would
happen? Ask yourself that first of all.
Ask yourself also if you really believe
that you deserve what you want. Because
many individuals do not attract into
their lives what they truly want because
they have a stronger belief that they
somehow don't deserve
it or that they won't be able to handle
it or that they won't be able to
appreciate it. You follow
me? If any of these apply, examine these
ideas first. Now once
again we will refer you if you have not
already been
referred to very strong methodology
provided by consciousness you know as
Lazarus manifesting in your life what
you desire. This already exists and many
individuals in the room can refer you to
this tape as you call
it. Have you already participated in
this interaction? Um, I've listened to
the first three sides but haven't filmed
the meditation.
Then what are you waiting for?
If you truly truly want what you say you
want, why would you ignore a tool that
is placed in your hand that is printed
boldly on that tool? Use this. You will
get what you want. Why would you
hesitate even one second? Examine that
honestly with yourself and then perhaps
you will know why you are not getting
what you
want, why you are hesitating. When you
are honest with yourself about why you
hesitate to use something that might be
able to actually bring it to you, then
you will know why you do not experience
it. I know why why I haven't done it is
because I'm afraid. Afraid of what? I
don't know. I don't know. Afraid of
failing. Yeah. Rejection.
Yeah. Rejection.
Rejection in what way?
No, I'm not good enough. Good enough for
what? For who?
For everybody else. Everybody else. May
I remind you of something?
Yes. No. Maybe. Oh, thank you. Do you
exist? Yes. Then you are obviously good enough
Yes. Then you are obviously good enough
for the infinite creator. Who else do
you need to worry about?
[Music] Well, the thing is that what I desire or
Well, the thing is that what I desire or
what I want. Yes. Um
in order for me to go as far as I want
to go with it. Oh, you think you will be
infringing on someone else. Other people
have to enjoy it. But
recognize if you truly are functioning
within your
integrity and you are then still
desirous of a certain idea to be
manifest in your life, let it manifest
in your life in whatever way will still
allow you to feel as if the core idea
has manifested and let it manifest in a
way that will attract to you whatever
individuals can enjoy it. going to think
that what you have manifested in your
life is something that will work for
them. You are not responsible for the
way they choose to believe what your
life is all about. That is your
responsibility. You are not responsible
for their choices. If you know you are
functioning within your integrity and
are not consciously attempting to do
anyone malicious harm in the creation of
what you desire most, then simply don't
worry about it. you will attract the
individuals that will be able to
appreciate it. And if those other
individuals do not wish to appreciate
it, that is their choice. They will go
and appreciate something else.
Was um the other thing that I um am
working toward somehow I don't I don't
see it in the future or I don't I don't
see it happening but I want it to and I
don't know if I should just stop and not
try. One moment. First of all, recognize
there is no need to try. But you are
also contradicting yourself. If you
cannot see it happening at all, then how
is it you are aware that this thing
exists within you? How do you know it is
something you want to do if you can't
see it? Well, it's it's existing, but
not to the potential that I want it to.
Yes. Then design it in your imagination
to exist at the potential you desire it
to. Okay? And again, stop judging where you
Okay? And again, stop judging where you
are to be less worthy of where you are
going. You follow me? Yeah. Where you
are is where you need to be. And again,
the paradox in life is that when you let
where you are be the perfect place you
need to be, you get to where you want to
go that much more quickly because you
are not invalidating where you are as
one of the stepping stones that will
take you where you are going. When you
don't let where you are be all right,
you can't use it to take the next
step because you are avoiding being now
and you only exist now. You will always
only exist now. If you avoid existing
now, then you do not create a place for
anything in your life that you desire to
come to. Now is the only place they have to
to. Now is the only place they have to
come. And when you don't let the now you
are be valid, you have locked them
outside.
You follow me? Yes, I do. Thank you.
Thank you very much for your own
awakening, your own awareness. All it
takes is the fact that you can love
yourself as unconditionally as infinite
creation loves you by having created you
to begin with, which obviously therefore
lets you know you deserve to exist.
Don't fight yourself. Relax. Love
yourself. Trust yourself. You know what
you are doing. Do not put so many
demands or expectations upon the idea.
Have the expectancy that you deserve
what you want. But there is no need to
rigorously define exactly how it must
come to you or you won't accept it.
Because there are many ways that it
could come to you that your conscious
mind may not be able to be aware of. And
if it comes to you in any of those other
ways, if you're only focused on saying,
"Well, it won't be valid if it doesn't
come in this form," then they can knock
at the doors until they are blue in the
face, and you will never hear them
because you will not allow those doors
to be open because you will not accept
this idea that you want to come in any
other version, any other
fashion other than the way you are
rigidly defining that it must come.
When it comes, no matter in what version
it comes, because it is the fulfillment
of what you desire, it will still feel
correct. All right. Thank you very much.
You may all take a short, relaxing, and
loving break.
I don't see sharing you.
Um, okay. So, I just want to tell you
that last Wednesday night, I guess it
was, um, I seem to have stepped through
a doorway, and that doorway is,
uh, I guess you could symbolize it by
saying that I stopped smoking, but it's
not the stopping smoking that did it. It
was what preceded the stopping smoking.
And what occurred was I was
instantly excited by everything. and the
excitement and I've gone through some of
the stuff that we've been talking about
about well do you know nothing excites
me
and but whatever this was perhaps it was
a distraction and then it no longer was
a distraction I was really really in
present time and being there I
discovered that place I I seem to be in
the middle of everything or the center
of everything or whatever it was still
am and in that place I I it's Every cell
was vibrating. That is the vibration of
excitement. So therefore, everything is exciting.
So therefore, everything is exciting.
Yes. So when everything is exciting,
everything just unfolds.
And that's what's been happening. Then I
I went into the grocery store and I I
saw this little child. She must have
been a year year and a half years old.
Appropo. She was
really uh probably the excitement you
felt was the excitement you feel as a
child. Oh, we should if you could have
seen her. She was the most beautiful.
She was the most radiantly loving child
I've ever seen. And and she looked at me
so directly and was such takes one to no
one. I realized later, I mean, I was almost
I realized later, I mean, I was almost
in tears looking at her. I just I took
my eyes off of her. She was so
wonderful. And I I went, "Oh my god,
that's me." Hey, listen. All of us,
right? And um all these wonderful,
beautiful symbols and the kind of
synchronicity I've been waiting for,
guys. It is all right here, right now,
in the very same moment with everything
else. Yeah, it's just exquisite. Um the
other thing I also noticed that in that
idea of blending the male and female
polarities um uh and the the universe
tending towards the positive um it seems
it seems you got a positive and a
negative somehow revolving around a ne a
neutrality. Is that correct? That's the
way it seems to me. I mean, I know it's
there's a little more to it than that is
when you get down to molecular whatever
biology, but um that concept is it the
fact that it is revolving around
something means that it is attracted to
that center thing in some way or or
somehow it's held together by that. We
went through this last week. It is held
together by that because it is it,
right? But in other words, they're all
the same thing. Yay. Yeah, that's all
pretty obvious. Thank you. Um,
thank you for being this gate, this
doorway and sharing of this recognition
and realization so that others can
cocreate with you their version of the
same doorway and recognize that many
times when we say to you, well, what
excites you the most? The idea is that
when you do live in the moment,
everything excites you. The beautiful
thing is that there is just a
fearlessness that is so wonderful.
That's like a a sword that that's made
out of lightning or something. I will do
anything. I have and I can't wait to do
it all. Right. It's that kind of
feeling. It's just an inspiration. Just
con just I am inspiration. Thank you
very much. Thank you. Sure.
So, further in the adventures of the
wizard. Uh the wizard has encountered
the little boy who didn't get to go to
the circus. Oh, all right. And it seems
like there's a battle uh of who is
stronger between the two. Uh there
between which two? The little boy who
didn't get to go to the circus and the
wizard. So cannot the wizard take the
little boy to the circus. The little boy
seems to be more powerful at this moment
than the wizard and do you mean that the
little boy does not want to go to the
circus? The little boy is holding a
position which is I'm not clear about
and maybe you can throw some light on
that. It seems What does the little boy
seem to be saying? Seems to be saying,
"I'm not going to let you do whatever
you want to do."
Will you ask the little boy if the
little boy does or does not want to go
to the circus? He doesn't want to go to
the circus.
All right. The bigger issue is being
chopped in the middle of his expectation
of going to the circuit and not getting
to go and then the position that he took
as a result of that. All
right. Is the
wizard capable of
recognizing in the little
boy those
qualities that created ultimately So
wizard is somewhat removed from my
consciousness. That's only a
perspective. Yes, that's the way it
appears. All right. But do you recognize
that the wizard came from the little
boy?
Uh, I haven't considered it up to this
moment. Is it an aspect of you? This
idea of the wizard is a little boy an
aspect of you. Are they not all aspects
in direct lineage of the idea you are
being right now? Yes. Then one is
connected to the other and they all
share the same power.
You can allow the little boy to
understand that regardless of the stance
they chose. Notwithstanding, they still
chose. Notwithstanding, they still
became not only capable of visiting the
circus anytime they wanted to, but of
actually being in charge of the
circus by becoming the wizard
eventually. Regardless of the stance
they took, regardless of what the little boy
took, regardless of what the little boy
created for himself to experience in
life with regard to the cutting off of
his expectations, even that which at the
time may have seemed to be such a
negative scenario still led to the
creation of an individual who was now
pondering himself as a wizard.
So no matter what the stance of the
little boy
was, you were still
undaunted. You still created the ability
to recognize yourself as becoming the
wizard. So in no way, shape or form did
that stance inhibit
you. You have still created and are
still creating what you desire. You are
visiting the circus every day.
You are the circus.
[Music] All the little boy needs to realize is
All the little boy needs to realize is
that at any given moment he always had
the ability to be the circus rather than
feel it was someplace beyond his reach
to attain by himself.
That's good. And limitations are only
definitions and not always to be
believed. And if one seems to be a limitation in
And if one seems to be a limitation in
one direction, then that is an
indication that you have the ability to
go in another direction to create the
same idea, which is what you have
done. You have used one apparent
limitation to create a being that is now
beginning to recognize himself as
unlimited. Congratulations.
Thanks. Thank you.
Welcome to the show.
Does that assist you? Yes, it helps.
Thank you very much. May I May I ask
another question? Of course. I've heard
that uh somebody by the name of Newman
is running a car around a track uh
somewhere in Kentucky without any fuel.
Uh I don't know anything more about it
than that. This
device will be one of the devices that
will become more and more prevalent in
your society as you recognize once again
that the earth itself is a generator and
that you can tap into it in many
different ways regardless of what let us
say your power companies tell you.
Is there a way of getting more
information about that? Yes,
I can do this. You got Okay, there you
go. Thank you. Thank you both.
Thank you. Thank you both.
Hey, venue. Oh, yes. I want to ask you
about frequencies. Uh I've become very
interesting interested in radionics. All
right. And before when I was in in Eugene, uh
And before when I was in in Eugene, uh
it's extremely quiet in Eugene, Oregon.
And at night, I would hear like this
high frequency. It was almost like a a
Morris Coke. And at first I tried not to
hear it and then I allowed myself to go
with the sound. Very good. For more and
more individuals are beginning to
perceive the background vibration of the
collective consciousness that you are
upon your planet.
Right. And that's what I thought it was.
And when I would go with the
sound, thank you. When I would go with
the sound, I would go with it all the
way and suddenly it would stop. Very
good. Um, since I've been here, I don't know
Um, since I've been here, I don't know
if it's noisy or what, but I haven't
been tuned into the sound. It is all
right. Many times recognize you will
simply give yourself a temporary
auditory manifestation of that vibration
to simply let you know you are of that
frequency. The idea is not to simply
continue to sit around and listen to it,
but to do something with the energy that
you now know you are the frequency of.
You will always shift the frequency a
little bit to give yourself the
opportunity to do something with the
energy. That is all. Thank you. Have a
good time. Thank you. Thank you,
guys. Hi. Hi.
Um, well, first of all, I got my piano.
I don't know if you remember our little
talk. Okay. Um, and I had budgeted that
it getting this grand piano I wanted was
about $15,000 worth of piano. Um, and
going back to music school would take me
financially about a year and a half to
to do because money and my credit,
whatever. But anyway, 17 days after my
conversation with you, I got the piano
and went back to school and I finished
finals two weeks ago. Congratulations.
You have graduated in more than once.
Yeah. Um, I um am playing a lot more
music now and and doing more performing,
which is what I've wanted all along. My
my
um uh one
I'm fine. Go on. Okay. Um one thing I
noticed some people get so excited by
success. Thank you.
Thank you.
Um, uh, one thing I noticed is that a
part of my identity that I've had for a
long time, I'm I'm one of those, uh, or
my past has been one of those seriously
trained Giuliard elitist pianists.
Quite a mouthful. Yes. And it has served
me uh, in a lot of ways positively. It
looks great on a resume and I've gotten
a lot of values out of it. All right.
But I'm finding that and
and and and I'm finding and I'm finding
that the new era musically that I want
to move into now in my life that won't
work anymore. It's this elitist thing is
building up more fear, more
self-exectation, um more paranoia about whether other
um more paranoia about whether other
people will like my craft. And I I want
to just let go and not and let divorce
my craft from this intense judgment. Go
right ahead. Continue by all means to
ahead. Continue by all means to
experience the same degree of joy and
ecstasy that has gotten you to this
point. And it will allow you to be a
flawless version of whatever you are
being. And you will be being enjoyed by
many individuals.
No reason to stop using joy. Wow.
I'm experiencing a lot of confusion
about well with this shift is an entire
shift in all of my musical values. Yes.
So I don't I no longer know what kind of
musician I am.
You are a happy one.
[Music]
You are now free to explore any form of
expression you desire. You are no longer
limited. What do you mean you have to
know what kind you are? You are a
musician. Play as you feel so inclined.
Well, okay. Oh, thank you.
Enjoy. All right. Thank you.
Keep it simple. Okay. Let it be.
Sherry. Yeah. Um, I might ask more. Um, a friend
Yeah. Um, I might ask more. Um, a friend
of mine um has uh um somewhat a low
self-esteem and has fits a very severe
depression. And I've been working with
this person for a few weeks and and last
week I brought them here to this uh
meeting and and she was very impressed
with the positive uh you know feeling
around. Anyway, at the end of last week,
um she disappeared and went away. Nobody
knows where without money, clothes or
anything. Um and and all her friends and
uh boss and everything was extremely
concerned. We got the police onto it and
everything. Anyway, she finally turned
up this afternoon and is not uh
communicative to anybody. Is is she's in
one of the very severe bits of
depression. Again, I'm I'm not sure
whether to the person I'm perhaps being
too encouraging or or in some way I'm
I'm I'm bewildered as say to be most
effective. All right. First of all,
start trusting yourself. Otherwise,
you're not going to be very effective
for anyone on any level. All right.
Start trusting your own instincts. Start
trusting your own compassion and your
own empathy and
sensitivity. Now, that individual took
many things that were discussed to
heart. both from us and from you and
simply went about attempting to apply
them. But this individual still did it
in the form of a test and so very
quickly reached a certain limit. They
will pass through it. It is their own
enforcement of their own type of
limitation for now in which there is
much connection taking place.
They will reemerge when they understand
that the so-called depression is only a
meditation and is only looked at as
negative by a society that thinks that
that is a form of running away instead
of understanding completely yourself.
When you know the answers cannot be
found externally, you go to where you
know they are within. That is simply a
meditative act. Does not have to be
looked at as negative depression in that
way. And when the individual reemerges
from this idea, they will be a new
person. Literally, what they are doing
now is going through major
reconstruction of the artificial
construct of the persona that they are.
You follow me? Yes.
Send your love. We will send out energy.
Allow them to know they are always
supported, unconditionally, always
loved. To some
degree, you may approach this individual
in much the same manner as you would
approach an autistic
individual. For that is similar in terms
of its idea of complete withdrawal.
Love them, support them, share with
them, touch them physically if that is
all right with them. Let them know you
are simply there. Let them know you
accept them as they are. And then they
will reemerge. Perhaps while your back
is turned, they will say something. You
will turn around and find a completely
new person staring at you.
Thank you. But begin to trust yourself
as well. Otherwise, then you will not
function as a reflection of that
infinite support.
Thank you. Thank
y first is um to
a recent friend I just made a friendship
with. Um she told me about an experience
she had with some uh dolphins. Um I
can't recall it was a few years ago. It
was off Malibu and she was with eight
other people on a boat and there was a
lot of boat other boats around for a
while but then all of a you know like
over a period of time all the other
boats went and they were the only craft
there. Nice. And
then over a thousand
dolphins surrounded their boat and kind
of hung out there for a few hours and
just kind of played and stuffed in the
water. Nice. And I was just wondering if
you have any reflections on that. We
have already suggested that that is a
very highly active area. one of the very
highly active areas containing many
dreamers which are the dolphins we refer
to that are specifically the ambassadors
between their species and your species
and willing to communicate with you not
only in dream states but in physical
awareness as well. They will simply
always show up when they need to reflect
to any individuals present aspects
within themselves. Generally speaking,
that those individuals now need to be
aware of physically because the
individuals that the dolphins generally
show up to particularly on that level in
that magnitude are individuals that
whether they consciously know it or not
have had many dream interactions with
those dolphins before and have simply
led themselves into a waking dream.
You follow me? Yes. It is one way of
beginning to learn how to blend the
dream and the physical reality into one
ecstatic moment of
experience. Let them follow their
hearts. They will discover more.
Can be in the same area if they wish.
Perhaps I'll present an idea. All right.
They are open invitations to share to
swim in the same sea to swim in the same
dream. Perhaps I'll do it. By all means.
The other thing was um yesterday I got
on the bus to go to work and
uh I've been exploring this whole idea
of abundance and the whole money thing
because money thing
in this life. Uh I've chosen to not
experience a lot of
abundance financially. And anyway, I got on the
financially. And anyway, I got on the
bus and You mean up till now? Yes, up
till now. All right.
I got on the bus and uh this lady
sitting next to me, she she just kind of
leaned over and she she said, "Did you
watch the Big Spin on
Saturday?" And and I said, "Uh, no. Did
you?" And she said, "Yes, my daughter
won $3.8 million."
And my you attract your symbols, don't
you? I've been uh
I've been uh
pondering what this symbol really means.
Well, it is an opportunity for you to
realize that you cannot see something in
someone else unless you contain the same
potential and that you will attract to you the
and that you will attract to you the
reflections of what you are on the same
vibratory level. So become just as
excited as she is and you will attract
the same vibrations. It is an
opportunity for you to see a symbol that
you can home in on a frequency that you
can identify with to create your reality
to be similar to their reality. So
something will rub off so to speak. You
give yourself a symbol that you can form
an identical identification pattern
with. You felt the vibration of her
excitement, did you not? Yes. Create it
as your own. And that vibratory
frequency will lead you to the same type
of experiences.
And it doesn't have to be about money.
No. But if that was the specific
vibrational frequency of that particular
event, in all likelihood it might be
because that's the particular frequency
she was excited about, the one you
attract to you. So you could learn how
to identify with it, copy it, and create
it to be your own.
Copy it in a literal sense. In a sense,
yes. Identification is mimicking other
patterns and creating them to be your
own so that you will then be of a
similar frequency and attract similar
experiences. [Laughter] [Laughter]
[Music]
understand. Yes, it is simple physics.
That the same as the abundance formula
that you shared with us last year to
some degree, but it is in many ways not
dissimilar to many of the ideas being
put forth on your planet now that you
colloially refer to as
neurallinginguistic programming.
The idea of finding someone that is
doing what you want and acting like them
so that you will be of the same
vibratory frequency and attract similar
events. Thank you Michelle. Michelle, are you
Thank you Michelle. Michelle, are you
through? Uh, one other thing then you
Yes. the idea of lightness that has been
coming to me today in body weight. Okay.
And like yesterday I weighed myself for
the first time in quite a while. Um, and
I found that I had actually lost bodily
weight, so to speak. You are turning
mass into energy. You are moving. You
are accelerating. Cuz I don't feel
physically any different. I feel fine.
We understand.
You are stopping waiting. You are now
doing. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Hey. Yeah. I was wondering
um what uh what your perception was of
the energy associated with the uh
following idea. Um there may be a
possibility for me to become part to
start well of a new company kind of
thing. And will it take as long to
happen as it took to say?
Well, it's it's still very vague.
Nothing's been decided and at times I'm
excited over it and at times I'm not but
I'm not unexited and my that sounds
exciting. Well well and it's not
something I'm I'm anxious about. I mean
it will happen or it will won't happen
but I was curious if you sensed any what
kind of energy you sensed around that
idea. Yes, I sense it is vague. [Music]
[Music]
Come, come, come.
A decision has been made within you.
I'm not aware that I've made a decision
about it.
The decision that you have made will
simply be reflective as to what happens
being in synchronous accord with what
excites you the most or not.
Well, the way I feel right now is that I
could make it exciting. I couldn't make
myself make it exciting. I could make I
could decide I'm going to be excited
over it. And what are you excited about
doing right now? Well, what I'm doing
right now is Are you excited about
waiting to see what happens?
Knowing that whatever comes out of this
will be representative of something that
you will find exciting. Yes, that I
totally agree with. All right, then
relax and enjoy yourself in the
meantime. But yeah, then enjoy what you
are doing now. You don't have to know
anything more about what will happen
since you know it will be in synchronous
accord with something you will enjoy one
way or another. I wasn't asking what
will happen. I was asking if you
perceived any kind of energy associated
with that at this time. A roundabout way
of saying what will happen.
Well, if I say what will happen, you say
you don't make predictions. Well, I will
not make a prediction no matter how you
phrase it.
But a lot of times you do say our
sensing of the energy at this time is
such and such. That's all I was trying.
At times I do say that. However, it is
always superseded by the phrase what do
you feel? I I understand that I do know
what I feel. Ah and obviously you don't
want to tell me what or maybe you don't
sense any energy associated with it.
Yes, I do. I sense that you waiting to
find out right now is what you need to
be doing.
You see, I can be just as vague as you.
Oh, okay. That's fine. And you don't
think we've learned anything from
I know you've learned things. I've
noticed it as I'm listening to you know
used to listen to earlier tapes and so
on and even listening to you each week I
have noticed that you have changed a lot
and sometimes you have
become I I don't like to say more
understanding but you seem
to know but it's true but you seem
to have a different perspective than you
you had maybe a few weeks I find that
very because all of you do. I I
understand that and I I find that
fascinating. Me too.
Nice talking with you.
I always love talking with you.
Anyway, as you say, right, our sensing
at this
time, basically what you feel to be
so-called vagueness about the situation
is your indication that you don't have
to think about it right now and you
don't have to ask anyone else. Let it
play out. Many decisions have not yet
fallen into place.
When they do, you'll have the
determinations you need. Okay, great.
Thank you. Enjoy in the I am. I am.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
There will be but a few moments
remaining for this interaction.
Um a while back ago you uh reflected
that I might find that shaped piece of
laport. sort of energy. Yes. And um I uh
went about getting it cut and uh I seem to
about getting it cut and uh I seem to
have created a a new opportunity to get
another one cut. Oh, what the the
gentleman I told him was a more
equilateral triangle and he goes, "Okay,
okay." And he wrote down tetra min which
looks like it the bottom triangle is not
the same side. All right. So the first
opportunity you have learned from this
symbol is clarity of communication.
Well, I did make it clear to him, but it
was obviously clear to him that he was
going to make what he wanted to make
anyway. Very good. But the the thing
which really gets me about this is he
says that it's impossible to cut it. And
I and it's an older gentleman who I'm
sure he knows a lot more about this
situation than I do, but I You're so
sure. Well, he thinks he does, I guess.
I don't know. It can't be impossible. It
is not far from it. Well, now I'm now
I'm uh just going to like uh do another
uh opportunity kind of just like run an
ad that somebody could just Perhaps
there are individuals present this night
of your time that have some
accessibility to information as to how
to have that stone cup in a tetrahedral
format. Thank you. Um I hear the noise.
You wonder if anybody
Thank you. Sure.
Would you share a title? Uh, you got the
title for last week and this week,
please. Already did.
The Awakening 2, three, and four coming
up. Awakening part one, two, three, four.
Awakening part one, two, three, four.
Thank you. I didn't hear that. Oh, yes.
Um, on the issue of integrity.
Integrity. Um, it seems like a beautiful
gift. I know it is. Um, here it comes. in I
in I
have I am working
with really establishing or discovering
the real me again or the me that I want
to actualize. No. Right. And I have in
the past considered being out of
integrity. No, of course. All of you
have at one time or another. Thank you.
That's it on that question then. Um it's
no big deal. In other words, no. You
have learned that that is not what you
prefer. So you have used it in a
positive way to become what you do
prefer. No big deal. Over and that was
then. Mrs. Oh, thank you. Um, another
question is I have something coming up
that has been a long time coming in a
sense in terms of dropping my
expectation but still working with my
beliefs as to allow it. Can you say
anything about that? Do you understand
what I said? Trust your expectancy.
Trust your
deservability. Own it now. You do not
think twice about something you already
own. Reach beyond it. If you know it is
already complete, what is the next thing
that will come after that? What will you
build on top of what you already own?
Reach beyond this idea and then you will
see that you already readily contain
this idea. It will be a foregone
conclusion that it is your experience.
Yeah. You're saying in a sense do think
about what you're going to do after
that. Think about what you're going to
use it for. Act as if this is already
done with that the process continues.
Otherwise, if you continue to place this
goal on the outer edge of your ability
or your perceptible reality, then you
will make it difficult to bring it in
unless they make something bigger after
it. Yes. Expand your horizon so that
that idea is well within the boundaries
of what you already take for granted to
be yours.
You follow me? Yes, very much. Just like
the karate job when you break a brick.
You are seeing yourself already beyond
the brick, not at the brick. Correct.
Correct.
Friendly at this timing there for as
each and every one of you
expands the previously held set of
limitations. Now
beyond those horizons, you will begin to
truly experience yourselves as unlimited
creators, which is what you
are. Again, colloquially, if you wish
the entire Earth, reach for the moon. If
you wish the moon too, reach for the
sun. If you wish for the sun as well,
reach for all the planets in your
system. And if you would like all of
that in your pocket, as you say, reach
for the stars. You will have it all
because you are all of
it. Unconditional joy, unconditional
excitement, and love do we experience in
all of our interactions with you. We
thank you for your infinitely loving
gift of willingness to allow us to
experience your world and share with us
our dream together. Bond and
unconditionally loving good night to you
all.