All right. I say synchronicity to you
all. Thank you.
Thank you.
So, as each and every one of
you individually and
collectively allow yourselves to
begin to freely explore the dimension of
your imagination.
Each and every one of you can find
contained therein many
therein many
ideas that can take
on the degree of reality that you have
previously only
ascribed to what you call your normal
day-to-day physical reality.
In this way, you will find that the
evening out and softening of your focus
upon what you have long considered to be
your only one solid real physical
reality will allow
you to defocus from what is exterior to
yourselves and focus on what is within.
In this way, you can hear the echoes of
a multitude of infinite realities that
all exist within your being, and you can
begin to pay attention to them. In a
sense, as really as you pay attention to
the outward reality you have considered
to be the only reality for so
long. In this way, you can begin to
explore all of the recesses you have
created within
yourself. All the different worlds that
exist within
you, all the different parallel
alternate realities, all of the ideas you have for
realities, all of the ideas you have for
so long considered to be nothing more
than merely shadows within yourself. You
can now begin to recognize that they
have substance just as much
substance just as much
substance as the world round and bound
to that you have created for you have
only created the world round and bound
to you from similar shadows similar
illusions similar ideas and imaginings
in this way and carried with them added
to them attached to them simply the idea
of
solidity. Now, as you begin to explore
the idea of your subconscious, your
unconscious mentality, as you attract to yourself
mentality, as you attract to yourself
all the archetypical symbols that flow
on a strata beneath the idea of your
outward consciousness, you can begin to
sink into that idea, to float freely
within the depths of your being and
drink deeply of the energies that you
are on every level of yourself and to
allow the underground
streams of energy that compose the other
levels of your being to begin to rise
and bubble to the surface. So that in
this way there can be this explosion
outwardly of all the different ideas you
have for so long suppressed within
yourself and they can come to the
surface through the channel that you
have now created within yourself to be
clear. the conduits, the avenues that
can allow these streams to bubble forth
with crystal clarity to the surface and
intermingle and interflow with the
energy of what you have long considered
to be the outward world. And you will
find in this way that you will
restructure the aura of your planet, the
aura of your being, so that it will
contain within it all probable forms of
communication to all probable
manifestations of any type of reality
that you wish to experience and
intermingle with upon the surface of
your planet within the integrity of your
civilization. Each and every one of you who are now
Each and every one of you who are now
willing to begin to live your dreams
will begin to find your world becoming a
dream world where the idea of what was
previously considered to be solid
reality. And the idea of what was
previously considered to be the nebulous
imagination will begin to eb and flow
into one another. And the ideas will all
be seen to be equally real, equally
solid, and paradoxically and
simultaneously equally fluid and
equally fluid and
shadowlike. And in this way you can form
with ease of creation, with ease of
action, the
intermingling of what you have
previously been so sure about and not so
sure about. And allow yourself to exist
in that one eternal moment in which you
know that all things are
possible. And in this way, in this one
moment of time, this one eternal
nowness, you will find that things are
not so hard-edged. In this way, you can
find that the meest
inflection, the most
filmy aspects,
aspects,
reflections, and shadows of your being.
Each and every one of those
symbolizes an idea, a reality, a
universe unto
itself. And you can begin to taste of
the fullness of your being to express
and experience the
totality that is in your terms
synergistically greater than the sum of
all the parts you have created yourself
to be.
the wholeness of the creation that you are sharing.
are sharing.
You about five weeks ago, I rediscovered
crystal. I haven't quite been the same
since. All right. You are never the same
in any moment of time. You are always a
new you. It's very exciting. I've been
having dreams about crystals. People
teaching you the crystals. Yes. Friends
have been having dreams about seeing me
with their folks. Very good. And it
feels like it's all leading up to
something working with somehow, but I
have not been able. As you allow
yourself to simply enjoy each and every
piece, you will through the same act of
synchronicity of
simultaneousness allow yourself to
recognize how your ideas will become
combinations of all the pieces. Enjoy
what you are doing in the moment and you
will find that the next moment will
allow you to fathom all of the ideas you
are bringing together collectively
within your consciousness.
Thank you. Thank you.
Me. Oh, thank you. Um yes. Okay. Lately
I do feel more and more that I'm um
blending with all of myself. Right.
Okay. Now um I'm also feeling as feeling
like as a part of that I'm feeling very
androgynous but to the point where I'm
feeling um I'm feeling alienated like I'm I'm
um I'm feeling alienated like I'm I'm
feeling right I'm feeling you will then
pass through that
phase for you're simply making the
comparisons of the reality you deem to
be round and bow you with the idea of
the measurement of the blending of
yourself in this way there can be to
some degree an alienation, no pun
intended. And in this way, simply allow
yourself to recognize that you are
simply recognizing the dichotomy of what
you are becoming compared to what you
have been in your society. It is only
one more phase of the blending. You will
acclimate and it will pass and it will
allow you to blossom forth in the idea
of your
uniqueness as opposed to the idea of
alienation. M follow me. Yes, I do. Um
is there anything to assist me right
now? Like I'm feeling a lot of sadness
like um again it is simply a part and
parcel as you say of the idea that as
you make this comparison as you create
the idea of alienation. You are forming
a separation the comparison of the you
now and the you then. You feel you have
lost something but you have lost
nothing. Mhm. You are simply exploring
one more facet, one more perspective of
the idea of yourself, the totality of
each and every portion of your
personality that you are blending
together. And in this way, as you view
them one at a time, you may feel some
detachment in this way. Mhm. But you are
not separated. You are simply making the
rounds within yourself. And when you
come back to the beginning and the
ending of your own circle in this way,
you will allow yourself to incorporate
all that you have experienced into your
own uniqueness.
and will then simply reflect the
totality of the facet that you are. You
can enjoy for now the
alieness for it is a part of you and it
will bring to you connections that you
have made to the idea of being in other
places and that will serve you in the
fullness of time.
All right. Okay. Thank you.
All righty then. Okay. Um, I've had at
least one fourth density experience
which impinged on third density and um,
I'm finding they are appearing as little
mysteries uh, from the third density viewpoint at
uh, from the third density viewpoint at
least at this stage of the game. All
right. I'd like to share this one. It's
kind of funny. All right. My girlfriend
and I uh were uh, getting ready to go to
bed. Well, we'd already been in bed and
we were up and we were in the bathroom
and uh she um she's putting a panty
liner in her panties, right? You know,
so uh that was all well and good. And we
go to bed. Next morning she's she's up.
She's taking a shower. And I come in,
she says, "Did you take my panties off
last night while I was
asleep?" I said, "No, I didn't touch
them." She says, "Well, look in the
trash." And there was this panty liner
that she had put in her panties the
night before. And uh I we both had a
picture as crystal clear as anything
that she put that panty liner in there
and neither of us had taken it
out. And I knew immediately that it had
to be a fourth density u
phenomen. Um and I just it's it's funny
because it comes off as a mystery unless
you realize what it can be, you know.
Okay. And what do you assume it can be
for I have one understanding of this
idea and would share this with you.
Please do. There is in the experience
more and more of force density
phenomena. The aspect that you call the
idea of billocation.
Do you follow me? Yes.
Would you uh elaborate on that please?
Simply in this way you will find that
from time to time at the same time
individuals may have the ability to be
in two places at the same time
and actually in a sense in that way play
out two probable
paths either one of which or more than
two can then be locked onto and become
the new reality regardless of what the
last moment brought. Uhhuh. Do you
follow me? Yes. Would you be specific in
this incident? Simply there was two
probabilities either in this way that
she did or did not. And both are real.
And in this way you lived up to a
certain point the path of one she did
not did not put any and then did not
take it out. Okay. And then abruptly
switched onto the path of the other
where she had already done so taken it
out. Uhhuh. In other words, for you
there was no intervening moments in
between living one path and then living
the other path. Right? You follow me?
Right. Would you be the one that had
billocated then? Yes. In that sense
allowing yourself to be the fulcrum of
the transformation. But you both did it
together in that way. Uhhuh. That's
interesting. So actually both of us
flipped paths. Yes. Although for myself,
it now in a sense recognize that you are
both still in a sense back there as
well. Yeah. On that path, the you that
you both are now is not the same you.
You are in another probable reality of
yourself, though you do not really in
that sense know the difference aside
from the clue you have left. Uhhuh.
This is one of the ideas we have meant
when we say that your physical reality
will begin to unlock.
You will now begin to physiologically,
experientially see what it means to be
in fourth density.
Wow. For you guys. Yes.
Uh is there any way to define from your
point of view define universe because my
feeling is more and more that when you
talk about all the different universes
it really doesn't mean the same than the
way we define universe in third density.
No, right. There can be many
definitions, but in this way, allow me
to say that a universe, if you wish,
within the multiverse of all that is,
can simply be considered to be the
one reality, no matter how large, that
you consider to be your total
reality in space and time.
Okay? And that's why it changes every
time you think something. Yes. Is that
okay? So it's really it's a different
conceptualization than than the way we
were brought up thinking about a
universe to some degree there are
similarities but in this way you may
simply understand that as you recreate
yourself to be a different universe.
Yeah. Or let us say from the other point
of view as you flip through the
universes you are simply redefining your
space-time concepts.
Okay. But it doesn't it's actually it's
not really all that important or is it I
mean not in the sense that you really
have to know well what universe is this
is this universe number 4281
4282 or somewhere in between for there
is an infinite number of universes in
between those two. Yes, I I realize that
but I I couldn't imagine uh I think
about last Friday when Leo was saying
each time you think about an apple, you
know, there's a new universe and Seth
has talked about the same thing. And um
this is simply the product of the
understanding that the totality of your
universe is defined by everything that
you perceive within it. If you make one
change, it is a totally new universe by
definition. In the same way, let us say
by analogy you have what you call a
cube. Each face of all six faces is of a
different color. Now let us say that you
change the color of only one face. Well,
all right. That one face only is
different, but the cube as a total cube
is now also different. That's right.
Right. I have another question and it
has to do with I have a fairly good
feeling now I think about no space and
no time and everything happening
simultaneously but at the same time I also have a
but at the same time I also have a
feeling that um even within this time of
can maybe this now there is some kind of
evolution going on. All right. Now as
you allow yourself to know that you are
creating time in the now moment you then
experience the idea of evolution. Yes,
because you are making there be a
continuity. But in this way it is both.
Again there is no need to allow yourself
to be confused with the idea that well
it's either that there is no time or
there is. Both are real. Both are real.
It is not this or that. It is this and
that. When you require the concept of
time, you will experience it. When you
do not, you won't. Okay. Well, it's
clearly about
um that we we have choices and we that
that is our future self to some extent
in a sense, but it's it's not quite
certain yet that this is actually the
the case even though there's no time.
There really never will be in that
ultimate sense a certainty about it. It
is simply one of the probability and it
is only one of an infinite number of
probabilities in that way and even in
that sense does not have to be so to
speak literal. Yeah. You have your own
future selves as well.
Okay. Thank you. Thank you.
you. You
You
um a person that I know committed
suicide last. Oh, right. And um I I'm
wondering how she is and why that
happened. Confused. She's confused for a
moment. Yes, she is now. Yes. And um
they are
scanning scanning at this time in terms
of what I will now perceive at this
time. My perception is that that
consciousness is scanning for a new
life. one that will reflect the ideas
that they did not allow themselves to
live through so that they can allow
themselves to gain the soul experience
that the soul desired the life to exist
for. They now recognize very shortly
that they will scan and emerge into
physical reality again.
So, she's going to be
happy one way or the other. She'll be
happy. Guys, I have two other questions.
My daughter and I last summer in July
were driving to get her a crystal body
and simply allow the idea of the opening of
simply allow the idea of the opening of
certain channels within that being the
recognition of agreements that that
being has made with other beings with
other consciousness.
Okay. So, what is that purpose for her?
can be simply at this time. Again, it is
be simply at this time. Again, it is
always perch choice, but the connection
is there in the basic sense of the way
in which we usually mean when we say
that we are your future selves. It is an
opening and an offering that our energy
exists for you to make use of in
whatever way you wish to allow yourself
the full recognition of your own
totality. And thus many times
individuals upon your planet will
connect into that energy and utilize it
for themselves forming the archetypal
symbology of recognizing our energy in
the process so that they can allow
themselves to make the connections to
themselves with ease through that
symbology by for now allowing it to be
someone else. Which may seem to be
contradictory but for many of you it is
easier to use us to go through our
symbol to arrive at yourselves than
simply allowing yourself to begin with
yourself to begin with.
Well, he's following.
All right. Thank you, guys. For sure.
The same person that Charlene was
talking about was a member of that group
of people known as Scientologists. Yes.
And I was wondering if you had a
perception as to whether a personal
matter for that soul or whether there
was a conscious intention to bring
examination. Any idea can function as a
service for other individuals who will
allow themselves to view the different
aspects that go into making up any idea.
Now, in this way, there did not have to
be the taking of the life to exemplify
the idea. But perhaps the physiological
personality of that individual did not
believe there was any other
way. She now knows differently.
And the exemplification therefore in the
life that will be lived now will be the
allowance of knowing that there are ways
to communicate to other individuals the
essence of the structure and the belief
system that you are without needing in
this way to feel that there is
any need to give away your power to do
so. You follow me? Right.
You follow me? Right.
For any individual that cares to, they
can utilize that act as a
service. But in this way, it is not that
that was necessary to happen in that
manner for the message to have gotten
across. But there was for that life the
exploration of
limitations. And in this way, the
physiological personality simply agreed
to believe that the limitation was more
real than the unlimitedness of the
being. You follow me?
You follow me?
I understand what you said. I'm not sure
I understand. When individuals create
for themselves the idea that their
reality offers them no way
out, they will then take the one way
they deem to be the only way. And in
this sense, it will be recognized in the
next life as a
polarity that any idea can be lived in
any way that one wishes all the way
through and expressed in unlimited joy
and sharing.
And in the claiming of one's own
power, there will not be the acceptance
of the judgment that comes from everyone
else to them about
themselves. I see. Are are you saying
that the that the church of Scientology
in fact has a structure that so judges
and so limits that that your perception
is that the person's
only that that's the result of this
person's feeling that was the it is the
result of what they chose to believe
about that
structure. Do you follow me? Oh yes. Now
in this way it is one more reflection of
the idea that that structure in general
does represent a structure that was
created for the purpose of allowing many
beings who have involved themselves with
that structure who have had associations
to other civilizations to allow
themselves to assimilate into this your
earth civilization allowing to bring with them
civilization allowing to bring with them
many of the ideas of positivity and
negativity that they are exploring in
the other civilization. In this way, you
will simply find that from time to time
because of the nature of the exploration
of the blending of positive and negative
energy in this way, some individuals
will remember what the structure was for
and some will not. Those that do not may
choose in this way to succumb to the
idea that the structure is too rigid to
allow them the life they chose to live.
What what is our purpose of the as was
just defined the idea of forming a
method of existing upon your planet that
is let us say paralleled similarly to
methods that existed in the
civilizations from which many of those
beings that are now involved in the
structure upon your planet came from.
Which civilizations are those?
Particularly the idea that you have
labeled Orion. M but why would they need this
Orion. M but why would they need this
structure to exist? Why couldn't they
just exist on this planet without that
structure? They are learning that they
do not need the structure but in coming
as you say to hear from there over a
period of many
lifetimes they had to I'll say work
themselves out of the habit
in in the raw materials and I think in
earlier sessions with you although in
truth there is no good or bad or right
and wrong. Correct. You have said that
in our form of reckoning the Orion
energy would be considered a negative.
There are positive factions.
Now the reason for many of the lives
that have been lived upon your planet
came from a time when there was
not understand that in this way the
reason for many individuals lives upon
your planet of earth stems
from the Orion
lives. In other words, all the lives you
have lived on Earth are a result of
choices made in the Orion lives to look
at it linearly. Therefore, since that
time, simply to speak linearly again,
there has grown the opportunity even in
the Orion systems for there to be a
positive and a negative
faction which did not exist at the time
the choice was made many many thousands
of years ago.
Okay, you follow me? Yes, I do. The
reasons that the individuals left the
system left its seed behind and that
seed has grown into an allowance that
did not previously exist in those
negatively oriented systems. For now
there is at this time what you would
call a positive and a negative
expression that mirrors now the
opportunity to recognize that in
synchronous timing you all the beings
from that system upon your earth have
now also created the opportunity for the
equal balancing of choice between
positive and negativity on your
planet. Okay. And many of the systems
that have been created, many of the
rituals, many of the ideas in this way
were simply the methodology that those
beings felt were required to allow them
to work through the last vestigages of
judgment that they brought with them
from those systems.
Very interesting. I spent I spent 17
years deeply involved immersed in
studying the teachings of that group of
people we refer to as Scientologists.
And since in the last few weeks and
perhaps occasion by the reported
physiological death of Mr. Hover, I've
had occasion
to evaluate all that I studied and
learned from the viewpoint of what the
raw people call the law of one. Yes. The
viewpoint that all that there is is the
all that there is. Yes. And I see
clearly um a tremendous confusion within
all of those teachings, Mr. Hbert's
writing. There are some things, many
things that he's written that are in
alignment with the law of war. Yes. And
I see a tremendous amount that is
directly opposed and actually frustrates
the published intention of that
structure. The published intention. How
you may allow yourself to understand
that the perspective of all rituals and
methodologies in this way that have been
borne out and lived through in third
density are now being I'll say beginning
to be viewed from the fourth density
perspective. And so there is then the
recognition now of the polarities within
the structure.
Are those polarities necessary or could
they be weeded out to make the structure
more consistent with the law of one?
Understand that when you are in fourth
density and in your terminology
consistent with the law of one, the
structure itself will no longer exist at
all. It will be relended into the
blending of its polarities and will not
exist in any recognizable form that you
would be able to identify as the same
structure. It is not that the structure
in and of itself will weed out the
negativity. It is simply that the need
for such a structure will no longer
exist. Well, I can see that it won't
exist for somebody who's passed into the
force density. But what my my interest
in my my interest is in determining
whether the structure as it exists now
has usefulness for those for people who
are still in the third density or
whether the structure could have the
negative parts weeded out and the
structure could be transformed to make
it more useful for people in the third
density to some degree individuals who
may choose to remain in third density
may engineer something to that effect,
but in this way also recognize simply
that the idea of that structure even in
the form it has existed has been of
service for it has gotten you where you
are. Agreed. But but I'm wondering
whether it could be re-engineered a
little bit to to provide greater service
to more people or whether it really is
in the best possible form for the
purpose of allow me to ask you the
question in this way.
Okay. Where are you going to be third or
fourth density? Fourth or beyond? Then
never mind.
For in this way third density
interaction will not occur in your life.
It won't be in my universe. But I'm But
then do not be concerned for those that
choose third density know what they are
doing and will engineer what they wish
to serve themselves in that third
density reality. Whether it is a
rearrangement of that structure or a
creation of an entirely new one. I agree
and I understand. But I have a purpose
for being here in physical form in the
same way you have a purpose for
channeling. Are you assuming that fourth
density is non-physical totally?
Um no then understand that you are
already transforming into fourth density
physical form. Yes. Therefore again your
purpose in that way is not so much still
connected to third density physical any
lower. My purpose personally isn't but a
different purpose similar to your
purpose. Your purpose in communicating
here has something to do with assisting
others to make the transition. We
understand your meaning and this we can
offer you. So we use the ideas that come
through in your imagination but
recognize this
in this way. The idea of so-called
weeding out the negativity will not be
getting rid of anything. It will be the
allowance of the integration of positive
and negativity as equal. In this way,
therefore, if you can see within this
so-called structure elements that to you
reflect the idea of positive
manifestation, then you can in whatever
manner your imagination tells you form
an arrangement of those elements in that
structure that will allow there to be
the effect of positive rather than
negative manifestation. But recognize
that positive and negative energy will
always be present because
polarity experienced in that way is
always one of the
key definitions of third density
reality. Say that again. Polarity
itself, the experience that you can have
a choice between positive and negative
effect is one of the definitions of
third density reality.
Mhm. I got it. Very hard times to eliminate.
I got it. Very hard times to eliminate.
Now you can have a life in which you do
not experience negative manifestation
physically but you cannot eliminate
negative energy. You follow me? Yeah, you cannot
energy. You follow me? Yeah, you cannot
get rid of anything that has been
created for there is nowhere to get rid
of anything to once something
exists. It does not not exist. You
follow me? Now it is up to you to allow
them to be equal so that you can choose
which one you prefer to manifest as the
effect in your life knowing that you
have always made a choice between two
things that always will exist. Now in
fourth density reality, there simply is
the opportunity to exercise that choice
to a degree where you do not
experience negative manifested physical
reality. But a fourth density being has
not eliminated anything. It has become
the sum of everything it has ever been
consciously and therefore makes
conscious choices as to what type of
manifested reality it prefers.
But it does this without judging what it
has been. For it knows that to judge
plops it right back into third density.
For then the judgment is the
expression and the reinforcement of
negative manifestation. Judgment itself.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Good evil saying. Yes.
Hard hover talks of a thing that he
describes as asiseness where by creating
something in it in its same unit of time
and space you will produce a
disappearance of the
thing. How does that relate to simply
what is being stated is that as you make
your conscious choices to vibrate
equally to any idea you wish to be then
anything not of that idea will
physiologically phase out of your
existence over a period of time. or
instantaneously depending upon the
degree of rapidity with which you make
the adjustment such as the example that
was provided earlier. You
following which example? The shifting of
the time track of the two individuals.
Danny Liner.
Well, this is for whatever reason this
is an area that has uh drawn my
attention to some degree. Oh, right. to
this evaluation of Hubard, his writings,
his structure, uh who he was, what the
truth is. And it suddenly struck me the
other day while thinking about it. It
seemed to me suddenly that the truth was
that on the one hand he was brilliant
and that in some at certain times and in
some ways he was very fourth density,
very much in alignment with the law of
one and in other right in almost in the
same sentence on the same page two
minutes later he would be very very
third. This this served the purpose of
allowing there to be the type of
fluctuation that would bring up the
questions you are creating now so that
you would understand that there is no
one way but the people in that structure
don't understand that that message is
not getting through to them. But
understand again at the time for them in
that moment it does not need to for if
it did they would not recognize it. Mhm.
You are always only in the reality that
serves you in the
moment. Right? And so I finally what
part of what I'm attempting to evaluate
just for my own satisfaction is although
I may not feel any longer a need for
that structure, yes, I'm curious I think
more than anything else. Well, you can
simply share with any individual in or
out of the structure your imagination
viewpoint on how you imagine the
structure might be rearranged to serve
other ideas, other purposes. But in this
way, you can simply offer it as a
sharing, not creating with your offering
the judgment that they need to take what
you have to offer. No, agreed. But I'm
also wondering if perhaps the structure
in its own way even in other words I may
look at it and I think well from my
viewpoint uh more in alignment with the
law of one uh I think that it should be
changed this way and this way but
perhaps one moment what you have just
said is a contradiction in alignment
with the law of one there are no shoulds
everyone is seen to be exactly where
they need to be at any given moment I
have I understand that but I have a
there's Another clarify yourself. There
is that structure and it is in the form
that it's in. Yes. And it obviously if I
I take what you said and I said it to
myself. It apparently served me because
it got me to where I am now or something
did and I use that. Yes. Where I am now
I look back on it and I see elements
that seem to me not in alignment with
the law of one. Correct. Just an
observation. Yes. Now I wonder to myself
if in spite of
that it is in some way perfect that if
those elements that I see as not in
alignment were to be brought into
alignment then the structure would cease
to serve the purpose that it's presently
serving. That's my question as that
structure. Yes. Would it serve be its
intended purpose better if it were
altered? Not better. It would be a
totally different structure with a
totally different purpose. Well it
purpose is to it stated purpose although
they don't put in their one moment. One
moment. one moment where you are
allowing yourself what I will call the
confusion is in assuming that one moment
is connected to the next and that one
idea is a piece of another
idea it is not one structure is a
structure that serves the purpose of
that structure as we discussed if it
changes even by one word by one letter
it is another structure with another
purpose Not better, not worse, only
different. Yes. And I'm not judging. But
their stated purpose, they wouldn't
describe it in this language, but I'll
put it in my language. Their purpose is
to assist in the harvest, in the
transformation from third and fourth
from third to fourth density that is
occurring on this planet. They don't
understand it in those terms, but I
think to give them the benefit of the
doubt, that is the purpose of that
structure. My curiosity, my wonder, it
is not the only purpose. What other
purposes do you see? Well, simply as
many purposes as there are individuals
attached to
it. For each individual is their own
purpose. Okay, understand there is not one path.
Okay, understand there is not one path.
If there were only one path, there would
only be one person.
But it is a characteristic of that
structure that claims that there is only
one path that we all people can follow.
All right. But understand again by
definition in this way that serves the
individual who believe that in the
moment they believe it as soon as they
change their belief they are not
partaking of the same
structure. They are in a different
reality altogether. Understand that even
when you and another individual think
you are in the same structure you are
not. For you are creating your version,
they are creating their version. And no
matter how similar it may seem, it is
not the same. Amen. I got that. But you
better not.
You I've been resisting choosing a stage
name for many years. Get too much more
attention than it deserves. I wonder if
you can much more attention than it
deserves.
uh much more serious consideration
perhaps. Is it something you wish to do?
Yes. And I'm I'd like you to shed some
light on perhaps my some light was just
shed. [Laughter]
[Laughter]
I'd like you to please shed some light
on my difficulty in choosing one. My
resistance. Choosing one. Why must it
always be one? It needs to be I need a I
need a surname. I need a last name. A
last name? Yes. Two of that. To go with
my first name. That would be What is
your first name? My first name is Gina.
What is your last name now?
You wish another last name? Different.
Different. All right. Gina different.
Do you like that one?
Oh. All right.
Now, if you know that you do not prefer
that one, then you must have some idea
of what you do prefer. You like fish
bang? Do you follow me?
Do you follow me?
Now allow yourself first of all to feel
like you would feel if you are already
acting as that individual in that way,
already complete within the sense of
your identity. Can you feel yourself to
be that being?
Yes. All right. Now, continue to be that
being and in your imagination, see
yourself doing many
things. The things that exemplify what
you wish to do in that way that excite
you and many other things in that way.
See yourself interacting with other
individuals. Can you see that?
All right. As this individual, are you
in your terms successful?
All right. When individuals write about
you, what name do they use?
Oh, all right.
Now, do you really need a last
name? Would it make a difference?
Can you be satisfied with simply dinner? Well,
then we be that person by being simply.
Thank you. Thank you.
you then you oh yes I have question
um the information that I have to live
not to try too many thank you um more
from my heart sometimes I get really
confused good
yes therefore you not run so often into
expectation and judgment
I was wondering if you could give me
some All right if you will do me a favor
give yourself the advice from my point
of you.
How do you imagine I would advise you?
You know, I I
blank.
I have no idea
either. You picked up on that one.
Now, do you know why it is like
Nick because I cannot advise you.
You see, you are better at this than you
thought.
Now, can you take that understanding
that no one else can determine the
methodology for you except you? Can you
take that to heart?
Then you are focused whether you need to
be focused.
Recognize that your
compassion is not only outward but
inward to yourself and that your
intention is in being of service to all
that is in your loving compassionate
way. Simply trust that you know what you
are doing no matter what it is you are
doing. Okay. Confusion is not
necessarily negative. No, it is
unlocking from one mode of thought and
allowing yourself the probable reality
of others. It is
confusion. Fusing with more of
yourself. You follow me? Uhhuh. You are
simply assuming that confusion is
negative. Okay? You are simply
disorienting from one reality and
reorienting to a new idea of yourself.
As soon as you allow yourself to enjoy
your confusion, it will serve you. Out
of the confusion will come clarity as to
why the confusion
exists. You are never
interrupted in your life. You only
assume that you are. And it is that
assumption that creates the feeling of
interruption. Everything that comes to
you is a product of the path you are. A
path is not what you are on. A path is
what you are. You cannot leave off of
yourself. Bring it to home. Bring
everything to
home. I am this or that, this and that.
Rather than the idea of I am doing this
or I am trying to do this, I am this.
I am
that. Even the ideas you create that you
usually deem to be negative will
dissolve into balance if you allow
yourself to be the idea rather than
attempt to throw it away from you or
push it
away. I am
doubt. Very strong.
You follow me? Yeah. I am confusion.
I choose to be confusion. I have made
this choice.
Then it is equal to any other choice you
can make if you know you are in control
of it. Right now all of this up to this
point I understand the one thing you
mean here.
Probably yes. Why probably yes? Okay.
Yes. Why yes? Because it makes a lot of
sense. All right. Does it feel right?
Yes. Then you understand it here too.
Okay. When you say I am doubt in that moment
When you say I am doubt in that moment
you would be manifesting it. You
understand that the reason the idea of
doubt or many other experiences of
negativity keep manifesting is because
you will not acknowledge it when you are
it in the moment. Oh, thank you. Thank
you. You understand if you say, "Oh, I'm
afraid I might doubt." then you are
pushing it away from a now experience.
Only as long as you refuse to experience
it now does it keep coming back.
When you say I am doubt, you have been
through it. You have lived it. You are
over with it. You go on to something
else because if you say well I am doubt.
Well now what?
So um in the in the moment the now
moment that comes up and I I am clear. I
am clear. Wow.
I don't have to do anything with it or
you are you are being it you are living
it acknowledging it loving it. And in
this way it offered you the opportunity
once having been lived to choose
something else.
The cycles of repetition that are
created in your society for several
thousand years are only the result of
not living the ideas contained within
them. Uhhuh. You only Yes, I do. And
judgment. Rejection. Yes.
Yes.
Yes. I am judgment. I am rejection.
Now what's for lunch?
Thank you very much.
Say that last thing again about
the stuff about how we've lived many
lives because of the result of
regression. What was that? The idea of
separation from the all that is that you
are judgment isolation of yourself in
this way. Refusing to allow the totality
of yourself to be lived in the moment
creates the repetition of cycles.
Because anything you refuse to
experience in the moment, your higher
self will always throw back in your
face. And so you will create the endless
cycle of repetition that you have come
to understand as what you call karma.
But you are creating it. I am.
When you live in the now, then there is
only one eternal now life. One. Yes.
Thank you.
Oh, I'm using you. Thank you. I wanted
to thank you so much for all this
because um it's so exciting. Thank you
for co-creating the excitement with us.
You're welcome.
Um I think one of the things that's
helped me most individual and unique
from every other moment at any moment
everything can change and it does and
it's my universe has become like a
my universe has become like a
kaleidoscope gorgeous patterns and every
time I have a new idea it shifts and it
changes and it changes every time you
are a new idea. Yes, it's wonderful. I
don't even know what I was going to ask.
I just wanted to share that with you.
Thank you. You have made the shift even
as we speak.
Thank you. Okay. I had a dream last
night and I would like to reflect it to
you and see if I understand some kind of
a house and I don't know if it was a
party or something was going on but
there were a lot of people there. They
weren't sleeping. They were like playing
a game and I I don't understand how this
was happening but they were being I was
just observing this and then all of a
sudden the little girl um hugs and puts
it on the face of the guy. Nice. And
then later on the guy u goes in his hair
and kicks out another slug. And and then
then all of a sudden they disappeared
and then I'm still lying in the bed and
I look over and I see more slugs on the
edge of the bed and and that was about
all I could remember. But somehow
because not necessarily not okay go
ahead. It can but the idea of what you
call your bed is also a symbol of the
idea of your detachment from the
physical form your dream self. The idea
of when you make the alignment to the
polarity within you to the totality of
yourself in this way which can be viewed
to be experienced and expressed to the
idea of the young female and the older
male in this way experiencing at one in
the same time the idea of the polarity
of time young and old and the idea of
the blending of male female energy
within yourself. The idea of the bed is
simply your symbol for
releasing and cojoining the totality of
your being in this way. Now the idea as
I perceive it which in no way shape or
form needs to match how you perceive it
and vice versa is simply that the
animals that you call the slugs will
represent many different ideas. One will
be the flow of
time. One will also be the idea of
guardians outside of time in in another
time track that are simply watching
observing guides so to speak.
Oh okay. They also to some
degree are the recognition that it is
the blending of those polarities of
male, female, young and old that allows for
female, young and old that allows for
the exchange of ideas within you at a
pace you can accept.
Do you follow me?
Um, what ideas? Any idea?
that your youngness, your oldness, your
maleness, your femaleness can exchange
ideas with each other that can be
exchanged at a rate that will allow them
to assimilate them at whatever rate is
comfortable. Mhm. You follow me? Yeah.
It's totally different than what I
thought it was. What did you think?
Well, I thought that now one moment
recognize again I am simply sharing my
perspective and in no way, shape or form
is that an invalidation of your
perspective. For my perspective and your
perspective do not have to be the same
understanding and it is not a measure of
what your capabilities of understanding
yourself are. If my perspective is
different, okay, you follow me? Yeah.
What is your perspective? I thought that
the uh the flood symbolized um like the
female while having sex because it's
like wet and slimy like that. And I know
that's um but when they were gone and
and these slugs were still on on my bed,
I chose not to like get up and throw
them away or take them off the bed or
get rid of them. I could go to sleep. So
I thought that what that meant was that
um although All right. Now allow me to
suggest some interchange within your
terminology. Perhaps what you may call
the idea
of a sexual act may in this way, let us
say, not be what you have been creating
in this way, but sexuality you have been
dealing with for quite some time and are
always expressing.
Therefore, understand that the
relationship in this way is still to
some degree similar in our different
perspectives. For again, the idea of the
blending of the male female energy
within yourself is an exploration of
sexuality of a type. Yeah. Yeah. Well, I
did secure the you know the the child
and the a llama and I was attacked and
allow me to suggest this and only this.
You can explore the aspects of the
interreationships of that idea as you
are creating them in the present if you
will also allow within your
also allow within your
vocabulary another
redefinition. How about you are creating
a relationship with a land friend rather
than a land lord.
All right.
That is all I can suggest to you for
now. Right. that I should change my
attitude concept about what that person
is and what that aspect reflects to you
about your country.
I don't understand landlord land surf
land friend. Okay. Okay. Okay. Great.
Thank you.
Yes. Uh in the past year or
Uh in the past year or
so I've been uh reaction. All right.
And uh and so what do you do with this
information?
I'm trying to you're what?
All right. These experiences in the hope
that in the what
in well knowledge
in the knowledge. All right.
I don't know if it's an it's at this
point an idea. What is the difference
between an idea and a knowledge?
Knowledge is the recognition that you
are an
idea. It is the allowance of the
expression of the idea that you are as
your life into your
life. What are you living? Understand
that you are creating your past from
your present. Your present is not a
result of the past. Therefore, it is not
so much that you are reacting and
reliving. You are living now these
ideas. What do they do for you to live
them
now? How do they serve you to live them
in this way? Now
uh I have experienced that they helped
free me up good from my reaction to
situation so that you can replace
reaction with action which is conviction
of the being that you are the knowledge
the trust being the idea living the idea
that is action not reaction which is
judgment. So it is serving you in that
way to allow you to move from separation
to
integration. Yes.
Yes. And I would like there to be a
quick quicker quicker quicker quicker.
All right. If you would like there to be
more acceleration, then simply continue
to assume that what you are experiencing
is serving you and experience it in the
joy that you know that as it serves you,
you will integrate more and more and
more of yourself and as you integrate
more and more and more of yourself
having that much more of your energy
present will increase your acceleration.
So the particular methods living the
ideas that you create in your life. So I
create the
yes it is that
simple. You can and because you just
conceived of it you just did.
Now it is up to you whether or not you
wish to create the idea that you are
going to forget what you just
created. Anytime you can conceive of an
idea, you are that idea and that is your
life in that moment. You are simply many
of you coming from the habit of assuming
that once you have a thought you must
create a process to achieve that thought
wherein the conception of the thought
itself is the end of the process. You
are in that moment because you could
perceive it that being that reality who
lives that way. It is up to you to
decide if you want to continue to create
yourself in that
light. As you have the idea that you are
already accelerated in that way, you
are. And your physical life because it
is obedient to what you consider
yourself to be will reflect that to
you. It is only a matter of trusting
that that is so. Trust is all there is.
Trust is what creates everything you
experience. Different degrees of the
idea of trust.
Follow it. Yes, of course.
Um you know are there
if you feel you need that symbol again
now knowing that you are accelerated
exactly as you need to be and that means
you will attract into your life
everything that you require. You can
simply take it for granted that if you
need such a symbol, you will find one in
no uncertain terms, very rapidly. Simply
allow yourself to be open to allowing it
to occur in any way that it can. Do not
put expectation that it has to occur in
a certain way at a certain time. Allow
yourself to be open to the idea that
everything that will serve your
recognition of your own acceleration
will be there to reflect it. So if you
need that type of symbol, it will be
there. If it is not there, you don't
need it. Trust no matter what occurs in
your life that that is what you need at
that moment. You follow. Thank you very much.
moment. You follow. Thank you very much.
You may all take a short break.
All right. I'll say sharing. You venue.
Okay. Returning to the candy lighter
paradox. Yes. Um, will you clarify
something for me? Uh, yes, of course. Or
you would not have experienced the same
idea. Except that I really didn't
experience except by her telling me
that. It is still your reality. In other
words, let me put it to you this way.
You would not have created an individual
who would have told you that. Yeah. The
individual you would have been with
would not have told you that. I
understand it. Okay. So, it wasn't as
though she was doing a force. You have
to be in order to be able to perceive
any form of communication about any
difference at all in that way. Yeah. Now
the difference is that uh I was able to
perceive that it was right which we
should probably call
FDPs and uh she would not have perceived
that had I not mentioned it to her. It
does not matter if it is conscious
awareness of terminology. The act is the
act. Yeah. Okay. That's neat. I have
another question. Um I've integrated my
All right. Thank you. You do not have to
look at it that way. You may right now
because we have discussed the idea that
you are creating your past and your
future from your present. If you wish
forget the entire notion of the future
self, forget the entire notion of the
past self. Anything you are doing, you
are doing as the present you. Therefore,
it is not a matter of slipping back into
something. You have decided to do it in
the present for specific reasons.
Period. Then when you examine and
explore those reasons, it all stays in
the present. You follow me? Okay. But you're
present. You follow me? Okay. But you're
not suggesting that I try to analyze.
Oh, why did I do this in this particular
time? No, no, no. Simply the idea that
what you are doing is the product of a
present choice, not a sliding back into
a past self. Okay. Now sometimes I
create something for myself that then
you know you don't prefer it and perhaps
that was the reason you created it.
Yeah. Just just make it. Yes.
You always are going to have the
offering of infinite choices. That is
all there is to
it. Take what you
prefer. You know what I mean? Yeah.
Okay. One last thing. There was much
activity of many systems in your
disguise that night of your time. By
systems, you're referring to
civilizations. What you call Sunday? A lot of other
What you call Sunday? A lot of other
people experienced restlessness in
sleep. Yes. And many individuals saw the
crafts. A lot of lot of civilizations around and
A lot of lot of civilizations around and
doing. Yes. And there was simply
recognition of the identification of the
vibration on whatever level you
perceived it to be.
Wow. Thank you. One moment. Yes. I've
had this uh reoccurring idea and a
friend suggested last night. Now, what
did you place as your
you place as your
intention along with the co-creation of
that idea into that idea? Uh accelerated
education. All right. Then recognize
simply this. What you allowed me to do
was to cocreate with you the belief in
the idea that the scenario was open and
idea that the scenario was open and
active and you yourself in this way
created the use of the tool as your
imagination saw
fit. You follow me? Yes.
In that way we perform the symbol of the
charging and now you are the idea of
that reality and so any objects in your
reality will reflect that idea as you
define them to do so. Thank you. That is
what has happened in the so-called
charging. You follow me? Yes.
Yes. I was wondering the other night you
told me that Daryl would live
approximately. Yes. And um that has to
do with changing over to the endocrine
system. Sense. Yes. Okay. Well, what I
was wondering was in our time frame, my
understanding in the cycle of
separation. Yes. Okay. Well, is the
transformation that's going to take
place in Daryl going to be this is not
yet determined. It is in a sense occurring
determined. It is in a sense occurring
now. And anything that is being laid
down is connected to that idea as it is
for many individuals in your society at
this time. Why was Daryl surprised? No
one has ever asked.
Okay. What about the uh endocrine or the
uh all of the glandular system will be
functioning on a higher level and will
be integrating in the inter relationship
that recognizes or let's say represents
the energy vibrational matrix that you
are. In other words, you will have a
more literal representation of the
energy structure that you are
represented by the glandular structure
rather than the organ structure in your
body. You follow me? Mhm.
The organ structure has served you
within the ideas of your understanding
of yourselves in the cycle of limitation
in this way and your bond to the idea of
your planet earth. Now, because you are
creating a new understanding, a more
rarified understanding of that way and
becoming more crystalline in that sense,
you are going to operate off of another
level of the system of your physical
form to represent the more energy being
that you are going to be.
Yes, I understand. Thank you. One one
other thing I was interested or more
similar to the representation of the
universe than some other geometric form.
In the sense of the idea that it is an
active idea to a degree.
Yes. In the idea that a spiral goes
inward and outward
simultaneously. Yes.
You follow me? Yes, I do. If and I have
heard the idea that the pyramids were
confirmed. Not all of them. Some of
them. Some of them were. Could Could you
explain that process to me? Explain the
process. Now, there were many symbolic
representations of that idea. Some of
which were in your terms
mechanical. But still there was the
recognition of the amplification of the
idea being brought into physical
reality. Some of this idea was put forth
in what you call sonics. You follow me?
The idea that sound vibration in and of
itself when tuned to the vibrational
pattern of any particular object, let us
say the stone, will tend to in a sense
in your terminology cancel the effect of
any other vibration upon it such as
gravity. You follow me? Therefore, in
that way, they were tuned into place.
You follow me? Now you will find in your
civilization that you can to a degree in
your terms rediscover this idea and then
many of what you previously have
considered to be construction endeavors
will actually take on a symphonic
quality.
So they were allowed to take they were
put into that shape because the shape
was already recognized by the engineers
to represent the lens of magnetism in
your electric field upon your planet.
The blocks individually of some of the
older structures as you count time were
simply laid into place in that way
floated into place. Okay. Then would I
be correct in inferring that the pyramid
well in a
sense it is let us say that the pyramid
is an
antenna tapping the
tapping the
electromagnetic force and focusing it in
a certain way like a lens. You follow
me? It is immersed within the field of the
It is immersed within the field of the
electromagnetic fluid of your planet and
represents a particular type of focus
within that field.
Well, okay. Margot was explaining to me
when I asked her what the light and
sound communication is that she said
that that idea came to her of the
pyramid with a spiral. All right. Yes.
Do do you have any uh well simply in
this way that will be the motion of the
energy of the magnetism as it is focused
it will take a spiral inwardly and
outwardly. Thank you.
Thank you.
Um I have heard that you talked a lot
about uh UFOs and so on in a sense. Yes.
Uh a couple of questions here. One of
them on one tape I heard or I heard all
right. Now in this way nothing is set in
stone. It is fluctuating. Right. You
will find however that one of the ideas
has already begun and is being balanced
out to some degree that will arrive in
your March time in this way with regard
to the idea of what you call your Soviet
Union. Okay. Now in uh a couple weeks
ago there was yes and I noticed in the
paper and I thought oh I wonder if
that's the beginning of it and it was
one aspect but the methodology by which
the aspect played itself out in a sense
in your terms let us say diffused some
of the other probabilities that could
have built up. There is also refocusing
of energy in the area you now call your
Philippines and in this way it is some
of the same energy I see. And because of
the manifestation that has occurred, it
also has in a sense rechanneled some of
that energy in a positive way. Yes.
Uhhuh. Uh and then in April, uh my
understanding from what you said Yes.
whether you are physiologically aware of
it or not. Although there is now a high
degree of probability that it will seem
so. We will be aware of it
physiologically. also potentially
potentially as was last Sunday night of
your time on what we call the date March
15th in your language as well. Okay.
Being what you call the eyes of March
which is the doorway that you have
created many times that you stepped
through to allow what is subconscious to
come to the surface.
In your past, you have utilized it as a
symbol that what emerges as secret to
the surface and becomes known can be
destructive. But now it simply functions
as a doorway to allow more of yourself
to be present. And thus it is that
vibration and stepping through that
doorway that can allow you to I'll say
vibrate equally with the frequency of
perception that will allow you to see
many of the craft at that time that are
already there. All right. On the on the
15th of March, we'll be Yes. Now has let
us say the greatest degree of
vibrational potential. Where should we
go? Anywhere.
I'm going to be in the desert somewhere.
All right. Anywhere that you find
yourself. Simply again, we are not
promising. Yes.
One moment. What is the difference now
between what's happening now? I mean,
everything's accelerating. things really
happen and what's going to be happening
in 30 to 50 years from now. What is the
difference? Is that what you are asking?
Yes. Simply the idea that you will
consciously be
living the result of all the blending
that is going on now. Uhhuh. You will be
interacting more as a unified
civilization. Okay. But we are already interacting in
Okay. But we are already interacting in
a fairly unified way. Yes. Okay. But
through the symbols of separation still.
Uhhuh. Okay. Thank you very much. Thank
you. Yes. For sure. Um you were talking
about the glands and the organs. Our
understanding of the body is present is
that the body needs vitamins and
minerals and so forth. What is your
perception of that? simply again that
you will still continue to absorb some
of those ideas from time to time in your
sustenance. It will simply become a
little bit more and more rarified
extending itself only to those things
that you feel are not manufactured
naturally at the time. But also you may
find that as you begin to enter more and
more fourth density physicality, some of
those things can be transmuted directly
out of the energy field of your earth
into your system rather than going
through the substances such as food.
Yes. Fabulous.
Thanks. For sure. Uh I've got uh got a
question for a friend Richard Smith
who's uh in Denver, Colorado. Uh he
channelneled something recently about
the champion of the circle and he wanted
any information that you might have on
that. Our only perception at this
Our only perception at this
time is that the
idea of what you call the circle and the
champion of the circle is that which
exists at its
center. The creator of the
circle is the idea of the center of the
circle. Without the
center there is nothing to surround.
You follow me? Yes. That is the
information we can share at this moment.
There can be more in what you call a
later date because this is a process
that involves connection with other
consciousness and we do not at this time
want to step on any toes. Very good. Uh,
was there any comment you'd like to make
about the brown out symbol we had at the
beginning of the session tonight? Well,
I already did many times.
The idea is simply again of the
allowance of the defocusing in this way
of your external reality and the
reliance upon your internal reality as
equals. The dimension of imagination.
The dimension of imagination.
When you say defocusing, are you
referring to Yes. to equal to
great and uh what title would you
suggest for tonight's channeling?
I believe many of you had many
suggestions connected to the idea of
your darkness in this way. How about
laugh in the dark? All right.
dancing in the dark. Very good. The last
comment I have sharing I thought it
was bology that the the new president of
u of the Philippines her first name
Spanish for the heart and I thought that
was great because they're they're
experiencing apparently a lot of opening
of the heart chakra there. You are very
adept in this way at creating your
symbols all of you and recognize of
course in this way but that area is also
part and parcel of the idea of the heart
chakra on your planet. Right. But the
fact that she's a woman and that and the
female represents that. Yes. Now, you
may also, if you wish, allow me to
suggest simply, although again to you,
that you may utilize the
title shedding some light. [Music]
[Music]
I have a question.
In your perception, what is the purpose
of who built the pyramid and what was
their purpose? In this way there was
connection to the idea of what you call
Atlantean civilization and also some
intermixing of what you call
extraterrestrial. In this way, the
so-called purpose was in the recognition
that in the focusing of the magnetic
energy in that way and the immersing of
a being standing in that focal point
would be utilized in what you call
initiations to allow there to be, let us
say, an acceleration or the forming of
an atmosphere that was conducive to the
idea of what you would call astral
travel and the learning of the higher
self. They are initiation temples that are
They are initiation temples that are
remnants, let us say different because
much of the idea was somewhat in your
terms of law, but they are somewhat akin
to the same idea of the pyramids that
were created in Atlantis and in this way
that is where they originated upon your
planet in Atlantis.
Does that answer your question? Yes. uh
in the book known as the raw material
which is supposed to which is
represented as a transcript of challenge
we're experiencing here raw describes
itself as a social memory complex sixth
density which took form on this planet
and among other things built the pyramid
as a single thought form so what would
their relationship be to Atlantis and so
forth in this way you will find simply
that much of the extraterrest
Terrestrial communication at that time
was ongoing in the early stages of what
you call the Aralandian
civilization. You follow me? So was it
that energy the raw energy in Atlantis
and subsequent? Yes. and other energies
as well. But they were involved in that
way and formed what would be the
extraterrestrial connection at that time
that allowed there to be the sharing of
that let us say
technology
that is only let us say a remnant of the
former level of the technology
for you one moment was it um okay you
talked about The musical was it? At that
time there were many methodologies as
well and in the overall sense it was in
a sense mental but in this way there was
the use of crystallin forms to allow
there to be the vibration as what you
call electric current was passed through
them and then simply focused or aimed.
So could that be done today or yes in a
sense although not exactly within the
same methodology for your technology is
slightly different. Is it being
rediscovered at this time? Yes, you will
understand that your civilization has
already to some
degree achieved the idea in your terms
of the suspension of the gravitational
field by sonic vibration on minute
scales. Was it was it the is the reason that the
Was it was it the is the reason that the
king was buried in the pyramid was it
because it was his name? Now understand
that in what you call to be the oldest
pyramids, no one was buried.
And that just came about later. Yes. For
it was what was remembered of the idea
and the assumption after the knowledge
had been in your terms lost that this
individual would be able to be preserved
in that sense and expanded in that sense
in their connection from physical life
to non-physical life. the idea of the
passage of the soul or what they called
the cop out of the body in this way.
Right? But simply what was forgotten was
that this in the early stages was done
while the body was still alive. The
passage into the living realm into the
realm of the dead so to speak. So so it
remained as a symbol of that idea but
the original intention was forgotten. So
in Atlantian times the people didn't
really die.
Is that what you said? Simply that in
those pyramids they were able to have
the out of body experience and knew that
that is what the pyramids were for was
for the initiation or activation of that
ability in that sense. Okay. Does it
matter what happens to the physical body
after we die? Does it matter? Well, I
mean some uh if if we're disembowled or
if a fluid is put into us or you know if
we're put into a pyramid, is it all
relative? Do you mean to the
consciousness that has left?
Well, it seems like in certain religious
philosophies they in a sense there is an
energy essence, the consciousness of the
world spirit still acting through the
matter of that form. But it is quite
different than the focused consciousness
that you recognize to be the personality
within the body. And in that sense to
that focused consciousness that has gone
on, it does not really much matter. Or
at least if it matters at first, it will
not after a
while. Although in this way, many
individuals then and still do well so to
speak, attend their own
funerals. And in that sense, at that
moment, what is being transacted may
satisfy them according to
recognizing that everyone allows
themselves to find their place within
their understanding of the event. But to
the soul that has passed on, very
quickly there comes the recognition that
it is simply one more symbolic idea, and
that is all. So, we don't have to die.
Not in that sense. And you never really
do. But I mean um I've been reading some
information regarding ascending and not
well in that sense but also do not
forget that that still incorporates the
idea of existing within at least a quasi
physical reality in that way and that in
your terms eventually you may choose to
become non-physical altogether even
after living for thousands of years
physically. You follow me? Uh, yes. As long as it
You follow me? Uh, yes. As long as it
serves your purpose to remain in that
ascended physical light body state, you
will do so. Mhm. You can still, even
after tens of thousands of years in that
state, choose to become completely
non-physical. But so in becoming
But so in becoming
non-physical, the connection I'm trying
to make is between taking the body with
you instead of leaving the body behind
and where wherever you go and sending
into the That is the point. The idea
simply is is that taking it with you
where that body can exist is still only
one portion of all of creation. much of
which is non-physical in nature. Now you
will always exist as everything you have
ever been and so in that sense you still
have every body you have ever been. You
follow me? Yes. And from even the
ascended so to speak point of view that
always will exist. But you can also
change the focus of your consciousness
to allow it to seem as if you no longer
have a body ascended or not.
You follow me? Yes. Therefore, recognize
in this way that entities or
consciousnesses that are not physical in
your terms simply can have the experience of
terms simply can have the experience of
an ascended body, so to speak, but do
not have to.
It is all simply a matter of perspective
or point of view.
There are always going to be all sorts
of different ways of expressing your
existence. And simply by definition,
some of them are non-physical,
right? Therefore, you are always going
to be a physical body, a non-escended
form, an ascended light body, and a
non-physical being all at the same time.
Now if you choose to spend eons as an
ascended physical body, you can do
so in terms of let us say assuming that
that is the only perspective through
which you are expressing yourself.
But with um in doing so this is I see
I'm not sure how to describe this
um the information that I have received
is that the body there's a way turn the
body into light energy. All right and I
think that's what I'm trying to say is
that the body doesn't necessarily have
to die. All right. It is more the idea
and not so much of what you recognize as
death but as phasing. And in this way
you can phase because you are like
energy right now. Mhm. You are made of
light. You are living light right now.
What you are speaking of is simply
different phases of light. And so even
when you are consciously a light body
and so to speak ascended, when you make
a decision, if you make a decision to
become another form of light body, it
will not be experienced as death but
only as phasing.
And it will still seem that you are a
light body in that sense. For light is
what everything is made of in that
sense. Light and love it is the same
thing. Mhm. You follow me? Yes, I do. It
is simply the conscious
recognition of what you are made of and
existing in that state.
Okay. Is that clear? Yes, it is. Thank
you. The universe is made of love. Existence
The universe is made of love. Existence
is unconditional love. Love is the
substance of what you are made. Like
love. Same
thing. Do we have within is it
within our present as we call it
lifetime to we is it available to some of many of
to we is it available to some of many of
us for our physical forms as they are
now to live several hundred years
although again it will not be exactly as
they are now they will be more forth
density but basically yes but I mean
they're not going to turn into elephants
and giraffes no no no they're going to
kind of look like what they look Yes.
Yes. Yes. What is the fourth density? I
hear you speaking that tonight. I simply
the idea of the energy state of
existence in that way in which you are
more aware of more of yourself and have
the opportunity to look through the
illusions that in third density are
taken as the real reality.
Living in the moment. I see. Okay.
Sure. Sure.
Okay. Some more questions on sound. No.
All right. uh one is that I have heard
that there's enough sound en there's
enough energy within this room from a
sound point of view to power the whole
of Los Angeles. In other words, there's
an enormous amount of energy available.
There is enough energy in one particle
of existence to do that.
And does that relate to sound?
Everything is
vibration. everything and therefore in a sense keep
everything and therefore in a sense keep
sound. Okay. Is the technology available
in our present time to convert that
energy into use in our civilization?
Let us say the technology is available.
The understanding is not yet there.
You follow me? Yes. Would it be
advantageous to to the process of the
blending for this understanding to
become more available and so make energy
available? Of course. And all you have
to do is follow your
imagination and explore that idea in
whatever way you wish to. Then you will
be making that difference by being that
reality. You follow me? Yes. Thank you
for sir. you sure we first of all it's
nice uh speaking with you again coming
that Wednesday is the first day of my
week so all the ideas I pick up here I
carry along till next week but anyway we
talked a little bit about sound and
light and one of the problems in in in
physics and chemistry is one of the what
in physics one of the problems problems
well I haven't reached a final solution
as to there never will be oh you know
what I'm going to ask understand in this
way that a problem is only situation You
will not allow to change shape. And in
this sense, it is simply that there are
understandings, situations,
perspectives, they always change, for
change is the only constant in any
equation. There's nothing permanent
except change. Thank you. So much for
that question.
They will however come to some
understandings that are reflective of
some of the ideas they do wish to
experience in terms of the unified field
ideas. So it goes back to you know you
get the result your experiment is
designed. Okay that's that's what I was
talking about. Okay. Another thing uh
last week we briefly mentioned and again
Monday you briefly mentioned the process
you called cold fusion. Nice. Uh would
you elaborate on that for us? No. That
simple. Simply in this way, the idea can
be for now looked
at an
opportunity for two matrices to
interlink along lines that
express the common relationship.
What type of relationship? Magnetic,
electronic? are conscious. We explore those things.
are conscious. We explore those things.
It is a matter
of whether was one identity and another
separate identity forming a third
identity that in and of itself contains
the aspects of the
two but as a single
identity. That is the
relationship between them. In other
words, this if this may make it
this if this may make it
clearer, you have one object and you
have another object. Now understand that
in your day-to-day perception, the
reason you experience the idea that this
is one object and that is another object
is actually the result of what you
actually recognize on another level to
be the
interreationship between them. It is the
interreationship that is really there
and the two objects are projected
polarity illusions of the actual reality
which is really the relationship between
them. Okay. It is in allowing that
relationship to be the solid reality and
the reflections being the illusion that
allows you the cold fusion idea.
So again it's because of our idea of
reality that pulled it in a sense. Yes.
So the cold fused result would be
literally a third not so much from an
atomic change but rather from a matrix
social change. Yes. Sure.
You when you were talking about the cold
fusion, I had something that occurred to
me just now that I'd like to share. Oh,
right. That that
and get your reflection.
Um I've spent
uh consistently more and more time in
the last few weeks working on the
relationship between the strong weak
nuclear forces, gravitational and
magnetic forces and trying to
pull consciousness into that mechanism.
All right. And do not forget the
hypercharge that you have recently
created. And and yes, and the uh the
thing that that occurred to me is that
is that in in an expression that would
bring the equations together on on the
four different kinds of energy levels
and that would in fact unite all of
those that combined with the concept of
a gravitational field and the whole
phenomenon of black holes and the plasma
containment for being able to produce a
fusion reaction i.e. a cold what you
could call I guess a cold fusion
reaction. If you relate now you
understand that what we are terming cold
fusion has nothing at all to do with
what you understand to be fusion on your
planet at all.
Uh okay. How it is not an atomic fusion
process in that way. It is an
identifying of matrices within the
foundational template of existence
itself. Uh well in in in that sense I'm thinking
Uh well in in in that sense I'm thinking
in terms of the actual 3D manifestation
of of
of what what could be a fusion reaction
as the result of the 4D equations that
would relate to bringing the unified
field theory together. Is that a wrong
is that is that wrong direction? It is
not wrong direction but it is simply a
different idea. Oh,
from what we are discussing.
Well, let me continue.
Um, because it occurred to me that if if
if we can make gravity waves now, right?
And and if we have a shell and and and
the big problem with creating in essence
unlimited energy has to do with not
being able to contain the heat of the
plasma away from the container itself.
If we understood the equations that
relate the four basic elemental forces
i.e. the unifi unified field and somehow
could combine those in a gravitational
spherical energy that could in fact then
your fusion reaction that you are after
would seem immediately obsolete
for a new type of emergence of energy
would be seen. Yeah. Well, that's what
occurred because it seems to me if you
could create that, you you could in
essence drop an electron into it and it
would fall to the center with greater
and greater acceleration and virtually
disappear as though in a black hole
thereby releasing enormous amounts of
energy. Yes, that is one utilization.
Although you will understand this in one
type of modulation of that particular
field that you can create the field
interacting upon itself at 90° tensor
vectors will in and of itself provide
you with a new type of energy that can
be utilized beyond anything you think
can be controlled. Now it wouldn't even
it wouldn't even use third density
material, would it? No, it would like be
as as as third density material in fact
disappears in the gravity well of a black hole. So
in the gravity well of a black hole. So
would
that appear in a sense energy in reverse
is what is is am I getting it? Yes.
Energy. Structured
Structured
energy. Yes. structured energy without
material form.
You follow me? Yes. It's a template,
isn't it? Oh, it is a
manifestation yet again on top of the
template. The template in itself is not
The template in itself is not
experiential in third density nor even
in that way in fourth. Okay. It is
simply, let us say, a more closely
aligned reflection of the template.
However, so once we get the equations
and they're known and once we can in
fact unify them, all we're really doing
is going in reverse because the one
thing modern physics doesn't explain is
the black hole. And the feeling is that
the unified field will in fact explain
it. And all we do is if you solve the
equation, you know, you if you know X,
you find Y. And if you know Y, you get
X. And all right, you will understand
that there is no such thing as black
hole without a white one, right? And
what you will be perceiving in the
creation of this non-material energy
fluxed matrix will be that it is
convoluting inwardly and outwardly
simultaneously. Right? It's it's like
picking up the backside of a black hole.
All right. Yes. that to a degree it will
seem it will seem in a sense to so to
speak violate what you hold to be some
conservation laws right though so to
speak it will not be but the immediate
effect is that it will seem to be in
your terminology as you have called it
holding itself up by its own bootstraps
right well black holes already blows a
theory in all of modern physics anyway
all right so it wouldn't be unreasonable
to assume on the other side there is
that all right polarity polarity nice
right what you can even say about this
phenomena you can create is that in a
sense in a sense you are actually
creating a device that exemplifies the
energy of polarity itself
in a very raw state
it is a demonstration of polarity acting
upon your physical universe.
There will be in your terms a few
minutes remaining.
Yes. Would you be willing to co-create a
movie script as a symbol to express the
blending? Not at this time.
Not at this time.
Sometime maybe, maybe not. Simply
recognize that at this time that
particular endeavor involves many
degrees of symbology in this way that
are particular to your own process. And
in this sense recognize that what we are
sharing with you in any particular
encounter. You are free to use in any
way you
wish but at this time not towards that
specific end except as you choose to
create it thus. You follow me? Yes sir.
Thank you.
Then you I have the idea that this is the
you I have the idea that this is the
first time I'm meeting you. I wanted to
say hello and thank you. This is
wonderful and and more.
Um I was talking to Daniel at the break
and he said something about the fact
that you've been getting funnier over
the time that you've been visiting and
um I I think your sense of I mean I
really appreciate your sense of humor
and I was curious it it dawns on me that
when we look at children that we really
love, we laugh at them a lot. And I was
wondering how our humor seems to you if
from from where from where you and your
people are and and how does your humor
different is is it simply in this
way the idea of our humor is without
judgment. We do not in this way create
the idea of well so to speak laughing at
but laughing
with as you have said upon your planet
yourself. It is the recognition of the joy and the
It is the recognition of the joy and the
ecstasy within each expression of
creation. You follow me? Mhm. It is not
the idea of being at someone's expense,
so to
speak. You follow me? Yes. Will this
have answered your question?
Uh, yes. Yeah. I I I you know Yeah. I'd
love to say give more. You know, let's
have some examples. Let's play with this
one. But um that's all right. Yes. You
would laugh. Depends upon their reason for
laugh. Depends upon their reason for
creating that
reality. If their purpose was to have us
laugh, we
will. However, we do not have
bananas. That particular symbol has no
appeal.
Yes. My question is
um a while back in a meditation I had
found myself
um speaking someone the information that
I received had to do with
um I'm not sure whether call a past life
or um a more of a beginning existence.
Did I at some time come from another
planet? In a sense, none of you are
original to this planet. Uh-huh. Now
understand, even though, however, that
those connections are still being made
in the present. Yes, you can look at it
both ways. It is literally true
linearly. And it is true that you are
creating it now. I'm sorry, I don't
understand. The idea that you have had
past life is a reality as a past life
and also that you are creating the idea
that you have had a past life in the
present. Both are true like they're
existing at the same time. Yes. Okay. Is
it possible to ask
um what the planet was? What the name of
it was or name name? How was the feeling
of the planet?
This is interesting. It feels like blue.
Blue. All right.
Do you have any idea of what you to use
your terminology of past tense did then?
Um, no. It it was it seemed like it was
sort of a short experience. I don't know
if it was my fear that brought me back
or maybe that was all the information.
All right. Allow me to ask you this then
in our co-creation of the exploration of
this particular aspect of your
personality. What do you feel
recognizing a connection to that
civilization does for you now in this
civilization? Oh well that is a good question. Um oh
Oh well that is a good question. Um oh
thank
you question way to look at
okay um True. No, I was going to say oh
I I feel that it has a lot to do with um
the way I have created my life now of
course and the knowledge that I've come
in contact with and things that seem to
come in right what do you think in a
sense let us say that you brought with
you that you have to share to be of
service with in this civilization during
this transformational
um that I feel I have to really think
about a little bit more. Oh, why? Why?
Why? Why? Why? What do you love to do?
What do you love to be? Sing sound
again. Vibration. All right.
Now for now allow me to say that the
idea of that civilization that you are
tapping into that you project the idea
of coming
from was more of an energy planet in a
sense not so much exactly
physiological. You follow me? Yes. It
was in a sense a very actively
vibrational existence. And that is why
you are exemplifying the idea into sound
in this life. For you recognize that the
patterns of vibrations can flow in
harmonious and synchronous ways. And you
have given yourself a symbol, one of the
symbols that this planet recognizes as a
projection of that particular type of
consciousness that is acceptable so that
your communication can be in a way that
is comfortable for you and for everyone
else. Oh, thank you. You have answered
about a thousand questions of that.
Thank you very much. Thank you for
integrating the thousand questions into
your own single answer.
Yes. Yes. Um, can
you you addressed a few different things
as far as physical
uh phenomenon talking for example about
pyramids and also about crystals. I
sense that you're what what you're
saying about crystals is that they're
they're they function based on someone's
creating the idea that they would
function that way. Yes. Whereas pyramids
you seem to be describing that it's an
both the same
thing. Recognize that both are in a
sense crystallin forms and are focusing
energy in a similar fashion. And in this
way, the idea is that in your math
consciousness there is an overall
agreement basically at least on a
fundamental level that you do believe
they function in that way.
So if we believe that a a sphere would
work as a pyramid then it would also
work that way. Oh yes and it does in
many ways that is why you have created
the idea in your perceptions of what you
call crystal
ball for it is another type of focus in
that way and another type of symbol and
it simply functions differently. It is a
differently shaped tool but it utilizes
the same energy
crystal. So you're now understand first
and foremost that all of this comes from
you. all of it.
Okay. So, even your descriptions of um
um the cold fusion and all this stuff,
you're describing a result of our ideas
more than say an a presence that they're
independent of our ideas. Oh. Oh, yes.
Nothing is independent. You are the
creator. The reality you experience is
the reality you create. and anything
that exists within it is a symbolic
reflection of what you believe your
reality to be
whether individually and or
collectively. So then our our uh sir say for unified
So then our our uh sir say for unified
theory uh in a sense it's a joke we're
just creating it. Um well then have a
good laugh.
So we think we're describing a present
now. One moment. One moment. Recognize
that even what you call your own
physicists, the ones that are working
with that idea, they themselves have
already realized that their equations
and their
terminologies do not describe a universe
as it
is. They know that. They know that their
terminologies describe what they think
the universe to be and that is all it
can describe.
And by doing that are they creating the
universe to be that way? Yes. And they
also are beginning to recognize that.
And they have said as much. They do
recognize already that there is no such
thing as a phenomena that you perceive
that you are not a part of.
Thank you. Yes. Yes. Bashar. Uh I have
been exploring
um quite a bit recently in the area of
of my dreams and um with the idea of
becoming more conscious so as to
integrate that part of my life with
Right. What you want a suggestion?